>>> TONIGHT, YOUR MONEY, YOUR
TAXES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NEW PLAN.
WHAT IT MEANS FOR YOU.
AFTER SEVERAL EFFORTS TO REPEAL
OBAMACARE FAIL, THE PRESIDENT
NOW TURNS TO A MAJOR TAX
OVERHAUL.
PROPOSED CUTS FOR MIDDLE CLASS
FAMILIES, ALSO MAJOR CUTS FOR
CORPORATIONS AND WEALTHY
AMERICANS.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, THE CRISIS IN
PUERTO RICO.
A FULL WEEK AFTER THE HURRICANE
HIT, MORE THAN A MILLION PEOPLE
WITHOUT POWER OR DRINKING WATER.
THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN TONIGHT
SAYING PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO
DIE.
>>> THE DEADLY SHOWDOWN.
THE POLICE VIDEO JUST RELEASED.
THE SUSPECT JUMPING FROM HIS
PICKUP, FIRING AT POLICE.
OFFICERS RESPONDING.
>>> TONIGHT, ABC NEWS OBTAINING
SOME OF THE RUSSIAN ADS BOUGHT
ON FACEBOOK.
YOU WILL SEE THEM FOR YOURSELF.
POSING AS AN AMERICAN GROUP, THE
ADS SAY, "WE NEED TRUMP."
>>> THE MASSIVE EXPLOSION,
30,000 FORCED TO EVACUATE.
AUTHORITIES NOW ASKING, WAS THIS
AN ACCIDENT OR NOT?
>>> AND THE FIRST AIRLINE TO
OFFER FREE TEXT MESSAGES WHILE
YOU'RE FLYING.
ARE PHONE CALLS NEXT?
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN WITH THE
PRESIDENT'S SWEEPING NEW TAX
PLAN, AND WHAT IT COULD MEAN FOR
MIDDLE CLASS AMERICANS,
CORPORATE AMERICA AND THE
WEALTHIEST AMERICANS, TOO.
LATE TODAY IN INDIANAPOLIS, THE
PRESIDENT PROMISING A
REVOLUTIONARY CHANGE FOR MIDDLE
CLASS FAMILIES.
BUT STILL UNANSWERED TONIGHT,
HOW WILL HE PAY FOR IT?
AND EVEN SOME REPUBLICANS THIS
EVENING SAYING THIS WILL BE EVEN
MORE CHALLENGING THAN THEIR
EFFORTS TO KILL OBAMACARE.
ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL,
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: AFTER FAILING YET
AGAIN TO GET A REPUBLICAN HEALTH
CARE PLAN THROUGH CONGRESS,
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS NOW PROMISING
TO DELIVER ON SOMETHING EVEN
MORE AMBITIOUS -- A MASSIVE NEW
TAX CUT.
>> THERE'S NEVER BEEN TAX CUTS
LIKE WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
>> Reporter: DETAILS ARE STILL
SKETCHY, BUT THE PLAN CALLS FOR
SLASHING THE TAX ON
CORPORATIONS, NOW 35%, TO 20%.
FOR INDIVIDUALS AND FAMILIES,
REDUCING THE NUMBER OF TAX
BRACKETS FROM SEVEN TO JUST
THREE.
DOUBLING THE STANDARD DEDUCTION
FOR FAMILIES.
THAT WOULD MEAN NO INCOME TAX
WHATSOEVER ON THE FIRST $24,000
OF INCOME.
THE PRESIDENT INSISTS HIS PLAN
WILL BENEFIT THE WORKING CLASS,
AND NOT THE WEALTHY.
>> THEY CAN CALL ME ALL THEY
WANT.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HELP.
I'M DOING THE RIGHT THING, AND
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR ME.
BELIEVE ME.
>> Reporter: OF COURSE, IT'S
IMPOSSIBLE TO KNOW HOW ANY PLAN
WILL AFFECT THE PRESIDENT
BECAUSE HE STILL HAS NOT
RELEASED HIS TAX RETURNS.
BUT THERE'S ONE BIG PROVISION
THAT WOULD CLEARLY BENEFIT THE
WEALTHY.
HE WANTS TO ELIMINATE THE ESTATE
TAX.
SOMETHING THAT IS ONLY PAID ON
ESTATES VALUED AT MORE THAN $5.5
MILLION FOR INDIVIDUALS, $11
MILLION FOR COUPLES.
WHILE CONGRESS WILL SURELY MAKE
CHANGES IN THE PLAN, THE
PRESIDENT INSISTS THERE'S ONE
THING HE WON'T BUDGE ON -- THAT
HUGE TAX CUT FOR CORPORATIONS.
>> 20 IS MY NUMBER.
SO, I'M NOT NEGOTIATING THAT
NUMBER.
20 IS A PERFECT NUMBER.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT
DOESN'T EXPLAIN HOW TO PAY FOR
THESE HEFTY TAX CUTS, LEAVING
CONGRESS, ALREADY DEEPLY
DIVIDED, TO FIGURE THAT OUT.
>> TAX REFORM IS GOING TO MAKE
HEALTH CARE LOOK LIKE A PIECE OF
CAKE.
>> SO, LET'S GET TO JON KARL
LIVE AT THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT.
AND JON, ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS HAVE SAID THEY WANT
TAX REFORM DONE BY THE THIS
YEAR.
BUT YOU HEARD SENATOR CORKER
THERE, THIS IS GOING TO BE A
VERY HEAVY LIFT.
>> Reporter: THAT IS AN
EXTREMELY AMBITIOUS TIMELINE.
THIS WILL BE A HEAVY LIFT EVEN
TO GET DONE BY NEXT YEAR, DAVID.
THAT SAID, THERE IS IMMENSE
PRESSURE ON REPUBLICANS, BOTH
HERE AT THE WHITE HOUSE AND ON
CAPITOL HILL, TO SHOW THAT THEY
CAN DELIVER ON THIS.
>> JON KARL LEADING US OFF
TONIGHT.
JON, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW, TO ANOTHER MAJOR
HEADLINE INVOLVING YOUR MONEY
TONIGHT.
YOUR TAX DOLLARS BEING SPENT BY
CABINET MEMBERS FLYING ON JETS.
ONE OF THOSE CABINET MEMBERS
INSTALLING A $25,000 PHONE BOOTH
IN HIS OFFICE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ASKED ABOUT
IT TODAY, ASKED ABOUT HOW
SECRETARY TOM PRICE AND HIS
EXPENSIVE CHARTER PRICE, WHICH
ARE NOW UNDER INVESTIGATION.
ABC'S CECILIA VEGA REPORTING,
IT'S YOUR MONEY.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
TODAY MAKING IT CLEAR, HE IS
ANGRY WITH HIS HEALTH
SECRETARY'S PENCHANT FOR PRIVATE
PLANES ON THE PUBLIC DIME.
>> I'LL TELL YOU, PERSONALLY, I
AM NOT HAPPY ABOUT IT.
I AM NOT HAPPY ABOUT IT.
>> WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO
ABOUT IT, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> I'M GOING TO LOOK AT IT.
I'M NOT HAPPY ABOUT IT, AND I
LET HIM KNOW IT.
>> Reporter: SECRETARY TOM PRICE
UNDER FIRE FOR HIS LUXURY JET
TRAVEL, COSTING TAXPAYERS MORE
THAN $400,000.
AN INVESTIGATION NOW UNDER WAY,
AND PRICE SAYS THOSE HIGH PRICED
TRIPS ARE ON HOLD.
>> WE'VE HEARD THE CRITICISM.
WE'VE HEARD THE CONCERNS.
AND WE TAKE THAT VERY SERIOUSLY
AND HAVE TAKEN IT TO HEART.
>> Reporter: BUT TODAY, THE
PRESIDENT MADE IT CLEAR, PRICE'S
FUTURE IS IN QUESTION.
>> WOULD YOU FIRE HIM, SIR?
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> Reporter: THREE CABINET
SECRETARIES NOW UNDER
INVESTIGATION FOR EXPENSIVE
TRAVEL.
TREASURY SECRETARY STEVE MNUCHIN
ACCUSED OF TAKING COSTLY
GOVERNMENT JETS OVER COMMERCIAL
FLIGHTS, INCLUDING THAT TRIP TO
KENTUCKY WITH HIS WIFE, WHERE
THEY VIEWED THE ECLIPSE.
AND NEW REVELATIONS ABOUT THE
EPA ADMINISTRATOR.
SCOTT PRUITT'S FREQUENT TRIPS
HOME TO OKLAHOMA, PAID FOR BY
TAXPAYERS, ALREADY UNDER THE
MICROSCOPE.
AND NOW HE'S UNDER FIRE FOR
INSTALLING A $25,000 SECURE
PRIVATE PHONE BOOTH IN HIS
OFFICE.
SOMETHING PREVIOUS
ADMINISTRATORS DIDN'T HAVE.
A SPOKESWOMAN SAYS PRUITT, A
VOCAL CRITIC OF THE AGENCY
BEFORE HE TOOK THE TOP JOB,
NEEDS THE SECURE PHONE BOOTH SO
HIS CALLS ARE NOT SUBJECT TO
HACKING FROM THE OUTSIDE.
>> CECILIA VEGA WITH US FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE AS WELL TONIGHT.
AND CECILIA, THREE CABINET
SECTARIANS UNDER SCRUTINY HERE.
AND TONIGHT, BOTH PARTIES ARE
DEMANDI IING MORE FROM THE WHIT
HOUSE?
>> Reporter: REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS LAUNCHED THIS
INVESTIGATION.
THEY ARE FOCUSED ON SENIOR
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS, AND
THEY WANT TO SEE THEIR TRAVEL
RECORDS AND THE COST OF THOSE
TRIPS SINCE INAUGURATION DAY.
>> CECILIA VEGA WITH US TONIGHT.
CECILIA, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT HERE TO THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS UNFOLDING IN
PUERTO RICO.
THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN NOW SAYING
PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO DIE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP THIS WEEK FACING
PRESSURE, DENYING HE WAS TOO
PREOCCUPIED WITH THE NFL,
TWEETING ABOUT SPORTS INSTEAD OF
PUERTO RICO OVER THE WEEKEND.
AND TONIGHT, IS THERE A LAW, THE
JONES ACT, THAT IS PREVENTING
AID FROM REACHING MILLIONS OF
AMERICAN CITIZENS IN NEED?
ABC'S EVA PILGRIM FROM SAN JUAN
AGAIN TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, A LIFELINE
TO A TOWN CUT OFF SINCE THE
HURRICANE.
>> I WANT TO TALK TO THEM.
I WANT TO TELL THEM THAT I'M
OKAY.
THEY DON'T WORRY FOR ME.
>> Reporter: THE RED CROSS
SETTING UP SATELLITE INTERNET
FOR THE RESIDENTS OF VEGA ALTA.
FOR LYDIA RIVERA, IT'S A GOD
SEND.
ONCE SHE'S CONNECTED, RELIEF AS
HER PHONE LIGHTS UP WITH
MESSAGES FROM HER FAMILY.
LEAVING A VOICEMAIL FOR HER
MOTHER.
>> HELLO, MOMMY.
>> Reporter: MILITARY OPERATIONS
ARE BRINGING TONS OF EQUIPMENT
AND SUPPLIES, BUT RESIDENTS IN
THIS TOWN TELL ME THEY'RE STILL
WAITING FOR HELP.
>> THERE'S SUPPLIES COMING
TOMORROW.
THAT'S WHAT THEY TOLD US.
>> Reporter: A FULL WEEK AFTER
THE STORM RAVAGED THIS U.S.
TERRITORY, THOUSANDS ARE STILL
IN SHELTERS.
ONE MAN POSTING VIDEOS FROM
RESIDENTS IN UTUADO ON FACEBOOK.
>> MY NAME IS ROBERT STONE, AND
IF THEY SEE THIS THING, KNOW
THAT I AM OKAY AND THAT I'M WELL
TAKEN CARE OF.
>> WHAT'S OUT THERE IS TOTAL
DEVASTATION, TOTAL ANNIHILATION,
PEOPLE LITERALLY GASPING FOR
AIR.
>> Reporter: NEARLY HALF OF THE
ISLAND STILL WITHOUT WATER.
THE LINES OF PEOPLE HOPING TO
GET GAS, FOOD, EVEN MONEY, SEEM
LONGER THAN EVER.
AND A CROWD AT THE AIRPORT.
PEOPLE HOPING FOR A SEAT ON ONE
OF THE FEW FLIGHTS OUT.
>> AND EVA PILGRIM WITH US LIVE
AGAIN TONIGHT.
EVA, SOME PEOPLE IN CONGRESS ARE
ASKING HOMELAND SECURITY TO
WAIVE THE JONES ACT.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
FOR HURRICANES HARVEY AND IRMA,
A WAIVER OF THAT ACT WAS
GRANTED.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS HE'S
CONSIDERING THE SAME FOR
HURRICANE MARIA, BUT THAT A LOT
OF SHIPPERS AND PEOPLE WHO WORK
IN THE SHIPPING INDUSTRY DON'T
WANT IT WAIVED.
THE PRESIDENT IS PLANNING TO
VISIT PUERTO RICO ON TUESDAY.
DAVID?
>> EVA PILGRIM TONIGHT, THANK
YOU.
>>> AND MARIA, GAINING STRENGTH
TODAY, UNBELIEVABLY, GROWING
BACK TO A CATEGORY 1 HURRICANE.
STRONG WAVES AND FLOODING STILL
ALONG THE OUTER BANKS OF NORTH
CAROLINA.
TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS STILL IN
EFFECT TONIGHT.
MARIA TEETERING ON THE EDGE
BETWEEN A TROPICAL STORM AND A
HURRICANE, BUT MOVING SHARPLY
EAST, SOON OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
AND GOOD RIDDANCE.
>>> OVERSEAS TONIGHT, THE IMAGES
AFTER A FIERCE ROCKET ATTACK ON
THE AIR PORT IN KABUL IN
AFGHANISTAN.
IT CAME AFTER JIM MATTIS ARRIVED
THERE, AND AFTER THE U.S.
REVEALED, HERE BACK SOME TIME
AGO THAT MORE U.S. TROOPS ARE ON
THE WAY.
ABC'S CHIEF GLOBAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT MARTHA RADDATZ
WITH IMAGES OF THE ATTACK.
>> Reporter: THIS BURNING PLUME
AFTER THAT BARRAGE OF FIREPOWER,
SOME 40 ROUNDS OF MUNITIONS,
82MM ROCKETS AND ROCKET
PROPELLED GRENADES LAUNCHED
TOWARDS KABUL'S AIRPORT.
THE TARGET, CLAIMS THE TALIBAN,
THE AIRCRAFT DEFENSE SECRETARY
JIM MATTIS HAD FLOWN IN ON HOURS
BEFORE.
AT THE TIME OF THE ATTACK,
MATTIS WAS MEETING AFGHANISTAN'S
PRESIDENT.
BUT NOT ONLY DID THE TALIBAN
TAKE CREDIT, BUT SO DID ISIS,
RELEASING A VIDEO THEY CLAIMED
SHOWS THE ATTACK IN PROGRESS.
AFGHAN SPECIAL FORCES RAIDED A
NEARBY HOUSE.
THEY WERE BACKED UP BY A U.S.
AIR STRIKE.
A MISSILE FROM AN APACHE
HELICOPTER MALFUNCTIONED,
KILLING ONE WOMAN AND WOUNDING
SEVERAL OTHERS.
THIS WAS MATTIS'S FIRST VISIT
SINCE THE U.S. ANNOUNCED IT
WOULD BE ADDING 3,000 AMERICAN
TROOPS TO THE 11,000 ALREADY
THERE.
THIS ATTACK IS A STARK REMINDER
THAT EVEN AFTER 16 YEARS OF
TRYING TO DEFEAT THE TALIBAN,
AND THE LOSS OF THOUSANDS OF
LIVES, THEY STILL REMAIN A
FORMIDABLE THREAT.
DAVID?
>> MARTHA RADDATZ FROM
WASHINGTON.
MARTHA, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, ABC NEWS
OBTAINING SOME OF THOSE ADS
BOUGHT ON FACEBOOK BY RUSSIAN
AGENTS.
FACEBOOK ADMITS THEY WERE PAID
MORE THAN $100,000 BY RUSSIAN
COMPANIES DURING THE ELECTION.
TONIGHT, YOU'RE GOING TO SEE THE
ADS FOR YOURSELF, AND WERE THE
RUSSIANS AT IT AGAIN, JUST
WITHIN THE LAST WEEK DURING THE
DEBATE OVER THE NFL?
ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT BRIAN ROSS WITH
WHAT THOSE ADS SAID.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, ABC NEWS
HAS OBTAINED SOME OF THE POSTS
AND ADS CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE RUSSIANS
PLANTED ON FACEBOOK AS PART OF
THE KREMLIN EFFORT TO HELP GET
DONALD TRUMP ELECTED.
AMERICANS WOULD HAVE NO IDEA
WHAT THEY WERE READING WAS
WRITTEN BY THE RUSSIANS.
THEY RAIL AGAINST ILLEGAL
IMMIGRANTS.
THIS ONE WARNS AGAINST SO-CALLED
REFUGEES JEOPARDIZING OUR
NATIONAL SECURITY.
THIS AD USES A POPULAR CARTOON.
DORA THE EXPLORER KNOWS HOW EASY
IT IS TO CROSS THE U.S. BORDER.
IT'S LIKE A CHILDREN'S GAME.
WITH THIS LINE -- WE NEED TO
STOP THIS MADNESS, WE NEED
TRUMP.
THE ADS SUPPOSEDLY COME FROM A
GROUP CALLED SECURED BORDERS,
BUT CONGRESSIONAL UNVEST GATORS
SAY THERE IS NO SUCH GROUP, THAT
THEY WERE, IN FACT, CREATED BY
RUSSIAN COMPANIES WHICH PAID
MORE THAN $100,000 TO FACEBOOK
TO POST THEM DURING AND AFTER
THE ELECTION.
>> THEIR GOAL WAS TO SPREAD
DISSENSION, WAS TO SPLIT OUR
COUNTRY APART, AND THEY DID A
PRETTY GOOD JOB.
>> Reporter: MANY OF THE ADS,
INVESTIGATORS SAY, CAME FROM AN
OPERATION IN ST. PETERSBURG,
RUSSIA, IN THIS BUILDING WHERE
YOUNG RUSSIANS ARE HIRED TO SEND
OUT FAKE NEWS.
A FORMER EMPLOYEE SAYS SHE TOOK
THIS UNDERCOVER VIDEO INSIDE
WHEN SHE WORKED THERE IN 2015,
HOPING TO EXPOSE THE OPERATION,
WHERE THE SO-CALLED TROLLS
WORKED 12-HOUR SHIFTS.
THE FORMER EMPLOYEE,
LYUDMILA SAVCHUK, TOLD ABC NEWS,
FA
FACEBOOK WAS ONE OF THEIR MAIN
PLATFORMS.
ACCORDING TO INVESTIGATORS SAY
THEIR SLANT, PRO-TRUMP,
ANTI-CLINTON.
THEIR TARGETS, VOTERS IN
SPECIFIC AREAS OF KEY SWING
STATES.
>> HOW DID THEY HAVE THAT LEVEL
OF SPECIFICITY?
THAT'S ONE OF THE QUESTIONS WE
NEED ANSWERED.
>> THAT IS THE QUESTION TONIGHT.
BRIAN WITH US, WHO HELPED THE
RUSSIANS TARGET THOSE ADS TO
PARTICULAR SWING STATES, SWING
VOTERS THAT WERE SO IMPORTANT IN
THIS ELECTION?
TODAY, THERE WAS ONE REPUBLIC
SENATOR WHO EVEN SAID THERE'S A
POSSIBILITY IF THE RUSSIANS ARE
STILL AT THIS, EVEN WEIGHING IN
DURING THE NFL DEBATE.
>> Reporter: YES, DAVID.
ON CAPITOL HILL TODAY, SENATOR
JAMES LANKFORD, MEMBER OF THE
SENATE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
SAILS RUSSIAN TROLLS HAVE BEEN
TWEETING ON BOTH SIDES OF THE
ISSUE, TRYING TO RAISE THE NOISE
LEVEL, HE SAID, AND PUSH
DIVISIVENESS IN THE COUNTRY.
BY THE WAY, THIS MORNING,
PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETED THAT HE
CONSIDERS FACEBOOK TO BE ANT
ANTI-TRUMP.
>> BRIAN ROSS WITH US TONIGHT.
BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, TO A MAJOR NEW
FALLOUT FROM THE SCANDAL ROCKING
COLLEGE BASKETBALL.
FAMED LOUISVILLE HEAD COACH RICK
PITINO PLACED ON UNPAID LEAVE.
THE HIGHEST PAID COACH IN THE
NCAA.
HIS ATTORNEY SAYS PITINO HAS
BEEN, IN EFFECT, BEEN FIRED.
ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS TONIGHT ON
WHY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, LEGENDARY
COACH RICK PITINO, OUT AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF LOUISVILLE.
>> EFFECTIVE IMMEDIATELY, COACH
PITINO HAS BEEN PLACED ON AN
UNPAID ADMINISTRATIVE LEAVE.
>> Reporter: IT COMES JUST ONE
DAY AFTER COLLEGE BASKETBALL WAS
ENSNARED IN A SWEEPING BRIBERY
AND CORRUPTION CASE, ANNOUNCED
BY THE FBI.
>> THESE DEFENDANTS CONSPIRED TO
SECRETLY FUNNEL SIX-FIGURE
PAYMENTS TO THE FAMILIES OF
THREE HIGH SCHOOL PLAYERS.
>> Reporter: AN ADIDAS EXECUTIVE
CHARGED WITH FUNNELING MONEY TO
A TOP HIGH SCHOOL RECRUIT TO
MAKE SURE HE COMMITTED TO
LOUISVILLE, A SCHOOL ADIDAS
SPONSORS.
THREE YEARS AGO, PITINO HIMSELF
COMPLAINED ABOUT THE ININFLUENCE
OF SHOE COMPANIES IN RECRUITING.
>> I NEVER THOUGHT THAT SHOES
WOULD BE THE REASON YOU RECRUIT
PLAYERS.
>> Reporter: LOUISVILLE IS
ALREADY ON PROBATION AFTER
ANOTHER SCANDAL INVOLVING
ESCORTS FOR RECRUITS.
>> WHILE THIS MAY BE A DARK DAY
FOR THE UNIVERSITY OF
LOUISVILLE, BETTER DAYS ARE
AHEAD.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, COACH
PITINO SAYS HE HAS BEEN
EFFECTIVELY FIRED, AND THAT THE
MATTER WILL FOLLOW ITS LEGAL
COURSE.
BUT HE ALSO SAYS THAT HE HAS
DONE NOTHING WRONG, AND THAT THE
FACTS WILL EXONERATE HIM.
DAVID?
>> LINSEY DAVIS, OUR THANKS TO
YOU AGAIN TONIGHT.
>>> NEXT, THIS EVENING, TO NEW
IMAGES JUST RELEASED OF A DEADLY
SHOWDOWN WITH POLICE IN
SACRAMENTO.
THE ENCOUNTER WITH A MURDER
SUSPECT, SHOWING WHAT HAPPENED
IN THE MOMENTS AFTER THEY PULLED
HIM OVER.
HERE'S ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: : POLICE BEGAN
FOLLOWING ERIC ARNOLD BECAUSE HE
WAS WANTED IN CONNECTION WITH A
DOUBLE MURDER.
THE SECONDS AFTER THE STOP, IT
BECAME CLEAR WHAT HE SEEMED
CAPABLE OF.
[ GUNSHOTS ]
TONIGHT, SACRAMENTO POLICE
RELEASING 15 DASH AND BODY
CAMERA ANGLED OF THE SEPTEMBER
7th SHOOTING.
AFTER THE STOP, YOU CAN HEAR THE
OFFICERS GIVE ARNOLD EXPLICIT
INSTRUCTIONS.
>> DROP THE KEYS OUT THE WINDOW.
>> Reporter: AND THEN, FROM
MULTIPLE ANGLES, YOU SEE ARNOLD
BURST OUT OF HIS TRUCK, SPIN AND
FIRE.
HE BLASTS SIX SHOTS FROM HIS
SEMI AUTOMATIC.
POLICE RESPOND WITH OVER 30
BULLETS.
ARNOLD WAS HIT OVER 1 TIMES.
BUT SOME OF HIS SIX SHOTS
HITTING THEIR MARK.
TWO OFFICERS WOUNDED.
THIS OFFICER, BADLY LI LY LIMPI.
>> Reporter: BOTH OF THOSE
OFFICERS ARE RECUPERATING.
THAT SUSPECT WAS PRONOUNCED DEAD
ON THE SCENE.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN, THANK YOU.
>>> A MASSIVE EXPLOSION THAT
OFFICIALS NOW SAY MAY BE
SABOTAGE.
A HUGE BLAST IN UKRAINE TEARING
THROUGH AN AMMUNITION DEPOT AT A
MILITARY BASE.
30,000 PEOPLE EVACUATED FROM THE
NEARBY TOWN.
UKRAINE HAS BEEN FIGHTING
RUSSIA-BACKED ACCEPT ARE CYSTS
FOR THREE YEARS NOW.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS WEDNESDAY.
THE HIGHWAY STANDOFF AT RUSH
HOUR.
TRAFFIC BACKED UP FOR MILES.
THE POLICE CHASE ENDING WITH A
SHOOTOUT ON A MAJOR HIGHWAY.
NEWS TONIGHT ABOUT THE SUSPECT.
>>> ALSO, THE MURDER MYSTERY
UNSOLVED FOR NEARLY THREE
DECADES IN THIS COUNTRY.
NOW, THERE IS A MAJOR BREAK, IN
WHAT HAD BEEN CALLED THE CASE OF
THE KILLER CLOWN.
>>> AND THE FIRST U.S. GLOBAL
AIRLINE TO OFFER FREE TEXT
MESSAGING WHILE YOU'RE FLYING.
SO MANY ASKING TODAY, WILL PHONE
CALLS ON PLANES BE NEXT?
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[radio alarm]
♪ ♪
Julie is living with metastatic
breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women with hormone receptor-
positive HER2- metastatic breast
cancer as the first
hormonal based therapy.
♪ ♪
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
And IBRANCE plus letrozole
shrunk tumors in over half of
these patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE can
develop low white blood cell
counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if you have
fever, chills,
or other signs of infection
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts...
...infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver
blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Julie calls it her "new" normal.
Because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one-prescribed,
FDA-approved oral combination
treatment for HR+/HER2- MBC.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
>>> A MAJOR BREAK TONIGHT IN A
27-YEAR-OLD UNSOLVED MYSTERY.
POLICE IN FLORIDA ARRESTING A
FEMALE SUSPECT IN WHAT HAD BEEN
CALLED THE KILLER CLOWN CASE.
ACCUSED OF KILLING A WOMAN WHILE
DRESSED AS A CLOWN, THEN
MARRYING THE VICTIM'S HUSBAND.
HERE'S ABC'S LINZIE JANIS.
>> Reporter: THE CRIME WAS AS
BIZARRE AS IT WAS CHILLING.
POLICE SAIL MARLENE WARREN
OPENED THE DOOR OF HER FLORIDA
HOME TO FIND A CLOWN, WHO HANDED
HER BALLOONS AND FLOWERS, THEN
PULLED OUT A GUN AND SHOT HER TO
DEATH.
FOR 27 YEARS, NO ARREST -- UNTIL
NOW.
>> THIS IS THE WOMAN WHO
DETECTIVES SAY DRESSED AS A
CLOWN.
>> Reporter: POLICE IN VIRGINIA
ARRESTING SHEILA KEEN WARREN,
WHO HAS BEEN MARRIED TO THE
VICTIM'S HUSBAND, MICHAEL
WARREN, SINCE 2002.
AT THE TIME OF THE MURDER,
INVESTIGATORS SUSPECTED KEEN
WARREN, WHO WORKED AT THE
COUPLE'S USED CAR DEALERSHIP.
POLICE RE-OPENING THE COLD CASE
THREE YEARS AGO AND DOING NEW
DNA TESTING.
>> TOOK US 27 YEARS TO BRING
CLOSURE TO THE VICTIM'S FAMILY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE
VICTIM'S SON, JOE, WHO SAYS HE
SAW THE CLOWN DRIVE AWAY THAT
DAY IN THIS WHITE CONVERTIBLE,
SAYS "I'M HAPPIER THAN I'VE BEEN
IN MANY YEARS."
AS FOR HIS STEP-DAD, MICHAEL
WARREN, HE SAYS, THERE IS NO
DOUBT HE WAS INVOLVED.
HOWEVER, POLICE ARE NOT SAYING
MICHAEL WARREN IS A SUSPECT.
DAVID, KEEN WARREN IS BEHIND
BARS IN VIRGINIA TONIGHT.
SHE WILL SOON BE EXTRA DIETED TO
FLORIDA WHERE SHE FACES CHARGES
OF FIRST DEGREE MURDER.
>> LINZIE JANIS, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, FREE TEXT
MESSAGING WHEN YOU FLY NOW?
>>> ALSO, THE PASSENGER DRAGGED
OFF THE PLANE TODAY, STRUGGLING
WITH POLICE.
SHE SAID SHE HAD AN ALLERGY.
>>> AND THE DEADLY STANDOFF ON
AN AMERICAN HIGHWAY AT RUSH
HOUR.
THE NEW DETAILS COMING IN.
type 2 diabetes... fighg
with Fitness...
Food...
And the pill that
starts with F.
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA
if you have severe
kidney problems,
are on dialysis,
or have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary tract
infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious
and may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about
the pill that starts with F
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
Approaching Medicare
eligibility?
Don't put off checking out your
options until sixty-five.
Now is a good time to get the
ball rolling.
Consider an AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like any of these types
of plans,
it could help you with
out-of-pocket
medical costs.
Call now and request your free
Decision Guide
and explore the range of AARP
Medicare Supplement Plans.
Start gathering the information
you need...
to roll into sixty-five with
confidence.
Americans,
83% try to eat healthy,
yet up to 90% fall short
on getting key nutrients.
Let's do more.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
Complete with 100% daily value
of more than 15 key nutrients.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
If you've been struggling
with belly pain
and you're overwhelmed
by everything you've tried--
all those laxatives,
daily probiotics,
endless fiber--
it could be wearing on you.
Tell your doctor
what you've tried,
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults
with IBS
with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help relieve
your belly pain
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.
Do not give LINZESS
to children less than six
and it should not be given
to children
six to less than eighteen.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS
if you have a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop
unusual or severe
stomach pain,
especially with
bloody or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe,
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor
right away.
Other side effects
include gas,
stomach-area pain
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
>>> TO THE INDEX.
THE DEADLY HIGHWAY STANDOFF
DURING THE MORNING RUSH HOUR.
POLICE IN A SHOOTOUT WITH A
HOMICIDE SUSPECT.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE DRIVER WAS
SHOT AND KILLED AFTER JUMPING
OUT OF HIS SUV.
>>> THEN, THE PASSENGER DRAGGED
FROM HER FLIGHT IN BALTIMORE.
THE SOUTHWEST CREW SAYS THE
PASSENGER DEMANDING TWO DOGS BE
REMOVED BECAUSE OF HER SEVERE
ANIMAL ALLERGY.
THEY SAID SHE NEEDED PROOF.
THEY SAY SHE THEN BECAME
BELLIGERENT.
>>> PASSENGERS ON DELTA FLIGHTS
WILL BE ABLE TO SEND AND RECEIVE
FREE TEXT MESSAGING IN THE AIR.
TEXTING ONLY.
NO CALLS.
NOT YET.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
THE FAMILY RECORDING THEIR
FAMILY MEMBERS AND THEIR
FRIENDS, ALL SAYING THE SAME
LINE INTO THE PHONE, BUT THE
VERY DIFFERENT REACTIONS.
YOU GOT TO SEE THIS.
osteoporosi.
..and a high risk for fracture,
so with our doctors...
...we chose Prolia®...
...to help make our bones
stronger.
Only Prolia® helps strengthen
bones...
...by stopping cells that damage
them...
...with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions, like
low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip or
tongue swelling...
...rash, itching or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems, as severe jaw bone...
...problems may happen or new or
unusual pain in your hip groin,
or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
peak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®,
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects, like low blood calcium;
serious infections, which could
need hospitalization;
...skin problems; and severe
bone, joint, or muscle pain.
If your bones aren't getting
stronger...
...isn't it time for a new
direction?
Why wait? Ask your doctor about
Prolia®.
When you have a cold
stuff happens.
Shut down cold
symptoms fast
with Maximum Strength
Alka Seltzer Plus
Liquid Gels.
After a DVT blood clot...
I sure had a lot on my mind.
My 30-year marriage...
...my 3-month old business...
Plus...what if this
happened again?
I was given warfarin
in the hospital,
but wondered, was this
the best treatment for me?
So I made a point to
talk to my doctor.
He told me about ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots
and reduces the risk
of them happening again.
Not only does ELIQUIS treat
DVT and PE blood clots.
ELIQUIS also had
significantly less
major bleeding
than the standard
treatment.
ELIQUIS
had both...
...and that
turned around my
thinking.
Don't stop ELIQUIS unless
your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal
injection while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling,
numbness, or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
and it may take longer than
usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about
all planned medical
or dental procedures.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots.
Plus had less
major bleeding.
Both made ELIQUIS
right for me.
Ask your doctor if switching
to ELIQUIS is right for you.
>>> FINALLY, AMERICA STRONG.
THE CHARLOTTE COUPLE WITH A
SURPRISE FOR THEIR FAMILY.
>> TAMMY AND DREW WALTZ FROM
CHARLOTTE, NORTH CAROLINA.
TAKING IN FOUR SIBLINGS, THREE
BOYS AND A GIRL, AGES 8 TO 11,
OVER CHRISTMAS LAST YEAR.
THEY ARE ORPHANS FROM EASTERN
EUROPE WHO CAME TO LIVE WITH
THEM TEMPORARILY DURING THE
HOLIDAYS THROUGH A NONPROFIT.
TOGETHER FOR FIVE WEEKS, THEY
INSTANTLY BONDED.
AND WHEN IT WAS TIME TO SAY
GOOD-BYE, THE WALTZES SAY THEIR
HOME, THEIR LIVES, FELT EMPTY.
THEY STAYED IN TOUCH AND BEGAN
TO TALK ABOUT ADOPTION.
THE KIDS WERE OVERJOYED.
AND WHEN TAMMY AND DREW DECIDED
TO GIVE THEM A PERMANENT HOME,
THEY BEGAN TO TELL THEIR FRIENDS
AND FAMILY, AND THEY RECORDED
EACH OF THEIR RESPONSES.
THIS SOON TO BE GREAT-GRANDMA
CAME FIRST.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO BE A
GREAT-GRANDMA.
TIMES FOUR.
WE'RE ADOPTING.
>> Reporter: FAMILY FRIENDS.
IN SOME CASES, TAMMY AND DREW
GAVE THEM A LINE TO SAY ON
CAMERA, BUT THEY DIDN'T KNOW WHY
UNTIL IT HIT THEM.
>> CONGRATULATIONS, YOU'RE
ADOPTING.
YOU'RE ADOPTING!
>> YOU ARE?
OH, MY GOSH!
I'M SO HAPPY.
I'M YOUR AUNT.
YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE ME.
>> Reporter: THE REACTIONS,
SURPRISED, STUNNED, OVERJOYED,
OVERCOME.
AND TONIGHT, THOSE NEW PARENTS
GETTING READY.
>> HEY, DAVID, IT'S DREW AND
TAMMY CHECKING IN.
SO EXCITED TO BE ON THE SHOW
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: WE'RE EXCITE D,
TOO.
AFTER LEARNING THOSE CHILDREN
COULD BE HERE IN TIME FOR THE
HOLIDAYS.
>> WE REALLY JUST DID THIS VIDEO
TO SHOW THE KIDS HOW MUCH WE
LOVE THEM, BUT NOT JUST US, BUT
OUR FRIENDS AND FAMILY LOVE
THEM.
>> CAN'T WAIT FOR THE BIG
ARRIVAL.
I'LL SEE YOU HERE TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> THIS IS WCVB NEWSCENTER 5 AT
7:00.
MARIA: WE BEGIN WITH BREAKING
NEWS FROM LOWELL, A SCHOOL BUS
DRIVER OFF THE JOB AFTER A
LITTLE BOY IS LEFT ALONE ON A
BUS FOR HOURS.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I'M MARIA STEPHANOS.
ED: I'M ED HARDING.
THIS IS ALL HAPPENING ON A WEEK
WHEN TEMPERATURES SOARED NEAR
90.
OUR JOHN ATWATER IS LIVE IN
LOWELL WITH WHAT WE'RE LEARNING
TONIGHT.
pJOHN.
JOHN: THAT BOY IS FIVE YEARS OLD
.
HE IS A SPECIAL EDUCATION
STUDENT.
HE WAS LEFT ON THE BUS FOR FIVE
HOURS FRIDAY MORNING.
ACTUALLY THE BOY IS OK.
THAT BOY WAS SUPPOSED TO THE
DROPPED OFF, BUT THE DRIVER
NEVER CHECKED THAT ALL THE KIDS
WERE OFF THE BUS.
HE FOUND HIM AT 1:00 IN THE
AFTERNOON.
THE SCHOOL