♪
>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS, THE
U.S. BRACING FOR A HURRICANE.
MANDATORY EVACUATIONS.
HURRICANE WARNINGS IN EFFECT
RIGHT NOW.
STATES OF EMERGENCY IN SEVERAL
STATES.
NATE, ALREADY DEADLY, NOW TAKING
AIM AT THE GULF TONIGHT.
THE TRACK THEN HAS THE STORM
MOVING RIGHT UP THROUGH THE
NORTHEAST.
>>> ALSO BREAKING FROM LAS VEGAS
TONIGHT.
WHAT POLICE HAVE JUST REVEALED
ABOUT THE SECURITY GUARD WHO
APPROACHED THAT DOOR.
WHAT LED HIM THERE IN THE FIRST
PLACE.
AND WHAT WAS WRITTEN ON THE
GUNMAN'S NOTE.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP SUDDENLY
SUMMONING REPORTERS, TELLING
THEM THEY'RE WITNESSING THE
"CALM BEFORE THE STORM."
OUR REPORTER ASKS THE WHITE
HOUSE TONIGHT -- WHAT IS HE
TALKING ABOUT?
>>> A FAMOUS DALLAS COWBOYS STAR
AND HIS SON.
TONIGHT, A CAMPUS FRATERNITY
ACCUSED OF HAZING HIM DESCRIBED
AS A FIGHT CLUB.
>>> IN NEW YORK CITY,
AUTHORITIES SAY IT WAS AN
ALLEGED TERROR PLOT.
POLICE SAY THE PLANS FOR TIMES
SQUARE AND THE NEW YORK CITY
SUBWAY.
>>> AND KEITH URBAN.
THE MOMENT THAT MOVED SO MANY,
AS WE HONOR THE FACES.
GOOD EVENING AND IT IS GREAT TO
HAVE YOU WITH US ON A FRIDAY
NIGHT.
WE ARE A HURRICANE WEARY NATION
AND YET TONIGHT ANOTHER POWERFUL
STORM HEADED FOR THE U.S.
NATE IS SPEEDING UP AND GAINING
STRENGTH.
RIGHT NOW HEADING INTO THE WARM
WATERS OF THE GULF.
STATES OF EMERGENCY ACROSS THE
GULF.
THE SYSTEM DEADLY BEFORE
ARRIVING.
22 LIVES LOST.
PREPARATIONS UNDER WAY AT THIS
HOUR AND THERE ARE NOW SOME
MANDATORY EVACUATIONS UNDER WAY.
LET'S GET TO GINGER ZEE WITH US
TONIGHT BECAUSE THIS WILL NOT
ONLY HIT THE GULF BUT WILL
TRAVEL THROUGH THE COUNTRY.
>> UP THROUGH THE NORTHEAST.
WE HAVE GOT TO WATCH FOR FLASH
FLOODING ALL THE WAY THROUGH
PENNSYLVANIA.
THE PENINSULA IS SHOWING THE
STORM EAST.
FLYING AT 21 MILES PER HOUR.
HURRICANE WARNING IN PLACE FOR
NEW ORLEANS, GULF PORT, BILOXI
EXTENDING TO INLAND THERE.
THE BRUNT WILL BE FELT SATURDAY
NIGHT THROUGH SUNDAY MORNING.
THAT'S WHEN IT IS GOING TO MAKE
LANDFALL AND SPEEDS UP THROUGH
THE OHIO VALLEY INTO THE
NORTHEAST AND OUT BY TUESDAY.
BUT BEFORE THAT, THE IMPACT
STORM SURGE, FOUR TO SIX FEET.
THE BAY, GULF SHORES UP TO EIGHT
FEET AND TEN INCHES OF RAIN.
>> TRACKING IT INTO THE WEEKEND.
THANK YOU.
IN THE CROSSHAIRS OF THIS STORM
NEW ORLEANS AND THE LOW LYING
CITIES ALONG THE GULF DANGEROUS
FLOODING AND STORM SURGE IS
LIKELY AND THIS QUESTION
TONIGHT.
ARE THE PUMPS READY IN NEW
ORLEANS?
ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI IS THERE.
>> Reporter: ACROSS THE GULF
TONIGHT, THIS IS THE STATE OF
EMERGENCY AND THEY'RE RACING TO
GET READY FOR THIS STORM.
>> WE'RE GOING TO FLOOD.
>> IN NEW ORLEANS A DOZEN OF THE
CITY'S DRAINAGE PURPOMPS AREN'T
WORKING.
TEAMS ARE CLEARING DRAINS AND
PARTS OF JEFFERSON PARISHES,
MORE THAN 1,000 FAMILIES FORCED
TO LIVE THEIR HOMES.
>> ONE OF THE GREATEST THREATS
TO THIS STORM IS NOT NECESSARILY
INTERIOR RAIN, BUT STORM SURGE.
>> Reporter: BILLY ROST IS
LEAVING TONIGHT.
HE'S MOVED EVERYTHING OF THE
GROUND.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE SURGE
IS GOING TO DO.
IF YOU DON'T PICK IT UP YOU LOSE
IT.
THIS IS LIKE A GAMBLE.
>> Reporter: THREE FEET OF STORM
SURGE AND HE'S FINE.
SIX FEET, HE LOSES EVERYTHING.
HE'S EXPECTING FIVE.
>> YOU CAN ONLY DO SO MUCH.
YOU CAN'T RUN FROM WATER, BABY.
>> Reporter: THE STORM HAS
ALREADY KILLED.
AT LEAST 11 DEAD IN NICARAGUA,
AND EIGHT IN COSTA RICA.
DOZENS MORE MISSING AFTER
MUDSLIDES WASHED AWAY HOMES, AND
STEVE JOINS US LIVE TONIGHT.
STEVE, YOU WERE TELLING US THOSE
PUMPS CAN PULL OUT AN INCH OF
RAIN IN AN HOUR?
>> Reporter: YES.
BUT THAT'S JUST DURING THE FIRST
HOUR.
AFTER THE ABILITY OF A PUMPING
STATION DROPS TO ABOUT HALF AN
INCH AN HOUR ASSUMING ALL THE
PUMPS ARE WORKING WHICH WOULD
SURPRISE JUST ABOUT EVERYONE IN
THE CITY.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS THAT IF
SEVERAL INCHES OF RAIN FALL OVER
NEW ORLEANS ALL AT ONCE, THIS
CITY WILL STILL FLOOD EVEN WITH
ALL OF THE PUMPS WORKING
PROPERLY.
>> WE ARE THINKING ABOUT THAT
CITY AND EVERY CITY ALONG THE
GULF.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE MOVE ON TO OTHER
HEADLINES AT THIS HOUR AND FROM
LAS VEGAS NEW DEVELOPMENTS.
WHAT DREW THAT HOTEL SECURITY
GUARD TO THE HOTEL ROOM IN THE
FIRST PLACE AND EVEN THOUGH HE
WAS SHOT THROUGH THE DOOR WAS HE
THE ONE WHO STOPPED MORE
BLOODSHED.
MATT GUTMAN FROM LAS VEGAS
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: FIVE DAYS AFTER THE
WORST MASS SHOOTING IN AMERICAN
HISTORY, LAS VEGAS POLICE
ACKNOWLEDGING THEY STILL DON'T
KNOW WHAT DROVE STEPHEN PADDOCK
TO OPEN FIRE ON THAT HELPLESS
CROWD.
>> I GET IT.
WE ALL WANT ANSWERS.
WE HAVE LOOKED AT EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT WE ARE
LEARNING THAT HERO SECURITY
GUARD JESUS CAMPOS MAY HAVE
PREVENTED FURTHER BLOODSHED.
POLICE SAY PADDOCK HAD BEEN
SHOOTING WHEN CAMPOS ARRIVED
RESPONDING TO A DOOR ALARM.
>> WE BELIEVE HE WAS SHOOTING
INTO THE CROWD, AND THEN THE
SECURITY GUARD WAS SHOT DURING
THAT EVENT.
>> Reporter: 48-YEAR-OLD DOUG
CARTER WAS ATTENDING THE CONCERT
WITH HIS WIFE AND SON.
BUT THEY BECAME SEPARATED IN THE
CHAOS.
YOU SEE THEM HERE DAZED AND
STAGGERING, A BULLET IN HIS ARM.
THE MAN TAKING THIS VIDEO RAY
PAGE TAKES HIM TO A MAKE-SHIFT
TRIAGE CENTER.
>> STAND RIGHT HERE.
HE'S IN SHOCK.
>> Reporter: IN THE DARK YOU
HEAR HIM MUMBLE ABOUT HIS GUN.
>> I GOT MY --
>> Reporter: WHEN THE PEOPLE
HELPING HIM PULL UP HIS SHIRT
THAT LIGHT ELIMINATES ANOTHER
BULLET HOLE IN HIS CHEST.
>> I DO GOT ONE?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: POLICE OFFICERS
KEEPING HIM CALM.
RAY PAGE THEN GOES TO GET HIS
TRUCK.
>> I'M GOING TO TRY TO FIND A
MEDIC.
>> Reporter: WHEN HE RETURNS
VICTIMS PILING INTO HIS PICKUP.
RAY PAGE DELIVERING DOUG AND THE
OTHERS TO SAFETY.
AND IT WOULD BE 14 AGONIZING
HOURS UNTIL DOUG WAS REUNITED
WITH HIS FAMILY.
DID YOU KNOW HE WAS HIT?
>> I HAD NO IDEA UNTIL 12:00 THE
NEXT DAY WHEN WE FOUND HIM IN
THE HOSPITAL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT HIS SON IS
THANKFUL TO THE HEROES WHO SAVED
HIS DAD.
>> JUST AMAZING THERE WAS
SOMEBODY THERE TO HELP MY DAD
AND HE WAS -- I THOUGHT HE WAS
ON THE STREET SOMEWHERE.
>> MATT POLICE ARE CALLING THAT
SECURITY GUARD A TRUE HERO.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
POLICE ARE SAYING AS THAT GUARD
NEARED THE DOOR IT DIVERTED HIS
ATTENTION FROM THE CROWD TO THE
HALLWAY.
HE BEGAN FIRING WILDLY INTO IT
INJURING THAT SECURITY GUARD.
SOMEHOW THAT GUARD MANAGED TO
ALERT AUTHORITIES.
HE'S BEING HAILED AS A HERO AS
THE CITY CONTINUES TO MOURN.
THERE HAVE BEEN THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE HERE AT THIS MEMORIAL
SITE ALL DAY DAVID.
>> ALSO TONIGHT, WHAT WAS
WRITTEN ON A NOTE FOUND IN THE
GUNMAN'S HOTEL ROOM AS WE
LEARNED HOW MUCH THE GUNMAN MADE
IN THE DAYS BEFORE THE ATTACK
AND THE MILLIONS HE MADE IN JUST
ONE YEAR.
HERE'S BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: SHE JUST RETURNED
TO THE US FROM THE PHILIPPINES
TWO DAYS AGO, BUT TONIGHT
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES HAVE PUT A
CLOSE WATCH ON MARILOU DANLEY TO
MAKE SURE SHE DOESN'T TRY TO
LEAVE THE COUNTRY AS THEY
STRUGGLE TO FIND THE MOTIVE
BEHIND HER BOYFRIEND'S CRIME.
>> WE HAVE NO CREDIBLE
INFORMATION TO REPORT TO YOU AS
TO MOTIVATION.
>> Reporter: FBI AGENTS AND
POLICE SAY THEY ARE SKEPTICAL OF
DANLEY'S CLAIMS THAT SHE KNEW
NOTHING ABOUT THE PLANS OF HER
LONGTIME BOYFRIEND
STEPHEN PADDOCK.
BUT A FAMILY FRIEND WHO VISITED
THEM IN NEVADA SAY THAT COULD
WELL BE TRUE, THAT SHE WAS
SUBSERVIENT TO HIM.
>> IT'S NOT WHAT I SAW AS A
LOVING, CARING RELATIONSHIP.
>> Reporter: ADAM LEFEVRE TOLD
AN AUSTRALIAN TV STATION HE
SPENT A WEEK WITH THE COUPLE IN
NEVADA IN 2015, STAYING WITH
THEM IN A LUXURY CASINO SUITE,
AND LATER AT HIS HOME, WHERE
PADDOCK SHOWED OFF WHAT HE
CALLED HIS GUN ROOM.
>> HE WAS VERY STRICT AND VERY
FIRM ON THE FACT THAT IT IS A
RIGHT, IT IS A CAPACITY, AND IT
IS THE FREEDOM OF EVERY AMERICAN
RESIDENT AND PERSON TO
PARTICIPATE, TO OWN A GUN AND
USE IT AS SEEN FIT WHEN NEED BE.
AND THAT LAW SHOULD NEVER BE
CHANGED.
>> Reporter: LATE TODAY
AUTHORITIES CONFIRMED REPORTS
THE SHOOTER LEFT BEHIND SOME
KIND OF A NOTE, WHICH
AUTHORITIES SAY CONTAINED A
SERIES OF CRYPTIC NUMBERS, BUT
WAS NOT A SUICIDE NOTE.
OFFICIALS ARE TRACKING EVERY
ASPECT OF HIS LIFE, BACK TO HIGH
SCHOOL IN LOS ANGELES AND
EARLIER, AND HIS RECENT
PRESCRIPTIONS FOR VALIUM.
>> WE ARE LOOKING AT EVERY
ASPECT FROM BIRTH TO DEATH OF
THIS SUSPECT IN THIS CASE.
>> Reporter: IN THE FINAL DAYS
BEFORE THE SHOOTING, OFFICIALS
TELL ABC NEWS HE WAS IN THE
COMPANY OF A PROSTITUTE, AND
WENT GAMBLING IN THE MANDALAY
BAY CASINO, WINNING BIG JACKPOTS
ON BOTH FRIDAY AND SATURDAY
NIGHTS.
>>> BRIAN YOU WERE SAYING
STEPHEN PADDOCK CALLED HIMSELF A
PROFESSIONAL GAMBLER.
>> IN THE YEAR 2015 HE REPORTED
INCOME OF $5 MILLION.
>> AND NO MOTIVE?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> BRIAN, THANKS.
I HOPE EVERYONE WILL JOIN US FOR
AN ABC NEWS 2020 DOCUMENTARY
PRESENTATION ON THE LAS VEGAS
MASSACRE, HEART BREAK AND
HEROES.
WE HAVE NEW REPORTING TONIGHT AT
10:00 EASTERN/9:00 CENTRAL.
NEXT TO THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT
PRESIDENT TRUMP RAISING NEW
QUESTIONS AFTER WHAT HE SAID
DURING A PHOTO ON SUMMONING
REPORTERS TELLING THEM THIS WAS
THE CALM BEFORE THE STORM.
CECELIA VEGA ASKING THE WHITE
HOUSE WHAT DID HE MEAN.
>> Reporter: IN THE STATE DINING
ROOM, THIS IS THE IMAGE
PRESIDENT TRUMP SUMMONED
REPORTERS TO SEE -- THE
PRESIDENT SMILING, SURROUNDED BY
HIS TOP MILITARY LEADERS AND
THEIR SPOUSES.
THEN CAME THE UNSOLICITED,
CRYPTIC COMMENT.
>> DO YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT THIS
REPRESENTS?
>> TELL US, SIR.
>> MAYBE IT'S THE CALM BEFORE
THE STORM.
>> WHAT'S THE STORM?
>> COULD BE THE CALM -- THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM.
>> WHAT STORM, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> WE HAVE THE WORLD'S GREAT
MILITARY PEOPLE.
I WILL TELL YOU THAT.
THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING.
THANK YOU.
>> WHAT STORM MR. PRESIDENT?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: AND TODAY IN THE
OVAL OFFICE, WE TRIED AGAIN.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, WHAT DID YOU
MEAN BY "CALM BEFORE THE STORM"?
YESTERDAY WHAT DID YOU MEAN BY
THAT?
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: AFTER A WINK, AND A
PAUSE --
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: THE COMMENT
ESPECIALLY OMINOUS AS THE UNITED
STATES IS ENGAGED IN A WAR OF
WORDS WITH NORTH KOREA, AND THE
PRESIDENT IS ON THE VERGE OF
DECERTIFYING THE NUCLEAR DEAL
WITH IRAN.
OR MAYBE THIS WAS JUST TRUMP
BEING TRUMP.
>> WE'RE NEVER GOING TO SAY IN
ADVANCE WHAT THE PRESIDENT IS
GOING TO DO.
>> HOW SERIOUSLY SHOULD THE
AMERICAN ADVERSARIES TAKE THESE
COMMENTS?
IS HE SERIOUS?
>> I THINK YOU CAN TAKE THE
PRESIDENT PROTECTING THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE ALWAYS EXTREMELY
SERIOUS AND IF HE FEELS THAT
ACTION IS NECESSARY, HE'LL TAKE
IT.
>> CECELIA VEGA PRESSING THE
WHITE HOUSE TODAY.
WE ALSO KNOW THE ADMINISTRATION
IS MOVING FORWARD TODAY ON A
ROLLBACK OF AN OBAMACARE MANDATE
REQUIRING EMPLOYEE COVERAGE OF
BIRTH CONTROL, 55 MILLION WOMEN
HAVE ACCESS TO WITHOUT A
COPAYMENT AND NOW SOME
EXCEPTIONS?
>> Reporter: EMPLOYERS WILL NO
LONGER OFFER THESE INSURANCE
PLANS THAT COVER BIRTH CONTROL.
IF THEY CLAIM IT VIOLATES
RELIGIOUS BELIEFS IT TAKES
EFFECT IMMEDIATELY.
DEMOCRATS ARE CALLING THIS A NEW
LOW AND REPUBLICANS ARE CHEERING
THIS AS THE PRESIDENT MAKING
GOOD ON A CAMPAIGN PROMISE.
>> TO PUERTO RICO.
MORE THAN TWO WEEKS AFTER THE
STORM JUST 10% OF THE ISLAND HAS
ELEX
ELECTRICITY BACK AND MORE THAN
HALF HAS DRINKABLE WATER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP STRESSING THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT'S COMMITMENT
AND PRONOUNCING PUERTO RICO THIS
WAY.
>> WE ARE ALSO PRAYING FOR THE
PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO.
WE LOVE PUERTO RICO.
PUERTO RICO.
>> WE LOVE YOU.
>> AND WE ALSO LOVE PUERTO RICO.
>> THE PRESIDENT ON PUERTO RICO
TONIGHT.
IN ANOTHER NEWS A VIDEO IN
CHARLOTTE, A TRAGIC MISS
UNDERSTANDING THAT LEFT ONE MAN
DEAD.
HERE'S PIERRE THOMAS TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT NEWLY
RELEASED VIDEO FROM A FATAL
POLICE SHOOTING IN CHARLOTTE
REVEALING HOW LIFE AND DEATH
SITUATIONS PLAY OUT IN SECONDS.
EARLY LAST MONTH POLICE RESPOND
AFTER RECEIVING A 911 CALL
TELLING THE 911 DISPATCHER I
CALLED YOU TO COME FOR ME.
HE ACKNOWLEDGES HE HAS A GUN BUT
SAYS IT'S EMPTY WITH WORD OF A
FIREARM, OFFICERS DON'T TAKE HIS
WORD BUT THE GUN WON'T BE
LOADED.
THEY MOVE IN GUNS DRAWN.
>> DROP THE GUN.
>> Reporter: THEN LESS THAN A
MINUTE ENDS THE LIFE OF RUBIN
GALINDO.
HE STEPS OUT, HIS HANDS IN THE
AIR.
POLICE SEE A GUN.
THE GUN WAS IN FACT EMPTY.
FAMILY MEMBERS CONCERNED THAT
THE OFFICERS ACTED TOO QUICKLY.
T
POLICE CHIEF IS STANDING BY HIS
MEN AND UP TO A PROSECUTOR
INVESTIGATING THE CASE.
>> FROM THE PENTAGON, A FOURTH
SOLDIER HAS DIED AND HIS
IDENTITY NOT REVEALED BUT THE
FACES OF THE THREE OTHERS WHO
DIED THERE.
STAFF SERGEANT BRIAN BLATT FROM
WASHINGTON STATE, STAFF SERGEANT
JEREMIAH JOHNSON FROM OHIO AND
DUSTIN WRIGHT FROM GEORGIA.
THEY WERE AMBUSHED WHILE ON A
JOINT PATROL.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD THIS FRIDAY.
THE ALLEGED TERROR PLOT IN NEW
YORK CITY.
THE DETAILS REVEALED TONIGHT.
THE PLAN FOR THE NEW YORK CITY
SUBWAY.
THE FBI SEIZING BOMB MAKING
MATERIALS.
MORE AFTER THE BREAK.
>>> A FAMOUS DALLAS COWBOYS STAR
AND HIS SON IN THE NEWS.
THE CAMPUS FRATERNITY ACCUSED OF
HAZING HIM.
A BAT TO THE STOMACH IN A
CULTURE DESCRIBED AS A FIGHT
CLUB.
>>> AND KEITH URBAN AND THE
MOMENT THAT MOVED SO MANY AS WE
HONOR THE FACES.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
of multi.
♪
That's why there's Trintellix,
a prescription medication
for depression.
Trintellix may help you take
a step forward
in improving your depression.
Tell your healthcare
professional right away
if your depression worsens,
or you have unusual changes
in mood,
behavior or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in children,
teens and young adults.
Do not take with MAOIs.
Tell your healthcare
professional about
your medications, including
migraine, psychiatric
and depression medications,
to avoid a potentially
life-threatening condition.
Increased risk of bleeding or
bruising may occur,
especially if taken with NSAID
pain relievers,
aspirin or blood thinners.
Manic episodes or
vision problems
may occur in some people.
May cause low sodium levels.
The most common side effects
were nausea,
constipation and vomiting.
TRINTELLIX had no significant
impact on weight
in clinical trials.
Ask your healthcare
professional about TRINTELLIX.
Rethink what's possible.
Rethink your allergy pills.
Flonase Sensimist Allergy Relief
helps block 6 key
inflammatory
substances
with a
gentle mist.
Most allergy
pills
only block
one.
And 6 is greater
than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
♪
Traders -- They're always
looking for advantages.
The smart ones look
to Fidelity to find them.
We give you research
and data-visualization tools
to help identify
potential opportunities.
So, you can do it this way...
or get everything you need to
help capture investment ideas
and make smarter trading
decisions with Fidelity
for just $4.95
per online U.S. equity trade.
Fidelity.
Open an account today.
♪
I AM TOTALLY BLIND.
AND NON-24 CAN THROW MY
DAYS AND NIGHTS OUT OF SYNC,
KEEPING ME FROM THE
THINGS I LOVE TO DO.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-214-2424.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE
ALLEGATIONS OF BRUTAL HAZING AT
THE UNIVERSITY OF OKLAHOMA.
THE SON OF A FORMER DALLAS
COWBOY STAR SUING A FRATERNITY
CLAIMING A PLEDGE RITUAL LEFT
HIM WITH BRAIN INJURIES AND
MEMORY LOSS.
HERE'S DAVID WRIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE
20-YEAR-OLD SON OF A DALLAS
COWBOYS LEGEND IS SUING A
UNIVERSITY OF OKLAHOMA
FRATERNITY OVER AN ALLEGED
HAZING RITUAL THAT HE SAYS LEFT
HIM WITH PERMANENT BRAIN DAMAGE.
FORMER COWBOY TIGHT END
JAY NOVACEK'S SON BLAKE IS SUING
OKLAHOMA'S CHAPTER OF BETA THETA
PI, ACCUSING THE FRATERNITY OF
VIOLENT HAZING RITUALS.
HIS LAWYER PROVIDED PHOTOS OF
WHAT HE SAYS WAS A "FIGHT CLUB,"
JUST LIKE THE MOVIE, THAT HE
SAYS LEFT NOVACECK WITH A BROKEN
NOSE.
NOVACEK IS SUING OVER A ANOTHER
ALLEGED INCIDENT.
>> HE WAS BEATEN WITH A BASEBALL
BAT AND KNOCKED UNCONSCIOUS.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS THE
INCIDENT LED TO TRAUMATIC BRAIN
INJURY AND SEVERE MEMORY LOSS.
THE LAWSUIT SAYS THAT INCIDENT
TOOK PLACE ON OCTOBER 11, 2015,
BUT THE FRATERNITY SAYS NOVACEK
WAS NOT EVEN IN OKLAHOMA THAT
DAY, CITING THIS INSTAGRAM PHOTO
POSTED FROM THE DALLAS COWBOY'S
GAME.
NOVACEK'S LAWYER SAYS DUE TO HIS
CLIENT CANNOT BE SURE OF THE
EXACT DATE BECAUSE OF THE MEMORY
LOSS.
SO THEY'RE AMENDING THE LAWSUIT.
THE FRATERNITY SAYS IT DOES NOT
CONDONE HAZING, AND CALLS THESE
CHARGES FALSE AND INFLAMMATORY.
DAVID?
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK BREAKING
NEWS COMING IN ON THE MAN BEHIND
SO MANY MOVIES OF OUR TIME.
HE APOLOGIZED YESTERDAY AND
WHAT'S HAPPENED TONIGHT.
ALSO, THE ALLEGED TERROR PLOT
INVOLVING NEW YORK CITY
TARGETING TIMES SQUARE AND THE
SUBWAY.
WHAT AUTHORITIES ARE NOW
REVEALING.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
CDs, baseball cards.
Your old magic set?
(Sigh)
And this wrestling ticket.
Which you still owe me for.
Seriously? $25?
I didn't even want to go.
Ahh, your diary!
"Mom says it is
totally natural..."
$25 is nothing.
(Alert beep)
Abracadabra, bro.
Settle up with your friends
on October 17th
with the Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
Settle up with your friends
on October 17th
When it comes to strong bones,
are you on the right path?
We have postmenopausal
osteoporosis...
..and a high risk for fracture,
so with our doctors...
...we chose Prolia®...
...to help make our bones
stronger.
Only Prolia® helps strengthen
bones...
...by stopping cells that damage
them...
...with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions, like
low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip or
tongue swelling...
...rash, itching or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems, as severe jaw bone...
...problems may happen or new or
unusual pain in your hip groin,
or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
peak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®,
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects, like low blood calcium;
serious infections, which could
need hospitalization;
...skin problems; and severe
bone, joint, or muscle pain.
If your bones aren't getting
stronger...
...isn't it time for a new
direction?
Why wait? Ask your doctor about
Prolia®.
Liberty Mutual saved us almost
eight hundred dollars when
we switched our auto and
home insurance.
Liberty did what?
Yeah, they saved us a ton,
which gave us a little wiggle
room in our budget.
Wish our insurance did that.
Then we could get a real
babysitter instead of
your brother.
Hey, welcome back.
This guy... right?
Yes.
Ellen.
That's my robe.
You could save seven hundred
eighty two dollars
when Liberty stands with you.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
I accept I take easier trails
than I used to.
I even accept I have a higher
risk of stroke due to AFib,
a type of irregular heartbeat
not caused
by a heart valve problem.
But no matter what path I take,
I go for my best.
So if there's something better
than warfarin,
I'll go for that too. ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS reduced the risk of
stroke better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS unless
your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and in
rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS, you may
bruise more easily...
...and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care for
sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about all
planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor about ELIQUIS.
.
>>> TO THE INDEX TONIGHT AND THE
DANGEROUS CHASE THROUGH THE
STREETS OF MIAMI.
A SUSPECTED BANK ROBBER TRYING
TO OUTRUN POLICE.
CARJACKING TWO DRIVERS AT
GUNPOINT.
POLICE SAY HE WAS STILL ARMED
WHEN HE JUMPED INTO A RIVER.
THE SUSPECT SHOT AND KILLED BY
OFFICERS.
HE THREATENED TO SHOOT AND
REFUSED TO SURRENDER.
>> HERE IN NEW YORK CITY
AUTHORITIES ARRESTING THREE
SUSPECTS TO DETONATE BOMBS AND
TAKING PICTURES OF THEIR
POSSIBLE TARGETS.
THEY MARKED UP A MAP OF THE
SUBWAY SYSTEM AND THE FBI SAID
THE SUSPECTS WERE FROM PAKISTAN
AND PHILIPPINES.
>>> HARVEY WINESTEIN WILL BE
SUSPEND FIRST RESPONDER THE
COMPANY THAT BEARS HIS NAME
PENDING IN INVESTIGATION INTO
CLAIMS OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT.
ALLEGATIONS MADE BY ASHLEY JUDD.
WINESTEIN APOLOGIZING FOR HIS
ACTIONS YESTERDAY.
>>> THE MOMENT THAT MOVED SO
MANY.
KEITH URBAN AND WHAT HE DID AS
WE REMEMBER TONIGHT.
When you have a cold...
stuff happens.
Shut down cold symptoms fast
with Maximum
Strength Alka Seltzer
Plus Liquid Gels.
Only have a sore throat?
Get long-lasting
relief for up to 6 hours
with New Alka Seltzer
Plus Sore Throat Relief.
DEPEND SILHOUETTE
ACTIVE FIT BRIEFS,
FEATURE A THIN DESIGN
FOR COMPLETE COMFORT.
THEY SAY "MOVE IT OR LOSE IT" -
AND AT MY AGE, I'M
MOVING MORE THAN EVER.
BECAUSE GETTING
OLDER IS INEVITABLE.
BUT FEELING OLDER?
THAT'S SOMETHING I CONTROL.
GET A FREE SAMPLE
AT DEPEND.COM.
With Advil, you'll ask
What twisted ankle?
THAT'S SOMETHING I CONTROL.
What muscle strain?
Advil makes pain a distant
memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
Remember that accident I got in
with the pole, and I
had to make a claim
and all that?
Is that whole thing
still dragging on?
No, I took some pics
with the app and...
filed a claim, but...
You know how they send you
money to cover repairs and...
They took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid
right away, but...
at the very end of
it all, my agent...
Wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy.
But if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience
for any reason,
they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim Satisfaction
Guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
only from Allstate.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, SINGER
KEITH URBAN AT A VIGIL IN
NASHVILLE FOR THE VICTIMS IN LAS
VEGAS.
HE TALKED ABOUT A QUESTION FROM
HIS 9-YEAR-OLD AND PERFORMED A
SONG.
TONIGHT WE REMEMBER 58 NAMES, 58
FACES LOST.
>> MY 9-YEAR-OLD AS I WAS
DRIVING HER TO SCHOOL SAID TO
ME, DAD, YOU SEEM QUIET.
I SAID, YEAH.
I'M REALLY -- A LOT OF PEOPLE
KILLED LAST NIGHT.
AND SHE SAID DID YOU KNOW ANY OF
THEM?
AND I SAID, NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
AND THEN SHE SAID, WELL, THEN
WHY ARE YOU SO SAD?
I SAID, WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
THESE WERE INNOCENT PEOPLE.
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WEARY ♪
♪ FEELIN' SMALL ♪
♪ WHEN TEARS ARE IN YOUR EYES ♪
♪ I WILL DRY THEM ALL ♪
♪ I'M ON YOUR SIDE ♪
♪ OH WHEN THE TIMES GET ROUGH ♪
♪ AND PRECIOUS CAN BE FOUND ♪
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN ♪
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN ♪
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN ♪
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN ♪
>> THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
ON ANOTHER DIFFICULT WEEK.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER TONIGHT ON
2020.
>> THIS IS WCVB NEWSCENTER 5 AT
7:00.
ED: TONIGHT A NEWTON MAN BEHIND
BARS, ACCUSED IN A DISTURBING
CASE OF CYBER STALKING.
I'M ED HARDING.
MARIA: I'M MARIA STEPHANOS.
THE SUSPECT ALSO CHARGED WITH
MAKING A SERIES OF BOMB THREATS
AGAINST THE WALTHAM SCHOOL
SYSTEM.
THE CHARGES WERE LAID OUT TODAY
IN BOSTON FEDERAL COURT.
OUR DAVID BEINICK REPORTS ON THE
INTENSE INVESTIGATION THAT LED
TO THE ARREST.
DAVID: INVESTIGATORS SAY ONE
REASON THIS CASE TOOK SO LONG TO
SOLVE IS THAT THE MAN THAT WAS
ARRAIGNED HERE THIS AFTERNOON
DID A GOOD JOB OF HIDING HIS
TRACKS IN CYBERSPACE.
AS RYAN LIN STOOD BESIDE BEFORE
A JUDGE IN FEDERAL COURT TO FACE
A CHARGE OF CYBER STALKING, ONE
OF HIS FORMER ROOMMATES, WHO'S
NOW MOVED OUT OF STATE,
EXPRESSED RELIEF.
>> IT WAS IMPERATIVE TO ALL OF
US WHO LIVED WITH RYAN THAT HE
WAS BEHIND THIS CYBER STALKING.
DAVID: INVESTIGATORS SAY AFTER
ANSWERING AND ON CRAIGSLIST,
LIN MOVED INTO THIS APARTMENT IN
WATERTOWN WITH THREE ROOMMATES,
ONE OF WHOM HE ALLEGEDLY
TARGETED.