>>> TONIGHT, THE GROWING
FIRESTORM.
PRESIDENT TRUMP VERSUS THE NFL.
GROWING BACKLASH TO THE
PRESIDENT'S ANGRY WORDS ABOUT
ATHLETES WHO PROTEST DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> GET THAT SON OF A [ BLEEP ]
OFF THE FIELD.
>> FROM PATRIOTS OWNER BOB
KRAFT, QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY TO
LeBRON JAMES, ON LIVE TV TODAY.
PLAYERS LOCKING ARMS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
TENSIONS BOILING OVER AMONG
FANS.
AND TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE IS
ASKED, WITH NORTH KOREA, WITH
HEALTH CARE, WITH THE EMERGENCY
IN PUERTO RICO, WHY THIS?
WHY NOW?
>>> ALL OF THIS AS THE GOVERNOR
OF PUERTO RICO SAYS THEY ARE
DEALING WITH A HUMANITARIAN
DISASTER, THAT THEY NEED HELP.
>>> HURRICANE MARIA.
TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS ALONG
PARTS OF THE EAST COAST RIGHT
NOW.
>>> CHAOS AND ARRESTS ON THE
HILL TONIGHT.
PROTESTERS WORRIED ABOUT LOSING
THEIR HEALTH INSURANCE HAULED
OFF.
REPUBLICANS CAN ONLY AFFORD TO
LOSE ONE MORE VOTE.
AND A KEY SENATOR ON THE FENCE
TONIGHT.
IS SHE ABOUT TO REVEAL HER
DECISION?
>>> AND SMOKE SUDDENLY FILLING
THE CABIN TODAY.
PASSENGERS MAKING A QUICK
ESCAPE.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A MONDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP, HIS WORDS ABOUT SOME
PLAYERS AND THE NFL, AND THE
BACKLASH, DIVIDING FANS.
AND LEADING TO PLAYERS AND TEAM
OWNERS, SOME OF WHOM SUPPORTED
THE PRESIDENT, TO NOW BREAK
RANKS WITH HIM ON THIS ISSUE.
TEAMS ACROSS THE COUNTRY THIS
WEEKEND SHOWING SOLIDARITY, SO
MANY LOCKED ARM IN ARM.
PATRIOTS QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY,
A FRIEND OF PRESIDENT TRUMP,
SPEAKING OUT TODAY, CALLING THE
PRESIDENT'S REMARKS DIVISIVE.
THE STEELERS PLAYER WHO STOOD
ALONE, HIS TEAM IN THE LOCKER
ROOM.
BUT A SHORT TIME AGO, NOW
APOLOGIZING, HE SAYS, FOR
INADVERTENTLY MAKING HIS TEAM
LOOK BAD.
AND AS I MENTIONED, WITH SO MUCH
AT STAKE ALREADY, WHY DID THE
PRESIDENT TARGET THIS?
ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, PRESIDENT
TRUMP DEFIANT AND UNAPOLOGETIC
ABOUT SPARKING A NATIONAL
FIRESTORM WITH THESE WORDS.
>> WOULDN'T YOU LOVE TO SEE ONE
OF THESE NFL OWNERS, WHEN
SOMEBODY DISRESPECTS OUR FLAG,
TO SAY, GET THAT SON OF A
[ BLEEP ] OFF THE FIELD RIGHT
NOW, OUT.
HE'S FIRED.
>> Reporter: AN ADMINISTRATION
SOURCE TELLS ABC NEWS THE
PRESIDENT HAD EVERY INTENTION OF
MENTIONING THE NFL BEFORE A
PACKED HOUSE IN ALABAMA, BUT HE
ALSO WENT WAY BEYOND WHAT WAS
WRITTEN IN THAT SPEECH,
ATTACKING PLAYERS LIKE FORMER
SAN FRANCISCO 49ers QUARTERBACK
COLIN KAEPERNICK, WHO TOOK A
KNEE DURING THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM, A SILENCE PROTEST
AGAINST POLICE BRUTALITY AND
RACIAL INJUSTICE.
>> IF YOU SEE IT, EVEN IF IT'S
ONE PLAYER, LEAVE THE STADIUM.
>> Reporter: THE REACTION
INSTANT.
♪ O SAY CAN YOU SEE ♪
>> Reporter: ON FOOTBALL FIELDS
AROUND THE COUNTRY, PLAYERS
UNITED IN PROTEST, MANY
KNEELING, OTHERS LINKING ARMS,
THEIR OWNERS AND COACHES JOINING
THEM, TOO.
FROM THE RAIDERS TO THE SAINTS,
PLAYERS SAT IN SILENCE.
IN NASHVILLE, EMPTY BENCHES.
BOTH TEAMS, THE TITANS AND
SEAHAWKS, STAYING THE LOCKER
ROOM WHEN THE ANTHEM PLAYED.
BUT THIS IMAGE OF STEELERS
LINEMAN ALEJANDRO VILLANUEVA
GOING VIRAL, TOO.
THE ARMY VET WHO SERVED THREE
TOURS IN AFGHANISTAN EMERGING
FROM THE TUNNEL TO PLACE HIS
HAND OVER HIS HEART, WHILE HIS
TEAMMATES STAYED BEHIND.
TONIGHT, HIS JERSEY SELLING MORE
THAN ANY OTHER PLAYER IN THE
NFL.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS, THIS IS NOT
ABOUT RACE.
>> THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
RACE OR ANYTHING ELSE.
THIS HAS TO DO WITH RESPECT FOR
OUR COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT, EVEN
SOME OF HIS OWN FRIENDS JOINING
IN THE CHORUS OF CRITICS.
PATRIOTS QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY
AMONG THOSE LINKING ARMS, AND
NOW HE IS SPEAKING OUT.
>> I CERTAINLY DISAGREE WITH,
YOU KNOW, WHAT HE SAID, AND
THOUGHT IT WAS JUST DIVISIVE.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CLOSE FRIEND, PATRIOTS OWNER BOB
KRAFT, SAYS HE IS DEEPLY
DISAPPOINTED WITH THE
PRESIDENT'S TONE.
AND FORMER NFL COACH REX RYAN, A
TRUMP SUPPORTER, SAYS HE'S
FURIOUS.
>> I'M PISSED OFF, I'LL BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE I SUPPORTED
DONALD TRUMP.
BUT I'M READING THESE COMMENTS
AND IT'S APPALLING TO ME.
>> Reporter: IT ALL COMES ON THE
HEELS OF THOSE PROTESTS IN
SHAR VOTS
CHARLOTTESVILLE -- WHITE
SUPREMACISTS MARCHING WITH
TORCHES, THE PRESIDENT SAYING
THERE WERE "VERY FINE PEOPLE" ON
BOTH SIDES.
DOES THE PRESIDENT BELIEVE THAT
THERE ARE VERY FINE PEOPLE
WHO KNEELED YESTERDAY WATCHING
THOSE GAMES, OR ARE THEY ALL
S.O.Bs?
>> I THINK YOU'RE TRYING TO
CONFLATE DIFFERENT THINGS HERE.
LOOK, WE CERTAINLY RESPECT THE
RIGHTS THAT PEOPLE HAVE, BUT I
THINK WE ALSO NEED TO FOCUS.
THIS IS ABOUT THE PRESIDENT
BEING FOR SOMETHING, THIS IS
ABOUT THE PRESIDENT BEING FOR
RESPECT IN OUR COUNTRY, THROUGH
SYMBOLS LIKE THE AMERICAN FLAG.
>> CECILIA VEGA WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
AND CECILIA, THE PRESIDENT
TWEETING ABOUT SPORTS, ABOUT 20
TIMES FROM OUR COUNT, SINCE
SATURDAY.
AND TODAY, THE WHITE HOUSE WAS
ASKED, YOU KNOW, WITH NORTH
KOREA, HEALTH CARE, THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO, WHY DID THE PRESIDENT
CHOOSE TO DO THIS?
>> Reporter: WELL, DAVID, THE
WHITE HOUSE SAYS THE PRESIDENT
IS STANDING UP FOR PATRIOTISM,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, SOURCES HERE
ARE STANDING BEHIND HIM.
THEY SAY THEY BELIEVE MOST
AMERICANS WILL SIDE WITH HIM ON
THIS ONE.
DAVID, THE PRESIDENT IS TWEETING
RIGHT NOW, AGAIN, SAYING THAT
THERE HAS BEEN TREMENDOUS
BACKLASH AGAINST THE NFL.
>> WE'VE SEEN THE DIVISION AMONG
FANS AND SOME PLAYERS, AS WELL,
CECILIA.
YOU TOLD US ABOUT THE STEELERS
PLAYER, THE ARMY VET WHO CAME
OUT TO THE FIELD FOR THE ANTHEM.
THE REST OF HIS TEAM WAS INSIDE.
THE LOCKER ROOM.
TONIGHT, HE SEEMS TO BE
APOLOGIZING TO HIS TEAM FOR JUST
INADVERTENTLY MAKING THEM FEEL
BAD?
>> Reporter: YEAH, DAVID, HE'S
BASICALLY SAYING THIS WAS A
MIXUP.
HE DIDN'T MEAN TO BE ACCEPT
RATED FROM HIS TEAM OUT THERE ON
THE FIELD.
HE IS APOLOGIZING TO THE
PLAYERS, TO THE COACH.
HE SAYS HE ACTUALLY SUPPORTS THE
PROTESTERS WHO ARE EXERCISING
THEIR FIRST AMENDMENT RIGHTS.
WE ARE HEARING FROM THAT TEAM'S
QUARTERBACK, DAVID, HE'S
SPEAKING OUT, SAYING THE ANTHEM
IS NEVER A TIME TO PROTEST.
>> CECILIA VEGA, THANK YOU.
>>> TODAY WAS SUPPOSED TO BE THE
DAY WHEN NBA PLAYERS WERE ASKED
ABOUT THE SEASON AHEAD.
IT'S MEDIA DAY.
INSTEAD, THEY WERE ASKED ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT.
AND AMONG THEM, LeBRON JAMES.
TONIGHT, WHAT HE SAID, AND NOW,
THE FANS IN THESE STADIUMS,
SUDDENLY AT ODDS WITH ONE
ANOTHER, TAKING SIDES.
ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN
TONIGHT IN GLENDALE, WHERE THE
COWBOYS PLAY THE CARDINALS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
BASKETBALL'S ICON LeBRON JAMES
KNEW THE QUESTIONS WOULD NOT BE
ABOUT THE SEASON AHEAD, BUT
ABOUT PRESIDENT TRUMP -- AND HE
WAS READY.
>> THE PEOPLE RUN THIS COUNTRY.
NOT ONE INDIVIDUAL, DAMN SURE
NOT HIM.
>> Reporter: IT WAS LeBRON JAMES
WHO THIS WEEKEND SAID PRESIDENT
TRUMP IS NOW USING SPORTS AS THE
PLATFORM TO TRY TO DIVIDE US.
>> HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND HOW
MANY KIDS, NO MATTER THEIR RACE,
LOOK UP TO THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES ME MORE SICK
THAN ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: AND RESPONDING TO
THE PRESIDENT'S CRITICISM THAT
THOSE WHO KNEEL LACK RESPECT FOR
THEY FLAG.
>> IT IS ABOUT EQUALITY AND
PEOPLE HAVING THE OPTION AND THE
FREEDOM TO SPEAK UPON THINGS
THAT THEY FEEL THAT'S NOT JUST.
>> Reporter: AND IN ADDITION TO
FOOTBALL AND BASKETBALL, THE
PRESIDENT DRAWING IN NASCAR.
>> WE ASK YOU THAT PLEASE RISE
AND REMOVE YOUR HATS.
>> Reporter: AFTER THE PRESIDENT
TWEETED, "SO PROUD OF NASCAR AND
ITS SUPPORTERS AND FANS, THEY
WON'T PUT UP WITH DISRESPECTING
OUR COUNTRY OR FLAG," NASCAR
ROYALTY, DALE EARNHARDT JR., NOT
BUYING IT, TWEETING A QUOTE BY
JOHN K. KENNEDY.
OTHER SPORTS ICONS WEIGHING IN,
LIKE TERRY BROW SHADSHAW.
>> FPEOPLE DIED FOR THAT FREEDO.
I'M NOT SURE IF OUR PRESIDENT
UNDERSTANDS THOSE RIGHTS.
>> Reporter: THE TYPICAL
FRICTION BETWEEN PLAYERS, OWNERS
AND LEAGUE BRASS MELTING AWAY.
OWNERS LINKING ARMS WITH
PLAYERS.
BUT THE PRESIDENT'S WORDS AND
THE PROTESTS THAT FOLLOWED ARE
ALSO IGNITING NEW TENSIONS
BETWEEN FANS.
>> I HATE YOU!
>> BOO!
>> Reporter: NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS FANS BOOING THE TEAM
INCLUDING TOM BRADY, AS MEMBERS
LINKED ARMS.
AFTER MOST OF THE STEELERS
STAYED IN THE LOCKER ROOM DURING
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM, JIM HEENEY
BURNED A MOUND OF STEELERS FAN.
>> I'M A LIFELONG STEELERS FAN.
NOT ANYMORE.
>> Reporter: DURING THE
CAMPAIGN, THE PRESIDENT MADE
THIS PREDICTION.
>> THE THING THAT WILL SURPRISE
PEOPLE, I'LL BE A UNIFYING.
I'M BRING PEOPLE TOGETHER.
THAT INCLUDING BLACKS AND WHITES
AND EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT, AS
FANS HEAD INTO THE STADIUM, NO
MATTER WHAT SIDE THEY ARE,
PEOPLE TELLING US THE
PRESIDENT'S MOST RECENT WORDS
ARE NOT DRAWING OPPOSING SIDES
ANY CLOSER.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S GOING TO
TURN INTO, LIKE, MORE LIKE WHITE
VERSUS BLACK.
>> MATT GUTMAN WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT, OUTSIDE THE
CARDINALS/COWBOYS GAME.
THE NFL COMMISSIONER WATCHING
ALL OF THIS CLOSELY.
AND NOW RESPONDING TO THE
PROTESTS, MATT?
>> Reporter: AND RESPONDING
STRONGLY, DAVID.
WRITING, "THE WAY WE REACTED
THIS WEEKEND MADE ME PROUD.
NOW, ODDLY ENOUGH, IT TOOK A
CONTROVERSY OF THIS MAGNITUDE,
AFTER YEARS OF FRICTION, TO
FINALLY UNITE THE LEAGUE.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> WE ARE ALSO FOLLOWING
BREAKING NEWS RIGHT NOW FROM
CAPITOL HILL IN THE SENATE'S
LATEST EFFORT TO KILL OBAMACARE.
REPUBLICANS COULD ONLY AFFORD TO
LOSE ONE MORE VOTE, AND TONIGHT,
IT APPEARS THEY'VE LOST IT.
ALL OF THIS AS HUNDREDS OF
PROTESTERS WORRIED ABOUT LOSING
THEIR HEALTH INSURANCE PACKED
THE HALLWAYS OF THE CALL TPITOL.
THERE ARE MANY
MARY BRUCE TONIGHT BACK ON THE
HILL.
>> Reporter: WITH PROTESTS
MOUNTING TONIGHT, THE REPUBLICAN
HEALTH CARE BILL APPEARS DOOMED
TO FAIL.
LATE WORD TONIGHT MAINE SENATOR
SUSAN COLLINS SAYS SHE IS A NO,
MAKING HER THE THIRD SENATOR TO
COME OUT AGAINST THE BILL.
THE REPUBLICANS TONIGHT DO NOT
HAVE THE VOTES.
THE DRAMATIC MOVE COMES AFTER
OPPOSITION TO THE REPUBLICAN
HEALTH CARE BILL CAME ROARING
THROUGH THE HALLS OF CAPITOL
HILL.
ANGER AND FRUSTRATION BOILING
OVER.
TODAY'S HEARING HAD JUST BEGUN
WHEN THE CRIES RANG OUT.
>> IF YOU WANT A HEARING, YOU
BETTER SHUT UP.
>> Reporter: AND OUTSIDE, CHAOS.
>> MOVE AGAINST THE WALL!
RIGHT NOW!
MOVE AGAINST THE WALL!
>> Reporter: PROTESTER AFTER
PROTESTER HAULED OFF AND
ARRESTED, MANY IN WHEELCHAIRS.
THIS MAN PHYSICALLY DRAGGED OUT.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN LINING UP HERE
FOR HOURS.
CHECK THIS OUT.
THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING.
IT GOES ON AS FAR AS YOU CAN
SEE.
PAM WILLIS CAME ALL THE WAY FROM
WYOMING.
SHE SAYS THIS BILL IS A MATTER
OF LIFE OR DEATH FOR HER
DAUGHTER.
WHAT'S THE MESSAGE THAT YOU WANT
LAWMAKERS TO HEAR FROM YOU AND
FROM EVERYBODY ELSE IN THIS
LINE?
>> BE HUMAN.
CARE.
CARE ABOUT INSURANCE FOR
EVERYONE.
NOT JUST YOURSELVES.
OR YOUR RELATIVES.
CARE ABOUT EVERYONE.
EVEN FOR THE POOR.
>> Reporter: OPPONENTS OF THE
BILL, LIKE SENATOR JOHN McCAIN,
HAVE CALLED FOR AN OPEN AND
BIPARTISAN PROCESS, BUT THIS IS
THE ONE AND ONLY PUBLIC HEARING
ON THE LATEST PLAN.
THE WITNESS LIST, MOSTLY
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, NOT
AVERAGE AMERICANS.
>> IT'S A FRAUD.
IT'S A FAKE.
IT'S JUST A FACADE.
THEY DON'T WANT US TO TESTIFY.
THEY DON'T WANT US TO BE HERE.
>> Reporter: EARLIER TODAY, EVEN
THE PRESIDENT SEEMED TO
ACKNOWLEDGE DEFEAT.
>> WE HAVE 52 VOTES, SO, WE
CAN'T LOSE ANY VOTES.
I MEAN, PRAKT TICKLY.
SO, WE'RE GOING TO LOSE TWO OR
THREE VOTES AND THAT'S THE END
OF THAT.
>> BOTTOM LINE, MARY BRUCE LIVE
ON THE HILL.
MARY FISHGS OF ALL, DOES THIS
APPEAR TO BE DEAD, THIS EFFORT
TONIGHT?
THEY'VE BEEN TRYING TO DO THIS
FOR SEVEN YEARS, THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY DOES.
THEY WANTED TO DO THIS WITH A
SIMPLE MAJORITY, NOW THAT'S NO
LONGER AN OPTION?
>> Reporter: DAVID, RIGHT NOW,
THIS BILL AIL PEERS TO BE GOING
NOWHE
NOWHERE.
REPUBLICANS WILL LIKELY HAVE NO
CHOICE BUT TO WORK WITH
DEMOCRATS, EVEN AFTER ALL THIS
TIME, REPUBLICANS STILL CAN NOT
AGREE ON A PATH FORWARD.
TONIGHT, THE DIVISIONS BETWEEN
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY SEEM SIMPLY
TOO DEEP FOR THEM TO FULFILL
THEIR PROMISE TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, NOW IT BECOMES A
TEST FOR BOTH PARTIES.
MARY, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO THE GROWING
EMERGENCY UNFOLDING IN PUERTO
RICO.
THE GOVERNOR BEGGING FOR HELP
AFTER HURRICANE MARIA, CALLING
THIS A HUMANITARIAN DISASTER.
3.4 MILLION U.S. CITIZENS LIVE
THERE.
AND LOOK AT THIS SATELLITE IMAGE
OF THE ISLAND, LIT UP IN JULY.
AND NOW THIS IMAGE FROM THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT, JUST IN THE
DAYS AFTER MARIA STRUCK.
MOST OF THE ISLAND IN DARKNESS.
ABC'S EVA PILGRIM TONIGHT TAKING
US FLYING OVER PUERTO RICO IN A
HELICOPTER, AND YOU WILL SEE
WHERE THE EYE OF THE HURRICANE
HIT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, NEW
PICTURES OF THE DEVASTATION IN
PUERTO RICO, AS THE ISLAND'S
GOVERNOR PLEADS FOR MORE FEDERAL
HELP, CALLING HURRICANE MARIA'S
DESTRUCTION A "HUMANITARIAN
DISASTER" FOR ITS 3.4 MILLION
U.S. CITIZENS.
WE ARE MANY DAYS REMOVED FROM
HURRICANE MARIA MAKING LANDFALL,
AND YOU CAN SEE, THERE ARE STILL
SEVERAL NEIGHBORHOODS THAT ARE
FLOODED.
HOME AFTER HOME RIPPED TO
SHREDS.
MUDSLIDES LEAVING HOMES
TEETERING ON THE EDGE.
THE GROUND THEY WERE BUILT ON
GONE.
ON THE GROUND, FEAR OF A
CATASTROPHIC FAILURE AT THE
GUAJATACA DAM.
8,000 RESIDENTS TOLD TO GET OUT
NOW.
>> THE CREW THAT'S BEHIND US,
THEY WALKED ABOUT TWO MILES TO
GAIN ACCESS TO A PERSON WHO WE
KNEW NEEDED HELP.
>> Reporter: A STRUGGLE FOR
BASIC NECESSITIES IN THE
SWELTERISWELTER
ING HEAT.
WE MET JOSE VIDAL STANDING IN
THE SUN, TRYING TO GET A DAY'S
WORTH OF GENERATOR FUEL.
CULT OFF FROM FAMILY.
YOU HAVEN'T TALKED TO YOUR
FAMILY TO LET THEM KNOW YOU'RE
ACT YET?
>> NO, NO.
MY MOM, I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO HER.
>> Reporter: WE LET HIM BORROW
OUR PHONE.
>> HEY, MA.
HOW YOU DOING?
I'M OKAY.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
DOING OKAY.
DOING THE BEST WE CAN.
>> Reporter: A MOMENT OF CONTACT
AMID ALL THIS ISOLATION.
>> SO POWERFUL TO WATCH THOSE
PHONE CALLS.
FAMILIES CONNECTING.
EVA WITH US LIVE TONIGHT.
AND EVA, THERE'S BEEN SOME
PROGRESS INVOLVING COMMERCIAL
FLIGHTS IN AND OUT OF PUERTO
RICO?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
THE FAA SAYS THERE ARE ABOUT A
DOZEN FLIGHTS IN AND OUT OF SAN
JUAN EACH DAY, AND RIDESING.
BUT MARIA DESTROYED SOME
CRITICAL NAVIGATIONAL SYSTEMS.
THEY ARE HAVING TO USE CHAIN
SAWS TO GET TO ONE OF THE MAIN
RADAR SITES TO REPAIR IT.
DAVID?
>> EVA PILGRIM, THE WORK MONTHS
AND YEARS TO COME.
THANK YOU.
>>> AND NOW, A WEEK AFTER
HURRICANE MARIA FIRST HIT THOSE
CARIBBEAN ISLANDS, TROPICAL
STORM WARNINGS ARE UP ALONG
PARTS OF THE EAST COAST OF THE
U.S. TONIGHT.
MANDATORY EVACUATIONS FOR PARTS
OF NORTH CAROLINA AT THIS HOUR.
SO, LET'S GET TO CHIEF
METEOROLOGIST GINGER ZEE, STILL
TALKING ABOUT MARIMARIA.
>> Reporter: ONTO MOVING NORTH
AT 7 MILES PER HOUR.
GOING TO TAKE ITS TIME HERE.
BUT THE RIP CURRENTS AND THE
HIGH SURF COULD BE POSSIBLE FROM
FLORIDA TO MASSACHUSETTS, DAVID.
BUT YOU KIND OF ZOOM IN, YOU CAN
SEE WHO MARIA IS GOING TO EFFECT
THE MOST.
THAT WOULD BE THE OUTER BANKS OF
NORTH CAROLINA, COASTAL NORTH
CAROLINA.
TWO TO FOUR FEET OF STORM SURGE.
GUSTS UP TO 60 MILES AN HOUR,
BEFORE THIS STORM TURNS INTO THE
ATLANTIC THURSDAY AND FRIDAY,
AND QUICKLY, THE OTHER BIG
HEADLINE EVERYONE IS TALKING
ABOUT, THAT INTENSE HEAT.
THAT RIDGE HAS BEEN BUILT IN.
CLEVELAND, DETROIT, CHICAGO HAVE
SEEN FOUR, FIVE OR SIX-DAYS OF
90 PLUS.
THERE'S SOME RELIEF, LOOKS LIKE
GREEN ON THE MAP IS COMING.
>> IN SOME CASES, SCHOOLS
CLOSED.
>> Reporter: ABSOLUTELY.
>> GINGER, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT, TO THAT NEW THREAT
FROM NORTH KOREA TONIGHT.
ITS TOP DIP LOPE MAT SAYING THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S VERBAL ATTACKS
ARE A DECLARATION OF WAR AND HIS
COUNTRY NOW HAS THE RIGHT TO
RESPOND.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF GLOBAL
AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT MARTHA
RADDATZ TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, NORTH
KOREA CALLING THE ESCALATING
PUBLIC THREATS FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP A "DECLARATION OF WAR."
>> ROCKET MAN SHOULD'VE BEEN
HANDLED A LONG TIME AGO.
LITTLE ROCKET MAN.
WE'RE GOING TO DO IT.
BECAUSE WE REALLY HAVE NO
CHOICE.
>> Reporter: AFTER THOSE WORDS,
A TWEET.
THE PRESIDENT THREATENING THE
LEADERS OF NORTH KOREA, SAYING
THAT IF THEY KEEP UP
PROVOCATIONS, THEY "WON'T BE
AROUND MUCH LONGER."
WHILE U.S. BOMBERS PUSHING
FURTHER OFF THE COAST OF NORTH
KOREA, THE FARTHEST NORTH
THEY'VE BEEN IN NEARLY TWO
DECADES.
NORTH KOREA NOW THREATENING TO
SHOOT THOSE BOMBERS DOWN.
AND AT THE WHITE HOUSE TODAY --
>> WE'VE NOT DECLARED WAR ON
NORTH KOREA, AND FRANKLY THE
SUGGESTION OF THAT IS ABSURD.
>> WOW.
A LOT GOING ON AND LET'S GET TO
MARTHA NOW.
SOBERING WORDS FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER TONIGHT, H.R. McMASTER.
>> Reporter: YEAH, DAVID, HE
SAID WHAT WE HOPE TO DO IS TO
AVOID WAR, BUT WE CANNOT
DISCOUNT THAT POSSIBILITY.
AS YOU SAID, SOBERING.
>> MARTHA RADDATZ, GOOD TO HAVE
YOU HERE TONIGHT.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS MONDAY.
THE DEADLY CHURCH SHOOTING.
>>> ALSO, THE PLANE AND THE
SCARE, JUST TODAY.
SMOKE FILLING THE CABIN.
PASSENGERS RUSHING TO ESCAPE
THIS FLIGHT.
>>> WE HAVE NEWS TONIGHT ABOUT
ASPIRIN AND YOUR HEART AND THE
POSSIBLE RISK TO PATIENTS WHO
STOP TAKING THAT DAILY DOSE ON
THEIR OWN.
>>> AND THEN THE DEADLY CRASH.
THE MOTHER AND TWO CHILDREN
COLLIDING WITH A POLICE OFFICER
RESPONDING TO EMERGENCY CALL.
QUESTIONS TONIGHT ABOUT WHETHER
THE OFFICER SHOULD BE CHARGED.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
Whatever you're doing
to stay healthy...
...tmay be missing.g you
A key part of your wellness
that you may be...
...overlooking.
♪
It's your eyes.
That's why there's Ocuvite,
from Bausch + Lomb.
As you age your eyes can lose
vital nutrients.
Ocuvite helps replenish those
nutrients.
Ocuvite has Lutein, Zeaxanthin,
and Omega-3.
Nourish your eyes to help them
be their healthy best.
Ocuvite eye vitamins.
Be good to your eyes.
Patrick woke up
with a sore back.
But he's got work to do.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, THE DEADLY
CHURCH SHOOTING IN TENNESSEE.
THE SUSPECT BEHIND BARS.
AND AUTHORITIES NOW SAY HE HAD
BEEN TO THAT CHURCH BEFORE.
HERE'S STEVE OSUNSAMI.
>> Reporter: TENNESSEE POLICE
TONIGHT ARE HOLDING THE ACCUSED
MURDERER, 25-YEAR-OLD EMANUEL
SAMSON, WITHOUT BOND, AND SAY
MORE CHARGES ARE COMING.
>> THIS IS A LEVEL ONE MASS
CASUALTY INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: THEY WERE JUST
GETTING OUT OF SUNDAY SERVICES
AT THIS NASHVILLE CHURCH WHEN
POLICE SAY THE SUDANESE
IMMIGRANT PULLED INTO THE
PARKING LOT WITH THREE PISTOLS
AND A RIFLE.
WITNESSES SAY WHEN 39-YEAR-OLD
MELANIE CROW WALKED OUT, HE
GUNNED HER DOWN.
>> THERE'S NO UNDERSTANDING
EVIL.
THERE'S NO UNDERSTANDING HATE.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY SAMSON
HAD ATTENDED SERVICES AT THE
CHURCH BEFORE.
SIX OTHER PEOPLE, INCLUDING THE
PASTOR, WERE WOUNDED.
>> WE GOT A POSSIBLE SIX
VICTIMS.
THE SUSPECT IS DOWN.
>> Reporter: THE MORNING OF THE
SHOOTING, IT LOOKS LIKE HE
POSTED THESE PICTURES FROM THE
GYM, IN "BEAST MODE" ON
FACEBOOK.
HE ALSO PUT UP STRANGE MESSAGES,
INCLUDING "BECOME THE CREATOR
INSTEAD OF WHAT'S CREATED."
POLICE HAVE STOPPED SHORT OF
EXPLAINING A MOTIVE, BUT THEIR
REPORTS SAY SAMSON'S FATHER
THOUGHT HE WAS SUICIDAL IN JULY.
SUNDAY'S SHOOTING WAS STOPPED BY
A CHURCH USHER WHO FOUGHT WITH
HIM.
CALEB ENGLE GOT A GUN FROM HIS
OWN CAR AND HELD HIM UNTIL
POLICE ARRIVED.
POLICE SAY THAT 22-YEAR OLD
USHER SAVED LIVES.
AND THEY'RE CALLING HIM A HERO.
DAVID?
>> STEVE, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
THE MAJOR HEADLINE THIS EVENING
ABOUT ASPIRIN AND YOUR HEART.
AND THEN, THE AIR SCARE TODAY.
SMOKE SUDDENLY FILLING THE
CABIN.
PASSENGERS HAVING TO ESCAPE.
WE'LL BE BACK.  Crohn's disease.
...I was always searching for
ways to manage my symptoms.
I thought I had it covered.
Then I realized managing was
all I was doing.
When I finally told my doctor,
he said HUMIRA was for people
like me
who have tried other
medications,...
but still experience the
symptoms
of moderate to severe
Crohn's disease.
In clinical studies,
the majority of patients
on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom
relief...
...and many achieved remission.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections...
...including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,...
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,...
...and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested
for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,...
...hepatitis B, are prone to
infections,
...or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
If you're still just managing
your symptoms,
ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA, remission
is possible.
I take pictures of sunrises,
but with my back pain
I couldn't sleep
and get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
I CAN DO MORE TO LOWER MY A1C.
AND I CAN DO IT WITH
WHAT'S ALREADY WITHIN ME.
BECAUSE MY BODY CAN STILL
MAKE ITS OWN INSULIN.
AND ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
ACTIVATES MY BODY TO RELEASE IT.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT COMES IN A ONCE-WEEKLY,
TRULY EASY-TO-USE PEN.
IT WORKS 24/7, AND YOU DON'T
HAVE TO SEE OR HANDLE A NEEDLE.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU HAVE A PERSONAL
OR FAMILY HISTORY OF
MEDULLARY THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU HAVE MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU'RE ALLERGIC
TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE A LUMP OR
SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
OR SYMPTOMS LIKE ITCHING,
RASH, OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE,
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY WORSEN
KIDNEY PROBLEMS.
I CHOOSE ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
TO ACTIVATE MY WITHIN.
IF YOU NEED HELP LOWERING
YOUR A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR,
ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
It's like nothing
you've seen.
T 24HR protectionum
from frequent heartburn.
All day, and all night.
Now packed into
a pill so small,
We call it mini.
New ClearMinis from Nexium 24HR.
See Heartburn Differently.
>>> TO THE INDEX.
THE DEADLY POLICE CRASH IN NEW
MEXICO.
VID KNOW SHOWS JONATHAN McDONALD
SPEEDING TO AN EMERGENCY CALL IN
APRIL, CLIFDING WITH A MOTHER
AND HER TWO CHILDREN IN THEIR
SUV.
HER 6-YEAR-OLD SON DIED THE NEXT
DAY.
McDONALD DRIVING UP TO 80 MILES
PER HOUR.
THE D.A. DECIDING IF HE WILL
FACE CHARGES.
>>> THE PLANE SCARE MOMENTS
AFTER LANDING IN FRESNO TODAY.
SMOKE FILLING THE CAB BUN.
PASSENGERS TOLD TO COVER THEIR
FACES.
THE AIRLINE NOW SAYS IT WAS A
MECHANICAL ISSUE.
>> TO ASPIRIN AND HEART DISEASE.
A NEW STUDY SHOWING PATIENTS WHO
TAKE A LOW DOSE ASPIRIN DAILY
FOR AT LEAST ONE YEAR WILL
UNCREASE THEIR RISK OF HEART
DISEASE IF THEY STOP ON THEIR
OWN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR FIRST.
THE STUDY APPEARS IN THE JOURNAL
CIRCULATION.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
THE U.S. MARINE THAT JUST MADE
HISTORY.
SHE IS AMERICA STRONG.
♪
Your body was made for better
things than
rheumatoid arthritis.
Before you and your
rheumatologist move to another
treatment, ask if XELJANZ is
right for you.
XELJANZ is a small pill for
adults with
moderate to severe RA for whom
methotrexate did not work well.
XELJANZ can reduce joint pain
and swelling in as little as
two weeks, and help stop further
joint damage.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma and other
cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ if you have
an infection.
Tears in the stomach or
intestines, low blood cell
counts and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you were in
a region where fungal
infections are common and if you
have had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or are prone
to infections.
XELJANZ can reduce the symptoms
of RA,
even without methotrexate, and
is also available
in a once-daily pill.
Ask about XELJANZ XR.
When you have a cold
stuff happens.
Shut down cold
symptoms fast
with Maximum Strength
Alka Seltzer Plus
Liquid Gels.
♪
For my constipation,
my doctor recommended I
switch laxatives.
Stimulant Laxatives
make your body go
by forcefully stimulating the
nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX is different.
It works with the
water in your body
to hydrate and soften.
Unblocking your
system naturally.
MiraLAX.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
AMERICA STRONG.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN ITS
242-YEAR HISTORY, THE MARINE
CORPS WELCOMING ITS FIRST FEMALE
INFANTRY OFFICER.
THIS LIEUTENANT MADE HISTORY
TODAY, BECOMING THE FIRST FEMALE
INFANTRY OFFICER IN THE U.S.
MARINES CORPS, IN ITS NEARLY
250-YEAR HISTORY.
>> NO WE'RE GOING TO PUSH TO THE
FRONT.
GET YOUR GUN READY TO MOVE.
>> Reporter: THE MARINE CORPS
PUTTING OUT THESE IMAGES.
SHE WOULD RATHER US SKIP HER
NAME.
ASKING THAT SHE SIMPLY SERVE
WITH HER FELLOW MARINES.
SHE COMPLETED A GRUELING 13-WEEK
INFANTRY OFFICER COURSE.
ALL OF THE ELITE CLASS TRAINING
TO BE A COMMANDER IN THE FIELD.
IT WAS LESS THAN TWO YEARS AGO,
THE DECISION WAS MADE TO OPEN
ALL COMBAT ROLES TO WOMEN.
AND TONIGHT, SHE'S MADE HISTORY.
THAT LIEUTENANT, THE FIRST
FEMALE TO SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETE
THIS COURSE, AMERICA STRONG.
AND WE SALUTE HER TONIGHT.
THANKS FOR WATCHING HERE ON A
MONDAY NIGHT.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
UNTIL THEN, GOOD NIGHT.
>> THIS IS WCVB NEWSCENTER FIVE
AT 7:00.
ED: BREAKING TONIGHT,
A POTENTIAL DEATH BLOW IN THE
NEW PUSH TO REPEAL THE
AFFORDABLE CARE ACT.
GOOD EVENING.
I'M ED HARDING.
MARIA: AND I'M MARIA STEPHANOS.
MAINE SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS IS A
NO ON THE NEW GRAHAM-CASSIDY
BILL.
BEN SIMMONEAU IS HERE WITH WHY.
BEN?
BEN SENATOR COLLINS LISTED 3
: REASONS SHE CANNOT SUPPORT IT,
IT SUBSTANTIALLY CUTS MEDICAID.
NUMBER ONE, NUMBER IT WEAKENS
TWO, PROTECTIONS FOR PEOPLE WITH
PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS.
AND NUMBER AS THE CONGRESSIONAL
THREE, BUDGET OFFICE CONFIRMED
TONIGHT, MILLIONS MORE PEOPLE
WILL BE UNINSURED UNDER IT.
THAT'S ALSO WHY THOUSANDS
DESCENDED ON THE CAPITOL DURING
A HEARING TODAY.
>> I WANT TO WELCOME EVERYONE,
AND I DO MEAN EVERYONE.
>> BEFORE THE SENATE FINANCE
COMMITTEE HEARING COULD EVEN
BEGIN,
PROTESTORS WERE REMOVED, SOME
FROM THEIR WHEELCHAIRS, AS THEY
CHANTED IN ANGER OVER A NEWLY
REVISED HEALTHCARE BILL.