>>> TONIGHT, SEVERAL BREAKING
STORIES AS WE COME ON THE AIR.
THE MASSACRE IN LAS VEGAS.
NEW IMAGES INSIDE THE KILLER'S
HOTEL ROOM.
THE DOOR BLOWN OFF.
REICHELS ON THE FLOOR.
AND TONIGHT, WE HAVE JUST
LEARNED THE GUNMAN WAS FIRING AT
THE CROWD FOR NINE MINUTES.
AND THIS EVENING, WHAT WE DID
NOT KNOW.
HE HIT A CAMERA IN A SERVICE
CART IN THE HOTEL HALLWAY.
SO HE WOULD KNOW WHEN POLICE
WERE MOVING IN.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, FOR THE FIRST
TIME, WE TAKE YOU INSIDE THE
TRAUMA WARD AT A LAS VEGAS
HOSPITAL.
MORE THAN 100 PATIENTS BROUGHT
TO THIS HOSPITAL ALONE.
TONIGHT, THE SURVIVORS.
ONE OF THEM AT THE CONCERT FOR
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, PRESIDENT
TRUMP IN PUERTO RICO.
AFTER TWEETING ABOUT PUERTO
RICO, THAT THEY WANT EVERYTHING
DONE FOR THEM.
TODAY, THE PRESIDENT TOSSING OUT
SUPPLIES.
AT ONE POINT, COMPARING TO WHAT
HE SAW TO A, QUOTE, REAL
CATASTROPHE LIKE KARINA.
>>> AND IN NEW YORK CITY, THE
NEW IMAGES TONIGHT, THE PRESSURE
COOKER BOMB LEFT ON THE STREET
TO EXPLODE.
>>> AND REMEMBERING AN AMERICAN
ORIGINAL TONIGHT.
TOM PETTY.
>>> AND GOOD EVENING FROM LAS
VEGAS TONIGHT.
WHERE AUTHORITIES CAME BEFORE
THE CAMERAS JUST A SHORT TIME
AGO AND REVEALED SEVERAL
STUNNING FINDINGS TONIGHT.
WE NOW NOW THE GUNMAN WAS FIRING
FOR NINE MINUTES AFTER THAT
FIRST 911 CALL CAME IN.
AND WHAT HE HAD HIDDEN IN THE
HALLWAY OF THE 32nd FLOOR OF
THAT HOTEL RIGHT BEHIND ME.
WE ARE SEEING INSIDE THE HOTEL.
THE DOOR THAT S.W.A.T. TEAMS
BROKE DOWN.
IT TURNS OUT HE HAD A CAMERA
ATTACHED TO A CART IN THE
HALLWAY SO HE WOULD KNOW WHEN
POLICE WERE MOVING IN.
ONE OF THE 23 WEAPONS HE HAD
WITH HIM IN THAT ROOM, THE
EVIDENCE MARKER STILL IN PLACE.
AND TONIGHT, VIDEO OF THAT VERY
ROOM TAKEN BY A TOURIST WHO
STAYED IN THAT ROOM JUST A YEAR
AGO.
AND THE VIEW FROM THE WINDOW,
RIGHT DOWN ONTO THE CONCERT
SITE.
THE GUNMAN CHECKED INTO THAT
HOTEL WITH TEN SUITCASES.
THOSE SUITCASES WERE FULL OF
WEAPONS.
ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN ON THE
SUSPECT'S FINAL 48 HOURS.
♪
>> Reporter: THIS WAS THE CROWD
AT THE HARVEST FESTIVAL.
22,000 PEOPLE JOINING TOGETHER
FOR GOD BLESS AMERICA.
BUT HIGH ABOVE THE LAS VEGAS
STRIP, ANOTHER SPECTATOR WAS
WATCHING THEM.
A MASS MURDERER.
AND JUST ONE HOUR LATER --
[ GUNFIRE ]
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, WE ARE
LEARNING MORE ABOUT HOW
64-YEAR-OLD STEPHEN PADDOCK
PLANNED HIS ATTACK.
AUTHORITIES SAY HE CHECKED INTO
THE GLITTERING MANDALAY BAY
RESORT LAST THURSDAY.
ON SEPTEMBER 28th, HE CHECKED
IN, CARRYING MULTIPLE BAGS AND
LIKELY PASSING A SIGN JUST LIKE
THIS.
BUT PADDOCK DOESN'T JUST BRING
IN A FIREARM.
HE BROUGHT AN ARSENAL.
TEN SUITCASES, 23 GUNS.
TODAY, OUR FIRST GLIMPSE INSIDE
THAT HOTEL ROOM.
AN AR-15 SEEN THROUGH THE
BATTERED DOORWAY OF THE
SHOOTER'S LUXURY SUITE.
THAT GUN OUTFITTED WITH A SCOPE
TYPICALLY USED FOR HUNTING AND A
BIPOD TO STABILIZE THE WEAPON.
PARTS OF WHAT EYEWITNESSES
CALLED THAT KILL BOX WERE A FULL
FIVE FOOTBALL FIELDS AWAY FROM
THAT SHOOTER'S PERCH UP THERE ON
THE 32nd FLOOR.
A RANGE THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
IMPOSSIBLE HAD HE JUST BEEN
USING HANDGUNS INSTEAD OF THOSE
LONG GUNS.
HE SHUTTERED HIMSELF IN HIS
SUITE, TAKING IN ROOM SERVICE,
SAY POLICE, AS THE COUNTRY MUSIC
FESTIVAL KICKED OFF ON FRIDAY,
WAITING.
SUNDAY, THAT JOY TURNING TO
PANIC.
WHEN AT 10:08 P.M., HIGH ABOVE
THE CROWDS, POLICE SAY PADDOCK
HAMMERED THROUGH TWO OF THE
HOTEL'S THICK WINDOWS AND
STARTED FIRING DOWN ON THE CROWD
BELOW.
ON THE GROUND, PEOPLE RUNNING,
HUDDLING TOGETHER, SHOTS FIRED
FOR NEARLY NINE MINUTES.
THEN, OFFICERS SPOT THE SHOOTER.
>> I SEE THE SHOTS COMING FROM
MANDALAY BAY, HALFWAY UP.
>> Reporter: BUT AS S.W.A.T.
TEAMS APPROACHED THE 32nd FLOOR,
TONIGHT, WE ARE LEARNING THE
SHOOTER MAY HAVE HAD EYES ON
THEM.
POLICE SAY HE'D SET UP AT LEAST
TWO CAMERAS.
ONE MONITORING THE HALLWAY, SEEN
RIGHT THERE ON THAT SERVICE
CART, POSSIBLY TO MONITOR LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
THE OTHER INSIDE HIS ROOM.
AND WHEN OFFICERS FINALLY BROKE
DOWN THE DOOR --
>> BREACH, BREACH, BREACH.
>> Reporter: -- PADDOCK WAS
ALREADY DEAD.
>> JUST SOME CHILLING NEW
DETAILS TONIGHT.
MATT GUTMAN WITH US LIVE IN LAS
VEGAS.
AND MATT, WE KNOW THE GUNMAN
STAYED IN THAT ROOM UNDETECTED
FOR DAYS.
EVEN ORDERING ROOM SERVICE
SEVERAL TIMES?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
ROOM SERVICE.
MULTIPLE HOTEL EMPLOYEES HAD
BEEN IN THAT ROOM BEFORE THE
SHOOTING, WHICH BEGS THE MAJOR
QUESTION, GIVEN HOW ELABORATE
THE SETUP HAD BEEN WITH THE TEN
CASES OF LUGGAGE, THE 23
FIREARMS, THOUSANDS OF ROUNDS OF
AMMUNITION AND OF COURSE, THOSE
CAMERAS, HOW NOBODY NOTICED
ANYTHING SUSPICIOUS.
DAVID?
>> YEAH, SOMEHOW IT WENT
UNNOTICED.
MATT GUTMAN LEADING US OFF.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> AND THERE WAS ANOTHER MAJOR
DEVELOPMENT LATE TODAY.
THE GUNMAN'S LONG-TIME
GIRLFRIEND, RIGHT NOW, OUT OF
THE COUNTRY, IS NOW BEING CALLED
A PERSON OF INTEREST TONIGHT.
ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES TONIGHT
LABELED THE SHOOTER'S
GIRLFRIEND, MARILOU DANLEY, AS
CENTRAL TO THE ONGOING
INVESTIGATION, MUCH MORE THAN
SIMPLY A WITNESS.
>> CURRENTLY, SHE'S A PERSON OF
INTEREST.
>> Reporter: ESPECIALLY AFTER
THE DISCOVERY BY POLICE OF SO
MANY WEAPONS, SO MUCH AMMUNITION
AND EXPLOSIVES AT THE HOME THEY
SHARED IN MESQUITE, NEVADA.
>> HOW COULD SHE NOT KNOW WHAT
WAS GOING ON IN HER OWN HOUSE
WITH THESE WEAPONS?
SHE HAD TO KNOW SOMETHING, AT
THE VERY LEAST, QUESTION HIM AS
TO WHERE ARE THESE WEAPONS
COMING FROM, WHY DO YOU HAVE ALL
THESE WEAPONS?
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO
DOCUMENTS OBTAINED BY ABC NEWS,
DANLEY, WHO USES AN AUSTRALIAN
PASSPORT, TRAVELED TO HER HOME
COUNTRY, THE PHILIPPINES, TWO
WEEKS BEFORE THE SHOOTING, ON
SEPTEMBER 15th.
PADDOCK VISITED HER FAMILY IN
THE PHILIPPINES FOUR YEARS AGO.
NOW, U.S. OFFICIALS WANT TO KNOW
WHY PADDOCK BEGAN TO TRANSFER
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS TO
SOMEONE IN THE PHILIPPINES JUST
PRIOR TO THE SHOOTING.
>> I ANTICIPATE SUBSTANTIAL
AMOUNT OF INFORMATION TO COME IN
IN THE NEXT 48 HOURS.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO
RELATIVES, DANLEY APPARENTLY MET
PADDOCK AT THIS HOTEL CASINO IN
RENO, WHERE SHE WORKED AS A
HOSTESS TO ENTERTAIN HIGH
ROLLERS, LIKE PADDOCK.
EMPLOYEES AT THIS BAR IN
MESQUITE, AND FORMER NEIGHBORS,
SAY THE COUPLE WERE REGULARS
HERE, DRINKING BEER, TEQUILA AND
PLAYING VIDEO POKER AND THE
SLOTS.
>> SO, HE JUST ONE TIME PULLED
HIS PHONE OUT AND SAID, HERE'S A
PICTURE OF THE SLOT MACHINE
WHERE WE WON $20,000.
>> BRIAN ROSS JOINS US LIVE
TONIGHT.
AND BRIAN, WE HEARD YOUR REPORT
THERE THAT AUTHORITIES ARE NOW
CALLING THE SHOOTER'S GIRLFRIEND
A PERSON OF INTEREST.
THEY'RE MAKING PLANS FOR HER TO
RETURN TO THE U.S.?
>> Reporter: YES, DAVID.
THE FBI IS ACTUALLY INVOLVED TO
MAKE SURE SHE GETS ON PLANE TO
COME BACK TO THE U.S.
DAVID?
>> BRIAN ROSS AGAIN TONIGHT.
>>> FOR THE FIRST TIME, WE WERE
GIVEN ACCESS TODAY TO ONE OF THE
TRAUMA WARDS AT A HOSPITAL RIGHT
HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
ONE OF THE SURGEONS TAKING US
FROM ROOM TO ROOM, AND WE MET
THE SURVIVORS.
ONE OF THEM, A 19-YEAR-OLD GIRL
BROUGHT ON THE BACK OF A PICKUP
TRUCK.
THE E.R. SUDDENLY OVERFLOWING.
DOCTORS DIDN'T KNOW WHO THEY
WERE OPERATING ON, IT WAS
HAPPENING SO FAST.
THEY SIMPLY MOVED IN AND SAVED
LIVES.
WE HELD INTO DESERT SPRINGS
HOSPITAL MEDICAL CENTER HERE IN
LAS VEGAS.
WHERE MORE THAN 100 VICTIMS WERE
RUSHED IN.
HAVE YOU CAUGHT YOUR BREATH AT
ALL?
PETER CARAVELLA IS A SURGEON
HERE WHO GOT THE EMERGENCY CALL
AT 11:00 SUNDAY NIGHT.
>> WE GOT HERE THERE WAS
PROBABLY 50, 60 PEOPLE IN THE
E.R.
>> Reporter: THERE WERE
50, 60 PEOPLE HERE ALREADY?
>> ALREADY, BEFORE WE GOT HERE.
>> Reporter: IT SOUNDS AS THOUGH
THERE WERE SO MANY PATIENTS, YOU
DIDN'T EVEN HAVE TIME, YOU
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHO THESE
PATIENTS WERE?
>> I HAD NO IDEA.
THE E.R. DOCS REALLY DID A GREAT
JOB.
THEY BASICALLY TRIAGED EVERYBODY
AND SAID THIS ONE'S CRITICAL,
THIS ONE'S CRITICAL, THIS ONE
NEEDS THIS, THIS ONE NEEDS THAT
AND WE BASICALLY WENT BED TO BED
TO BED.
>> Reporter: FOUR OF THE VICTIMS
WERE PRONOUNCED DEAD SHORTLY
AFTER THEY ARRIVED HERE.
SO MANY OF THE PATIENTS WITH
MULTIPLE GUNSHOT WOUNDS.
AND THIS SURGEON TELLS ME, THIS
TIME, IT WAS DIFFERENT.
>> WE SAW DIFFERENT PIECES OF
MACHINERY AND ARTILLERY THAT
WERE BECAUSE SICKLY DISPERSED
THROUGHOUT THE ABDOMEN, CHEST.
>> Reporter: IT APPEARED THIS
SUSPECT WANTED TO INFLECT
MAXIMUM DAMAGE HERE?
>> CLEARLY, CLEARLY.
>> Reporter: THE SURGEON TAKES
US INTO SHELDON MACK'S ROOM, ONE
OF THE PATIENTS HE HELPED SAVE.
SHELDON WAS AT THE CONCERT FOR
HIS 21st BIRTHDAY.
SHELDON.
>> IT ALL KIND OF HAPPENED SO
FAST.
IT SEEMS SURREAL.
LIKE A BAD NIGHTMARE I'M GONNA
WAKE UP FROM.
BUT I JUST KEEP SEEING IT IN MY
MIND STILL AND IT JUST HAUNTS
ME.
>> Reporter: YOU SEE IT ALL
PLAYING OUT STILL.
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: HE SHOWED ME THE
VIDEO HE TOOK OF THE CONCERT
JUST MOMENTS BEFORE THE GUNFIRE
BEGAN.
AND YOU WERE SEEING PEOPLE
AROUND YOU GET HIT FIRST?
>> YEAH, I SAW A GIRL, LIKE TWO
ROWS AHEAD OF ME, AND SHE GOT
HIT IN THE NECK AND WENT DOWN.
>> Reporter: SHELDON BEGAN
TRYING TO HELP THE PEOPLE AROUND
HIM.
THEN HE GOT SHOT, TWICE.
IN THE ARM AND IN THE ABDOMEN.
>> AND THEN SOME HERO CAME AND
SAVE ME.
WHICH --
>> Reporter: DO YOU KNOW HIS
NAME?
>> I WISH I DID.
>> Reporter: AND HE CAME ALL THE
WAY TO THE HOSPITAL WITH YOU.
>> YEAH, HE WOULDN'T LEAVE MY
SIDE.
SAVED MY LIFE.
>> Reporter: HE TELLS US SHE
STILL WANTS TO MEET THAT HERO,
AND HIS MOM AND DAD WOULD LIKE
TO MEET HIM, TOO.
THEY KNOW THEIR SON HAS SO MANY
QUESTIONS, AMONG THERJS WHY?
>> HE WAS SAYING, YOU KNOW, WHY
WOULD SOMEONE DO THIS?
SUCH EVIL?
YOU KNOW, I -- I HAVE A LIFE
AHEAD OF ME, WHY DOES SOMEONE
WANT TO KILL ME AND LEAVE ME
LYING ON THIS FIELD AND
EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> Reporter: THERE WAS MA KEN
THAT PERRY, TOO.
IT WAS HER BOYFRIEND AND GOOD
SAMARITANS THAT SAVED HER.
WERE YOU IN THE BACK OF A TRUCK?
>> YEAH, HE HAD A TWO-SEATER
TRUCK.
I WAS LAYING IN THE BED WITH HIS
GIRLFRIEND AND MY BOYFRIEND.
>> Reporter: IN THE BACK?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: AND IT WAS OPEN.
>> Referee: WHATEVER IT TAKES.
I'M GLAD IT GOT YOU HERE.
SHE CAN'T GET THAT NIGHT OUT OF
HER HEAD.
>> I DON'T KNOW, IT HASN'T FULLY
HIT ME.
IT'S KIND OF STARTING TO, BUT --
NOT FULLY.
>> Reporter: IT'S HARD TO EVEN
THINK ABOUT.
>> I JUST KNOW THAT THERE WERE A
LOT OF PEOPLE WHO HAD IT A LOT
WORSE.
SO, IT'S KIND OF JUST, LIKE,
HARD TO KNOW THAT THERE'S A LOT
OF PEOPLE DEAD FROM IT, TOO.
>> Reporter: AND HER MOTHER WAS
AT THE CONCERT, TOO.
YOUR DAUGHTER WAS SAYING THAT
THE HARD PART WAS KNOWING SO
MANY PEOPLE DIDN'T GET OUT.
>> I THINK THAT'S THE HARD PART
FOR ALL OF US.
AND SEEING WHAT WE SAW.
AND I THINK, AS A MOM, KNOWING
THAT THEY HAD TO SEE THAT, AND
THAT'S STUCK WITH THEM FOREVER.
>> THE SURGEON TOLD US THAT BOTH
OF THOSE PATIENTS ARE GOING TO
BE OKAY.
AND THEY'RE GRATEFUL TO THOSE
DOCTORS AND NURSES.
AND AS FOR SHELDON, HE WANTS TO
MEET THAT HERO WAS BY HIS SIDE.
THEY BELIEVE THAT THE HERO WAS
GRAZED BY A BULLET, TOO, BUT IS
NO LONGER AT THE HOSPITAL.
SO, IF THAT HERO IS WATCHING
TONIGHT, SHELDON'S FAMILY WANTS
TO THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP, IN PUERTO RICO TODAY,
MEETING WITH OFFICIALS INCLUDING
THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN.
SHE WENT ON LIVE TVP, BECKING
THE ADMINISTRATION FOR HELP, AND
HE THEN TOOK HIM A AT HER ON
TWITTER.
HE ALSO TWEETED OF PUERTO RICO,
"THEY WANT EVERYTHING DONE FOR
THEM."
WHAT HIS MESSAGE WAS TODAY WHEN
HE LANDED THERE.
ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL FROM
PUERTO RICO.
>> Reporter: THERE HAS NEVER
BEEN A PRESIDENTIAL VISIT TO A
DISASTER ZONE QUOTE LIKE THIS.
AT A CHURCH IN SAN JUAN,
PRESIDENT TRUMP TOSSED PAPER
TOWELS TO HURRICANE VICTIMS AS
IF HE WERE PLAYING BASKETBALL.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF LOVE IN THIS
ROOM.
>> Reporter: SITTING RIGHT NEXT
TO PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR, HE
TOUTED THE DEATH COUNT AS IF HE
WERE KEEPING SCORE.
>> IF YOU LOOK AT A REAL KA AS
THE TROE TEE LIKE KA TREE
ANYWAY, AND YOU LOOK AT THE
TREMENDOUS HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS
AND HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE THAT
DIED, WHAT IS YOUR DEATH COUNT
AS OF THIS MOMENT, 17?
>> 16.
>> 16 PEOPLE, CERTIFIED.
16 PEOPLE VERSUS IN THE
THOUSANDS.
YOU CAN BE VERY PROUD.
>> Reporter: AND EVEN AS HE
TALKED UP THE FEDERAL RECOVERY
EFFORT --
>> THE WHOLE TEAM HAS BEEN
AMAZING.
>> Reporter: -- THE PRESIDENT
COULDN'T HELP BUT BRING UP THE
HIGH COST.
>> I HATE TO TELL YOU,
PUERTO RICO, BUT YOU'VE THROWN
OUR BUDGET A LITTLE OUT OF
WHACK.
>> Reporter: ALSO IN THE ROOM,
THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN, WHO THE
PRESIDENT HAS SLAMMED
RELENTLESSLY ON TWITTER FOR
SAYING PUERTO RICO NEEDS MORE
THAN IT'S GETTING.
>> SIR.
>> NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> IT'S ALL ABOUT SAVING LIVES,
IT'S NOT ABOUT POLITICS.
>> Reporter: AFTERWARDS, THE
MAYOR CALLED THE MEETING
PRODUCTIVE.
BUT ON CNN, SHE DISMISSED THE
PRESIDENTIAL VISIT AS PUBLIC
RELATIONS.
>> RATHER THAN COMMANDER IN
CHIEF, HE SORT OF BECOMES
MISCOMMUNICATOR IN CHIEF.
>> Reporter: NOT FAR FROM THERE,
WE MET UP WITH HECTOR GARCIA HE
HAD NO IDEA THE PRESIDENT WAS ON
THE ISLAND, BUT HE TELLS US,
HE'S HAPPY HE'S HERE.
"HE CAME HERE," GARCIA TOLD US,
"BECAUSE HE KNOWS WE'RE IN
CRISIS."
DAVID, THE GOVERNOR'S BEEN
DIPLOMATIC TONIGHT.
HE SAYS HE APPRECIATES THE
PRESIDENT'S VISIT AND HIS
COMMITMENT TO THE ISLAND OF
PUERTO RICO.
HE WANTS TO SEE RELIEF EFFORTS
CONTINUE, INCLUDING THINGS LIKE
THE U.S. NAVAL HOSPITAL SHIP
BEHIND ME.
THIS JUST GOT HERE TODAY, TWO
WEEKS AFTER THE STORM HIT THE
ISLAND.
DAVID?
>> JON KARL, OUR THANKS TO YOU
TONIGHT.
>>> AND WE WANT TO LET EVERYONE
KNOW AT HOME WE WERE IN PUERTO
RICO OVER THE WEEKEND WHEN THE
SHOOTING BROKE OUT HERE IN LAS
VEGAS, AND BEFORE WE LEFT TO
COME HERE, WE HAD GONE TO A
NEIGHBORHOOD, JUST A SHORT DRIVE
FROM WHERE THE PRESIDENT WAS
TODAY.
NEARLY TWO WEEKS AFTER THE HER
KHAN, WE DISCOVERED FAMILIES IN
SWELTERING HERE, NO POWER, NO
RUNNING WATER, AND A CALL FOR
HELP.
WE WENT LOOKING FOR AN APARTMENT
BUILDING, JUST 15 MINUTES FROM
THE AIRPORT IN SAN JUAN.
BECAUSE WE HAD HEARD THAT NEARLY
TWO WEEKS AFTER THE HURRICANE
HIT, THEY WERE STILL WITHOUT
POWER AND WOULD RUNNING WATER.
WE WALK UP THE DARKENED
STAIRWELL AND DOWN THE HALLWAY.
L
LIZBETH VAZQUEZ DELGADO LIVES IN
NEW YORK CITY.
BUT SHE IS HERE TAKING CARE OF
HER PARENTS.
THE PRESIDENT HAD TWEETED DAYS
AGO, ALL BUILDINGS NOW
INSPECTED.
AND WE WONDER, HAVE THEY SEEN
ANY EMERGENCY OFFICIALS OR THE
GOVERNMENT.
WE HAD HEARD THAT INSPECTORS HAD
BEEN VISITING BUILDINGS ALL OVER
PUERTO RICO.
HAVE YOU SEEN ANY INSPECTORS?
>> NO.
NOT AT ALL.
THEY HAVE NOT COME TO SEE WHAT'S
HAPPENED TO THESE APARTMENTS.
>> Reporter: NO ONE HAS COME?
>> NO ONE HAS COME.
>> Reporter: AND HOW MUCH FOOD
AND WATER HAVE THEY BROUGHT?
>> NONE.
>> Reporter: NOTHING?
>> NONE AT ALL.
>> Reporter: AND WITH NO POWER,
NO CLEAN DRINKING WATER.
CAN YOU DRINK THE WATER?
>> NO, WE CANNOT.
AT ALL.
>> Reporter: INSIDE HER PARENTS'
TINY APARTMENT, THEIR WINDOWS
STILL BLOWN OUT BY HURRICANE
MARIA.
AND IN THE BEDROOM, HER PARENTS,
ELMER AND GLORIA, ON THE BED IN
NEED OF MEDICATION.
THIS WAS THE FIRST DAY ANY
DOCTOR HAD PAID A VISIT.
THIS IS THE FIRST MEDICINE?
>> THIS IS THE FIRST MEDICINE.
>> Reporter: AND IT'S MOTRIN.
>> I HAD A PIECE OF BREAD, HALF
OF BREAD AND I SHARED IT WITH,
LIKE, FOUR APARTMENTS.
>> Reporter: DOWN THE HALLWAY,
WE SEE OTHER RESIDENTS, SOME
CARRYING FLASHLIGHTS.
AND WE HEAD INTO ONE OF THOSE
APARTMENTS, WHERE WE MEET A
WOMAN LIZBETH HAS BEEN SHARING
HER BREAD AND WATER WITH.
MARIA DIAZ IS 70, WHO HAS BEEN
DRINKING THE WATER FROM THE
FAUCET, EVEN THOUGH SHE KNOWS
IT'S NOT SAFE.
SHE HOLDS AN EMPTY BOTTLE OF
WATER.
TELLING US IT COSTS $6.
WITH LITTLE FOOD AND NO CLEAN
WATER, SHE IS PANIC-STRICKEN,
TELLING ME, I DON'T WANT TO DIE
HERE.
IN SO MANY OF THESE APARTMENT
BUILDINGS, THEY ARE UNAWARE OF
THE FEMA HELP, BECAUSE THEY HAVE
NO POWER, NO ACCESS TO THE NEWS.
AND TONIGHT, JUST 7% OF THE
ISLAND HAS POWER BACK.
THIS BUILDING DOES NOT.
A GENERATOR IS TURNED ON A
COUPLE OF HOURS A NIGHT.
AND WE WALK P THE STAIRS,
KNOWING THERE ARE 13 STORIES IN
THIS BUILDING.
AGAIN, THEY TELL US, NO FOOD.
DOWN THE HALL, YOU CAN SEE THE
DESTRUCTION THROUGH THE WINDOW.
WE STEP OVER A DOORWAY BLOWN
IN BY THE HURRICANE.
FLOOR AFTER FLOOR, WE HEAR THE
SAME CONCERNS.
WHILE BACK DOWN ON THE FOURTH
FLOOR, LIZBETH, SHARING WHAT
LITTLE BREAD SHE HAS AND A SLICE
OF CHEESE WITH HER NEIGHBOR.
>> I'M SHARING IT WITH EVERYONE.
AND I'M NOT ONLY ASKING FOR MY
PARENTS.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE HERE
THAT DON'T HAVE FAMILY.
>> WE CHECKED BACK IN WITH THEM
THIS AFTERNOON, THEY ARE STILL
ASKING FOR HELP TONIGHT.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON THIS SPECIAL EDITION OF
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT" THIS
TUESDAY.
THE PRESSURE BOMB EXPLOSION IN
NEW YORK CITY.
NEW SURVEILLANCE TONIGHT, NEVER
BEFORE SEEN VIDEO, WHEN ONE OF
THOSE BOMBS WAS SET OFF.
>>> ALSO, THE NEW HEALTH
HEADLINE TONIGHT ABOUT YOUR
WEIGHT AND CANCER.
>>> AND WE CELEBRATE TOM PETTY.
SOME OF HIS MOST FAMOUS SONGS.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
Your body was made for better
things than
rheumatoid arthritis.
Before you and your
rheumatologist move to another
treatment, ask if XELJANZ is
right for you.
XELJANZ is a small pill for
adults with
moderate to severe RA for whom
methotrexate did not work well.
XELJANZ can reduce joint pain
and swelling in as little as
two weeks, and help stop further
joint damage.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma and other
cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ if you have
an infection.
Tears in the stomach or
intestines, low blood cell
counts and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you were in
a region where fungal
infections are common and if you
have had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or are prone
to infections.
XELJANZ can reduce the symptoms
of RA,
even without methotrexate, and
is also available
in a once-daily pill.
Ask about XELJANZ XR.
My checkups go well,
but I want awesome!
So my dentist told
me about this...
Go Pro with Crest HD.
Crest HD cleans and whitens my
teeth to eye-popping levels.
Crest HD. 6x cleaning,
6x whitening.
I did it, I did it, I
impressed the dentist.
You owned your car
for four years.
You named it Brad.
You loved Brad.
And then you totaled him.
You two had been through
everything together.
Two boyfriends, three jobs...
you're like
nothing can replace Brad.
Then Liberty Mutual calls...
and you break into
your happy dance.
If you sign up for
Better Car Replacement™,
we'll pay for a car that's
a model year newer
with 15,000 fewer miles
than your old one.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE,
CELEBRATING AN AMERICAN
ORIGINAL.
TOM PETTY HAS DIED.
HERE'S MY "20/20" CO-ANCHOR,
ELIZABETH VARGAS.
>> Reporter: TOM PETTY'S RAW
STYLE SERVED AS THE SOUNDTRACK
FOR GENERATIONS.
♪ AND I WON'T BACK DOWN ♪
>> Reporter: HE QUIT SCHOOL,
ESCAPED AN ABUSIVE FATHER,
STARTED A BAND.
IN HIS DISTINCTIVE, RASPY VOICE
HE SANG SONGS ABOUT REBELS AND
REFUGEES.
♪ NO YOU DON'T HAVE
TO LIVE LIKE A REFUGEE ♪
>> Reporter: HE SOLD MORE THAN
80 MILLION RECORDS AND WORKED
WITH MUSICAL ROYALTY.
HE BROKE THROUGH WITH THE
HEARTBREAKERS IN 1976.
♪ SHE WAS AN AMERICAN GIRL ♪
>> Reporter: THE BAND WAS STILL
TOURING STADIUMS JUST LAST WEEK.
PETTY'S LIFE CHANGING MOMENT
CAME WHEN HE WAS JUST 11, AND A
YOUNG TOMMY MET ELVIS.
♪ SHE'S A GOOD GIRL
CRAZY 'BOUT ELVIS ♪
>> Reporter: ECHOED IN ONE OF
HIS CLASSICS.
>> I THIANKS THE FANS FOR SUCH
WONDERFUL LIFE.
♪ YEAH I'M FREE ♪
>> Reporter: FANS AND MUSICIANS
AROUND THE WORLD ARE MOURNING
PETTY'S LOSS AND CELEBRATING
PETTY'S MUSIC.
BOB DYLAN SAYING HE WAS FULL OF
LIGHT AND I'LL NEVER FORGET HIM.
DAVID?
>> ELIZABETH, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, THE NEW HEALTH ALERT
ABOUT THE LINK BETWEEN WEIGHT
AND CANCER.
>>> AND THE NEW SURVEILLANCE
IMAGES TONIGHT.
THE PRESSURE COOKER BOMB
EXPLOSION IN NEW YORK CITY.
WHAT WE HAVE NOT SEEN BEFORE.
Wt
from our eyes every day.
I should know.
I have Chronic Dry Eye
caused by reduced
tear production
due to inflammation.
So I use RESTASIS MultiDose®.
It helps me make more
of my own tears,
with continued use,
twice a day, every day.
It's also what I prescribe
to my patients
who have this condition.
RESTASIS MultiDose®
helps increase your
eyes' natural ability
to produce tears,
which may be reduced
by inflammation
due to Chronic Dry Eye.
RESTASIS MultiDose® did
not increase tear production
in patients using
anti-inflammatory eye drops
or tear duct plugs.
To help avoid eye injury
and contamination,
do not touch the bottle tip
to your eye or other surfaces.
Wait 15 minutes after use
before inserting
contact lenses.
The most common side effect
is a temporary
burning sensation.
Ask your eye doctor about
RESTASIS MultiDose®.
Savings Card
holders pay as
little as $0
for three bottles.
Start saving today
at restasis.com.
Approaching Medicare
eligibility?
Don't put off checking out youry
options until sixty-five.
Now is a good time to get the
ball rolling.
Consider an AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like any of these types
of plans,
it could help you with
out-of-pocket
medical costs.
Call now and request your free
Decision Guide
and explore the range of AARP
Medicare Supplement Plans.
Start gathering the information
you need...
to roll into sixty-five with
confidence.
With Advil, you'll ask
What twisted ankle?
What muscle strain?
Advil makes pain a distant
memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
With my moderate to severe
Crohn's disease,...
.ways to manage my symptoms.r
I thought I had it covered.
Then I realized managing was
all I was doing.
When I finally told my doctor,
he said HUMIRA was for people
like me
who have tried other
medications,...
but still experience the
symptoms
of moderate to severe
Crohn's disease.
In clinical studies,
the majority of patients
on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom
relief...
...and many achieved remission.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections...
...including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,...
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,...
...and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested
for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,...
...hepatitis B, are prone to
infections,
...or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
If you're still just managing
your symptoms,
ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA, remission
is possible.
>>> TO THE INDEX OF OTHER NEWS
TONIGHT.
YOU THIS BOMBING VIDEO IN NEW
YORK CITY.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS REVEALING
SURVEILLANCE IMAGES, ALLEGEDLY
SHOWING THE DEFENDANT WHEELING
TWO SUITCASES.
NEVER BEFORE SEEN VIDEO SHOWING
ONE BOMB EXPLODING ON THE
SIDEWALK LAST YEAR.
30 PEOPLE WERE HURT.
THE OTHER BOMB DID NOT GO OFF.
>>> THE U.S. EXPEOPLING 15 CUBAN
DIPLOMATS.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT ORDERING
THEM OUT OF THE COUNTRY,
CLAIMING CUBA HAS NOT PROTECTED
AMERICAN EMBASSY PERSONNEL FROM
MYSTERY ATTACKS IN HAVANA.
THERE ARE NOW 22 CONFIRMED
CASES.
>>> AND THE NEW HEALTH HEADLINE
TONIGHT ABOUT OBESITY AND
CANCER.
THE CDC REVEALING EVIDENCE
LINKING EXCESSIVE WEIGHT GAIN
WITH 13 DEADLY TYPES OF CANCER
INCLUDING BREAST CANCER.
THE REPORT FINDS BEING
OVERWEIGHT PUTS YOU AT A MUCH
HIGHER RISK.
RESEARCHERS SAY OBESITY IS TIED
TO ABOUT 40% OF ALL CANCER
CASES.
MUCH MORE ON OUR WEBSITE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, MORE OF THE FACES OF
THOSE WE LOST HERE, FROM THE
NAVY VETERAN, TO THE WIFE WHO
DIED IN HER HUSBAND'S ARMS.
WE REMEMBER.
Hi, I'm Mindy Kearns. It's great
to finally meet you.
ce to meet you too.
Your parents have been
talking about you for years.
Sorry about that.
They're all about me
saving for a house,
or starting a
college fund for my son.
Actually, I want to
know what you're thinking.
Have a seat.
Knowing that the most
important goals are yours.
Multiplied by 14,000 financial
advisors, it's a big deal.
And it's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
When you have a cold...
stuff happens.
Shut down cold symptoms fast
with Maximum
Strength Alka Seltzer
Plus Liquid Gels.
Only have a sore throat?
Get long-lasting
relief for up to 6 hours
with New Alka Seltzer
Plus Sore Throat Relief.
[radio alarm]
♪ ♪
Julie is living with metastatic
breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women with hormone receptor-
positive HER2- metastatic breast
cancer as the first
hormonal based therapy.
♪ ♪
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
And IBRANCE plus letrozole
shrunk tumors in over half of
these patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE can
develop low white blood cell
counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if you have
fever, chills,
or other signs of infection
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts...
...infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver
blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Julie calls it her "new" normal.
Because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one-prescribed,
FDA-approved oral combination
treatment for HR+/HER2- MBC.
>>> AND FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
FOR ALL OF THE HEROIC EFFORTS OF
FRIENDS, STRANGERS AND THE
MEDICAL TEAMS HERE IN LAS VEGAS,
WE CANNOT FORGET THE 59 LIVES
LOST.
WE LEARNED LATE TODAY, ALL BUT
THREE HAVE NOW BEEN IDENTIFIED,
AND THESE ARE SOME OF THEIR
FACES.
THE LOVED ONES WHO DIDN'T MAKE
IT HOME.
AMONG THEM, NEYSA TONKS.
DENISE BURR DIE TIS, MARRIED 32
YEARS.
SHE DIED IN HER HIS'S ARMS.
AND CHRISTOPHER ROYBAL, A NAVY
VETERAN.
ALL OF THEIR LIVES CUT SHORT AT
THAT CONCERT HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
WE WILL STAY ON THIS STORY, AND
WE THANK YOU FOR WATCHING HERE
ON A TUESDAY NIGHT.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I'LL SEAL YOU EING IN THE MORNI
"GMA" AND RIGHT HERE FOR "WORLD
NEWS TONIGHT" TOMORROW NIGHT.
UNTIL THEN, HAVE A GOOD EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> FROM BOSTON'S NEWS LEADER,
THIS IS WCVB NEWSCENTER 5 AT
7:00.
>> MY FIRST THOUGHT WAKING UP
THIS MORNING WAS, I WILL NEVER
SEE MY BABY GIRL AGAIN.
ED: THAT IS A MOTHER PREPARING
TO SAY GOOD-BYE TO HER DAUGHTER.
A TEWKSBURY WOMAN KILLED IN THE
LAS VEGAS MASSACRE.
RHONDA LAROCQUE'S MOTHER TELLING
NEWSCENTER 5, RHONDA WAS SIMPLY
PERFECT.
GOOD EVENING EVERYONE.
I'M ED HARDING.
NICHOLE: AND I'M NICHOLE BERLIE
IN FOR MARIA STEPHANOS.
NEWSCENTER 5'S SHAUN CHAIYABHAT
BEGINS OUR COVERAGE LIVE IN
TEWKSBURY TONIGHT.
SHAUN: THE FAMILY IS SIMPLY
DEVASTATED, BUT THEY'RE TALKING,
TO TELL THE WORLD WHO SHE WAS.
>> I'LL NEVER SEE MY BABY GIRL
AGAIN.
I LOVED HER SO MUCH.
SHAUN: IT WAS NEWS NO MOTHER
EXPECTS.
BUT PRISCILLA CHAMPAGNE HAD A
FEELING BEFORE THE DEVASTATING