>>> TONIGHT BREAKING
DEVELOPMENTS AS WE COME ON THE
AIR.
THE URGENT WARNING IN PUERTO
RI
RICO.
THEIR BRACING FOR A MAJOR DAM TO
COLLAPSE TELLING TENS OF
THOUSANDS TO SEEK HIGHER GROUND
AND THE NEW STORM MODELS SHOWING
THE TRACK OF HURRICANE MARIA
ONCE AGAIN CLOSER TO THE EAST
KOES
COAST OF THE US.
WE HAVE THE TIMING AND THE
POSSIBLE PATH.
>>> ALSO A MAJOR BLOW TO THE
EFFORT TO KILL OBAMACARE.
JOHN MCCAIN AND HIS DECISION
LATE TODAY.
JIMMY KIMMEL TWEETING HIM AND
TONIGHT THE TWO KEY SENATORS WHO
COULD MAKE OR BREAK THIS BILL.
WHERE THEY STAND RIGHT NOW.
>>> THE STUNNING MOMENT NOW DAYS
AFTER THE EARTHQUAKE.
THIS PERSON PULLED FROM THE
RUBBLE ALIVE.
>>> NORTH KOREA TONIGHT AND
THEIR NEW WARNING RESPONDING TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
NOW PROMISING AN H-BOMB IN THE
PACIFIC.
>>> AND BREAKING NOW, THE
HOSTAGE SITUATI UNFOLDING AT
THIS HOUR INSIDE A BANK.
SEVERAL REPORTEDLY TRAPPED
INSIDE.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US
ON A FRIDAY NIGHT.
WE BEGIN WITH THE URGENT
HEADLINE FROM PUERTO RICO AT
THIS HOUR.
A DAM AT IMMINENT RISK OF
FAILURE, A LIFE FLAET
THREATENING SITUATION.
A MASS EVACUATION UNDER WAY.
SOME 70,000 PEOPLE ACROSS THE
ISLAND.
CATASTROPHIC FLOODING AND
MUDLIEDS ALREADY.
THE COVER SAYING IT'S TIME TO
GET PEOPLE OUT.
WE BEGIN WITH ABC'S ROB MARCIANO
ON THE SCENE TO GET TENS OF
THOUSANDS TO HIGHER GROUND.
>> Reporter: A LARGE DAM IS
BEGINNING TO FAIL.
TWO TOWNS AND TENS OF THOUSANDS
OF PEOPLE IN DANGER DOWNSTREAM.
A FLASH FLOOD EMERGENCY IN
EFFECT RIGHT NOW.
OFFICIALS URGING PEOPLE TO GET
TO HIGH GROUND.
THIS IS A LIFE-THREATENING
SITUATION HAPPENING NOW.
TONIGHT THE NEW EMERGENCY IN
THIS UNFOLDING DISASTER.
THE BATTERING OF HURRICANE MARIA
AND HER 40 INCHES OF RAIN
CAUSING THIS MAJOR DAM'S
FAILURE.
FLASH FLOODING FERSING 70,000
PEOPLE TO EVACUATE IMMEDIATELY.
OFFICIALS SAYING A CRACK IS
FORMING IN THE GUAJATACA DAM.
PEOPLE'S LIVES ARE IN DANGER.
UTTER DEVASTATION BEING FELT
THROUGHOUT THE U.S. TERRITORY.
THE CHAOS AND DESPERATION ETCHED
INTO CAREGIVER MARIA ORTEZ'S
VOICE.
>> WE CAN'T LET THEM DIE.
WE CAN'T LET THEM DIE.
WE NEED ALL THE HELP WE CAN GET.
PLEASE.
>> Reporter: WE FIRST MET HER
THURSDAY AS SHE STRUGGLED TO
KEEP 11 NURSING HOME PATIENTS
ALIVE.
THEIR GENERATOR LOW ON FUEL.
I SEE WHEN THAT RUNS OUT --
>> WHAT WE GOING TO DO?
>> Reporter: THOSE PATIENTS IN
SWELTERING CONDITIONS INSIDE.
SOME CLINGING TO LIFE.
WHEN WE RETURNED TODAY HELP HAD
NOT ARRIVED.
THE GENERATOR OUT OF FUEL.
IT'S BEEN 20 HOURS SINCE WE
CALLED THE GOVERNOR'S OFFICE ON
HER BEHALF.
CALLING AGAIN TODAY.
WE HAD TROUBLE GETTING THROUGH
AND WE'RE NOT ALONE.
COMMUNICATIONS NEARLY IMPOSSIBLE
ACROSS THE ISLAND.
DRIVERS LINED UP HERE AS FAR AS
THE EYE CAN SEE TO ACCESS ONE OF
THE ONLY WORKING CELL PHONE
TOWERS.
MARIA HASN'T SEEN OR HEARD FROM
HER MOTHER SINCE BEFORE THE
HURRICANE HIT.
SOME RELIEF KNOWING HER PARENTS
ARE OKAY.
THEN THE SON OF ONE OF HER
PATIENT'S SHOWS UP WITH A DIESEL
THAT THE CARE CENTER DESPERATELY
NEEDS.
HOW LONG DOES A TANK LAST?
>> EIGHT HOURS.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER TEMPORARY
PHYSICIAN.
FIX.
ELATION WITH KNOWING THERE'S
ENOUGH FUEL TO AT LEAST GET
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
>> ROB MARCIANO IS BACK WITH US.
WE'RE GLAD TO SEE THE NURSING
HOME AT LEAST GOT SOME FUEL.
THE OTHER MAJOR CONCERN YOU
REPORTED ON THE DAM, TENS OF
THOUSANDS TOLD TO GET TO HIGHER
GROUND IMMEDIATELY?
>> Reporter: YEAH.
THE GOVERNOR CUT HIS PRESS
CONFERENCE SHORT TO HEAD OUT
THERE.
THE MILITARY VEHICLES TRYING TO
GET PEOPLE OUT RIGHT NOW.
IT'S GOING TO BE A DANGEROUS
NIGHT AHEAD DAVID.
>> THE MEANTIME THE POSSIBLE
PATHS FOR HURRICANE MARIA AS IT
MOVES TOWARDS THE EAST COAST.
THEY SEEM TO SHIFT NIGHT TO
NIGHT ROB.
>> Reporter: WE DIDN'T GIVE THE
U.S. THE ALL CLEAR AND NOW
THEY'RE SHIFTING CLOSER TO HOME.
RIGHT NOW IT'S A CAT 3 AND WILL
WEAKEN FATHER NORTH BY
WEDNESDAY.
NORTH CAROLINA, THE FORECAST
GETTING CLOSE TO THE U.S. AND
OUR SPAGHETTI MODELS SPREAD OUT.
THERE COULD BE SOME DIRECT
IMPACTS FROM MARIA IN THE U.S.
BY THE END OF NEXT WEEK.
DAVID.
>> ROB MARCIANO ON THE GROUND IN
PUERTO RICO AGAIN TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
TO MEXICO CITY AT THIS HOUR.
DAYS AFTER THAT EARTHQUAKE AND
THE CHEERS ERUPTING AT A FACTORY
THAT CAME DOWN DURING THE
EARTHQUA
EARTHQUAKE.
MATT GUTMAN WITH THE MOMENT THAT
ANOTHER PERSON WAS FOUND ALIVE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT AMIDST THE
FLATTENED BUILDINGS THERE ARE
SPIKES OF HOPE.
CHEERS ERUPTING AT THIS
FLATTENED FACTORY WHERE ANOTHER
PERSON WAS FOUND ALIVE.
THOSE RESCUES DANGEROUS AS WE
SAW FIRSTHAND.
DEBRIS CRASHING DOWN AROUND US.
>> WATCH IT WATCH IT!
>> MOMENTS LATER OFFICIALS
CLEARING THE SCENE FEARING
ANOTHER COLLAPSE.
WE JOINED THE SEARCH AND RESCUE
TEAM AT THIS PANCAKED OFFICE
BUILDING GEARING UP FOR A GRIM
SEARCH.
FIRE RESCUE TEAMS SAY THAT THOSE
SIX STORIES COLLAPSES SO DENSELY
THAT THERE'S NO VOID SPACE AND
CONCERN IS NOBODY COULD HAVE
SURVIVED.
AND UNDER THESE TARPS THE
FAMILIES OF THE DOZEN OR SO
MISSING PRAYED.
IT WAS AFTER THOSE PRAYERS THAT
WE MET FABIOLA.
HER BROTHER IS IN THAT BUILDING.
SHE SHOWED US AROUND THE
IMPROVISED TENT WHERE FAMILIES
HAD BEEN LIVING FOR THE PAST
FOUR DAYS.
THEY'RE ALL THERE.
COUSINS, SIBLING, FRIENDS.
AND THEN THAT CALL FOR SILENCE.
>> SHH.
>> Reporter: NOW THEY CALL FOR
SILENCE BECAUSE THAT'S WHEN THEY
TRY TO LISTEN TO SOMETHING IN
THE RUBBLE.
THESE ARE THE MOMENTS OF HOPE.
SHE TOLD US THEY NEED TO SHOW
STRENGTH.
BUT AFTER FOUR DAYS EVEN IRON
WILL CAN SNAP.
CH
SHE SAYS HER BROTHER IS VERY
STRONG.
♪
>> Reporter: EVERYWHERE
SOLIDARITY FOR MEXICO.
♪
>> Reporter: ON THE RUBBLE OF
THIS BUILDING A SALUTE TO THE
MEXICAN NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> AND MATT FROM MEXICO CITY.
THE SCENE OF THAT APARTMENT
BUILDING AND MATT YOU'RE HEARING
THEY'RE BRINGING IN A CRANE TO
LIFT UP SECTIONS OF THE
BUILDING?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT DAVID.
THE CRANE IS GOING TO LIFT
LAYERS OF THAT BUILDING WHERE
YOU SEE THAT SWARM OF RESCUERS.
WHICH IS A SIGN THAT THIS COULD
TURN FROM A RESCUE OPERATION TO
A RECOVERY OPERATION.
FOR DAYS WE HAVE BEEN ASKING
MEXICAN OFFICIALS FOR THE LIST
OF THE MISSING BUT IN THE SCOPE
OF THIS DEVASTATION THEY SAY
THEY STILL DON'T HAVE ONE.
DAVID.
>> MATT GUTMAN ON THE SCENE.
THE MAJOR HEADLINE, A MAJOR BLOW
IN THE NEW EFFORT TO KILL
OBAMACARE AND IT COMES FROM THE
SAME SENATOR WHO KILLED THE
REPEAL THE LAST TIME.
SENATOR JOHN MCCAIN DECLARING HE
WILL VOTE KNOW.
THE TWO KEY SENATORS WHO WILL
BREAK OR MAKE THIS REPEAL.
WHERE DO THEY STAND TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN JUST
EIGHT WEEKS SINCE THE COUNTRY
WATCHED JOHN MCCAIN WALK ONTO
THE SENATE FLOOR, SHOCKING HIS
OWN PARTY, WITH THIS DEFIANT
THUMBS DOWN.
>> Reporter: HIS VOTE
DELIVERING THE FINAL BLOW TO THE
PRESIDENT'S ATTEMPT TO REPEAL
AND REPLACE OBAMACARE.
TONIGHT, WITH ONE MORE CHANCE AT
A REPEAL BEFORE NEXT WEEK'S
DEADLINE, JOHN MCCAIN STUNNING
THE PARTY AGAIN.
ANNOUNCING TODAY, "I CANNOT IN
GOOD CONSCIENCE VOTE FOR" THE
LATEST REPUBLICAN PLAN.
HE SAYS A "BILL OF THIS IMPACT
REQUIRES A BIPARTISAN APPROACH."
MCCAIN MIGHT HAVE JUST KILLED
THIS NEW REPEAL, BECAUSE THEY
CAN ONLY AFFORD TO LOSE TWO
VOTES.
RAND PAUL HAS ALREADY SAID NO.
AND MCCAIN DID THIS, EVEN THOUGH
HIS OWN BEST FRIEND IN THE
SENATE, LINDSEY GRAHAM IS ONE OF
THE ARCHITECTS.
>> I DON'T EXPECT HIM TO VOTE
BECAUSE WE'RE FRIENDS, I EXPECT
HIM TO VOTE FOR WHAT'S BEST FOR
THE COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: THE BILL WOULD GIVE
STATES MORE FLEXIBILITY TO CRAFT
THEIR OWN HEALTH COVERAGE, BUT
WITH FAR LESS FEDERAL FUNDING.
AND WITH NO GUARANTEE OF HOW
THEY WOULD COVER AMERICANS WITH
PRE EXISTING CONDITIONS.
EXPERTS SAY IT COULD LEAVE
MILLIONS MORE WITHOUT INSURANCE.
ALL EYES NOW ON TWO KEY
SENATORS.
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS OF MAINE,
AND LISA MURKOWSKI OF ALASKA.
COLLINS TONIGHT IS LEANING NO.
>> I JUST HAVE TO DO WHAT'S
RIGHT OF THE PEOPLE OF MAINE AND
OUR COUNTRY, AND IF I DON'T DO
THAT I CAN'T LOOK AT MYSELF IN
THE MIRROR.
>> Reporter: AND SENATOR LISA
MURKOWSKIS OFFICE PROTESTERS
CAMPED OUT URGING HER TO PROTEST
THIS BILL LIKE SHE DID THE LAST
TIME.
>> I SAID IN JANUARY WE SHOULD
NOT REPEAL WITHOUT A
REPLACEMENT.
JUST AN INDEFINITE HOLD ON THIS
JUST CREATES MORE CHAOS AND
CONFUSION.
>>> MARY BRUCE BACK WITH US FROM
WASHINGTON.
AND JIMMY KIMMEL WHOSE OWN BABY
NEEDS SEVERAL OPERATIONS, AND
FOUGHT FOR OTHER FAMILIES TO
HAVE COVERAGE IF THEY'RE IN THE
SAME SITUATION.
HE TWEETED SENATOR MCCAIN.
>> Reporter: YEAH.
KIMMEL WITH A TWEET OF PRAISE
SAYING THANK YOU JOHN MCCAIN FOR
BEING A HERO AGAIN AND AGAIN AND
NOW AGAIN.
AND JOHN MCCAIN'S WIFE RESPONDED
TWEETING THANK YOU FOR THE KIND
WORDS ABOUT MY HUNDREDS AND GOD
BLESS YOUR SWEET BABY.
DAVID.
>> AS WE HEAD INTO THE WEEKEND,
MARY THANK YOU AGAIN.
MEANTIME NEXT TO THE NEW THREAT
FROM NORTH KOREA.
KIM JONG-UN SAYING PRESIDENT
TRUMP WILL QUOTE, PAY DEARLY FOR
HIS SPEECH.
AND NORTH KOREA WITH THE
HYDROGEN BOMB TEST IN THE
PACIFIC.
HERE'S MARTHA RADDATZ TONIGHT.
>> TONIGHT A DRAMATIC ESCALATION
OF TENSIONS.
NORTH KOREA NOW THREATENING TO
TEST A HYDROGEN BOMB ABOVE THE
PACIFIC OCEAN.
THEIR RESPONSE TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
>> THE UNITED STATES HAS GREAT
STRENGTH AND PATIENCE, BUT IF IT
IS FORCED TO DEFEND ITSELF OR
ITS ALLIES, WE WILL HAVE NO
CHOICE BUT TO TOTALLY DESTROY
NORTH KOREA.
>> Reporter: FOR MONTHS, THE
PRESIDENT'S HEATED LANGUAGE HAS
SO FAR FAILED TO STOP KIM.
3 MISSILE TESTS AND AN
UNDERGROUND H-BOMB TEST SINCE
TRUMP WARNED OF FIRE AND FURY.
BUT DETONATING A NUCLEAR BOMB
OVER THE PACIFIC WOULD BE KIM'S
MOST PROVOCATIVE MOVE YET.
>> A HYDROGEN BOMB, A THERMO
NUCLEAR WEAPON IS GOING TO HAVE
A LOT OF RADIATION.
IF IT HITS THE WATER, THERE IS
GOING TO BE CONTAMINATION FOR
HUNDREDS OF MILES AROUND.
>> Reporter: ON GMA, DAVID
CONTINUED TO PRESS SECRETARY OF
STATE REX TILLERSON ABOUT THE US
RESPONSE.
>> BUT IF WE SEE THIS DETONATION
OF AN H-BOMB IN THE PACIFIC,
WHAT WILL THE U.S. DO?
>> WELL, WE WILL CONTINUE OUR
EFFORTS IN THE DIPLOMATIC ARENA
BUT ALL OUR MILITARY OPTIONS, AS
THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID, ARE ON
THE TABLE.
>> Reporter: THE TWO LEADERS
THEMSELVES, TRADING A VOLLEY OF
INSULTS.
KIM FOR THE FIRST TIME
RESPONDING DIRECTLY TO TRUMP,
CALLING HIM "MENTALLY DERANGED."
THE PRESIDENT BRANDING THE NORTH
KOREAN DICTATOR "A MADMAN" WHO
"WILL BE TESTED LIKE NEVER
BEFORE."
>>> MARTHA YOU AND I HAVE BOTH
BEEN TALKING TO COLONEL STEVE
GANYARD AND NOW THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT TESTING A HYDROGEN BAUM IN
THE PACIFIC.
DO THEY HAVE THE CAPABILITY TO
PULL THAT OFF?
>> Reporter: THEY HAVE ALREADY
TESTED A HYDROGEN BOMB AND AN
INTERCONTINENTAL BALLISTIC
MISSILE.
WE DON'T KNOW FOR SURE BUT THIS
HAS TO BE TAKEN SERIOUSLY.
THIS WOULD BE AN EXTRAORDINARILY
ALARMING AND DANGERS MOVE AND
THE ADMINISTRATION WOULD HAVE TO
RETHINK WHAT IT IS DOING.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU MARTHA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP RESPONDING
TONIGHT AFTER FACEBOOK REVEALED
THOUSANDS OF ADS WERE BOUGHT BY
RUSSIAN AGENTS DURING THE
ELECTION, ADS THAT PRAISED
DONALD TRUMP OR ATTACKED HILLARY
CLINTON.
MARK ZUCKERBERG SAYING HE WILL
TURN THOSE ADS OVER TO CONGRESS.
TODAY PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETING
THE RUSSIA HOAX CONTINUES, NOW
ITS ADS ON FACEBOOK.
>>> NEXT TO YOUR MONEY.
TAXPAYER MONEY SPENT ON FLIGHTS
ON PRIVATE JETS.
ANOTHER CABINET SECRETARY UNDER
SCRUTINY FOR HIS TRAVEL HABITS.
HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES CHIEF
TAKING PRIVATE JETS DOZENS OF
TIMES FROM D.C. TO PHILADELPHIA.
CECELIA VEGA WITH THE PRICE TAG.
HOW MUCH YOU HAVE SPENT ALREADY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT HEALTH
SECRETARY TOM
PRICE UNDER INVESTIGATION FOR
DOZENS OF TRIPS ON LUXURY
PRIVATE PLANES.
>> THE AMERICAN PEOPLE NEED TO
KNOW THAT THEIR TAX DOLLARS ARE
BEING SPENT WISELY.
>> Reporter: AS A CONGRESSMAN,
PRICE ONCE TWEETED "CONGRESS
DOESN'T NEED TO HAVE PRIVATE
JETS."
BUT NOW ACCORDING TO POLITICO,
HIS PENCHANT FOR
PRIVATE PLANES HAS COST
TAXPAYERS MORE THAN THREE
HUNDRED THOUSAND DOLLARS.
LAST WEEK ALONE, ON A LUXURY JET
LIKE THIS, HE TOOK FIVE FLIGHTS.
ONE OF THEM, A SHORT 30 MINUTE
ROUND TRIP TO PHILADELPHIA.
THE COST, $10,000.
COMPARED TO ABOUT $700 FOR A
COMMERCIAL FLIGHT.
>> IT'S JUST NOT RIGHT, IT'S
JUST NOT RIGHT.
>> Reporter: TODAY IN A SCATHING
LETTER, THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE
HOUSE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE TELLS
PRICE, "THE AMOUNT OF TAXPAYER
FUNDS YOU SPENT ON JUST ONE
SINGLE FLIGHT IS MORE THAN SOME
OF MY CONSTITUENTS MAKE IN A
YEAR."
>> I JUST SAY TO THE SECRETARY,
MR. SECRETARY YOU CAN DO BETTER
AND YOU NEED TO SET THE EXAMPLE
FOR THE ENTIRE ADMINISTRATION.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST THREE
TRUMP CABINET
SECRETARIES NOW UNDER
INVESTIGATION FOR EXPENSIVE
TRAVEL ON THE PUBLIC DIME.
TONIGHT, ABC NEWS HAS LEARNED
THAT AFTER ONE MEETING WITH THE
PRESIDENT AT TRUMP TOWER,
TREASURY SECRETARY STEVE MNUCHIN
FLEW BACK TO WASHINGTON ON AN
AIR FORCE JET, COSTING TAXPAYERS
AT LEAST $25,000.
A GOVERNMENT JET TRIP TO
KENTUCKY, WHERE MNUCHIN AND HIS
WIFE VIEWED THE ECLIPSE IS ALSO
UNDER REVIEW.
ON TOP OF MNUCHIN'S REQUEST TO
HAVE A GOVERNMENT PLANE FLY HIM
AND HIS WIFE TO THEIR HONEYMOON
OVERSEAS, A REQUEST HE
ULTIMATELY WITHDREW.
>>> CECELIA VEGA, SECRETARY
PRICE, SECRETARY MNUCHIN BOTH
UNDER SCRUTINY.
>> Reporter: PRICE'S OFFICE SAYS
HE USES THE PRIVATE PLANES IN
ORDER TO ACCOMMODATE HIS
DEMANDING SCHEDULE.
THEY SAY HE HAS TAKEN COMMERCIAL
FLIGHTS BUT YOU HEARD THE
DEMOCRATS.
THEY ARE CALLING THIS A
MILLIONAIRE MIND-SET TOO COMMON
IN THIS ADMINISTRATION.
>>> CECELIA VEGA THANK YOU.
STILL MUCH MORE AHEAD THIS
FRIDAY.
THE MAJOR AMERICAN COMPANY
ANNOUNCING A HIRING BOOM.
>>> THE HOSTAGE SITUATION
UNFOLDING INSIDE A BANK.
SEVERAL PEOPLE TRACHED AND
S.W.A.T. TEAMS ON THE SCENE.
A NEW SINKHOLE.
A DANGEROUS SCENE.
>>> AMID SO MUCH DEVASTATION
THIS WEEK YOU NEED TO HEAR THE
STORY OF FRITA.
THE LIFE SAVING LABRADOR.
MUCH MORE NEWS AHEAD.
us.
I write them a poem instead!
And one for each of you too!
That one's actually yours.
That one.
Regardless, we're stuck
with the bill.
To many, words are
the most valuable currency.
Last I checked,
stores don't take "words."
Some do.
Not everyone can be the poetic
voice of a generation.
I know, right?
Such a burden.
The Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
The fast, secure and simple way
to send money.
Don't let dust and allergens
get between you
and life's beautiful moments.
Flonase outperforms the #1
non-drowsy allergy pill.
It helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause symptoms.
Pills block one
and 6 is greater than 1.
Flonase changes
everything.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
My friends think doing this
at my age is scary.
protect yourself.
What is scary?
Pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's a serious disease.
My doctor said the risk is
greater now that I'm over 50!
Yeah...ya-ha...
Just one dose of the PREVNAR 13®
vaccine can help protect you
from pneumococcal pneumonia-
an illness that can cause
coughing, chest pain,
difficulty breathing,
and may even put you
in the hospital.
PREVNAR 13® is approved for
adults 18 and older to help
prevent infections from
13 strains of the bacteria that
cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
You should not receive
PREVNAR 13® if you have had
a severe allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
If you have a weakened
immune system,
you may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects
were pain, redness,
and swelling at
the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Get this one done!
Ask about PREVNAR 13®
at your next visit to your
doctor's office or pharmacy.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, YOUR MONEY AND
GROCERY STORE AND BIG BOX STORES
COMPETING FOR IT.
AND THIS QUESTION, WOULD YOU LET
WALMART IN WHEN YOU'RE NOT HOME
IF THEY DELIVERED GROCERIES
RIGHT TO YOUR REFRIGERATOR?
REBECCA JARV
REBECCA JARVIS TRACKING YOUR
MONEY.
>> Reporter: WHAT IF YOU DIDN'T
FEEL LIKE YOU HAD TO BE AT TWO
PLACES AT ONCE.
WALMART TAKING THE CONVENIENCE
OF HOME DELIVERY A FEW STEPS
FARTHER TESTING A NEW SERVICE.
>> THE DRIVER ENTERS A ONE-TIME
USE CODE.
>> Reporter: THE COMPANY
PARTNERING WITH LOCKMAKER AUGUST
HOME PLACED AN ORDER ONLINE AND
WALMART'S DELIVERY PERSON CAN
GAIN ENTRY TO YOUR HOME, EVEN
STOCK YOUR FRIDGE, ALL WHILE
YOU'RE WATCHING IN REALTIME ON
YOUR SMARTPHONE.
>> I THINK FOR YOUNGER FOLKS
WORKING AND PUTTING IN ALL KINDS
OF HOURS AND HAVING A LARGE
COMMUTE IT'S A TREMENDOUS IDEA.
>> Reporter: BUT RAISING
QUESTIONS, TOO.
>> NOT SO SURE ABOUT THEM COMING
IN MY HOME WHEN I'M NOT THERE.
>> Reporter: BOTTOM LINE, DAVID,
THIS IS ONE MORE STEP IN THE
MAJOR COMPETITION BETWEEN
WALMART AND AMAZON.
BOTH RETAILERS DUELING TO
INCREASE CONVENIENCE AND OF
COURSE, PROFITS, TOO.
DAVID.
>> THANK YOU.
WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT, THE
COMPANY HIRING 95,000 PEOPLE AND
OF COURSE THAT WILD MOMENT TODAY
ON THE PRICE IS RIGHT AND AHEAD
THE DEVELOPING HEADLINE I
MENTIONED, SEVERAL PEOPLE
REPORTEDLY HELD HOSTAGE INSIDE A
BANK AND WE'LL HAVE REPORTING
AFTER THE BREAK.
Don't let dust and allergens
get between you
and life's beautiful moments.
Flonase outperforms the #1
non-drowsy allergy pill.
It helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause symptoms.
Pills block one
and 6 is greater than 1.
Flonase changes
everything.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
When a critical patient is far
from the hospital,
the hospital must come to the
patient.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
The AT&T network is helping
first responders
connect with medical teams in
near real time...
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
...Saving time when it matters
most.
Stay with me, Mrs. Parker.
That's the power of and.
For my constipation,
my doctor recommended I
switch laxatives.
Stimulant Laxatives
make your body go
by forcefully stimulating the
nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX is different.
It works with the
water in your body
to hydrate and soften.
Unblocking your
system naturally.
MiraLAX.
(Traffic sounds)
Con artists...
They'll try anything to get your
Medicare card number.
So they can steal your identity,
commit Medicare Fraud.
What can you do?
Guard your Card?
Just like your credit card.
Nobody gets my number, unless I
know they should have it.
To protect your identity,
new Medicare cards without
Social Security numbers
will be mailed next year.
Visit Medicare.gov/Fraud
Stay sharp people!
I accept I don't bike
as far as I used to.
I even accept I have a
higher risk of stroke
due to AFib,
a type of
irregular heartbeat
not caused by a
heart valve problem.
But no matter
where I ride,
I go for my best.
So if there's something
better than warfarin,
I'll go for that too.
ELIQUIS.
the risk of stroke
better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor
tells you to,
as stopping increases your
risk of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
...and it may take
longer than usual
for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate
medical care
for sudden signs
of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about
all planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor
about ELIQUIS.
♪
>>> TO THE INDEX AND A HOSTAGE
SITUATION IN TENNESSEE.
POLICE RESPONDING TO A BANK IN
THE CITY OF COLUMBIA WHERE A MAN
ARMED WITH A MACHETE IS HOLDING
SEVERAL PEOPLE INSIDE AFTER A
FAILED BANK ROBBERY ATTEMPT.
FOUR HOSTAGES RELEASED.
S.W.A.T. TEAMS ON THE SCENE.
>>> A SECOND SINKHOLE AFTER
HURRICANE MARIA.
MEASURING 30 FEET ACROSS IN THE
HARD HIT CITY.
IT'S ON THE SAME ROAD WHERE A
SINKHOLE EARLIER THIS WEEK
CAUSED A PARTIAL HOME COLLAPSE.
>>> UPS A HIRING EXPECTING TO
HIRE 95,000 SEASONAL EMPLOYEES
STARTING IN NOT
VEMBER.
35% WERE HIRED FULL TIME.
>>> THE PRICE WAS VERY RIGHT FOR
THREE
GAME SHOW CONTESTANTS
NAILING $1 AND TWO OF THOSE
HITTING $1 AGAIN IN THE SPINOFF.
EACH EARNING A BONUS AND
$80,000.
I WATCHED AS A KID AND NEVER SAW
THAT HAPPEN.
WHEN WE COME BACK, THE STORY OF
A DOG NAMED FRITA.
WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE TO
THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE,
DOES PSORIASIS EVER GET IN
THE WAY OF A TOUCHING MOMENT?
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE
TO SEVERE PSORIASIS,
YOU CAN EMBRACE
THE CHANCE
OF COMPLETELY CLEAR
SKIN WITH TALTZ.
TALTZ IS PROVEN TO GIVE YOU A
CHANCE AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
WITH TALTZ, UP TO
90% OF PATIENTS
HAD A SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT
OF THEIR PSORIASIS PLAQUES.
IN FACT, 4 OUT OF 10 EVEN
ACHIEVED COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DO NOT USE IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING YOU
SHOULD BE CHECKED
FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE YOUR
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU ARE BEING TREATED
FOR AN INFECTION
OR HAVE SYMPTOMS.
OR IF YOU HAVE RECEIVED
A VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ.
INCLUDING WORSENING
OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
JUST ASK YOUR
DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
♪
♪You are loved♪
parodontax,
the toothpaste that helps
prevent bleeding gums.
If you spit blood
when you brush or floss
you may have gum problems
and could be on the journey
to much worse.
Help stop the journey
of gum disease.
Try parodontax
toothpaste.
♪
This is the story of John Smith.
Not this John Smith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
.
>>> AND FINALLY TONIGHT, AMID SO
MUCH DEVASTATION THIS WEEK THE
STORY OF FRITA, THE DOG LEADING
TEAMS THROUGH THE RUBBLE.
CHEF HAS SAVED LIVES BEFORE AND
MANY OF THEM.
THIS WEEK IN MEXICO THOSE
MOMENTS OF HEROISM GIVING SO
MANY RENEWED HOPE THAT MORE
LIVES WOULD BE SAVED.
FIREFIGHTERS RESCUING THIS WOMAN
PULLING HER OUT THROUGH A HOLE
IN THE CEILING.
HER HAND TO HER FACE IN
DISBELIEF.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> CHILDREN TRAPPED INSIDE THIS
SCHOOL.
RESCUERS AND NEIGHBORS PUSHING
THROUGH THE RUBBLE.
REACHING BEHIND THIS WALL TO
LIFT THEM OUT.
AND AMONG THE FIRST RESPONDERS
ARE AT THAT SCHOOL, FRITA.
THE 7-YEAR-OLD LABRADOR IS PART
OF THE MEXICAN NAVY'S CANINE
UNIT SEARCHING FOR TRAPPED
SURVIVORS.
SHE HAS SAVED A DOZEN LIVES IN
HER CAREER.
IN THOSE GOGGLES PROTECTING HER
EYES FROM THE DIRT AND DEBRIS
AND THE BOOTIES TO PROTECT HER
PAWS.
THEY HAVE BEEN CRAWLING INTO
THOSE DANGEROUSLY TIGHT SPACES
FOR DAYS NOW.
THE CORNERS RESCUERS CANNOT GET
TO.
TONIGHT AS HOPE FADES SO MANY
TRYING TO FOCUS ON THE LIVES
SAVED.
AND THE FIRST RESPONDERS AND
THEIR PARTNERS, THOSE DOGS
INCLUDING FRITA ANSWERING THE
CALL AGAIN.
CANNOT FORGET FRITA AND THOSE
DOGS WITH ALL OF THOSE RESCUE
TEAMS.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING THIS
WEEK.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO TO SEE YOU ON MONDAY
UNTIL THEN HAVE A GOOD EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> FROM BOSTON'S NEWS LEADER,
THIS IS WCVB NEWSCENTER FIVE AT
7:00.
ED: A FATHER KILLS HIS OWN SON
BEFORE TAKING HIS OWN LIFE.
THIS PHOTO OF THEM WAS TAKEN
JUST THIS WEEK.
AND ONLY ON 5 TONIGHT, WE ARE
HEARING FROM THAT AUNT OF THAT
LITTLE BOY.
GOOD EVENING.
I'M ED HARDING.
MARIA: I'M MARIA STEPHANOS.
NEWSCENTER 5'S NICOLE ESTAPHAN
IS LIVE IN FOXBORO TO BEGIN OUR
COVERAGE OF THIS HEART-BREAKING
STORY.
NICOLE: THIS IS TOUGH, A FAMILY
MOURNING THE LOSS OF A LITTLE
BOY AND HIS FATHER, A MAN THEY
SAY HAS LONG SUFFERED WITH
MENTAL ILLNESS, THEY SAY THERE
WERE GOOD TIMES MIXED IN WITH
THE BAD.
THEY NEVER THOUGHT IT WOULD
INTELLECT IS VIEWED -- IT WOULD
END LIKE THIS.
>> ANTHONY WAS VERY PRECOCIOUS,
SILLY CHILD.
NICOLE: JUST SIX YEARS OLD, A
KINDERGARTENER, KILLED BY HIS
OWN FATHER.
>>