♪
>>> TONIGHT, SEVERAL BREAKING
HEADLINES AS WE COME ON THE AIR.
THE MASSACRE IN LAS VEGAS.
POLICE BODY CAMS SHOWING
OFFICERS RESPONDING.
AND WHAT WE'VE JUST LEARNED
TONIGHT ABOUT THE GUNMAN.
HE CHECKED INTO MULTIPLE HOTELS
ON THE EVE OF THE SHOOTING.
ALL WITH A VIEW OF THE CONCERT.
ALSO, THE GUNMAN'S GIRLFRIEND,
BACK IN THE U.S. TONIGHT BEING
QUESTIONED BY THE FBI.
PUSHED IN A WHEELCHAIR THROUGH
THE AIRPORT.
WHAT HAS SHE REVEALED?
DID SHE KNOW ANYTHING?
OUR TEAM STANDING BY.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HERE IN LAS
VEGAS.
WHAT HE SAID ABOUT THE
SURVIVORS.
THE WOUNDS HE SAW FIRST-HAND.
AND WHAT THE PRESIDENT IS NOW
SAYING ABOUT GUN CONTROL.
>>> A MAJOR NEW TROPICAL SYSTEM
CLOSING IN ON THE AMERICAN
COAST.
POTENTIALLY BRINGING HURRICANE
WINDS.
THE POSSIBLE PATHS FROM THE
GULF, ALL THE WAY TO THE
NORTHEAST.
>>> IN NEW YORK CITY, NEW
SURVEILLANCE JUST RELEASED.
THE BOMB SUSPECT ALLEGEDLY
CARRYING TWO CONCEALED DEVICES.
>>> AND THE MOTHER PUT BEHIND
BARS TONIGHT AFTER REFUSING TO
VACCINATE HER SON.
IT'S NOW BELIEVED HE WILL BE
VACCINATED WHILE SHE'S LOCKED
UP.
>>> GOOD EVENING ON THIS
WEDNESDAY NIGHT FROM LAS VEGAS.
AND AS WE COME ON THE AIR, WE
ARE FOLLOWING BREAKING NEWS.
ABC NEWS HAS LEARNED OF THE
GUNMAN'S EXTRAORDINARY PLANNING.
POSSIBLY CHECKING INTO MULTIPLE
HOTELS BEFORE THE ATTACK, ALL
WITHIN SHOOTING DISTANCE OF THAT
CONCERT SITE.
JUST AS WE ALSO SEE THE POLICE
RESPONSE THROUGH THEIR BODY
CAMS.
THE OFFICERS TAKING COVER, THEN
JUMPING INTO ACTION.
INSIDE THAT HOTEL ROOM, IMAGES
OF HIS DEADLY ARSENAL.
23 WEAPONS.
HUNDREDS OF ROUNDS OF
AMMUNITION.
AND WE HAVE NEW REPORTING
TONIGHT ON THE SECURITY GUARD,
THE FIRST PERSON TO GET TO THAT
HOTEL HALLWAY, TO THE DOOR OF
THAT HOTEL ROOM.
BEFORE THE GUNMAN SHOT HIM RIGHT
THROUGH IT.
THAT GUARD, STILL ABLE TO TELL
POLICE HE'D FOUND THE GUNMAN.
ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN
LEADING US OFF TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, POLICE
BODY CAMERAS REVEAL OFFICERS
RISKING THEIR OWN LIVES AMID
UNCEASING GUNFIRE.
>> GET DOWN!
GO THAT WAY!
GET OUT OF HERE, THERE'S
GUNSHOTS COMING FROM OVER THERE.
GO THAT WAY!
>> Reporter: WITH SIRENS BLARING
AND BULLETS FLYING, OFFICERS
HUDDLED BEHIND A WALL, TRYING TO
PINPOINT THE SOURCE OF THE
MAYHEM.
>> NORTH OF THE MANDALAY BAY.
COMING OUT OF A WINDOW.
>> Reporter: EXHIBITING
EXTRAORDINARY CALM, THOSE
OFFICERS DIRECTING CONCERT-GOERS
AWAY FROM THE SHOOTING TO
SAFETY.
>> THIS WAY, THIS WAY, THIS WAY.
GO, GO, GO.
>> Reporter: IT WOULD BE AN HOUR
BEFORE POLICE BREACHED STEPHEN
PADDOCK'S LUXURY SUITE.
TONIGHT, THESE PHOTOS REVEALING
THEIR DESTRUCTIVE POWER.
THIS ASSAULT REICHEL, ONE OF 12
OUTFITTED WITH AN ATTACHMENT
CALLED A BUMP STOCK.
THIS VIDEO COMMON STRAITING HOW
IT WORKS.
ON THE TIP OF THE RIFLE, A FLASH
HIDER, MAKING ITS FIERY BLAST
DIFFICULT TO SPOT.
AND IN THE CORNER, A PILE OF 17
MAGAZINES HOLDING 100 ROUNDS
EACH.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT 1,700 BULLETS.
PAD DOM DOCK INSTALLING HIS OWN
SURVEILLANCE CAMERA.
ALL RIGGED SO HE COULD SEE
POLICE APPROACHING.
AND NOW, WE ARE LEARNING HE
SPOTTED A HOTEL SECURITY GUARD.
>> HE WAS ADVANCING TOWARDS THE
ROOM WHEN THE SUSPECT FIRED
THROUGH THE DOOR AT THE SECURITY
GUARD AND STRUCK HIM.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THAT
SECURITY GUARD IDENTIFIED AS
JESUS CAMPOS.
SOMEHOW HE WAS ABLE TO GET AWAY
AND TELL THE TACTICAL TEAM THAT
PAD DOM WAS IN ROOM 135.
AN HOUR LATER, THEY BREACHED THE
DOOR.
>> BREACH, BREACH, BREACH.
>> Reporter: AND DISCOVERED HIM
ALREADY DEAD.
TONIGHT, FEDERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT
SOURCES TELLING ABC NEWS THEY
ARE INVESTIGATING REPORTS THAT
THE DAY BEFORE THE MASSACRE, HE
CHECKED INTO MULTIPLE HOTELS
OVERLOOKING THE CONCERT VENUE.
AND HE MAY HAVE LOOKED FOR OTHER
OPPORTUNITIES.
FEDERAL SOURCES SAY HE LOOKED
INTO RENTING A ROOM IN THIS
BUILDING RIGHT NEXT TO ANOTHER
MUSIC FESTIVAL JUST THE WEEK
BEFORE.
AND FROM THIS PERCH HE WOULD
HAVE HAD A CLEAR FIELD OF FIRE
RIGHT DOWN INTO THOSE TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE PACKED INTO
THAT CONCERT BELOW.
BUT FOR SOME REASON, HE DIDN'T
PURSUE THE PLAN, INSTEAD, HE
WAITED A WEEK FOR THE HARVEST
FESTIVAL.
AND MATT GUTMAN JOINS US LIVE
TONIGHT HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
MATT, WE NOW KNOW HE MAY HAVE
HAD SEVERAL HOTEL OPTIONS FOR
THIS ATTACK, UMENT MATLY
SPENDING MORE THAN THREE DAYS IN
THE MANDALAY BAY HOTEL BEHIND
ME.
AND YOU'RE LEARNING WHAT HE
MIGHT HAVE DONE THE DAY BEFORE?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
WE'RE LEARNING HE WASN'T JUST
SHUTTERED UP IN THAT LUXURY
SUITE IN THAT HOTEL.
NOW, LAW ENFORCEMENT HASN'T
WEIGHED IN ON THIS YET.
I SPOKE TO A CASINO WITH WORKER
WHO SAID THEY SAW HIM PLAY HIGH
STAKES VIDEO POKER FOR EIGHT
CONTINUOUS HOURS THE MORNING OF
THE ATTACK.
16 HOURS THAT WEEKEND.
AND WHAT TAKES MANY SO
DISTURBING IS THAT IT MEANS HE
WAS MILLING ABOUT WITH THE
PUBLIC, OUT IN THE OPEN, FOR
DAYS BEFORE THE ATTACK.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN LEADING US OFF
TONIGHT.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> AND THE OTHER MAJOR
DEVELOPMENT, THE GUNMAN'S
GIRLFRIEND, SHE IS BACK IN THE
U.S. TONIGHT, BEING QUESTIONED
BY THE FBI.
HER BROTHER TELLING ABC NEWS
THAT SHE ASSURED HER FAMILY SHE
HAS A, QUOTE, CLEAN CONSCIENCE.
BUT TONIGHT, SHE REMAINS A
PERSON OF INTEREST, AS THEY NOW
ASK, HOW THE GUNMAN ASSEMBLED
SUCH AN ARSENAL WITHOUT ANYONE
NOTICING.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, JUST
12 HOURS AFTER SHE ARRIVED ON A
FLIGHT FROM THE PHILIPPINES, THE
SHOOTER'S LONG-TIME GIRLFRIEND,
MARILOU DANLEY TOLD THE FBI,
ACCORDING TO LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIALS, THAT SHE HAD NO
KNOWLEDGE OF HIS PLANS OR HIS
PURCHASE OF SO MANY GUNS.
HER LAWYER READ HER STATEMENT
AFTER THE FBI SESSION ENDED.
>> HE NEVER SAID ANYTHING TO ME
OR TOOK ANY ACTION THAT I WAS
AWARE OF THAT I UNDERSTOOD IN
ANY WAY TO BE A WARNING THAT
SOMETHING HORRIBLE LIKE THIS WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: DANLEY HAD BEEN
PADDOCK'S LIVE-IN GIRLFRIEND FOR
AT LEAST THREE YEARS.
HE MET HER WHEN SHE WAS A CASINO
HOSTESS.
THEY GAMBLED TOGETHER, PLAYING
VIDEO POKER AND THE SLOTS.
INVESTIGATORS WANT TO KNOW IF HE
WENT ALONG WHEN SHE TRAVELED TO
DUBAI, WHERE SHE POSTED THIS
SMILING PHOTO.
ACCORDING TO HER SISTERS IN
AUSTRALIA, WHO WANTED THEIR
FACES BLURRED, NO ONE KNOWS MORE
ABOUT PADDOCK.
>> NO ONE CAN PUT THE PUZZLES
TOGETHER.
NO ONE.
EXCEPT MARILOU.
>> Reporter: THE SISTERS SAID
PADDOCK WHO SENT HER TO THE
PHILIPPINES JUST TWO WEEKS
BEFORE THE SHOOTING.
>> HE SENT HER AWAY.
SO THAT HE CAN PLAN WHAT HE IS
PLANNING WITHOUT INTERRUPTIONS.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES NOW ARE
PUTTING TOGETHER A PSYCHOLOGICAL
PROFILE OF THE SHOOTER.
A 64-YEAR-OLD ONE-TIME
ACCOUNTANT AND IRS AGENT, WHO
CLAIMED TO BE A
MULTIMILLIONAIRE.
BUT INVESTIGATORS SAY A PICTURE
IS EMERGING OF A MAN "DESCENDING
INTO MADNESS," LOSING WEIGHT,
DIMINISHED PHYSICAL APPEARANCE,
WHAT ARE DESCRIBED AS "CRAZY
EYES."
COUPLED WITH EASY ACCESS TO THE
POWERFUL WEAPONS HE BEGAN TO
ACCUMULATE AT LEAST A YEAR AGO,
A DEADLY COMBINATION.
>> BRIAN ROSS WITH US LIVE FROM
NEW YORK TONIGHT.
AND BRIAN, WE HEARD YOUR REPORT
THERE, THE SHOOTER'S GIRLFRIEND
SPENT HOURS TODAY TALKING TO THE
FBI.
BUT SHE IS DENYING KNOWING
ANYTHING ABOUT THIS PLOT?
>> Reporter: YES, DAVID.
OFFICIALS SAY SHE CLAIMS SHE HAD
NO IDEA ABOUT THE DOZENS OF GUNS
HER BOYFRIEND BOUGHT OVER THE
LAST YEAR, AND AS YOU SAID, HER
BROTHER TELLS ABC NEWS, SHE TOLD
HER FAMILY SHE HAS A CLEAN
CONSCIENCE, DAVID.
>> BRIAN ROSS AND YOUR TEAM.
WE THANK YOU AGAIN TONIGHT.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP, MEANWHILE,
WAS HERE IN LAS VEGAS TODAY.
IT IS THE FIRST TIME HE'S HAD TO
VISIT THE SCENE OF A MASS
SHOOTING, MEETING WITH SURE VOI
VORS.
WHAT HE SAID TO DOCTORS AND
NURSES HERE, AND WHAT HE'S NOW
SAYING ABOUT GUN CONTROL.
ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA, ALSO
HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
>> Reporter: IN LAS VEGAS TODAY,
PRESIDENT TRUMP, IN A NEW
ROLE --
COMFORTER IN CHIEF.
WITH THE FIRST LADY BY HIS SIDE,
THEIR FIRST STOP, THE HOSPITAL
TREATING DOZENS OF PATIENTS,
STILL FIGHTING FOR THEIR LIVES.
>> SOME WERE VERY, VERY BADLY
WOUNDED AND THEY WERE BADLY
WOUNDED BECAUSE THEY REFUSED TO
LEAVE AND THEY WANTED TO HELP
OTHERS BECAUSE THEY SAW PEOPLE
GOING DOWN ALL OVER.
AND IT'S AN INCREDIBLE THING TO
SEE.
THERE'S TREMENDOUS BRAVERY.
>> Reporter: THE FOCUS ON THOSE
SURVIVORS.
BUT THIS WAS ALSO A THANK YOU
TOUR.
IT MAKES YOU VERY PROUD TO BE AN
AMERICAN, WHEN YOU SEE THE JOB
THAT THEY'VE DONE.
>> Reporter: AT THE COMMAND
CENTER, SURROUNDED BY FIRST
RESPONDERS, THE PRESIDENT
PRAISING THEIR HEROISM, LIKE
THESE DISPATCH OPERATORS WHO
ANSWERED THOSE FRANTIC CALLS FOR
HELP.
>> CALM AND STRONG, SHARP.
>> Reporter: FOR THE SHOOTER, HE
HAD HARSH WORDS.
>> HE'S A SICK, GHANTED MAN.
>> Reporter: AND FOR THE NATION,
A MESSAGE OF UNITY --
>> AMERICA IS TRULY A NATION IN
MOURNING.
>> Reporter: AND HOPE.
>> AMERICANS DEFIED DEATH AND
HATRED WITH LOVE AND WITH
COURAGE.
>> Reporter: BUT AS THE DEBATE
ABOUT GUNS IN THIS COUNTRY GROWS
LOUDER, THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF,
NOT WILLING TO GO THERE, NOT
TODAY.
>> DOES AMERICA HAVE A GUN
VIOLENCE PROBLEM?
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO TALK ABOUT
THAT TODAY.
>> AND CECILIA VEGA JOINS US
LIVE TONIGHT.
CECILIA, THE PRESIDENT SAID ANY
DISCUSSION ABOUT GUNS WILL COME
DOWN THE ROAD TODAY, BUT ON
CAPITOL HILL TODAY, THERE WAS A
LOT OF FOCUS ON WHAT ARE CALLED
BUMP STOCK ATTACHMENTS THAT MATT
REPORTED ON, THAT CAN
ESSENTIALLY TURN ASSAULT RIFLES
INTO AUTOMATIC WEAPONS.
AND THERE IS WORD TONIGHT THAT
SENATOR GRIN FEINSTEIN AND TWO
REPUBLICAN LAWMAKERS ARE TALKING
ABOUT LEGISLATION TO BAN THEM?
>> Reporter: YEAH, DAVID.
A HANDFUL OF SENATE REPUBLICANS
SEEM OPEN TO THE IDEA OF HOLDING
HEARS ON THIS SUBJECT.
A SIMILAR MOVEMENT IS IN THE
HOUSE, AS WELL.
BUT MITCH McCONNELL SAYS IT'S
PREMATURE TO BE TALKING ABOUT
THIS.
A VOTE SEEMS LIKE A LONG WAY
OFF.
>> CECILIA VEGA WITH US HERE IN
LAS VEGAS TONIGHT.
>>> THERE WAS AN EXTRAORDINARY
MARE MOMENT THAT PLAYED OUT HERE
TAESHGSD AFTER AN INTERVIEW WE
BROUGHT YOU LAST NIGHT HERE.
A SON, WHO WAS AT THE CONCERT
FOR HIS 21st BIRTHDAY, HE WAS
SHOT, AND THEN SAVED BY A YOUNG
MAN WHO HELD PRESSURE TO HIS
WOUNDS ALL THE WAY TO THE
HOSPITAL, STAYING NEXT TO HIM IN
THE E.R.
HE TOLD US HE WANTED TO MEET
THAT HERO, AND SOMEONE HEARD
THAT LAST NIGHT.
TONIGHT HERE, THE LIST OF
HEROES, AND WHAT HAPPENED IN
THAT VERY SAME HOSPITAL ROOM
TODAY.
TONIGHT, THE NEW STORIES NOW
EMERGING OF THE QUIET HEROES WHO
SAVED SO MANY LIVES HERE.
MIKE KORDICH, A FIREFIGHTER, WAS
GIVING CPR TO SOMEONE WHEN HE
WAS SHOT IN THE ARM.
>> I KEPT DOING CHEST
COMPRESSIONS WITH ONE ARM UNTIL
I NOTICED I WAS STARTING TO
BLEED A LOT.
>> Reporter: NURSE NATALIE
VAND
VANDERSTAY HIT BY A BULLET AND
SHRAPNEL.
CONCERT-GOERS GETTINGER TO THE
HOSPITAL, KEEPING PRESSURE ON
HER WOUNDS.
>> IF IT WASN'T FOR THAT CAB
DRIVER I WOULDN'T BE HERE.
AND I DON'T KNOW WHO HE IS.
>> Reporter: THERE WAS
5-YEAR-OLD ADEN HUSER, SEPARATED
FROM HIS MOTHER WHEN THE
SHOOTING BEGAN.
>> I LOST HER AND I WAS SAD, I
DIDN'T KNOW WHERE TO RUN.
>> Reporter: WHEN A STRANGER,
LINDSEY ROGERS, SAW HIM STANDING
ALONE, SHE STAYED BY HIS SIDE.
>> HE WAS REALLY BRAVE AND
REALLY GOOD.
>> Reporter: LINDSEY AND A
FRIEND POSTING THIS PHOTO ON
FACEBOOK.
HIS RELATIVES SAW IT.
HE'S BEEN REUNITED WITH HIS
MOTHER.
AND IT WAS LAST NIGHT HERE, WE
WALKED INTO A ROOM AT DESERT
SPRINGS HOSPITAL MEDICAL CENTER
HERE IN LAS VEGAS, WHERE SHELDON
MACK IS RECOVERING.
HE WAS AT THE CONCERT FOR HIS
21st BIRTHDAY.
>> IT JUST KEEP SEEING IT IN MY
MIND STILL.
IT HAUNTS ME.
>> Reporter: YOU SEE IT ALL
PLAYING OUT STILL.
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: HE TOLD ME ABOUT
THE MAN WHO SAVED HIS LIFE.
>> SOME HERO CAME AND SAVE ME.
AND THROW ME IN AND TAKE CARE OF
ME.
>> Reporter: THAT HERO HOLDING
HIS FINGER TO THE BULLET WOUND.
THE GUY THAT WAS BY YOUR SIDE,
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO FIND
OUT WHERE HE IS --
>> NO.
>> Reporter: WHO HE IS?
>> YEAH, I NEED TO.
I -- I OWE HIM A BEER, AT LEAST.
YEAH, I REALLY APPRECIATE ALL
HE'S DONE FOR ME.
>> Reporter: THAT'S A PRETTY
GOOD TRADEOFF.
SHELDON'S PARENTS TELLING US,
THEY WANT TO MEET THAT HERO.
>> HE'S AN ANGEL AND SAVED HIM.
HE WAS SHOT IN THE LEG, AS WELL.
>> Reporter: IT TURNS OUT,
FRIENDS OF THAT HERO WERE
WATCHING THE NEWS LAST NIGHT.
JIMMY GROVER, A 25-YEAR-OLD
PARAMEDIC FROM ORANGE COUNTY,
CALIFORNIA, WAS HERE IN LAS
VEGAS VISIT IING.
AND TODAY, HE PAID ANOTHER
VISIT, WALKING INTO THAT ROOM ON
CRUTCHES.
JIMMY REVEALING HE KNEW SHELDON
WAS IN TROUBLE AFTER BEING SHOT
IN THE ARM AND THEN THE BULLET
PIERCING THE ABDOMEN, AS WELL.
AND HE RODE WITH HIM IN A TRUCK
ALL THE WAY TO THAT E.R.
SHELDON'S MOM, GRATEFUL.
AND AFTERWARD, THERE WAS ONE
MORE REUNION IN THAT SAME ROOM.
ERIC FRAZIER, THE MARINE VET WHO
DROVE BOTH JIMMY AND SHELDON TO
THE HOSPITAL, IT TURNS OUT THAT
MARINE VET RUSHED A DOZEN
VICTIMS TO THE E.R. THAT NIGHT.
AND TONIGHT, THE SURVIVOR'S
FAMILY AND THE HERO'S FAMILY,
ALL TOGETHER AFTER THE HORROR.
>> AND BY THE WAY, SHELDON'S DAD
TOLD US TONIGHT THAT HIS SON
TOLD HIS HERO, JIMMY, HE'S GOING
TO MAKE GOOD ON THAT PROMISE OF
A BEER, AND SOON.
>>> AND WHILE THE PRESIDENT WAS
HERE IN LAS VEGAS TODAY, HE WAS
ALSO ASKED ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE.
ABOUT A REPORT THAT HIS
SECRETARY OF STATE, REX
TILLERSON, CALLED THE PRESIDENT
A MORON AFTER A NATIONAL
SECURITY MEETING.
THE PRESIDENT'S RESPONSE TODAY,
AND THE SECRETARY OF STATE, REX
TILLERSON HIMSELF, COMING BEFORE
THE CAMERAS TODAY.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF GLOBAL
AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT MARTHA
RADDATZ TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: SECRETARY OF STATE
OF STATE REX TILLERSON TODAY
MAKING A RARE, IMPROMPTU
APPEARANCE.
>> THERE ARE SOME NEWS REPORTS
THIS MORNING THAT I WANT TO
ADDRESS.
>> Reporter: A REPORT ROCKETING
AROUND WASHINGTON.
NBC NEWS REPORTING TILLERSON HAD
CALLED TRUMP A MORON LAST JULY,
AFTER A NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM
MEETING AND WAS THEN ON THE
VERGE OF RESIGNING.
>> THE VICE PRESIDENT HAS NEVER
HAD TO PERSUADE ME TO REMAIN AS
SECRETARY OF STATE, BECAUSE I
HAVE NEVER CONSIDERED LEAVING
THIS POST.
>> Reporter: AND THAT REPORT OF
CALLING THE PRESIDENT A MORON?
>> CAN YOU ADDRESS THE MAIN
HEADLINE OF THIS STORY THAT YOU
CALLED THE PRESIDENT A MORON,
AND IF NOT, WHERE DO YOU THINK
THESE REPORTS ARE --
>> I'M NOT GOING TO DEAL WITH
PETTY STUFF LIKE THAT.
I'M JUST NOT GOING TO BE PART OF
THIS EFFORT TO DIVIDE THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
>> Reporter: NOT A FLAT-OUT
DENIAL, BUT HIS SPOKESPERSON
LATER, MORE DEFINITIVE.
>> HE DID NOT SAY THAT.
>> Reporter: THE FULL COURT
PRESS PLEASING THE PRESIDENT.
>> YEAH, I'M VERY HONORED BY HIS
COMMENTS.
IT WAS FAKE NEWS.
IT WAS A TOTALLY PHONY STORY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT WAS MADE UP BY NBC.
THEY JUST MADE IT UP.
THANK YOU, ALL.
TOTAL CONFIDENCE IN REX.
>> Reporter: BUT TRUMP AND
TILLERSON HAVE APPEARED AT ODDS
WITH ONE ANOTHER RECENTLY.
JUST LAST WEEKEND, AFTER
TILLERSON SAID DIALOGUE WITH
NORTH KOREA WAS POSSIBLE, TRUMP
TWEETING, "I TOLD REX TILLERSON,
OUR WONDERFUL SECRETARY OF
STATE, THAT HE IS WASTING HIS
TIME TRYING TO WE GAUCHE YAT
WITH LITTLE ROCKET MAN.
SAVE YOUR ENERGY, REX.
WE'LL DO WHAT HAS TO BE DONE."
>> AND SO MARTHA, A VERY PUBLIC
STATEMENT OF LOYALTY FROM REX
TILLERSON, BUT A LEADING
REPUBLICAN SENATOR DID SAY TODAY
THAT TILLERSON HASN'T ALWAYS HAD
THE BACKING HE DESERVES?
>> Reporter: THAT'S EXACTLY
RIGHT, DAVID.
REPUBLICAN SENATOR BOB CORKER,
CHAIRMAN OF THE FOREIGN
RELATIONS COMMITTEE, SAID
TILLERSON ISN'T GETTING THE
SUPPORT HE NEEDS FROM THE
ADMINISTRATION, ADDING THAT
TILLERSON, SECRETARY MATTIS AND
JOHN KELLY ARE THE PEOPLE WHO,
QUOTE, HELP SEPARATE OUR COUNTRY
FROM CHAOS.
DAVID?
>> MARTHA RADDATZ WITH US
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, MARTHA.
>>> WE'RE FOLLOWING TWO NEW
TROPICAL SYSTEMING BREWING
TONIGHT.
ONE OF THEM GROWING STRONGER.
AT THIS HOUR, ON TRACK TO MAKE
LANDFALL IN THE U.S. ON SUNDAY.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO ROB MARCIANO.
ROB?
>> Reporter: HEY, DAVID.
THEY ARE BOTH PRETTY CLOSE TO
HOME.
WHAT WILL DEVELOP AND STRENGTHEN
IS THIS DISTURBANCE SOUTH OF THE
HONDURAS/NICARAGUA BORDER BY 180
MILES.
TROPICAL STORM WARNINGS UP FOR
THOSE TWO COUNTRIES.
POTENTIALLY AS A CATEGORY 1
HURRICANE ON SATURDAY, MAKING
LANDFALL ON SUNDAY.
BUT OUR COMPUTER MODELS ALL OVER
THE PLACE.
ANYWHERE FROM EAST TEXAS TO WEST
FLORIDA NEED TO BE WARY OF THIS
STORM.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, WE'RE WATCHING.
ROB, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS WEDNESDAY.
THE MOTHER OF TWO BEHIND BARS
TONIGHT, ORDERERED TO SPEND A
WEEK IN JAIL.
HER DEFIANT SHOWDOWN WITH A
JUDGE, REFUSING A COURT ORDER TO
VACCINATE HER SON.
WE WANT YOUR OPINION ON THIS
ONE.
>>> NEWLY RELEASED SURVEILLANCE
TONIGHT IN NEW YORK CITY.
THE BOMB SUSPECT ALLEGEDLY
CARRYING TWO CONCEALED DEVICES
THROUGH ONE OF THE BUSIEST TRAIN
STATIONS IN AMERICA.
>>> AND THE CHEMICAL PLANT
EXPLOSIONS.
SMOKE AND FLAMING FILLING THE
AIR.
FAMILIES TOLD TO STAY INDOORS.
NEWS COMING IN AT THIS HOUR.
Essential for vinyl,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and further
joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma
and other cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Tears in the stomach
or intestines,
low blood cell counts
and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels
have happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you start
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you
were in a region
where fungal infections
are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
A must for vinyl.
But for you,
one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
Liberty Mutual saved us almost
eight hundred dollars when we
switched our auto and
home insurance.
With Liberty, we could afford
a real babysitter instead
of your brother.
Hey.
Oh. That's my robe.
Is it?
You could save seven hundred
eighty two dollars
when Liberty stands with you.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
...What are you doing??
I thought you had a cold?
I don't need all this.
Mucinex Fast-Max can handle
pretty much every symptom.
Even...
Yea - I can read, you know.
Ahhh!
Mucinex Fast-Max.
9 symptoms. 1 dose.
Max strength.
Let's End This.
♪ Stare with me into the abyss ♪
( ♪ )
>>> NEXT, A MOTHER SENTENCED TO
ONE WEEK IN JAIL, AFTER DENYING
A JUDGE'S ORDER TO VACCINATE HER
9-YEAR-OLD SON.
HERE'S ABC'S ARIEL RESHEF.
>> I AM A PASSIONATE MOTHER WHO
CARES DEEPLY ABOUT MY CHILDREN,
THEIR HEALTH, AND THEIR
WELLBEING.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THIS
MICHIGAN MOM OF TWO IS HEADED TO
JAIL, HEAD IN CONTEMPT FOR
DELIBERATELY DISOBEYING A COURT
ORDER TO VAC NATE HER
9 1/2-YEAR-OLD SON.
>> Reporter: PLEADING HER CASE
BEFORE A JUDGE, SAYING SHE AND
HER EX-HUSBAND AGREED TO SPACE
OUT AND ULTIMATELY SUSPEND THEIR
SOME'S VACCINES.
THE JUDGE SAYING THAT BOY WILL
BE VACCINATED.
>> OKAY, MA'AM, I'M GOING TO
STOP YOU.
BUT THE TRUTH MATTERS TO ME.
I UNDERSTAND YOU LOVE YOUR
CHILDREN, BUT WHAT I DON'T THINK
YOU UNDERSTAND IS THAT YOUR SON
HAS TWO PARENTS.
AND DAD GETS A SAY.
>> Reporter: WHILE THE STATE OF
MICHIGAN DOES ALLOW PARENTS TO
OPT THEIR CHILDREN OUT OF
CERTAIN VACCINATIONS, BOTH
PARENTS MUST AGREE.
THE AMERICAN ACADEMY OF
PEDIATRICS SAYS VACCINES ARE
SAFE, VACCINES ARE EFFECTIVE,
VACCINES SAVE LIVES.
DAVID, REBECCA'S EX-HUSBAND WAS
GRANTED ITEM PRARP CUSTODY OF
THEIR SON WHILE SHE SERVES HER
SEVEN-DAY JAIL SENTENCE.
SHE IS EXPECTED TO BE BACK IN
COURT NEXT WEEK.
DAVID?
>> AIR YES, MA'AM, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, YOUR MONEY.
DID A MAJOR COMPANY CASH IN ON
THAT SECURITY BREACH INVOLVED
YOUR INFORMATION?
>>> THE EXPLOSION TONIGHT.
FAMILIES ORDERED TO SHELTER IN
PLACE.
>>> AND NEWLY RELEASED
SURVEILLANCE.
THE BOMB SUSPECT IN ONE OF NEW
YORK CITY'S BUSIEST TRAIN
STATIONS.
type 2 diabetes...
with Fitness...
Food...
And the pill that
starts with F.
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA
if you have severe
kidney problems,
are on dialysis,
or have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary tract
infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious
and may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about
the pill that starts with F
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
Whatever you're doing
to stay healthy...
...tmay be missing.g you
A key part of your wellness
that you may be...
...overlooking.
♪
It's your eyes.
That's why there's Ocuvite,
from Bausch + Lomb.
As you age your eyes can lose
vital nutrients.
Ocuvite helps replenish those
nutrients.
Ocuvite has Lutein, Zeaxanthin,
and Omega-3.
Nourish your eyes to help them
be their healthy best.
Ocuvite eye vitamins.
Be good to your eyes.
When it comes to heartburn
trust the brand doctors
trust for themselves.
Nexium 24HR is the number one
choice of doctors
and pharmacists for their
own frequent heartburn.
And all day
all night protection.
When it comes to frequent
heartburn, trust Nexium 24HR.
Liberty Mutual stood with me
when I was too busy with the
kids to get a repair estimate.
I just snapped a photo
and got an estimate in 24 hours.
My insurance company
definitely doesn't have that...
You can leave worry behind when
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
I accept I don't bike
as far as I used to.
I even accept I have a
higher risk of stroke
due to AFib,
a type of
irregular heartbeat
not caused by a
heart valve problem.
But no matter
where I ride,
I go for my best.
So if there's something
better than warfarin,
I'll go for that too.
ELIQUIS.
the risk of stroke
better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor
tells you to,
as stopping increases your
risk of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
...and it may take
longer than usual
for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate
medical care
for sudden signs
of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about
all planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor
about ELIQUIS.
♪
>>> TO THE INDEX, THE CHEMICAL
PLANT EXPLOSION IN KINGS PORT,
TENNESSEE.
VIDEO SHOWING THE ERUPTION OF
SMOKE AND FIRE AT THE EASTMAN
CHEMICAL COMPANY.
EMPL
EMPLOYEES URGED TO SHELTER IN
PLACE.
IN INJURIES REPORTED.
>>> SURVEILLANCE OF THE ALLEGED
NEW YORK CITY BOMBER.
HE'S SEEN CARRYING TWO EXPLOSIVE
DEVICES CONCEALED IN DUTCHLE
BAGS THROUGH A VERY CROWDED PENN
STATION WUCHBLT OF THE PRESSURE
COOKER BOMBING EXPLODING ON THE
STREET ABOUT AN HOUR LATER.
>>> TONIGHT, EQUIFAX ACCUSED OF
PROFITING FROM THAT MASSIVE
SECURITY BREACH.
SENATOR ELIZABETH WARREN
GRILLING THE FORMER CEO ON
CAPITOL HILL, SAYING EQUIFAX
COULD MAKE $200 MILLION IN VEF
KNEW IF ONE MILLION CUSTOMERS
BUY CREDIT MONITORING AFTER THE
BREACH.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
YOU HAVE TO HEAR IT.
THE SONG THAT MOVED EVERYONE
HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
Patrick woke up
with a sore back.
But he's got work to do.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Check this Sunday's paper
for extra savings on
products from Aleve.
Time for Medicare, huh.
I have no idea how we're going
to get through this.
Follow me.
UnitedHealthcare has the people
and tools
to help guide you through the
confusion.
Well that wasn't so bad at all.
That's how we like it.
UnitedHealthcare.
WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE TO
THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE,
DOES PSORIASIS EVER GET IN
THE WAY OF A TOUCHING MOMENT?
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE
TO SEVERE PSORIASIS,
YOU CAN EMBRACE
THE CHANCE
OF COMPLETELY CLEAR
SKIN WITH TALTZ.
TALTZ IS PROVEN TO GIVE YOU A
CHANCE AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
WITH TALTZ, UP TO
90% OF PATIENTS
HAD A SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT
OF THEIR PSORIASIS PLAQUES.
IN FACT, 4 OUT OF 10 EVEN
ACHIEVED COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DO NOT USE IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING YOU
SHOULD BE CHECKED
FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE YOUR
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU ARE BEING TREATED
FOR AN INFECTION
OR HAVE SYMPTOMS.
OR IF YOU HAVE RECEIVED
A VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ.
INCLUDING WORSENING
OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
JUST ASK YOUR
DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
I'm Val. The Orange Money
retirement squirrel from Voya.
I represent the money you save
for the future.
Who's he?
He's the green money you can
spend now. What's up?
Gonna pay some bills, maybe buy
a new tennis racket.
He's got a killer backhand.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement, it's time to get
Voya.
It's time to rethink
what's possible.
Rethink the experience.
Rethink your allergy pills.
Flonase Sensimist Allergy Relief
uses unique MistPro Technology
and helps block
6 key
inflammatory
substances
with a
gentle mist.
Most allergy
pills
only block
one.
And 6 is greater
than one.
Rethink your
allergy relief.
Flonase Sensimist.
♪
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, AMERICA
STRONG.
WE SEE IT EVERYWHERE HERE, THE
ACTS OF KINDNESS.
♪ AMAZING GRACE ♪
>> Reporter: ALL ACROSS LAS
VEGAS, TESTAMENTS TO THE
STRENGTH AND RESOLVE OF THIS
COMMUNITY.
WE SEE IT IN THE FACES HERE,
AMID UNIMAGINABLE GRIEF, FINDING
COMFORTABLE  IN ONE ANOTHER.
A MESSAGE OF SOLIDARITY.
OUR PRAYERS FOR THE VICTIMS.
OUR GRATITUDE FOR THE FIRST
RESPONDERS.
♪ I ONCE WAS LOST ♪
>> Reporter: WE SEE IT IN THE
SMALL MOMENTS, TOO, HERE.
THIS FAMILY PAUSING TO HUG A
POLICE OFFICER.
AND AT THE CANYON RIDGE
CHRISTIAN CHURCH, THOUSANDS OF
VOICES UNITING IN ONE POWERFUL
CHORUS.
♪ NOW I SEE ♪
>> THANK YOU FOR WATCHING HERE
ON A WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> FROM BOSTON'S NEWS LEADER,
THIS IS WCVB NEWS CENTER 5.
>> INVESTIGATORS PRESS FOR
ANSWERS IN THE LAS VEGAS
SHOOTING MASSACRE
MARIA: PRESIDENT TRUMP VISITING
THE TRAUMATIZED CITY TODAY.
THE PRESIDENT AND FIRST LADY
SPEAKING TO SURVIVORS OF THE
SHOOTING AND THANKING FIRST
RESPONDERS FOR SAVING 70 LIVES.
ED: THE GIRLFRIEND OF THE GUNMAN
IS BACK TO THE UNITED STATES
BEING QUESTIONED BY THE FBI.
FAMILYMEMBERS AND HER ATTORNEY
ASSIST SHE KNEW NOTHING ABOUT
THE ATTACK -- INSIST SHE KNEW
NOTHING.
>> INVESTIGATORS ARE LOOKING TO
THE POSSIBILITY THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK LOOKED TO ATTACK ANOTHER
CONCERT ONE WEEK EARLIER.
ED: STUNNING STORIES OF
SURVIVAL.
>> A NORTH READING WOMAN SHARING
HOW A GIRLS TRIP WITH HER
FRIENDS TURNED TERRIFYING.