>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS AS WE
COME ON THE AIR.
THE VERY PUBLIC APOLOGY LATE
TODAY TO AMERICAN TAXPAYERS.
ONE OF PRESIDENT TRUMP'S TOP
CABINET OFFICIALS, TOM PRICE,
NOW APOLOGIZING FOR SPENDING
MORE THAN $400,000 ON LUXURY
JETS.
>>> THE GROWING CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO TONIGHT.
THE WHITE HOUSE NOW SENDING A
THREE-STAR ARMY GENERAL.
AND REPORTS OF THOUSANDS OF
SHIPPING CONTAINERS FILLED WITH
SUPPLIES SITTING THERE UNLOADED.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NEW TAX
PLAN.
THE WINNERS AND LOSERS.
TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE IS
PRESSED.
HOW MUCH WILL MIDDLE CLASS
AMERICANS SAVE?
AND HOW MUCH WILL WEALTHY
AMERICANS AND CORP RATE AMERICA
SAFE?
>>> THE NFL CONTROVERSY TONIGHT.
SOME FANS SETTING JERSEYS ON
FIRE.
AND THE GREEN BAY PACKERS, WHAT
THEY'RE ASKING THEIR FANS TO DO
TONIGHT.
>>> AND THE PRESIDENT LATE TODAY
SAYING TODAY, NFL OWNERS ARE
AFRAID OF THEIR OWN PLAYERS.
>>> THE CONGRESSMAN'S RETURN TO
A STANDING OVATION.
>>> AND ACTRESS JULIA
LOUIS-DREYFUS AND HER VERY
PERSONAL BATTLE REVEALED.
HER NEW MESSAGE TONIGHT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US
HERE ON A THURSDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN WITH THAT RARE AND
PUBLIC APOLOGY LATE TODAY TO THE
AMERICAN TAXPAYERS.
TOM PRICE APOLOGIZING FOR
SPENDING MONEYS OF THOUSANDS OF
DOLLARS ON LUXURY FLIGHTS.
IT WAS JUST 24 HOURS AGO WHEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ASKED IF
PRICE WOULD KEEP HIS JOB.
HE ANSWERED, "WE'LL SEE."
AND IT'S NOT JUST PRICE UNDER
SCRUTINY TONIGHT.
EPA CHIEF SCOT PRUITT UNDER FIRE
FOR SPENDING $58,000 ON CHARTER
FLIGHTS AND GOVERNMENT PLANES.
AND BIDDING A $25,000 PHONE
BOOTH IN HIS OFFICE.
AND TREASURY SECRETARY STEVE
MNUCHIN WHO REQUESTED A
GOVERNMENT PLANE FOR HIS
OVERSEAS HONEYMOON.
TONIGHT, EVEN LEADING
REPUBLICANS ON CAPITOL HILL ARE
NOW DEMANDING AN INVESTIGATION.
ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, A TOP
SENATE REPUBLICAN IS DEMANDING
ANSWERS, ASKING WHY PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S CABINET SECRETARIES ARE
FLYING ON PRIVATE JETS AND
GOVERNMENT PLANES ON THE
TAXPAYERS' DIME.
IT COMES AS HEALTH SECRETARY
TOM PRICE IS NOW APOLOGIZING FOR
TAKING MORE THAN TWO DOZEN WORK
TRIPS ON LUXURY JETS.
AFTER BEING ON THE DEFENSIVE FOR
DAYS --
>> WE HEARD THE CRITICISM, WE
HEARD THE CONCERNS AND TAKE THAT
VERY SERIOUSLY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, IN HIS
STATEMENT, PRICE ADMITS, "I WAS
NOT SENSITIVE ENOUGH TO MY
CONCERN FOR THE TAXPAYER, AND
THE TAXPAYERS WON'T PAY A DIME
FOR MY SEAT ON THOSE PLANES."
BUT PRICE SPENT MORE THAN
$400,000 IN TAXPAYER MONEY ON
THOSE FLIGHTS, AND IT TURNS OUT
HE'S ONLY REIMBURSING THE
GOVERNMENT FOR THE COST OF HIS
OWN SEAT -- $51,887.31.
PRICE IS A MULTI-MILLIONAIRE AND
HIS JOB IS NOW ON THE LINE.
>> WOULD YOU FIRE HIM, SIR?
>> WE'LL SEE.
>> Reporter: IT'S NOT JUST
PRICE.
THREE MEMBERS OF THE PRESIDENT'S
CABINET UNDER FIRE FOR EXPENSIVE
TRAVEL.
EPA DIRECTOR SCOTT PRIUTT FACING
NEW QUESTIONS ABOUT $58,000
WORTH OF FLIGHTS ON A CHARTERED
JET AND GOVERNMENT PLANES, NOT
TO MENTION HIS FREQUENT
TAXPAYER-FUNDED TRIPS HOME TO
OKLAHOMA.
TREASURY SECRETARY STEVE MNUCHIN
ALSO ACCUSED OF TAKING COSTLY
GOVERNMENT JETS OVER COMMERCIAL
FLIGHTS, LIKE THAT TRIP TO
KENTUCKY WITH HIS WIFE, WHERE
THEY VIEWED THE ECLIPSE.
IN ALL, AT LEAST $610,000 IN
TRIPS BY PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CABINET, NOW UNDER SCRUTINY.
AND TODAY, THE WHITE HOUSE UNDER
FIRE, TOO.
>> TO BE CLEAR, ALSO, THE WHITE
HOUSE DOES NOT HAVE A ROLE ON
THE FRONT END OF APPROVING
PRIVATE CHARTER FLIGHTS AT THE
AGENCIES, AND THAT'S SOMETHING
THAT WE'RE CERTAINLY LOOKING
INTO.
>> AND CECILIA VEGA JOINING US
TONIGHT FROM OUR STUDIO BACK IN
NEW YORK.
AND CECILIA, ONE TOP REPUBLICAN
IS NOW DELIVERING A STERN
WARNING TO PRESIDENT TRUMP?
>> Reporter: EXACTLY, DAVID.
THE POWERFUL CHAIRMAN, CHUCK
GRASSLEY, WROTE A LETTER TO THE
PRESIDENT, SAYING I'M URGING YOU
TO EMPHASIZE TO CABINET
SECRETARIES THE NECESSITY OF
USING REASONABLE AND COST
EFFECTIVE MODES OF TRAVEL.
DAVID?
>> Reporter: CECILIA VEGA, THANK
YOU.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE ALSO ASKED
TONIGHT ABOUT THE PRESIDENT'S
RESPONSE TO THE GROWING
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO.
TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT HAS NOW
SENT A THREE-STAR ARMY GENERAL
TO COMMAND THE RELIEF OPERATION.
AMID IMAGES OF THOUSANDS OF
CARGO CONTAINERS SITTING THERE,
FULL OF SUPPLIES, BUT NOT
DELIVERED.
MORE THAN A WEEK NOW AFTER THE
HURRICANE.
NEARLY 3.5 MILLION AMERICAN
CITIZENS LIVE ON THE ISLAND.
MILLIONS WITHOUT POWER AND
WATER.
AND TONIGHT, OUR TEAM RIGHT
HERE, FLYING TO VIEQUES.
WHAT WE HAVE NOT SEEN UNTIL
TONIGHT.
ABC'S EVA PILGRIM IS THERE
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, WE FLY TO
VIEQUES, THE ISLAND OFF THE EAST
COAST OF PUERTO RICO, FOR THE
FIRST TIME, AFTER BEING TOLD IT
WAS COMPLETELY WIPED OUT.
WE FLEW IN WITH TWO RESIDENTS
WHO ARE CONDUCTING RESCUE
MISSIONS.
THEY JUST GOT A MAN WITH A HEART
CONDITION MUCH-NEEDED HELP.
THE ISLAND, HANGING BY A THREAD.
NO POWER OR RUNNING WATER, THE
HOSPITAL DAMAGED SO BADLY
THEY'VE SET UP A TRIAGE TENT
OUTSIDE OF IT BECAUSE THEY CAN'T
TREAT PATIENTS INSIDE.
>> JUST WAITING.
WE'RE STILL WAITING.
>> Reporter: A DOCTOR TELLING ME
FEMA'S ONLY BROUGHT THEM WATER
SO FAR.
THIS IS WHAT'S LEFT OF SOMEONE'S
HOME.
YOU CAN SEE THE WINDOWS
COMPLETELY BLOWN OUT.
THE CONCERN NOW?
LOOTERS.
SOMEONE WRITING "KEEP OUT" ON
THEIR HOME.
ACROSS THE U.S. TERRITORY, THE
RACE TO GET THE MOST BASIC OF
NEEDS TO THE PEOPLE MORE URGENT
THAN EVER, BUT IMAGES LIKE
THESE, THOUSANDS OF COMMERCIAL
SHIPPING CONTAINERS SITTING IN
PORT, ARE RAISING QUESTIONS
ABOUT HOW QUICKLY MUCH-NEEDED
SUPPLIES CAN BE DISTRIBUTED.
LATE TODAY, THE WHITE HOUSE,
DEFENDING THE GOVERNMENT'S
RESPONSE.
>> WE HAD PROVIDED AS MANY
COMMODITIES AS WERE NECESSARY TO
THE ISLAND.
THE CHALLENGE BECAME, THEN,
LAND-BASED DISTRIBUTION.
THAT REMAINS THE CHALLENGE.
THAT REMAINS THE PRIORITY TODAY.
>> Reporter: AND TONIGHT, A KEY
REPUBLICAN, SENATOR MARCO RUBIO,
WHO VISITED THE ISLAND THIS
WEEK, WRITING AN URGENT LETTER
TO THE PRESIDENT.
"THERE IS NO CLEAR COMMAND,
CONTROL AND COMMUNICATION
BETWEEN LOCAL 0 FIRMS AND THE
GROUND AND FEDERAL AGENCIES."
BACK IN VIEQUES, WE HELPED
JUNE LANDRUM FINALLY GET THROUGH
TO HER LOVED ONES.
>> HEY, DAVID.
IT'S YOUR MOM.
>> Reporter: AFTER EIGHT DAYS,
FIRST, RELIEF --
>> I JUST WANT YOU TO KNOW,
EVERYTHING'S FINE.
>> Reporter: THEN, OVERCOME WITH
EMOTION.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AND EVA IS BACK WITH US FROM
SAN JUAN AGAIN TONIGHT.
AND EVA, JUST INCREDIBLE
PICTURES THERE.
I WANT TO GO BACK TO THE
SHIPPING CONTAINERS, THE
SUPPLIES THAT NEED TO GET TO THE
PEOPLE.
AND IS THE PRESIDENT STILL
PLANNING TO TRAVEL THERE NEXT
TUESDAY?
>> Reporter: WELL, DAVID, FEMA
SAMES THOSE CONTAINERS ARE
COMMERCIAL SHIPPING CONTAINERS
FOR GROCERY STORES AND BIG BOX
STORES, NOT FEMA'S.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS THE PLAN IS
STILL FOR THE PRESIDENT TO VISIT
ON TUESDAY, UNLESS THEY HEAR
THAT A VISIT WOULD BE COUNTER
PRODUCTIVE.
THEN, THE PLAN COULD CHANGE.
DAVID?
>> EVA PILGRIM AND OUR TEAM ON
THE GROUND IN PUERTO RICO AGAIN
TONIGHT.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S NEW TAX PLAN, PROMISING
A MIDDLE CLASS MIRACLE.
HOW MUCH WILL MIDDLE CLASS
AMERICANS SEE?
AND HOW MUCH WILL WEALTHY
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL.
>> Reporter: THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY CLAIMED PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
TAX PLAN COULD SAVE THE AVERAGE
AMERICAN FAMILY UP TO $1,000 A
YEAR.
>> IF WE ALLOW A FAMILY TO KEEP
ANOTHER 1,000 DISEASE OF THEIR
NEXT, WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
THEY CAN RENOVATE THEIR KITCHEN,
THEY CAN BUY A NEW CAR, THEY CAN
TAKE A FAMILY VACATION.
>> Reporter: BUT THE DETAILS ARE
STILL SKETCHY, AND THE
PRESIDENT'S TOP ECONOMIC ADVISER
TODAY COULDN'T GUARANTEE THAT
EVERY MIDDLE CLASS FAMILY WOULD
BENEFIT.
>> I GUARANTEE YOU -- I'LL
GUARANTEE YOU, YOU CAN FIND
SOMEONE IN THIS COUNTRY, MAYBE
ONE PERSON WHO THEIR TAXES MAY
NOT GO DOWN.
>> Reporter: ON "GMA," COHN SAID
THE PLAN WON'T SAVE THE
WEALTHIEST AMERICANS ANYTHING AT
ALL.
>> THE WEALTHY ARE NOT GETTING A
TAX CUT UNDER OUR PLAN.
>> Reporter: BUT THAT DOESN'T
APPEAR TO BE TRUE.
FOR ONE, THE PLAN ELIMINATES THE
ESTATE TAX.
SOMETHING THAT IS ONLY PAID ON
ESTATES VALUED AT MORE THAN $5.5
MILLION FOR INDIVIDUALS, $1
MILLION FOR COUPLES.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS IT'S ABOUT
HELPING FARMERS AND SMALL
BUSINESS OWNERS.
>> THE FARMERS, IN PARTICULAR,
ARE AFFECTED.
THEY HAVE WONDERFUL FARMS, BUT
THEY CAN'T PAY THE TAX, SO THEY
HAVE TO SELL THE FARM.
>> Reporter: BUT ACCORDING TO
THE TAX POLICY CENTER, A GRAND
TOTAL OF ABOUT 5,500 ESTATES
WILL BE BIG ENOUGH TO OWE TAX
THIS YEAR, AND OF THOSE, ONLY
80 ARE SMALL FARMS OR
CLOSELY-HELD BUSINESS.
ONE FAMILY THAT WOULD CERTAINLY
BENEFIT?
THE TRUMPS, EVEN THOUGH THE
PRESIDENT INSISTS HIS PLAN WON'T
CUT HIS OWN TAXES.
>> I'M DOING THE RIGHT THING AND
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR ME.
BELIEVE ME.
>> Reporter: BUT TODAY, COHN
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS RESPECT
BUYING.
THEY SAY, POINT BLANK, WE'RE NOT
GOING TO DO A TAX PLAN THAT'S
GOING TO BENEFIT THE WEALTHY.
>> AGAIN, WHEN WE SEE MORE,
YOU'LL KNOW MORE OF THE FACTS.
>> JON KARL WITH US LIVE FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT.
AND JON, WE HEARD THE
PRESIDENT'S TOP ECONOMIC ADVISER
SAYING TODAY THAT THE AVERAGE
AMERICAN FAMILY WOULD SAVE UP TO
$1,000.
BUT THIS PLAN ALSO INCLUDES A
PRETTY HUGE TAX BREAK FOR
CORPORATIONS.
>> Reporter: WELL, THE WHITE
HOUSE BELIEVES THAT CUTTING THE
TAXES ON CORPORATIONS WILL BE A
BIG BOOST TO THE ECONOMY.
AS IT STANDS NOW, DAVID, THE
UNITED STATES HAS ONE OF THE
HIGHEST CORPORATE TAX RATES IN
THE ENTIRE WORLD.
>> JON KARL AT THE WHITE HOUSE
TONIGHT.
JON, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT HERE TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP VERSUS THE NFL.
TODAY, THE PRESIDENT WEIGHING IN
AGAIN ON THIS, SAYING NFL TEAM
OWNERS ARE, QUOTE, AFRAID OF
THEIR PLAYERS.
AND NOW, THE BIG PACKERS GAME
TONIGHT, AND WHAT THE TEAM IS
NOW ASKING FANS IN THE STADIUM
TO DO THIS EVENING.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, GREEN BAY
FANS EXPRESSING OUTRAGE.
>> I'M OUT, AS A PACKERS FAN,
AND I'VE BEEN ONE FOR 44 YEARS.
>> Reporter: SOME SAY THEY ARE
CHEESEHEADS NO MORE, BURNING
TEAM GEAR.
>> YOU WILL NEVER GET A CENT
FROM ME OR MY FAMILY EVER AGAIN.
>> Reporter: THIS MAN USED A
BLOW TORCH EMBLAZONED WITH A
TRUMP STICKER.
THIS, AFTER THE TEAM ASKED THEIR
FANS TO JOIN THEM, BY LOCKING
ARMS IN THE STANDS AT TONIGHT'S
GAME DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
AARON RODGERS AND THE PACKERS
LINKED ARMS AS MOST TEAMS DID
LAST SUNDAY, PROTESTING SOCIAL
INJUSTICE.
>> THIS IS ABOUT UNITY AND LOVE
AND GROWING TOGETHER AS A
SOCIETY.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING,
PRESIDENT TRUMP POURED FUEL ON A
FIRE MANY SAY HE STARTED, WITH
NEW COMMENTS ABOUT TEAM OWNERS.
>> THEY SAY, WE ARE IN A
SITUATION WHERE WE HAVE TO DO
SOMETHING.
I THINK THEY'RE AFRAID OF THEIR
PLAYERS.
>> Reporter: BACKLASH ON SOCIAL
MEDIA WAS SWIFT, SOME CALLING
TRUMP'S COMMENTS RACIST.
"IF HE THINKS THE NFL IS SOME
SORT OF PLANTATION, HE IS SADLY
MISTAKEN.
FOOTBALL IS ABOUT THE PLAYERS."
TONIGHT, A TENNESSEE BUSINESSMAN
IS PULLING ADVERTISING FROM NFL
GAMES IN 30 MARKETS.
DAVID?
>> LINSEY DAVIS AGAIN TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO AN
EXTRAORDINARY MOMENT ON CAPITOL
HILL TODAY.HOMECOMING OF SORTS.
THE CONGRESSMAN SHOT AT THAT
BASEBALL PRACTICE, AND WE ONLY
LEARNED IT WAS FAR MORE SERIOUS
THAN WE THOUGHT, IN THE WEEKS
AFTERWARD.
WELL, TODAY REPRESENTATIVE STEVE
SCALISE RETURNING FOR THE FIRST
TIME.
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS ON
THEIR FEET, A RESOUNDING
OVATION, AND SOME VERY EMOTIONAL
MOMENTS, AS HE SINGLED OUT THE
HEROES, RIGHT THERE IN THE
CHAMBER.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE, BACK ON THE
HILL TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THE MOMENT
STEVE SCALISE CAME AROUND THE
CORNER, HIS COLLEAGUES CAME TO
THEIR FEET, WELCOMING HIM BACK
TO FLOOR WITH THUNDEROUS
APPLAU
APPLAUSE.
>> FOR WHAT PURPOSE DOES THE
GENTLEMAN FROM LOUISIANA SEEK
RECOGNITION?
>> TO SPEAK OUT OF ORDER, MR.
SPEAKER.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN THREE
MONTHS DAYS SINCE HE WAS GUNNED
DOWN ON THAT VIRGINIA BASEBALL
FIELD.
>> SO, I'M DEFINITELY A LIVING
EXAMPLE THAT MIRACLES REALLY DO
HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: THANKING THE
CAPITOL POLICE OFFERS HE CALLS
HIS ANGELS.
CRYSTAL GRINER AND DAVID BAILEY,
WHO WAS THERE TODAY.
>> DAVID, YOU ARE MY HERO, YOU
SAVED MY LIFE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Reporter: ALSO ON THE FIELD,
CONGRESSMAN AND DOCTOR BRAD
WENSTRUP.
>> THE TOURNIQUET HE APPLIED,
MANY WILL TELL YOU, SAVED MY
LIFE, SO, BRAD WHERE, ARE YOU
AT?
RIGHT DOWN FRONT.
>> Reporter: AND FOR THE
COLLEAGUES WHO WERE THERE WHEN
HE NEEDED THEM MOST --
>> BOTH REPUBLICAN AND DEMOCRAT
REACHED OUT IN WAYS THAT I CAN'T
EXPRESS THE GRATITUDE IN HOW
MUCH IT MEANS TO ME.
>> Reporter: AS HE WALKED OFF
THE FLOOR, THE PUBLIC WAITING --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WHAT'S IT LIKE TO BE BACK ON THE
FLOOR?
>> IT FELT INCREDIBLE TO BE BACK
IN THE HOUSE CHAMBER, AND
VOTING, AND BACK TO MY NORMAL
JOB.
>> Reporter: IT WAS QUITE A
MOMENT.
>> I FEEL GREAT, I FEEL GREAT.
>> Reporter: THE CONGRESSMAN,
BACK HOME AND TRIUMPHANT.
>> REALLY POWERFUL MOMENT OF
UNITY TODAY THERE ON THE HILL.
AND MARY BRUCE JOINS US LIVE
FROM THE CAPITOL.
THE CONGRESSMAN, NOW BACK TO
WORK FULL TIME?
>> Reporter: YEAH, DAVID.
SCALISE IS NOW BACK ON THE HILL
FULL TIME.
BUT LAWMAKERS TELL ME, HE'S
ALREADY BEEN WORKING FOR WEEKS,
BEHIND THE SCENES, ON THE PHONE,
KEEPING UP WITH ALL THE ACTIVITY
HERE.
DAVID?
>> GREAT TO SEE STEVE SCALISE
BACK TONIGHT.
MARY BRUCE, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT TO THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION ON CAPITOL HILL.
WE TOLD YOU HERE LAST NIGHT THAT
FACEBOOK ADMITTED THEY SOLD ADS
TO RUSSIAN COMPANIES, POSING AS
AMERICANS.
AT LEAST 300,000 ADS.
TONIGHT, TWITTER IS REVEALING
THEY DID THE SAME.
IDENTIFYING 200 TWITTER ACCOUNTS
THAT SPREAD MISINFORMATION.
ONE RUSSIAN COMPANY SPENDING
$274,000 FOR ADS AIMED AT SWING
STATES TO HELP SEW DOUBTS ABOUT
HILLARY CLINTON AND HELP DONALD
TRUMP GET ELECTED.
>>> NEXT HERE TONIGHT,
REMEMBERING HOUREMEMBER
ING HUGH HEFNER HE WAS ADMIRED
BY SO MANY.
REVILED BY OTHERS.
BUT HE DID MAKE HIS MARK.
ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN, RIGHT
HERE IN LOS ANGELES TONIGHT.
>> I'M HUGH HEFNER, EDITOR AND
PUBLISHER OF "PLAYBOY" MAGAZINE.
>> Reporter: FROM THAT HAREM OF
GIRLS, TO THE SMOKING JACKET,
AND THE POLARIZING PRODUCT HE
CREATED --
>> "PLAYBOY" EXPLOITS SEX LIKE
"SPORTS ILLUSTRATED" EXPLOITS
SPORTS.
>> Reporter: HUGH HEFNER WASN'T
ALWAYS BELOVED, BUT HE WAS
ALWAYS NOTICED.
LATE WEDNESDAY, HIS ESTATE
ANNOUNCED HE DIED IN HIS SLEEP
AT THE PLAYBOY MANSION.
THE SON TO TWO DEVOUT SCHOOL
TEACHERS, HEFNER FIRST PUBLISHED
"PLAYBOY" IN CONSERVATIVE 1953.
ON THAT COVER, MARLILYN MONROE.
BY THE 1970s, IT WAS SELLING A
MILLION COPIES A MONTH.
A PAGEANT OF AMERICAN WOMEN
POSED FROM SHARON STONE,
KIM BASINGER, CINDY CRAWFORD,
AND DREW BARRYMORE.
"PLAYBOY" TOOK FLAK FROM BOTH
CONSERVATIVES AND FEMINISTS,
MOST THEM MORE BLY IN THIS 1988
SPARRING SESSION
BETWEEN GLORIA STEINEM,
PUBLISHER OF "MS." AND HEFNER,
35 YEARS AFTER SHE WENT
UNDERCOVER AS A PLAYBOY BUNNY.
>> I DO NOT FIND THE BODY OF
WORK ADMIRABLE AT ALL.
I THINK IT'S PART OF THE
PROBLEM, NOT PART OF THE
SOLUTION.
>> WE DO KNOW IN NATURE AT EVERY
KIND OF LEVEL THERE IS THE
PURSUER AND THE PURSUED.
>> THAT'S JUST NOT TRUE.
>> Reporter: INDEED HEFNER
RECENTLY SAID HE WANTED TO BE
REMEMBERED AS A TRAILBLAZER OF
SEXUALITY.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO BE REMEMBERED
AS SOMEBODY WHO PLAYED SOME
POSITIVE PART IN CHANGING THE
SOCIAL SEXUAL VALUES OF MY TIME.
>> Reporter: DAVID, HEFNER'S
ESTATE SAYS IT HASIBLE
FORMALIZED EITHER FOR A MEMORIAL
OR A FUNERAL SERVICE, BUT WE DO
KNOW THAT HEFNER OWNS A CEMETERY
PLOT NOT FAR FROM HERE, RIGHT
NEXT TO MARILYN MONROE.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN HERE IN
CALIFORNIA TONIGHT.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS THURSDAY.
THE HEADLINE ABOUT THE DEADLY
ROCKSLIDE AT YOSEMITE HERE IN
CALIFORNIA.
>>> ALSO, THE MAJOR HEADLINE
INVOLVING JULIE LOUIS-DREYFUS,
REVEALING HER PERSONAL BATTLE.
THE NEWS SHE LEARNED, THE DAY
AFTER HER RECORD EMMY WIN, JUST
A COUPLE OF DAYS BACK, AND HER
NEW MESSAGE, RIGHT HERE TONIGHT.
>>> ALSO, NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN
THE UNSOLVED MURDER OF TWO YOUNG
GIRLS, KILLED WHILE HIKING.
THE PICTURE THEY TOOK OF THE
SUSPECT, AND THE POSSIBLE BREAK
IN THE CASE TONIGHT.
>>> AND THEN, PRINCE HARRY AND
THE LITTLE GIRL IN THE STANDS,
THE TINY THIEF HE CAUGHT
RED-HANDED, AND HIS REACTION
TONIGHT.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
Medicare only covers about 80%
of your Part B medical expenses.
The rest is up to you.
So think about an AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like any standardized Medicare
Supplement insurance plans,
they help cover some of what
Medicare doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide and learn more.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
After a DVT blood clot...
I sure had a lot on my mind.
My 30-year marriage...
...my 3-month old business...
Plus...what if this
happened again?
I was given warfarin
in the hospital,
but wondered, was this
the best treatment for me?
So I made a point to
talk to my doctor.
He told me about ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots
and reduces the risk
of them happening again.
Not only does ELIQUIS treat
DVT and PE blood clots.
ELIQUIS also had
significantly less
major bleeding
than the standard
treatment.
ELIQUIS
had both...
...and that
turned around my
thinking.
Don't stop ELIQUIS unless
your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal
injection while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling,
numbness, or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
and it may take longer than
usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about
all planned medical
or dental procedures.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots.
Plus had less
major bleeding.
Both made ELIQUIS
right for me.
Ask your doctor if switching
to ELIQUIS is right for you.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, THE EMMY
AWARD WINNING ACTRESS AND HER
VERY PERSONAL BATTLE.
YOU LA LOUIS-DREYFUS ANNOUNCING
SHE HAS BREAST CANCER.
HERE'S ABC'S LINZIE JANIS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
JULIA LOUIS-DREYFUS REVEALING
HER DIAGNOSIS, TWEETING, "1 IN 8
WOMEN GET BREAST CANCER.
TODAY, I AM THE ONE."
>> JEWEL LA LOUIS-DREYFUS.
>> Reporter: THE 56-YEAR-OLD
ACTRESS GETTING THE NEWS THE DAY
AFTER WINNING A RECORD-BREAKING
SIXTH CONSECUTIVE EMMY FOR HER
ROLE IN "VEEP."
>> I AM STILL A YOUNG WOMAN.
>> YES.
>> REALLY, LOOK AT MY HANDS.
>> GORGEOUS.
>> LOOK AT MY NECK.
>> OH.
>> Reprorter: THE STAR ALSO
WADING INTO THE HEALTH CARE
DEBATE, SAYING, "I HAVE
FANTASTIC INSURANCE THROUGH MY
UNION, BUT NOT ALL WOMEN ARE SO
LUCKY.
SO, LET'S FIGHT ALL
CANCERS AND MAKE UNIVERSAL
HEALTH CARE A REALITY."
THE ACTRESS HAS TWO SONS WITH
HER HIS OF 30 YEARS.
WRITER/DIRECTOR BRAD HALL.
TONIGHT, SUPPORT POURING IN.
BREAST CANCER SURVIVORS LIKE
ACTRESS CHRISTINA APPLEGATE
TWEETING, "MAMA, FIND ME.
LET'S TALK IF YOU WANT."
AND RITA WILSON WRITING, "GOD
BLESS YOU.
STAY STRONG."
DAVID, HBO HAS EXPRESSED ITS
SUPPORT, SAYING "VEEP" WILL
ADJUST ITS PRODUCTION SCHEDULE
FOR HER TREATMENTS IF NECESSARY.
DAVID?
>> LINZIE JANIS WITH US TONIGHT.
LINZIE, THANK YOU.
>>> AND THE FORMER VICE
PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN JUST
TWEETING MOMENTS AGO, HIS BEST
SWISHI
WISHING, SAYING, "WE VPs STAY ON
THE."
>>> STILL TO COME, THE MYSTERY
DEATHS OF TWO YOUNG GIRLS WHILE
HIKING.
POLICE REVEALING A POSSIBLE
BREAK IN THE INVESTIGATION.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I take pictures of sunrises,
but with my back pain
I couldn't sleep
and get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
With my moderate to severe
Crohn's disease,...
.ways to manage my symptoms.r
I thought I had it covered.
Then I realized managing was
all I was doing.
When I finally told my doctor,
he said HUMIRA was for people
like me
who have tried other
medications,...
but still experience the
symptoms
of moderate to severe
Crohn's disease.
In clinical studies,
the majority of patients
on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom
relief...
...and many achieved remission.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections...
...including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,...
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,...
...and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested
for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,...
...hepatitis B, are prone to
infections,
...or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
If you're still just managing
your symptoms,
ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA, remission
is possible.
>>> TO THE INDEX OF OTHER NEWS
TONIGHT.
AND THE DEADLY ROCK SLIDE AT
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK HERE IN
CALIFORNIA.
THE PARK SERVICE NOW SAYING ONE
BRITISH TOURIST WAS KILLED, AND
ANOTHER INJURED, WHEN A SHEET OF
GRANITE 130 FEET TALL AND 65
FEET WIDE DROPPED FROM EL
CAPITAN.
SEVEN ROCK FALLS, 1,300 TONS IN
A FOUR-HOUR SPAN.
>>> A POSSIBLE BREAK TONIGHT IN
THE UNSOLVE MURDER IN DELPHI,
INDIANA.
TWO TENGERS WERE KILLED WHILE
HIKING IN FEBRUARY.
AUTHORITIES NOW SAY THEY TOOK A
PICTURE OF THE SUSPECT AND
RECORDED HIS VOICE.
POLICE IN COLORADO WITH A PERSON
OF INTEREST IN CUSTODY, AN
INDIANA SEX OFFENDER ACCUSED OF
THREATENING HIKERS THERE.
>>> AND PASS THE POPCORN
TONIGHT.
PRINCE HARRY MAKING A NEW
FRIEND, RIGHT THERE IN THE
STANDS AT THE INVICTUS GAMES.
EMILY HENSON CAUGHT RED-HANDED,
TRYING TO STEAL HIS POPCORN.
HARRY PLAYING ALONG WITH A NEW
FRIEND THAT HE MADE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK ON A
THURSDAY NIGHT, WITH SO MANY
NATURAL DISASTERS, WE HAVE
PROMISED TO GO BACK, AND
TONIGHT, THE REMARKABLE HEADLINE
OUT OF HOUSTON.
THE TEARS.
YOU HAVE TO SEE THIS.
Needles.
Essential for vinyl,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and further
joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma
and other cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Tears in the stomach
or intestines,
low blood cell counts
and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels
have happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you start
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you
were in a region
where fungal infections
are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
A must for vinyl.
But for you,
one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
Rethink what's possible.
Rethink your allergy pills.
Flonase Sensimist Allergy Relief
helps block 6 key
inflammatory
substances
with a
gentle mist.
Most allergy
pills
only block
one.
And 6 is greater
than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
♪
Us.
It's what this country
is made of.
But right now,
our bond is fraying.
How do we get back to "us"?
The Y fills the gaps.
And bridges our divides.
Support to your local Y today.
Because where there's a Y,
there's an us.
Americans,
83% try to eat healthy,
yet up to 90% fall short
on getting key nutrients.
Let's do more.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
Complete with 100% daily value
of more than 15 key nutrients.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
If you've been struggling
with belly pain
and you're overwhelmed
by everything you've tried--
all those laxatives,
daily probiotics,
endless fiber--
it could be wearing on you.
Tell your doctor
what you've tried,
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults
with IBS
with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help relieve
your belly pain
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.
Do not give LINZESS
to children less than six
and it should not be given
to children
six to less than eighteen.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS
if you have a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop
unusual or severe
stomach pain,
especially with
bloody or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe,
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor
right away.
Other side effects
include gas,
stomach-area pain
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
AMERICA STRONG, HOUSTON STRONG.
THE ROOKIE FOOTBALL STAR, HIS
FIRST CHECK AFTER AN NFL GAME --
AND WHO HE GAVE IT TO.
IT'S BEEN ONE MONTH SINCE
HURRICANE HARVEY RAVAGED
HOUSTON.
ONE MONTH OF ACTS OF KINDNESS,
NEIGHBORS HELPING NEIGHBORS.
DESHAUN WATSON, THE 22-YEAR-OLD
HOUSTON TEXANS ROOKIE
QUARTERBACK NOW AMONG THEM.
>> I'M EXCITED TO DO A LITTLE
SURPRISE FOR THE CAFETERIA
LADIES THAT'S BEEN HELPFUL FOR
ALL OF US, SO -- IT'S GOING TO
BE COOL.
>> Reporter: WALKING INTO THE
STADIUM'S CAFETERIA WITH A
SURPRISE FOR THREE OF THE
WORKERS THERE, WHOSE HOMES WERE
DAMAGED BY HARVEY.
>> WHAT Y'ALL DO FOR US EVERY
DAY AND NEVER COMPLAIN.
I REALLY APPRECIATE Y'ALL.
SO, I WANTED TO GIVE MY FIRST
GAME CHECK TO Y'ALL TO HELP
Y'ALL OUT.
SOME TYPE OF WAY, SO -- HERE YOU
GUYS GO.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> Reporter: HE GAVE THEM HIS
FIRST NFL GAME CHECK.
THE WORKERS, GRATEFUL.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Reporter: AS A BOY, DESHAUN
WATSON AND HIS MOTHER BUILT I
MOVED INTO A HOME BY HABITAT FOR
HUMANITY.
>> I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
THIS IS WCVB NEWSCENTER 5 AT
7:00.
>> TONIGHT UPSET OVER NEW
, ENGLAND PATRIOTS PLAYERS
TAKING A KNEE DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM, A SOUTH COAST
MAN IS HOLDING A JERSEY BURNING
CEREMONY.
THANKS FOR JOINING US, I'M MARIA
STEPHANOS.
NICHOLE: I'M NICHOLE BERLIE IN
FOR ED.
IT'S THE LATEST FALLOUT SINCE
PRESIDENT TRUMP CALLED-OUT THE
NFL A WEEK AGO.
OUR DIANE CHO IS LIVE IN SWANSEA
WITH OUR TOP STORY.
DIANE.
REPORTER: YOU CAN SEE THE CROWDS
ARE GATHERING.
MANY PEOPLE HERE ARE SITTING
DOWN HOLDING AMERICAN LACK --
FLAGS NEAR THE BONFIRE.
POLICE ARE GATHERING HERE WITH A
PROTEST IS SCHEDULED TO TAKE
PLACE.
HE SAYS HE IS EXPECTING HUNDREDS
TO TURN OUT, BUT NOW HE SAYS HE
DOESN'T KNOW HOW MANY