Join us r good.
>>> TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT
RESPONDS.
WHEN ASKED, HAS HE DONE ENOUGH
FOR PUERTO RICO.
THE GOVERNOR THERE SAYING THEY
FACE A HUMANITARIAN DISASTER.
NEARLY 3.5 MILLION AMERICAN
CITIZENS.
CRITICS SAYING THE PRESIDENT
TWEETED ABOUT THE NFL ALL
WEEKEND, NOT PUERTO RICO.
AND WHEN HE DID FINALLY TWEET,
WAS HE COMPASSIONATE OR DID HE
TAKE ON PUERTO RICO FOR ITS
PROBLEMS?
>>> THE BATTLE WITH THE NFL
TONIGHT.
THE SHOW OF UNITY, WITH JERRY
JONES AND THE COWBOYS.
AND THE CARDINALS.
THE BOOS FROM THE STANDS.
NOW, THE PRESIDENT TONIGHT
SAYING THERE SHOULD BE A NEW
RULE FOR NFL PLAYERS.
>>> THE PLAN TO KILL OBAMACARE.
THE EFFORT IS DEAD TONIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT ANGRY.
THERE WILL BE NO VOTE.
SUSAN COLLINS AND LISA MURKOWSKI
REVEALING TONIGHT WHY THEY WERE
NOT CONVINCED.
>>> THE FBI ARRESTS TONIGHT.
FOUR COACHES IN THE NCAA, BIG
NAME SCHOOLS.
AND WHAT THEY'RE ACCUSED OF.
>>> AND WE HAVE NEWS ON O.J.
SIMPSON TONIGHT.
SET TO GO FREE IN JUST DAYS.
WHAT THE PAPERWORK REVEALS.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A TUESDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN WITH WHAT
AUTHORITIES ARE CALLING A
HUMANITARIAN DISASTER IN PUERTO
RICO.
MORE THAN 3 MILLION AMERICAN
CITIZENS LIVE THERE.
AND TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT IS
ASKED, WAS HE PREOCCUPIED WITH
THE NFL AND HIS TWEETS?
THE PRESIDENT TWEETING 24 TIMES
ABOUT THE NFL, BUT HE DID NOT
TWEET ABOUT PUERTO RICO OVER THE
WEEKEND.
TONIGHT, HE'S DEFENDING HIMSELF,
AND THE WHITE HOUSE RELEASING
THIS PHOTO OF A MEETING IN THE
SITUATION ROOM, TO SIGNAL THEY
ARE DOING ALL THEY CAN.
TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT PLANS TO
NOW VISIT PUERTO RICO.
AND ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP IN
THE ROSE GARDEN TODAY WITH A
MESSAGE FOR PUERTO RICO.
>> WE WILL GET THROUGH THIS AND
WE WILL GET THROUGH IT TOGETHER.
>> Reporter: AND THE GROUND,
TOTAL DEVASTATION.
NEARLY THE ENTIRE ISLAND STILL
WITHOUT POWER.
MORE THAN HALF OF IT WITHOUT
WATER.
BUT MANY SAY, UNTIL NOW, HIS
THE PRESIDENT'S PUBLIC RESPONSE
HAS BEEN SUBDUED.
OVERNIGHT, IN A SERIES OF
TWEETS, PRESIDENT TRUMP
EMPHASIZED PUERTO RICO'S MASSIVE
DEBT, SAYING IT OLS "BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS TO WALL STREET AND THE
BANKS, WHICH SADLY, MUST BE
DEALT WITH."
AMONG THOSE WHO CALLED HIM OUT,
THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN, WHO SAID,
"YOU DON'T PUT DEBT ABOVE
PEOPLE, YOU PUT PEOPLE ABOVE
DEBT."
NEW YORK CONGRESSWOMAN
NYDIA VELAZQUEZ GOING EVEN
FURTHER.
>> THIS IS GOING TO TURN TO BE
MR. TRUMP'S KATRINA.
>> Reporter: AND TODAY, WE PUT
THE QUESTION TO THE PRESIDENT.
IS PUERTO RICO GETTING ALL THE
HELP IT NEEDS FROM YOU, MR.
PRESIDENT?
>> PUERTO RICO IS VERY IMPORTANT
TO ME, AND PUERTO RICO, THE
PEOPLE ARE FANTASTIC PEOPLE.
I GREW UP IN NEW YORK, SO I KNOW
MANY PEOPLE FROM PUERTO RICO.
I KNOW MANY PUERTO RICANS.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT
HIGHLIGHTING THE PRAISE HE'S
RECEIVED.
>> IT'S THE MOST DIFFICULT JOB,
BECAUSE IT'S ON AN ISLAND IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE OCEAN.
IT'S OUT IN THE OCEAN.
YOU CAN'T JUST DRIVE YOUR TRUCKS
THERE FROM OTHER STATES.
AND THE GOVERNOR SAID, WE ARE
DOING A GREAT JOB.
>> Reporter: WHILE BRUSHING OFF
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER HE'S
BEEN PREOCCUPIED BY HIS BATTLE
WITH THE NFL.
>> WAS I PREOCCUPIED?
NOT AT ALL.
I HAVE PLENTY OF TIME ON MY
HANDS.
ALL I DO IS WORK.
>> Reporter: AND TODAY, THE
WHITE HOUSE RELEASED THESE
PHOTOS TO SHOW IT.
THE PRESIDENT IN THE SITUATION
ROOM, BEING BRIEFED ON PUERTO
RICO.
>> SO, LET'S GET TO CECILIA
VEGA, LIVE AT THE WHITE HOUSE
TONIGHT.
AND CECILIA, THE PRESIDENT
ANNOUNCING HE WILL NOW TRAVEL TO
PUERTO RICO?
>> Reporter: HE SAYS HAD WILL GO
THERE ON TUESDAY, BUT ALSO
HEADED TO PUERTO RICO, THE U.S.
NAVY SHIP COMFORT.
IT'S A MEDICAL SHIP WITH AS MANY
AS 1,200 ACTIVE DUTY AND
REEVERYONE IS ON IT.
IT WILL TAKE ABOUT A WEEK BEFORE
IT ARRIVES.
>> A WEEK.
CECILIA VEGA, THANK YOU.
>>> OUR CORRESPONDENT IN PUERTO
RICO TONIGHT, ASKING THE MAYOR
OF SAN JUAN IF SHE HAS A MESSAGE
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP, AND SHE
DID.
WHAT ELSE WE FOUND THERE, A
RETIREMENT HOME WITH RESIDENTS
TRAPPED AT THE TOP OF THE
BUILDING.
NO RUNNING WATER, NO
ELECTRICITY, IN SWELTERING HEAT.
ABC'S EVA PILGRIM FROM SAN JUAN
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, AT THIS
SWELTERING 14-STORY RETIREMENT
HOME IN SAN JUAN --
>> WE'RE GOING DOOR TO DOOR
TO DOOR, DOING A SEARCH.
>> Reporter: THERE'S NO RUNNING
WATER.
THE ONLY WAY OUT FOR THE ELDERLY
RESIDENTS?
THESE STAIRS.
>> WHAT CAN I DO?
LEAVE THEM HERE?
>> Reporter: HERE WE MEET
LISBETH VASQUEZ, TRYING TO CARE
FOR HER PARENTS.
>> I CAN'T WALK TOO MUCH.
>> Reporter: WHO DESPERATELY
NEED MEDICINE.
THEY WERE JUST TREATED FOR
DEHYDRATION.
>> IF I WOULD HAVE NOT TAKEN
THEM TO THE HOSPITAL, THEY
WOULD'VE BEEN DEAD.
>> Reporter: HUNDREDS AT THE
AIRPORT.
SUSANA GARNER HAS BEEN HERE FOR
TWO DAYS, TRYING TO GET OUT.
>> I HAVE HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
AND I'M NOT SUPPOSED TO BE IN
THIS HEAT AND IT'S NOT GOOD.
>> Reporter: SIX DAYS SINCE THE
CATEGORY 4 STORM MADE LANDFALL
ON THE U.S. TERRITORY, 95% OF
THE ISLAND HAS NO POWER.
LONG LINES FOR GAS.
ENTIRE VILLAGES AND TOWNS REMAIN
CUT OFF.
ARE YOU GETTING THE STUFF YOU
NEED FAST ENOUGH?
>> NO.
NO.
AND I'M SORRY, THAT'S NOT
POLITICALLY CORRECT TO SAY.
>> Reporter: SAN JUAN'S MAYOR
TELLING ME BUREAUCRATIC RED TAPE
IS HOLDING UP RELIEF EFFORTS.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP, PLEASE.
WHATEVER YOU NEED TO DO.
LET FEMA DO THEIR JOB.
>> AND EVA JOINS US NOW FROM SAN
JUAN.
YOU TALKED TO THE GOVERNOR OF
PUERTO RICO, AS WELL.
AND HE TOLD YOU, SUPPLIES ARE
GETTING TO PURT LEE COPE, BUT
THEY ARE HAVING TROUBLE
DISTRIBUTING THEM?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
HE SAID HE REALLY NEEDS THE
DRIVERS TO COME BACK TO WORK SO
THEY CAN DELIVER THE GOODS.
THE FUEL, THE WATER AND THE FOOD
TO PLACES IN NEED.
BUT MANY OF THOSE DRIVERS,
THEY'RE PUERTO RICANS
THEMSELVES, WHO HAVE BEEN
CLEANING UP THEIR OWN HOUSES IN
THE AFTERMATH OF THIS STORM.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, AN ISLAND
OVERWHELMED STILL.
EVA, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE WAS ONE MORE MOMENT WE
WITNESSED TODAY.
HUNDREDS OF AMERICAN MEDICAL
STUDENTS WHO ARE STILL STRANDED
ON THE ISLAND OF DOMINICA.
A FULL EIGHT DAYS AFTER THE
HURRICANE HIT.
ABC'S IAN PANNELL WITH THEM, AS
THEY TRY TO GET OUT, AND THE
U.S. MILLION TEAR, BACKED BY
SPECIAL FORCES, IS NOW SWEEPING
THAT ISLAND TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE RACE
TO RESCUE HUNDREDS OF AMERICAN
STUDENTS STRANDED ON THIS
CARIBBEAN ISLAND RAVAGED BY
HURRICANE MARIA.
SOME HAVE BEEN STRANDED FOR OVER
A WEEK, AS THE ISLAND'S
RESIDENTS FACE DIRE CONDITIONS.
THE DESTRUCTION ON THE ISLAND IS
SHOCKING.
IN PARTS, BUILDINGS HAVE JUST
BEEN COMPLETELY BLOWN AWAY.
PEOPLE ARE SHORT OF FOOD,
THEY'RE SHORT OF ELECTRICITY.
>> HAVE YOUR NUMBERS OUT.
>> Reporter: AND INTERNATIONAL
TEAM WORKING TO EVACUATE
STUDENTS FROM DOMINICA WITH
INCREDIBLE STORIES OF SURVIVAL.
>> ONE GIRL, HER ENTIRE HOUSE
WENT OUT AND SHE WAS JUST
HOLDING ONTO THE FLOORBOARDS,
LIKE, FOR THE ENTIRE STORMENT.
I SAW HER FACE AT, LIKE, 2:30 IN
THE MORNING, HER FACE WAS JUST
RED FROM THE WIND.
NOT FROM CRYING, JUST FROM THE
WIND IN HER FACE.
>> AFTER THIS WE'RE BROTHERS,
NOT FRIENDS.
YOU DON'T GO THROUGH CATASTROPHE
AND NOT HAVE FAMILY AFTERWARDS.
>> HI MOM!
>> Reporter: AND TONIGHT, ALL
THOSE STUDENTS NOW ON THEIR WAY
HOME AND TO SAFETY.
SO, ALL STUDENTS OFF THE ISLAND,
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN ALL
AMERICANS RESCUED.
U.S. SPECIAL FORCES, TOGETHER
WITH THE MILITARY, ARE SCOURING
THE ISLAND.
BUT DON'T FORGET THOSE WHO CALL
THIS HOME.
THEY HAVE NO ESCAPE PLAN.
DAVID?
>> IAN PANNELL WITH US TONIGHT.
IAN, THANK YOU.
>>> MARIA, NOW A TROPICAL STORM,
APPROACHING THE EAST COAST AT
THIS HOUR.
KICKING UP ROUGH SURF AND
DANGEROUS RIP CURRENTS FROM
FLORIDA TO MAINE OVER THE NEXT
FEW DAYS.
ITS CLOSEST POINT, NEAR NORTH
CAROLINA'S OUTER BANKS TOMORROW
MORNING.
EVACUATIONS IN PLACE.
OUR WEATHER TEAM SAYS IT COULD
BE A ROUGH NIGHT AHEAD.
WIND AND SURF, POSSIBLE RIP
CURRENTS.
THAT TRACK, MAKING A HARD RIGHT
TURN BEFORE GOING OUT TO SEA.
WE'LL CONTINUE TRACKING IT.
>>> AND IN THE WEST AT THIS
HOUR, AN EVACUATION ORDER IS
STILL IN PLACE TONIGHT, A
WILDFIRE IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA.
BURNING IN THE SANTA ANA
MOUNTAINS, GROWING TO MORE THAN
2,000 ACRES, FORCING MORE THAN
1,000 PEOPLE FROM THEIR HOMES.
FIREFIGHTERS BATTLING THROUGHOUT
THE NIGHT THERE TO SAVE THOSE
HOMES.
THE FLAMES BURNING VERY CLOSE TO
THE 91 FREEWAY.
TWO LANES HAVE BEEN CLOSED FOR
PART OF THIS DAY.
>>> TO PRESIDENT TRUMP VERSUS
THE NFL TONIGHT.
AFTER THAT SHOW OF UNITY, JERRY
JONES AND THE DALLAS COWBOYS,
LINKING ARMS WITH THE CARDINALS,
AS WELL, TONIGHT.
IT HAPPENED OVERNIGHT, THERE
WERE BOOS.
NOW, THIS EVENING, THE PRESIDENT
IS CALLING FOR A NEW RULE FOR
NFL PLAYERS.
ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN AGAIN
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, WITH SO
MUCH CROSSING HIS DESK, WITH THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS TO PUERTO
RICO TO THE SHOWDOWN WITH NORTH
KOREA, THE PRESIDENT IS BEING
ASKED ABOUT HIS FOCUS ON THE
NFL.
>> THERE'S SOME CONCERN THAT YOU
WERE PREOCCUPIED WITH THE NFL,
INSTEAD OF DEALING WITH PUERTO
RICO.
WHY ISN'T THAT A FAIR
ASSESSMENT?
>> I WASN'T PREOCCUPIED WITH THE
NFL.
I WAS ASHAMED OF WHAT WAS TAKING
PLACE.
BECAUSE, TO ME, THAT WAS A VERY
IMPORTANT MOMENT.
I DON'T THINK YOU CAN DISRESPECT
OUR COUNTRY, OUR FLAG, OUR
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> Reporter: JUST BEFORE MONDAY
NIGHT'S GAME, THE DALLAS
COWBOYS, INCLUDING ITS OWNER,
JERRY JONES, WHO HAD BEEN
CRITICAL OF PLAYERS KNEELING IN
PROTEST OF POLICE BRUTALITY,
TOOK A COLLECTIVE KNEE.
>> BOOS CAN BE HEARD.
>> Reporter: JERRY JONES, TAKING
A KNEE.
>> THAT'S AMAZING.
I'M GLAD HE DID.
>> Reporter: BOTH THE COWBOYS
AND THE CARDINALS ROSE, LINKING
ARMS DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
AT FIRST, PRESIDENT TRUMP
TWEETED THAT THE BOOING WAS THE
"LOUDEST I HAVE EVER HEARD.
GREAT ANGER."
THEN, HE SEEMED TO COMMEND THE
COME BOYS FOR POLICING THE
DIFFERENCE AND STANDING DURING
THE ANTHEM.
"BIG PROGRESS BEING MADE.
WE ALL LOVE OUR COUNTRY."
THE PROTESTS SPARKED BY THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN WORDS.
>> GET THAT SON OF A [ BLEEP ]
OFF THE FIELD RIGHT NOW.
OUT.
HE'S FIRED.
>> Reporter: A COMMENT THAT
UNITED FIGURES FROM ACROSS THE
SPORTING WORTH, ENCAPSULATED BY
THIS "SPORTS ILLUSTRATED" COVER.
DAVID, IN THE LATEST OF THE
PRESIDENT'S 24 TWEETS ON THE
TOPIC, HE TOOK IT EVEN A STEP
FURTHER, CALLING FOR A RULE THAT
YOU CAN'T KNEEL DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT HERE TO THE
NEWEST EFFORT TO KILL OBAMACARE.
IT IS DEAD ON ARRIVAL.
THERE WILL BE NO VOTE.
TONIGHT, TWO RRM SENATORS, SUSAN
COLLINS AND LISA MURKOWSKI, ON
WHY THEY WERE NOT CONVINCED.
AND EVEN AFTER JOHN McCAIN SAID
HE WOULD VOTE NO, SUPPORT FOR
HIM FROM THE SENATOR WHO HELPED
WRITE THE BILL.
MARE RIP BRUCE, BACK ON THE HILL
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
REPUBLICANS ARE CONCEDING
DEFEAT.
>> WE'VE MADE THE DECISION SINCE
WE DON'T HAVE THE VOTES, WE WILL
POSTPONE THAT VOTE.
AM I DISAPPOINTED?
ABSOLUTELY.
>> Reporter: BUT FOR MOM
SAMANTHA McGOVERN, WHO WORRIED
WHAT THIS BILL WOULD MEAN FOR
HER DAUGHTER, JOSEPHINE, RELIEF.
>> I'M MUCH HAPPIER TODAY THAN I
WAS THE LAST TIME I SAW YOU.
>> Reporter: THE FATAL BLOW
DEALT BY SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS
OF MAINE.
>> IT WAS CLEAR TO ME THAT THE
GRAHAM/CASSIDY BILL WAS NOT THE
ANSWER.
>> Reporter: HER OBJECTIONS TO
THE BILL?
THE DEEP CUTS TO MEDICAID, AND
THE CONCERN MILLIONS WOULD LOSE
COVERAGE.
LISA MORE COW SKI OF ALASKA WHO
OPPOSED THE LAST ATTEMPT --
>> I SAID IN JANUARY, WE SHOULD
NOT REPEAL WITHOUT A
REPLACEMENT.
>> Reporter: DIDN'T LIKE THE
PROCESS THIS GO-ROUND, SAYING
THE U.S. SENATE CANNOT GET THE
TEXT OF A BILL ON A SUNDAY
NIGHT, THEN PROCEED TO A VOTE
JUST DAYS LATER, WITH ONLY ONE
HEARING.
JOHN McCAIN, WHO TOOK DOWN THE
LAST GOP ATTEMPT WITH THIS
DEFIANT THUMB'S DOWN, AGREED, HE
WANTS A BIPARTISAN PROCESS.
HIS BEST FRIEND IN THE SENATE,
LINDSEY GRAHAM, WHO DRAFTED THE
BILL, HAD THIS TO SAY.
>> JOHN McCAIN CAN DO WHATEVER
DAMN WELL HE WANTS TO.
HE HAS THAT RIGHT.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT, HE
SAYS THEY HAVE TO KEEP UP THE
FIGHT.
>> WE'LL GET KILLED IF WE DON'T.
>> Reporter: YOU'LL GET KILLED
IF YOU DON'T?
>> WE'LL GET KILLED.
CAN YOU IMAGINE, IF WE JUST
DON'T FULFILL THIS PROMISE?
>> MARY BRUCE WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT FROM THE CAPITOL.
AND NOW THAT THIS NEWEST
REPUBLICAN BILL IS DEAD FOR NOW,
MARY, REPUBLICANS WILL NOW NEED
60 VOTES INSTEAD OF A SIMPLE
MAJORITY.
THAT WOULD MEAN BOTH SIDES WOULD
HAVE TO COME TOGETHER ON THIS.
>> Reporter: EXACTLY, DAVID.
AND WORD TONIGHT, BIPARTISAN
SHIP IS BACK.
SENATORS FROM BOTH SIDES OF THE
AISLE ARE HEADED BACK TO THE
NEGOTIATING TABLE TO TRYING TO
HAMMER OUT IMMEDIATE STEPS TO
STABILIZE THE MARKETS AND GIVE
AMERICANS FACING HIGH PREMIUMS
SOME RELIEF.
DAVID?
>> BAY PARTISAN SHIP IS BACK.
WE HEART YOU SAID IT, MARY.
WE'LL KEEP TRACKING THAT.
MARY, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT TO A POLITICAL
BATTLE PLAYING OUT RIGHT NOW IN
ALABAMA TONIGHT.
TWO LARGER THAN LIFE CHARACTERS
COMPETING TO BE THE REPUBLICAN
CANDIDATE FOR SENATE.
JUDGE ROY MOORE, PICKING OUT A
GUN AT LAST NIGHT'S RALLY.
HE'S BEEN ENDORSED BY STEVE
BANNON, BUT NOT THE PRESIDENT.
THE OTHER CANDIDATE, 6'9"
SENATOR LUTHER STRANGE, IS THE
PRESIDENT'S PICK.
BUT DID THE PRESIDENT SIGNAL HE
IS NOW HAVING SECOND THOUGHTS
ABOUT HIS CHOICE?
ABC'S CHIEF NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT TOM LLAMAS IS
THERE FOR US.
>> I BELIEVE IN THE SECOND
AMENDMENT.
>> Reporter: FLASHING HIS GUN ON
STAGE, AND RIDING HIS HORSE TO
THE POLLS, FORMER ALABAMA CHIEF
JUSTICE ROY MOORE IS ALSO A HERO
TO THE RELIGIOUS RIGHT.
>> CRIME, CORRUPTION,
IMMORALITY, ABORTION, SODOMY,
SEXUAL PERVERSION, SWEEP OUR
LAND.
>> Reporter: MOORE'S TOP
SUPPORTER IN THIS SENATE
PRIMARY, PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
FORMER CHIEF STRATEGIST, STEVE
BANNON.
>> HE'S A COURAGEOUS MAN, AND
MOST IMPORTANTLY, HE'S A
RIGHTEOUS MAN.
>> Reporter: BUT THE PRESIDENT
IS SUPPORTING MOORE'S OPPONENT,
SENATOR LUTHER STRANGE.
WHAT WOULD YOU TELL TRUMP
SUPPORTERS WHO ARE CONFUSED?
WHO SHOULD THEY VOTE FOR?
>> I'M JUST AN INDIVIDUAL.
I WOULD HIGHLY RECOMMEND THAT
THE FOLKS SUPPORT JUDGE MOORE.
>> Reporter: BUT THE PRESIDENT
SAYS HE'S LOYAL TO STRANGE FOR
HELPING HIM ON HEALTH CARE, EVEN
CALLING HIM BIG LUTHER.
>> MET HIM ONCE, I SAID, THAT IS
THE TALLEST HUMAN BEING I'VE
EVER SEEN.
I'M TALL.
SHOULD BE ON THE NEW YORK
KNICKS.
THEY COULD USE HIM.
SO, LUTHER, THAT'S WHAT I CALL
HIM, BIG LUTHER.
>> Reporter: STRANGE MAKING IT
CLEAR HE WILL BE IN LOCK STEP
WITH THE PRESIDENT.
>> HE KNOWS I'VE GOT HIS BACK.
>> Reporter: BUT THE PRESIDENT
ACKNOWLEDGES HE MAY BE BACKING
THE LOSER.
>> AND I MIGHT HAVE MADE A
MISTAKE.
AND I'LL BE HONEST, I MIGHT HAVE
MADE A MISTAKE.
>> SO, TOM LLAMAS WITH US FROM
ALABAMA TONIGHT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYING HE MIGHT
HAVE MADE A MISTAKE.
AND HE'S MADE IT CLEAR THAT
HE'LL CAMPAIGN FOR WHOEVER WINS
TONIGHT?
>> Reporter: HE HAS, DAVID.
MANY ARE PREDICTING THIS IS
GOING TO BE A VERY TIGHT RACE
AND THE PRESIDENT KNOWS THAT.
AND HE SAID IF JUDGE MOORE DOES
WIN, HE WILL BE BACK DOWN HERE,
QUOTE, CAMPAIGNING LIKE HELL FOR
HIM.
DAVID?
>> TOM LLAMAS WITH US TONIGHT.
TOM, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT HERE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
WARNING THAT THE U.S. IS
PREPARED TO USE, QUOTE,
DEVASTATING MILITARY ACTION
AGAINST NORTH KOREA, IF
NECESSARY, AFTER THAT NATION
THREATENED TO SHOOT DOWN U.S.
WAR PLANES.
NORTH KOREA, BACKING UP THAT
THREAT WITH A NEW PROPAGANDA
VIDEO, SIMULATING THEIR MISSILES
DESTROYING U.S. PLANES AND
SHIPS.
NORTH KOREA SAYS PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S HARSH WORDS ARE A
DECLARATION OF WAR.
>>> AND AND ANGRY RESPONSE
TONIGHT FROM THE PARENTS OF OTTO
WARMBIER, THE COLLEGE STUDENT
HELD CAPTIVE BY THE NORTH
KOREANS FOR 18 MONTHS, RETURNING
HOME IN A VEGETATIVE STATE.
HE DIED SIX DAYS LATER.
TONIGHT, FRED AND CINDY WAR
BEIER ACCUSING OF THE NORTH
KOREANS OF TORTURE, REVEALING
DETAILS OF HIS FINAL DAYS.
>> WE HEARD THIS HOWLING,
INVOLUNTARY, INHUMAN SOUND.
HE WAS STARING BLANKLY INTO
SPACE, JERKING VIOLENTLY.
HE WAS BLIND.
HE WAS DEAF.
AS WE LOOKED AT HIM AND TRIED TO
COMFORT HIM, IT LOOKED LIKE
SOMEONE HAD TAKEN A PAIR OF
PLIERS AND REARRANGED HIS BOTTOM
TEETH.
>> Reporter: U.S. DOCTORS
FINDING NO EVIDENCE HE HAD
CONTRACTED BOTULISM, AS THE
NORTH KOREANS HAD CLAIMED.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS TUESDAY.
THE PLACE WHERE WOMEN WILL
FINALLY BE ALLOWED TO DRIVE.
THE GLOBAL HEADLINE TONIGHT.
>>> ALSO BREAKING THIS EVENING,
FOUR COACHES IN THE NCAA
ARRESTED BY THE FBI, ALL FROM
BIG NAME SCHOOLS.
WHAT THEY'RE ACCUSED OF DOING.
>>> THERE'S NEWS TONIGHT ON O.J.
SIMPSON.
SET TO GO FREE IN JUST DAYS.
AND WHAT THE PAPERWORK NOW
REVEALS TONIGHT.
>>> AND IT'S ONE OF THE MOST
POPULAR SHOWS ON CABLE TV,
"FIXER UPPER."
THE HOSTS TONIGHT WITH A BIG
HEADLINE ABOUT THEIR FUTURE AND
THE SHOW'S FUTURE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[radio alarm]
♪ ♪
Julie is living with metastatic
breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women with hormone receptor-
positive HER2- metastatic breast
cancer as the first
hormonal based therapy.
♪ ♪
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
And IBRANCE plus letrozole
shrunk tumors in over half of
these patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE can
develop low white blood cell
counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if you have
fever, chills,
or other signs of infection
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts...
...infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver
blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Julie calls it her "new" normal.
Because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one-prescribed,
FDA-approved oral combination
treatment for HR+/HER2- MBC.
It's great to finally meet you.
talking about you for years.
They're all about
me saving for a house,
or starting a
college fund for my son.
Actually, I want to know
what you're thinking.
Knowing that the most
important goals are yours.
It's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, THE FBI
SWEEPING IN AND ARRESTING FOUR
COACHES WITH THE NCAA.
WHAT THEY'RE ACCUSED OF DOING
TONIGHT.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS NOW.
>> Reporter: A MASSIVE SCANDAL
ROCKING COLLEGE BASKETBALL
TODAY, THE FBI ANNOUNCING FRAUD
AND CORRUPTION CHARGES AGAINST
TEN PEOPLE, INCLUDING FOUR
ASSISTANT COACHES AT SOME OF THE
COUNTRY'S TOP PROGRAMS.
AUBURN'S CHUCK PERSON, USC'S
TONY BLAND, ARIZONA'S
BOOK RICHARDSON AND OKLAHOMA
STATE'S LAMONT EVANS.
THE TWO-YEAR INVESTIGATION
ALLEGES COACHES TOOK CASH BRIBES
IN RETURN FOR STEERING NBA-BOUND
ATHLETES TOWARD SPECIFIC
FINANCIAL ADVISORS AND SPORTS
AGENTS.
>> TODAY'S ARREST SHOULD SERVE
AS A WARNING TO OTHERS, WE HAVE
YOUR PLAYBOOK.
>> Reporter: AMONG THOSE
CHARGED, THE GLOBAL HEAD OF
SPORTS MARKETING FOR BASKETBALL
FOR ADIDAS, JIM GATTO, ACCUSED
OF BRIBING THE FAMILIES OF HIGH
SCHOOL RECRUITS TO GET THEM TO
COMMIT TO COLLEGES WHERE ADIADS
WAS A SPONSOR.
>> THESE DEFENDANTS CONSPIRED TO
SECRETLY FUNNEL SIX-FIGURE
PAYMENTS TO THE FAMILIES OF
THREE HIGH SCHOOL PLAYERS.
>> Reporter: ADIDAS SAID TODAY
IT WAS UNAWARE OF ANY
MISCONDUCT.
THOSE FOUR COACHES HAVE BEEN
SUSPENDED AND THE NCAA TONIGHT
SAYING THE ALLEGATIONS IF TRUE
ARE A DESPICABLE BREACH OF
TRUST.
DAVID?
>> LINSEY DAVIS TONIGHT.
LINSEY, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE, IT
IS 2017, BUT TONIGHT, WHERE
WOMEN WILL FINALLY BE ALLOWED TO
DRIVE.
>>> ALSO NEWS TONIGHT ABOUT O.J.
SIMPSON.
WHAT THE PAPERWORK NOW TELLS US.
>>> AND IT IS A POPULAR SHOW,
"FIXER UPPER."
WHAT THE HOSTS HAVE JUST
REVEALED.
MORE NEWS AHEAD.
Americans,
83% try to eat healthy,
yet up to 90% fall short
on getting key nutrients.
Let's do more.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
Complete with 100% daily value
of more than 15 key nutrients.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
This is the story of John Smith.
Not this John Smith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
How do you chase what you love
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis?
Do what I did.
Ask your doctor about HUMIRA.
It's proven to help relieve pain
and protect joints
from further irreversible damage
in many adults.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to block
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes to RA symptoms.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 20 years.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
Ready for a new chapter?
Talk to your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA at work.
>>> TO THE INDEX OF OTHER NEWS
TONIGHT.
O.J. SIMPSON COUNTING THE DAYS
TO FREEDOM.
SIMPSON EXPECTED TO BE RELEASED
AS EARLY AS MONDAY.
HE WILL LIKELY HAVE TO REMAIN IN
THE STATE FOR NOW.
AUTHORITIES SAY HE HAS NET TO
FILE PAPERWORK THAT WOULD ALLOW
HIM TO LIVE WITH HIS CHILDREN IN
FLORIDA.
>>> TO SAUDI ARABIA TONIGHT.
THE KING LIFTING ONE OF HIS
COUNTRY'S MOST REPRESSIVE
POLICIES, NOW ALLOWING WOMEN TO
DRIVE FOR THE FIRST TIME IN THE
HISTORY OF THAT
ULTRACONSERVATIVE KINGDOM.
THE CHANGE TAKES EFFECT THIS
COMING JUNE.
>>> "FIXER UPPER," THE TV SHOW
IS ENDING.
THE SHOW WILL END AFTER FIVE
SEASONS.
CHIP AND JOANNA GAINES SAYING,
QUOTE, WHAT A RIDE.
>>> AND SOMETIMES 140 CHARACTERS
JUST WON'T DO.
TWITTER IS DOUBLING THE
CHARACTER LIMIT FOR A SMALL
SAMPLE OF GROUP USERS FROM 140
TO 280.
IF THE TEST IS A SUCCESS, THE
COMPANY MAY EXPAND THE LIMIT FOR
EVERYONE.
SO, TWEET ME, LET ME KNOW WHAT
YOU THINK OF THAT TONIGHT.
STILL IN 140 CHARACTERS.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE, THE
GROOM SUDDENLY DISAPPEARING.
WHY HE ENDED UP SOAKED AND WHY
HIS BRIDE IS BEAMING TONIGHT.
So let me get this straight.
You're a rabbit?
Im Vern, the Orange Money
retirement rabbit, from Voya.
Riiight. And that means...?
I'm the money you save for
retirement.
I help you get organized so your
money could multiply. See?
Got it. Who's he?
He's green money for spending
today.
You know, paying bills, maybe a
little online shopping...
Makes it easy to tell you apart.
That, and I am better looking.
I heard that.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement,
it's time to get Voya.
I take pictures of sunrises,
but with my back pain
I couldn't sleep
and get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
Whatever you're doing
to stay healthy...
...tmay be missing.g you
A key part of your wellness
that you may be...
...overlooking.
♪
It's your eyes.
That's why there's Ocuvite,
from Bausch + Lomb.
As you age your eyes can lose
vital nutrients.
Ocuvite helps replenish those
nutrients.
Ocuvite has Lutein, Zeaxanthin,
and Omega-3.
Nourish your eyes to help them
be their healthy best.
Ocuvite eye vitamins.
Be good to your eyes.
I CAN DO MORE TO LOWER MY A1C.
AND I CAN DO IT WITH
WHAT'S ALREADY WITHIN ME.
BECAUSE MY BODY CAN STILL
MAKE ITS OWN INSULIN.
AND ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
ACTIVATES MY BODY TO RELEASE IT.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT COMES IN A ONCE-WEEKLY,
TRULY EASY-TO-USE PEN.
IT WORKS 24/7, AND YOU DON'T
HAVE TO SEE OR HANDLE A NEEDLE.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU HAVE A PERSONAL
OR FAMILY HISTORY OF
MEDULLARY THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU HAVE MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU'RE ALLERGIC
TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE A LUMP OR
SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
OR SYMPTOMS LIKE ITCHING,
RASH, OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE,
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY WORSEN
KIDNEY PROBLEMS.
I CHOOSE ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
TO ACTIVATE MY WITHIN.
IF YOU NEED HELP LOWERING
YOUR A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR,
ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE, THE
BRIDE AND GROOM IN ONTARIO,
GETTING THEIR PHOTOS TAKEN WHEN
SUDDENLY, THE GROOM IS TESTED.
THIS LOOKS MORE LIKE YOUR
TYPICAL WEDDING PHOTO.
CLAY AND BRITTANY COOK, THIS
WEEKEND IN ONTARIO.
BUT THIS IS WHAT IT SOON LOOKED
LIKE.
THAT'S THE GROOM, SOAKED, NEARLY
WAIST DEEP IN THE WATER.
CLAYTON NOTICED A BOY HAD FALLEN
IN, AND WITHOUT HESITATION, LEFT
THE PHOTO SHOOT TO SAVE THE BOY.
>> HIS FACE WAS UNDER WATER AND
HE WAS FIGHTING, LIKE, HE WAS
REALLY FIGHTING.
LUCKY HE WAS ONLY A LITTLE GUY
AND I GRABBED HIM, SORT OF LIKE
RIGHT HERE AND I JUST KIND OF, I
JUST SORT OF HUFFED HIM UP.
>> Reporter: IT WAS JUST MOMENTS
EARLIER, THEY HAD BEGUN TO TAKE
THOSE PHOTOS WHEN THE
PHOTOGRAPHER NOTICED THE GROOM
WAS GONE.
>> HE WAS STRUGGLING TO SWIM AND
HE SWOOPED RIGHT UP THE LITTLE
GUY BY HIS ARM, JUST SOPPING WET
AND THE KID SAFELY WALKING AWAY
WHILE HE'S WAIST INTO THE RIVER.
>> Reporter: THAT LITTLE BOY,
HE'S OKAY TONIGHT.
AND SO IS THE BRIDE, SAYING,
THAT'S THE GUY I MARRIED.
>> THAT'S CLAY, LIKE, THAT'S
CLAY TO ME.
IT DOESN'T EVEN SURPRISE ME THAT
THAT HAPPENED.
IT'S SOMETHING HE WOULD JUST
INSTINCTIVELY DO.
>> GLAD THAT LITTLE GUY IS OKAY,
AND HERE'S TO THE BRIDE AND
GROOM TONIGHT.
THANKS FOR WATCHING HERE ON A
TUESDAY.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT HERE
TOMORROW.
>> THIS IS WCVB NEWSCENTER 5 AT
7:00.
ED: WE BEGIN WITH BREAKING NEWS,
AN ARREST IN THE MURDER OF
MUCH-LOVED ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
TEACHER IN HER REVERE HOME.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US, I'M ED
HARDING.
ERIKA: AND I'M ERIKA TARANTAL IN
FOR MARIA.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THIS IS A CASE
OF DEADLY DOMESTIC VIOLENCE.
OUR JORGE QUIROGA IS LIVE IN
REVERE WITH BREAKING
INFORMATION.
JORGE: NEWS OF TODAY'S ARREST
BOTH SURPRISING, BUT NOT
SHOCKING TO SOME NEIGHBORS.
THEY SAY BEHIND HER SMILE, THERE
WERE SIGNS OF TROUBLE AT HOME.
THIS AFTERNOON HER HUSBAND
ANDREW, 29 YEARS OLD, WAS
ARRESTED AND CHARGED WITH HER
MURDER.
LATE THIS AFTERNOON, RELATIVES
WERE SEEN LEAVING THE YELLOW
RANCH HOUSE ON GRAND VIEW
AVENUE, CARRYING A PLASTIC BAG
FULL OF BELONGINGS, REFUSING TO
SPEAK FOLLOWING THE ARREST OF
VANESSA MACCORMACK'S HUSBAND,
ANDREW.
THEY SAY IT WAS DOME