>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS.
THE SHAKEUP AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
TOM PRICE IS OUT.
THE PRESIDENT ASKS FOR HIS
RESIGNATION AFTER THE SECRETARY
OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES
SPENT HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF
DOLLARS ON LUXURY TRAVEL.
AND TONIGHT, THE LIST OF CABINET
MEMBERS AND THEIR SPENDING IS
GROWING.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO.
THE STUNNING MOMENT.
THE MAYOR ON LIVE TV TODAY
TAKING ON THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.
AND TONIGHT, THE THREE-STAR
GENERAL THE PRESIDENT SENT THERE
WHO SAYS THEY NEED MORE HELP.
>>> THE POLICE OFFICER KILLED,
ANOTHER OFFICER SAVED BY HIS
BULLETPROOF VEST, AFTER A
SUSPECT OPENS FIRE.
THE MANHUNT.
>>> THE NEW SURVEILLANCE OUT
TONIGHT.
THE NFL STAR.
WAS IT EXCESSIVE FORCE?
WHAT POLICE ARE NOW SAYING.
>>> O.J. SIMPSON GOES FREE AS
EARLY AS THIS WEEKEND.
WHERE IS HE HEADED?
>>> AND THE LITTLE GIRL WHO
FOUGHT -- AND WON -- AND WHO IS
NOW FIGHTING THE BATTLE FOR
OTHERS.
WHO IS OUR PERSON OF THE WEEK.
GOOD EVENING AND IT'S GREAT TO
HAVE YOU WITH US ON A FRIDAY
NIGHT.
WE END THE WEEK WITH THE
BREAKING HEADLINE FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP DEMANDING THE
RESIGNATION OF TOM PRICE, THE
SECRETARY OF HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES IS OUT.
HE'LL BE REPLACED AT MIDNIGHT
TONIGHT COMES AFTER SPENDING
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
OF YOUR MONEY ON LUXURY JETS AND
THAT LIST OF CABINET MEMBERS
UNDER FIRE FOR SPENDING IS
GROWING.
INTERIOR SECRETARY RYAN ZINKE
AND TOP REPUBLICANS ARE
DEMANDING AN INVESTIGATION AND
MARY BRUCE ON HOW MUCH OF YOUR
MONEY TAXPAYER DOLLARS HAS BEEN
SPENT AND THE QUESTIONS NOW
MOUNTING TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: AS HE BOARDED AIR
FORCE ONE TONIGHT, IT SOUNDED
LIKE THE PRESIDENT HAD MADE UP
HIS MIND ABOUT HEALTH SECRETARY
TOM PRICE.
>> I'M DISAPPOINTED IN HIM.
HE'S A GOOD MAN, BUT I'M
DISAPPOINTED IN HIM.
>> Reporter: JUST MINUTES
BEFORE, ABC'S JON KARL ASKED THE
PRESIDENT IF PRICE WAS GOING TO
LAST.
>> YOU'LL MAKE A DECISION ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT TO FIRE PRICE
TODAY?
>> PROBABLY SOMETIME TODAY.
>> I'M NOT HAPPY, OKAY?
>> Reporter: BY THE TIME THE
PRESIDENT LANDED IN NEW JERSEY,
PRICE WAS OUT.
A SENIOR WHITE HOUSE SOURCE
TELLS ABC NEWS THE PRESIDENT
ASKED THE SECRETARY TO RESIGN,
AND HE DID.
THE PRESSURE HAD BEEN BUILDING
FOR DAYS AFTER REPORTS PRICE
TOOK MORE THAN TWO DOZEN WORK
TRIPS ON LUXURY PRIVATE JETS.
>> WE HAVE HEARD CONCERNS.
I HAVE HEARD THE CRITICISMS.
CLEARLY WE WEREN'T SENSITIVE TO
THE TAXPAYER WHICH IS WHY I'VE
TAKEN THE ACTIONS I'VE TAKEN.
>> Reporter: THOSE FLIGHTS COST
TAXPAYERS MORE THAN $400,000.
PRICE PROMISED TO PERSONALLY
REIMBURSE THE GOVERNMENT, BUT
ONLY FOR THE COST OF HIS OWN
SEAT -- JUST $52,000.
>> HE'S PAYING BACK $52,000 AND
THE PLANES COST $400,000.
IS THAT ENOUGH?
>> NO, THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE.
NO, THAT WOULD BE
UNACCEPTABLE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, FIVE
CABINET SECRETARIES ARE NOW
UNDER FIRE FOR EXPENSIVE TRAVEL
HABITS TO THE TUNE OF MORE THAN
$625,000.
TODAY, INTERIOR SECRETARY
RYAN ZINKE, DEFIANT AMID
REVELATIONS HE SPENT MORE THAN
$15,000 ON THREE PRIVATE
FLIGHTS.
>> BEFORE WE GET STARTED, I'D
JUST LIKE TO ADDRESS, IN THE
WORDS OF GENERAL SCHWARZKOF, A
LITTLE BS ON TRAVEL.
>> Reporter: ZINKE SAYS HE
DIDN'T HAVE A CHOICE.
>> NO COMMERCIAL OPTIONS EXISTED
TO MEET THE PROMULGATED
SCHEDULE.
>> Reporter: ALSO NOW UNDER THE
MICROSCOPE, VETERANS' AFFAIRS
SECRETARY DAVID SHULKIN.
THE "WASHINGTON POST" REPORTING
TAXPAYERS PAID FOR HIS WIFE TO
FLY TO EUROPE ON AN OFFICIAL
TRIP, WHERE THEY TOOK IN THE
SIGHTS AND ATTENDED WIMBLEDON.
JUST ONE MONTH EARLIER, SHULKIN
ISSUED A MEMO TELLING EMPLOYEES
TO REVIEW THEIR OWN TRAVEL
PROCEDURES, WRITING, "I EXPECT
THIS WILL RESULT IN DECREASED
EMPLOYEE TRAVEL AND GENERATE
SAVINGS."
INVESTIGATIONS ARE ALREADY
UNDERWAY INTO TWO OTHER CABINET
SECRETARIES FOR THEIR TRAVEL
HABITS -- E.P.A. ADMINISTRATOR
SCOTT PRUITT WHO WAS UNDER
SCRUTINY FOR INSTALLING A 20,000
PHONE BOOTH IN HIS OFFICE AND
TREASURY
SECRETARY STEVE MNUCHIN, UNDER
SCRUTINY FOR TAKING COSTLY
GOVERNMENT JETS, INCLUDING THAT
TRIP TO KENTUCKY WHERE HE AND
HIS WIFE VIEWED THE ECLIPSE.
>> MARY WE WANTED TO SHOW
VIEWERS AT HOME BECAUSE THERE'S
BEEN ENOR NOUS TURNOVER.
AMONG THE NAMES ON THE LIST FROM
LEFT TO RIGHT, TOM PRICE, STEVE
BANNON, MICHAEL FLYNN, REINCE
PRIEBUS AMONG OTHERS OUT OF THIS
ADMINISTRATION.
SOME REPUBLICANS HAVE DEMANDED
AN INVESTIGATION INTO THE
SPENDING HERE?
>> Reporter: REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS ON THE HILL ARE
DEMANDING A FULL ACCOUNTING OF
ADMINISTRATION TRAVEL AND THE
PRESIDENT'S BUDGET DIRECTOR SENT
OUT GUIDELINES ON THE
APPROPRIATE USE OF GOVERNMENT
AND PRIVATE AIRCRAFT.
>> MARY BRUCE BACK ON THE STORY.
THANK YOU.
IN THE MEANTIME THE WHITE HOUSE
DEALING WITH THE GROWING
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO.
THE ACTING HOMELAND SECURITY
CHIEF UNDER FIRE FOR CALLING THE
RESPONSE A QUOTE, GOOD NEWS
STORY WHILE THE MAYOR OF SAN
JUAN TOOK ON THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION SAYING IT IS A
LIFE OR DEATH SITUATION ON THE
GROUND.
EVEN THE THREE STAR GENERAL ON
THE GROUND THERE SAYS MORE HELP
IS NEEDED TONIGHT.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL.
>> Reporter: AMIDST GROWING
FRUSTRATION IN PUERTO RICO, A
MOMENT OF ANGUISH PLAYED OUT ON
NATIONAL TELEVISION TODAY AS THE
MAYOR OF SAN JUAN LISTENED TO
ACTING HOMELAND SECURITY
SECRETARY ELAINE DUKE PRAISE THE
FEDERAL RESPONSE.
>> I AM VERY SATISFIED.
IT IS REALLY A GOOD NEWS STORY
IN TERMS OF OUR ABILITY TO REACH
PEOPLE AND THE LIMITED NUMBER OF
DEATHS THAT HAVE TAKEN PLACE IN
SUCH A DEVASTATING HURRICANE.
>> WELL, MAYBE FROM WHERE SHE'S
STANDING IT'S A GOOD NEWS STORY.
WHEN YOU'RE DRINKING FROM A
CREEK, IT'S NOT A GOOD NEWS
STORY.
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE FOOD FOR A
BABY, IT'S NOT A GOOD NEWS
STORY.
I'M SORRY, THAT REALLY UPSETS ME
AND FRUSTRATES ME.
DAMMIT, THIS IS NOT A GOOD NEWS
STORY.
THIS IS A "PEOPLE ARE DYING"
IT'S A LIFE-OR-DEATH STORY.
>> Reporter: WE ASKED PRESIDENT
TRUMP ABOUT DUKE'S COMMENTS.
>> WAS ELAINE DUKE WRONG TO SAY
THAT PUERTO RICO WAS A GOOD NEWS
STORY?
>> WELL, I HAVEN'T HEARD WHAT
SHE SAID.
I CAN TELL YOU THIS, WE HAVE
DONE AN INCREDIBLE JOB
CONSIDERING THERE'S ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING TO WORK WITH.
>> Reporter: THE ADMINISTRATION
HAS BEEN BEEFING UP THE
MILITARY'S ROLE, A THREE-STAR
GENERAL NOW ON THE GROUND
SUPERVISING THE FEDERAL
RESPONSE.
BUT TODAY THAT GENERAL SAID IT
WAS "NOT ENOUGH," AND PROMISED
TO BRING IN MORE RESOURCES.
>> WE WILL NOT REST, HOWEVER,
UNTIL THE PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO
ARE SAFE.
THESE ARE GREAT PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: BUT THE PRESIDENT
IS ALSO RAISING QUESTIONS ABOUT
WHETHER THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
SHOULD PAY TO REBUILD PUERTO
RICO.
HE HAS REPEATEDLY BROUGHT UP THE
ISLAND'S LARGE DEBT, TWEETING
THIS MORNING, "BIG DECISIONS
WILL HAVE TO BE MADE AS TO THE
COST OF ITS REBUILDING!"
>> THE GOVERNMENT OF
PUERTO RICO WILL HAVE TO WORK
WITH US TO DETERMINE HOW THIS
MASSIVE REBUILDING EFFORT WILL
END UP BEING ONE OF THE BIGGEST
EVER WILL BE FUNDED.
>> JON KARL WITH US LIVE FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE PRESIDENT STILL PLANS TO
VISIT PUERTO RICO ON TUESDAY?
>> Reporter: HE PLANS TO GO TO
PUERTO RICO TUESDAY TO GET A
FIRSTHAND LOOK.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS VERY
SENSITIVE TO CRITICISM THAT THE
FEDERAL RESPONSE HAS BEEN
INADEQUATE INCLUDING ONE SENATOR
WHO SAID THIS COULD BE TRUMP'S
KATRINA.
I CAN TELL YOU DAVID THAT
OFFICIALS HERE ARE DETERMINED
NOT TO REPEAT THE MISTAKES THAT
PRESIDENT BUSH MADE DURING THE
KATRINA DISASTER.
>> JON, THANKS.
SO MUCH OF PUERTO RICO IS STILL
HARD TO REACH.
NEARLY 3.5 MILLION CITIZENS LIVE
THERE.
ROADS AND BRIDGES ARE OUT.
AND EVA PILGRIM WHERE PEOPLE
HAVE TO HOLD ON TO A WIRE TO
CROSS RUSHES WATERS JUST TO
CHECK ON THEIR HOMES.
EVA.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT NINE DAYS
AFTER HURRICANE MARIA RAVAGED
PUERTO RICO, NEARBY COMMUNITIES
ARE UNREACHABLE.
WE JOURNEYED SOUTHWEST OF SAN
JUAN, ALONG ROADS CAKED WITH
DEBRIS, FINALLY ARRIVING AT THE
TOWN OF MOROVIS.
THIS USED TO BE PART OF A BRIDGE
THAT HAS COMPLETELY COLLAPSED IN
THE FORCE OF HURRICANE MARIA'S
WIND.
THIS TOWN NOW COMPLETELY
ISOLATED.
FAMILIES FORCED TO MAKE A
WHITE-KNUCKLE CROSSING WITH ONLY
A WIRE TO HOLD ON TO.
>> Reporter: YOU DON'T REALLY
HAVE A CHOICE?
>> NO, WE DON'T HAVE NO CHOICE.
WE JUST GOTTA DO IT.
>> Reporter: MAKING THE TREK
HOME WITH WHAT FEW GROCERIES HE
COULD FIND.
>> CHICKEN.
>> HE SAYS AFTER MARIA HIT HE
CARRIED HIS FATHER
ACROSS THE RAPIDS, DESPERATE TO
GET HIM LIFE-SAVING DIALYSIS
TREATMENT.
>> I HAD TO DO IT OR HE WAS
GOING TO DIE.
>> Reporter: WITH RESIDENTS ALL
ACROSS THE U.S. TERRITORY
SWELTERING IN LONG LINES FOR
EVERYTHING FROM GAS TO CASH, THE
THREE STAR GENERAL NOW IN PUERTO
RICO TO HELP LEAD THE RECOVERY
EFFORTS.
>> YOU'VE SUFFERED A TREMENDOUS
DEVASTATION, AND WE'RE THERE
WITH YOU.
THIS RECOVERY IS GOING TO TAKE A
VERY LONG TIME.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN
10,000 FEDERAL, CIVILIAN, AND
MILITARY PERSONNEL ARE ON THE
ISLAND.
>> EVA PILGRIM WITH US.
WE HEARD THE GENERAL SAY MORE
HELP IS NEED AND THE U.S. NAVY
HOSPITAL SHIP THE COMFORT IS ON
THE WAY.
HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE TO GET
THERE?
>> Reporter: THE COMFORT TOOK
OFF FROM THE NAVAL BASE AND
EXPECTED TO ARRIVE HERE IN
PUERTO RICO SOMETIME NEXT WEEK.
DAVID.
>> EVA PILGRIM WITH US TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
TO MAKE MATTERS WORSE ANOTHER
MAJOR THREAT FACING THE PEOPLE
OF PUERTO RICO.
ANOTHER TROPICAL SYSTEM IS
HEADED THEIR WAY, FLASH FLOOD
WATCHES UP FOR THIS WEEKEND.
LET'S GET TO ROB MARCIANO WHO
HAVE SPENT MANY DAYS IN PUERTO
RICO.
>> IT'S NOT A HURRICANE BUT IT
WILL BRING HEAVY RAIN.
WE HAVE ANOTHER TROPICAL WAVE
NEAR FLORIDA.
LET'S ZOOM TO PUERTO RICO.
FLASH FLOOD WATCHES UP THROUGH
THE WEEKEND.
TWO, THREE, FOUR INCHES OF RAIN
AS IT DIFFICULTIES OFF TO THE
WEST.
THE RADAR IS DOWN.
THE RADAR IS UP AND WORKING FOR
FLORIDA.
AS THIS WAVE DRIFTS NORTH WOOD.
40% CHANCE OF DEVELOPMENT
ESPECIALLY FOR THE EAST COAST OF
FLORIDA.
FOUR FIVE INCHES OF RAIN THROUGH
THE WEEKEND AND NASTY WEATHER IN
THROUGH NEXT WEEK.
>> THANK YOU.
IN OTHER NEWS TONIGHT, THE NEW
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE DEADLY
SHOOTING IN A TENNESSEE CHURCH.
THE GUNMAN IN CUSTODY.
WHAT INVESTIGATORS NOW SAY THEY
HAVE DISCOVERED IN HIS CAR.
ABC'S PIERRE THOMAS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT WAS A
TENNESSEE CHURCH SHOOTING FOR
ANOTHER CHURCH MASSACRE.
SOURCES SAYING POLICE FOUND A
NOTE IN THE CHAPPEM MASS
SHOOTING REFERENCING THE RAMPAGE
AT THE CHURCH IN CHARLESTON
SOUTH CAROLINA.
ROOF EXECUTED NINE PEOPLE SIMPLY
BECAUSE OF RACE.
HE WAS CHARGED WITH WALKING INTO
THE TENNESSEE CHURCH.
>> MASS CASUALTY INCIDENT.
>> THE SHOOTING ENDED A WHITE
WOMAN FATALLY SHOT AND SIX
WOUNDED.
>> POSSIBLE SIX VICTIMS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE FBI'S
INVESTIGATING A SHOOTING AS A
POSSIBLE HATE CRIME.
SOURCES TELL ABC NEWS THE NOTE
FOUND IN SIMILAR SON'S CAR IS
ONE OF THE REASONS WHY AN
INVESTIGATION.
>> NEW SURVEILLANCE FROM THE
TAKE DOWN OF A STAR FOOTBALL
PLAYER MICHAEL BENNETT.
BENNETT ACCUSED THE POLICE OF
EXCESSIVE FORCE AND RACIAL
PROFILING.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, NEW VIDEO
SHEDDING LIGHT ON THIS NOW
INFAMOUS TAKEDOWN OF A STAR NFL
PLAYER.
SEATTLE SEAHAWKS DEFENSIVE END
MICHAEL BENNETT AT A LAS VEGAS
CASINO LAST MONTH.
ACCUSING OFFICERS OF RACIAL
PROFILING, POINTING GUNS AND
USING EXCESSIVE FORCE.
TONIGHT POLICE SAID THEY FOUND
NO EVIDENCE OF EXCESSIVE FORCE
AND OFFICERS WILL NOT BE
CHARGED.
>> GOING THROUGH THE EVIDENCE,
IT'S EVIDENT THAT THEY ACTED
APPROPRIATELY.
>> Reporter: POLICE NOW
SAY THEY WERE ACTING TO REPORTS
OF AN ACTIVE SHOOTER.
YELLING AT HIM TO STOP THINKING
HE COULD BE THE SUSPECT.
BENNETT CONTINUES TO RUN.
THE OFFICERS TELL BENNETT THEY
ARE LOOKING FOR THE SUSPECT.
>> WHAT AM I BEING ARRESTED FOR?
>> EARLIER THIS MONTH BENNETT
TOLD BYRON PITTS HE WAS
TERRIFIED AND THOUGHT HE WAS
GOING TO DIE.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY TO YOU?
>> WE'LL BLOW YOUR [ BLEEP ]
HEAD OFF IF YOU MOVE.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES TONIGHT
SAYING THEY ALSO FOUND NO
EVIDENCE OF THAT.
DAVID.
>> THANK YOU.
NEXT HERE A FORCEFUL MESSAGE
FROM THE SUPERVISOR OF THE U.S.
AIR FORCE ACADEMY AFTER FIVE
BLACK CANDIDATES WOKE UP TO
MESSAGES SAYING GO HOME.
>> GRAB YOUR PHONES.
IF YOU'RE OUTRAGED BY THOSE
WORDS THAN YOU'RE IN THE RIGHT
PLACE.
IF YOU CAN'T TREAT SOMEONE WITH
DIGNITY AND RESPECT YOU NEED TO
GET OUT.
>> TONIGHT THE SUPERINTENDENT
SAYS HE WILL CONTINUE TO
INVESTIGATE THIS.
>> CUBA WARNING AMERICANS NOT TO
VISIT THERE AND ORDERING MORE
THAN HALF OF ITS STAFF TO RETURN
HOME.
AFTER THOSE MYSTERIOUS ATTACKS.
ABC'S MARTHA RADDATZ WITH WHAT
SHE'S LEARNED.
>> Reporter: THE MYSTERY IS SO
DEEP, THE HEALTH EFFECTS SO
SERIOUS, THAT TONIGHT THE STATE
DEPARTMENT IS ORDERING ALL
NON-ESSENTIAL EMBASSY PERSONNEL
AND ALL EMBASSY FAMILIES TO
LEAVE CUBA, AND WARNING
AMERICANS TO AVOID TRAVEL TO
CUBA.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT ALSO
SUSPENDING ALL ROUTINE VISAS TO
THE U.S. ISSUED IN CUBA.
>> VERY BAD THINGS HAPPENING IN
CUBA.
VERY BAD THINGS.
>> Reporter: THE ATTACKS,
INCLUDING SONIC HARASSMENT,
BEGAN LATE LAST YEAR,
MORE THAN 20 DIPLOMATS TARGETED
IN THEIR
HOMES AND HAVANA HOTELS.
REPORTS OF PERMANENT HEARING
LOSS, CONFUSION, LOSS OF
BALANCE, AND MILD TRAUMATIC
BRAIN INJURY.
ONE VICTIM REPORTEDLY JOLTED
FROM BED BY A "BLARING, GRINDING
NOISE," BUT JUST A FEW FEET FROM
THE BED -- SILENCE.
IT WAS LIKE PASSING THROUGH AN
INVISIBLE WALL WITH AN INVISIBLE
ASSAILANT.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHO IS
RESPONSIBLE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT IS
>> Reporter: OFFICIALS SAY THEY
CAN'T RULE OUT THAT CUBA,
RUSSIA, OR SOME OTHER THIRD
PARTY IS BEHIND THE ATTACKS.
TODAY JETBLUE RESPONDED TO THE
TRAVEL WARNING SAYING THEY WOULD
WAIVE ANY CANCELLATION FEES IF
CUSTOMERS HAVE ANY HESITATION
ABOUT VISITING THE ISLAND.
BUT SO FAR NO TOURISTS HAVE BEEN
TARGETED IN THESE MYSTERIOUS
ATTACKS.
>> MARTHA RADDATZ WHO CONTINUES
TO FOLLOW THE MYSTERY IN CUBA.
STILL MUCH MORE ON "WORLD NEWS
TONIGHT."
THIS FRIDAY THE POLICE OFFICER
KILLED AND ANOTHER OFFICER SAVED
BY HIS BULLETPROOF VEST AFTER A
SUSPECT OPENS FIRE.
WHERE THIS PLAYED OUT AND THE
MANHUNT.
O.J. SIMPSON SET TO WALK FREE
MONDAY.
WHERE IS SIMPSON HEADED?
WHAT WE ARE LEARNING TONIGHT.
NEW YORK TO SHANGHAI IN 39
MINUTES?
WOULD YOU TAKE THE TRIP IN THIS
NEW VEHICLE?
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪
Your body was made for better
things than
rheumatoid arthritis.
Before you and your
rheumatologist move to another
treatment, ask if XELJANZ is
right for you.
XELJANZ is a small pill for
adults with
moderate to severe RA for whom
methotrexate did not work well.
XELJANZ can reduce joint pain
and swelling in as little as
two weeks, and help stop further
joint damage.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma and other
cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ if you have
an infection.
Tears in the stomach or
intestines, low blood cell
counts and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you were in
a region where fungal
infections are common and if you
have had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or are prone
to infections.
XELJANZ can reduce the symptoms
of RA,
even without methotrexate, and
is also available
in a once-daily pill.
Ask about XELJANZ XR.
.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT O.J. SIMPSON
SET TO WALK FREE AFTER HIS FINAL
WEEKEND IN A LAS VEGAS PRISON
AND TONIGHT THE BREAKING
HEADLINE IS FLORIDA NOW TRYING
TO KEEP SIMPSON FROM COMING
THERE.
HERE'S ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT PRISZ
OFFICIALS GUARDING THE DETAILS
LIKE A STATE SECRET.
>> I TRIED TO BE HELPFUL TO
EVERYBODY.
>> BRACING PHENOMENON AN
ONSLAUGHT OF POP RAZ ZI THE
MINUTE HE WALKS FREE.
ANOTHER PERSON VOWING TO HOUND
AN O.J. SIMPSON FRED GOLD MAN.
>> WHAT WOULD THAT PICTURE LOOK
LIKE?
>> DISGUST.
>> GOLD MAN WHO WON A JUDGMENT
AGAINST SIMPSON FOR THE MURDER
OF HIS SON SAYS SIMPSON OHS HIM
$60 MILLION.
>> IT MIGHT AS WELL BE $6
BILLION.
>> SIMPSON'S LAWYER SCOFFING AT
THE NOTION.
>> HE'S BEEN IN PRISON FOR THE
LAST NINE YEARS.
>> AND THE NFL PENSION,
UNTOUCHABLE.
>> DAVID SIMPSON SAID HE WANTS
TO MOVE TO FLORIDA TO BE NEAR
HIS CHILDREN BUT COMPLICATING
THAT IS THE PAPERWORK TO GET HIM
THERE STILL HAS NOT BEEN FILED
AND NOW THE FLORIDA ATTORNEY
GENERAL WEIGHING IN SAYING SHE
OBJECTS TO HIS RELOCATION THERE.
DAVID.
>> MATT GUTMAN ON THIS FOR US.
WHEN WE COME BACK NEW DETAILS
ABOUT THE OFFICERS SHOT AND
KILLED.
A MOTHER AND FIVE YEAR VETERAN
AND THE MANHUNT AND THE SECOND
OFFICER WHO SURVIVED BECAUSE OF
HIS BULLETPROOF VEST.
MORE NEWS AHEAD.
unpredictable abdominal pain
or discomfort
and diarrhea.
I tried lifestyle changes
and over-the-counter treatments,
but my symptoms keep
coming back.
It turns out I have
Irritable Bowel Syndrome
with Diarrhea,
or IBS-D.
A condition that's really
frustrating.
That's why I talked to my
doctor about VIBERZI...
...a different way
to treat IBS-D.
VIBERZI is a
prescription medication
you take every day
that helps proactively manage
both abdominal pain and
diarrhea at the same time.
So I can stay ahead of
my symptoms.
VIBERZI can cause new or
worsening abdominal pain.
Do not take VIBERZI
if you have no gallbladder,
have pancreas or
severe liver problems,
problems with alcohol abuse,
long-lasting or
severe constipation,
or a bowel or
gallbladder blockage.
Pancreatitis may occur
and can lead to
hospitalization and death.
If you are taking VIBERZI,
you should not take medicines
that cause constipation.
The most common side effects of
VIBERZI include constipation,
nausea, and abdominal pain.
Stay ahead of IBS-D
with VIBERZI.
And the wolf huffed
and puffed...
Like you do sometimes, Grandpa?
Well, when you have COPD,
it can be hard to breathe.
It can be hard to get air out,
which can make it hard
to get air in.
So I talked to my doctor.
She said...
SYMBICORT could help
you breathe better,
starting within 5 minutes.
SYMBICORT doesn't
replace a rescue inhaler
for sudden symptoms.
SYMBICORT helps provide
significant improvement
of your lung function.
SYMBICORT is for COPD,
including chronic bronchitis
and emphysema.
It should not be taken
more than twice a day.
SYMBICORT contains formoterol.
Medicines like formoterol
increase the risk of
death from asthma problems.
SYMBICORT may increase your
risk of lung infections,
osteoporosis, and some
eye problems.
You should tell your doctor if
you have a heart condition
or high blood pressure
before taking it.
SYMBICORT could mean a day
with better breathing.
Watch out, piggies!
(Child giggles)
SYMBICORT. Breathe better
starting within 5 minutes.
Get SYMBICORT free for up
to one year.
Visit SaveonSYMBICORT.com today
to learn more.
Whoa. This looks worse than
I thought.
Mike and Jen Doyle?
Yeah.
Time for Medicare, huh.
I have no idea how we're going
to get through this.
Follow me.
Choosing a plan can be
super-complicated.
But it doesn't have to be.
UnitedHealthcare can guide you
through the confusion,
with helpful people, tools and
plans.
Including the only plans with
the AARP name.
Well that wasn't so bad at all.
That's how we like it.
AARP Medicare plans, from
UnitedHealthcare.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
>>> TO THE INDEX OF OTHER NEWS.
A SUSPECT IN CUSTODY AFTER
SHOOTING TWO GEORGIA POLICE
OFFICERS KILLING ONE OF THEM.
AUTHORITIES ARRESTING SETH
SPANGLER AFTER AN URGENT MANHUNT
IN PULP COUNTY.
HE FLED AFTER OPENING FIRE
DURING A TRAFFIC STOP.
DETECTIVE KRISTIN HEARN DIED
FROM HER WOUNDS.
A SECOND OFFICER SURVIVED PLANKS
R THANKS TO HIS VEST.
>> SPACE EX-FOUNDER ELON MASK
SAYS THIS COULD CARRY PASSENGERS
FROM NEW YORK TO SHANGHAI IN 39
MINUTES.
THAT SAME ROCKET WHICH COULD FLY
IN FIVE YEARS COULD BRING
PASSENGERS TO MARS TO BE
CONTINUED.
LOOK WHO IS 40 TONIGHT.
A MAJOR MILESTONE FOR ABC'S
2020.
THE EMPIRE STATE BUILDING
LIGHTING UP THE BUILDING IN 2020
COLORS TONIGHT.
ELIZABETH VARGAS AND I WERE
FLIPPING THE SWITCH.
THE FAMOUS TOWER WILL SHINE BLUE
AND WHITE IN HONOR OF THE
SEASON.
AND THAT VIEW COULDN'T HELP
OURSELVES AND WE COULD NOT
CELEBRATE THIS WITHOUT THINKING
OF HUGH DOWNS AND BARBARA
WALTERS WHO FOR SO MANY YEARS
TELLING YOU AT HOME WE'RE IN
TOUCH SO YOU BE IN TOUCH.
WHEN WE COME BACK, A LITTLE GIRL
WHO FOUGHT ONE BRAVE BATTLE.
SHE'S BACK TONIGHT TO HELP
OTHERS FIGHT THAT SAME BATTLE IN
THAT SAME PLACE.
Liberty Mutual saved us almost
eight hundred dollars when
we switched our auto and
home insurance.
Liberty did what?
Yeah, they saved us a ton,
which gave us a little wiggle
room in our budget.
Wish our insurance did that.
Then we could get a real
babysitter instead of
your brother.
Hey, welcome back.
This guy... right?
Yes.
Ellen.
That's my robe.
You could save seven hundred
eighty two dollars
when Liberty stands with you.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
How do you chase what you love
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis?
Do what I did.
Ask your doctor about HUMIRA.
It's proven to help relieve pain
and protect joints
from further irreversible damage
in many adults.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to block
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes to RA symptoms.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 20 years.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
Ready for a new chapter?
Talk to your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA at work.
I love kiwis.
I've always had that issue
with the seeds
getting under my denture.
Super Poligrip Free.
It creates a seal
of the dentures
in my mouth.
Just a few dabs
is clinically
proven
to seal out more
food particles.
Try Super
Poligrip Free.
♪
It's like nothing
you've seen.
T 24HR protectionum
from frequent heartburn.
All day, and all night.
Now packed into
a pill so small,
We call it mini.
New ClearMinis from Nexium 24HR.
See Heartburn Differently.
♪
♪  ♪
If You've Got A Life,
You Gotta Swiffer
>>> AND FINALLY TONIGHT, OUR
PERSON OF THE WEEK.
THE LITTLE GIRL WHO BRAVELY
FOUGHT A FIERCE BATTLE AND SHE
WON.
AND SHE LATER MADE THE PROMISE
TO HERSELF TO ONE DAY RETURN TO
THE SCENE OF THAT BATTLE TO HELP
OTHERS IN THEIR FIGHT.
TONIGHT RIGHT HERE IN OUR PERSON
OF THE WEEK.
>> Reporter: THIS WEEK,
24-YEAR-OLD MONTANA BROWN
STARTED A NEW JOB AS A PEDIATRIC
NURSE AT AFLAC CANCER CENTER AT
CHILDREN'S HEALTHCARE OF
ATLANTA, A PLACE SHE KNOWS WELL.
SHE'S A TWO-TIME CANCER SURVIVOR
HERSELF.
FIRST DIAGNOSED AT TWO WITH A
RARE TYPE OF CHILDHOOD CANCER
AFFECTING MUSCLES AND BONES, AND
THEN AGAIN AT 15.
BOTH TIMES, SHE WAS TREATED WITH
AT THE VERY SAME HOSPITAL WHERE
SHE RETURNS TO WORK.
SHE REMEMBERS THAT.
>> THE NURSES HERE THE LOVE THEY
SHOWED ME REALLY HELPED ME AND
PUSHED ME TO WANT TO BECOME A
NURSE.
>> MONTANA KNOWS WHAT ITS LIKE
TO BE YOUNG AND UP AGAINST A
BATTLE.
>> IT WAS A CALLING SHE KNEW
EARLY ON.
>> I WOULD ALWAYS SAY I'M ONLY
GOING TO NURSING SCHOOL TO DO
PEDIATRIC ONCOLOGY.
I DON'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING
ELSE.
I'M GOING TO SCHOOL STRICTLY TO
DO THAT.
>> HOLDING HER NEW BADGE
TONIGHT.
A DREAM REALIZED.
>> I'M NOT WALKING THROUGH THE
DOORS AS A PATIENT.
I'M WALKING THROUGH AS A STAFF
MEMBER AND I GET TO BE AN IDEA
OF HOPE AND INSPIRATION FOR
OTHER KIDS.
>> AND SO WE CHOOSE MONTANA
BROWN.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
A BEAUTIFUL SUNSET AND THE "20
CLSH 20" COLORS TURNING 40.
WE'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT 10:00
P.M.
UNTIL THEN, GOOD NIGHT.
ANNOUNCER: FROM BOSTON'S NEWS
LEADER -- THIS IS WCVB
NEWSCENTER 5 AT 7:00.
ED: A GUN SHOT RIGHT OUT OF HIS
HAND.
THIS MAN NOW BEHIND BARS AFTER A
CONFRONTATION WITH POLICE.
THE SUSPECT AND POLICE OFFICERS
EXCHANGING FIRE.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I'M ED HARDING.
MARIA: I'M MARIA STEPHANOS.
THIS ALL HAPPENING IN THE TOWN
OF LUNENBURG.
THAT'S WHERE WE FIND NEWSCENTER
5'S NICHOLE BERLIE WITH OUR TOP
STORY.
NICHOLE.
NICHOLE: IT HAPPENED EARLIER
THIS MORNING ALONG THE ROAD.
YOU CAN TILL SEE THE NEON
ORANGE EVIDENCE MARKERS.
INVESTIGATORS PLACED EVIDENCE
MARKERS ALONG CHASE ROAD, TAPE
ON A TREE BRANCH NEXT TO WHAT
APPEARS TO BE BLOOD.
EARLY FRIDAY MORNING, POLICE
RESPONDED TO A SUSPICIOUS PERSON
CALL.
12 HOURS LATER, 32-YEAR-OLD
BRIAN BINDER SINCE IN A
WHEELCHAIR BEING ARRAIGNED ON
MULTIPLE CHARGES.
>> Y