STILL GATHERED HERE, THE PARENTS
OF THE CHILDREN WHO ARE STILL
MISSING ARE HOPING AGAINST HOPE
THAT THEIR CHILD MAY STILL BE
ALIVE, MAY COME OUT FROM
UNDERNEATH THAT RUBBLE.
OBVIOUSLY, SHEP, WE'RE SOME 48
HOURS ON FROM THAT 7.1
EARTHQUAKE AND WITH EVERY
PASSING MINUTE, HOPES OF FINDING
SURVIVORS HERE OR ANY THE
OTHER SITES BEGIN TO DIM.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: MUCH OF THE FOCUS
HAS BEEN ON THE SCHOOL.
BUT YOU MENTIONED THE OTHER
SITES.
IT APPEARS THERE'S DOZENS AND
DOZENS.
ANY PROGRESS?
>> INDEED THERE'S BEEN SOME
PROGRESS, SHEP.
WE WERE AT AN OFFICE BUILDING
THAT COLLAPSED.
YOU MIGHT HAVE LIVE PICTURES, IF
NOT, VIDEO FROM THAT BUILDING.
THAT IS IN DOWNTOWN MEXICO CITY,
AN AREA KNOWN AS ROMA.
IT COLLAPSED OVERNIGHT.
A MIRACLE THERE.
TWO WOMEN AND ONE MAN PULLED OUT
ALIVE.
THE SEARCH AND RESCUE EFFORT
GOES ON THERE.
WE'RE TOLD BY FAMILIES OF PEOPLE
WHO THEY BELIEVE WERE IN THE
OFFICE BUILDING AND STILL
MISSING, THERE MAY BE 14 PEOPLE
STILL TRAPPED IN THERE.
WHETHER THEY ARE DEAD OR ALIVE,
WE DON'T KNOW.
AS THE PRESIDENT SAID, IT'S A
RESCUE OPERATION.
THEY WON'T GIVE UP UNTIL THEY'RE
CERTAIN THERE'S NO CHANCES OF
ANYBODY ELSE SURVIVING.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THANKS, JONATHAN.
SADLY WE'RE WATCHING ANOTHER
UNFOLDING CATASTROPHE AND WORD
THAT PARTS OF PUERTO RICO COULD
BE WITHOUT POWER FOR NOT WEEKS
BUT MONTHS.
THAT'S AS HURRICANE MARIA
CONTINUES ITS DEADLY TREK
THROUGH THE CARIBBEAN.
THE LATEST STORM TRACK AND HOW
THE UNITED STATES' MAINLAND MAY
BE AFFECTED.
THAT'S AHEAD.
QUIET CONFIDENCE...
AT THE PUSH OF A BUTTON.
FOR 480 BUCKS...
ELECTRICITY WITHOUT THE SHOCK.
CABELA'S OUTDOORSMAN
REMOTE START GENERATOR.
GREAT PRICE.
EVERY DAY.
ONLY AT CABELA'S.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
RUSSIA THREATENING TO STRIKE
BACK IF THE U.S. MILITARY OR
ALLIES FIRE AT RUSSIAN SOLDIERS
IN SYRIA.
THE KREMLIN WARNING THAT SPECIAL
FORCES ARE DEPLOYEDED IN SYRIA
WHERE U.S. BACKED FIGHTERS, ISIS
AND THE RUSSIAN-SUPPORTED SYRIAN
REGIME ARE BATTLING IT OUT.
AN EXPLOSION IN LOS ANGELES.
A BLAST DESTROYED A GARAGE AND
SEVERAL SURROUNDING HOMERS.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE RULED OUT
ILLEGAL DRUG MAKING OR OTHER
CRIMINAL ACTIVITIES.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
A RUN-AWAY GOAT WANDERED INTO A
HOTEL IN MASSACHUSETTS.
COPS SAY THE GOAT WAS ON THE
LOSE 24 HOURS BEFORE POLICE
BROUGHT HIM HOME.
HE JUMPED THE FENCE AND TOOK OFF
LIKE A CRIMINAL.
THE NEWS CONTINUES WITH SHEPARD
SMITH AFTER THIS.
I count on my
Dell Small Business Advisor
for tech advice.
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪♪
I didn't know where I
was from ethnically.
So we sent that sample
off to Ancestry.
My Ancestry DNA results
are that I am 26% Nigerian.
I am just trying to
learn as much as I can
about my culture.
I put the Gele on my
head and I looked
into the mirror and I
was trying not to cry.
Because it's a hat,
but it's like the most
important hat I've
ever owned.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
This is me
when I feel controlled
by frequent,
unpredictable abdominal pain
or discomfort
and diarrhea.
I tried lifestyle changes
and over-the-counter treatments,
but my symptoms keep
coming back.
It turns out I have
Irritable Bowel Syndrome
with Diarrhea,
or IBS-D.
A condition that's really
frustrating.
That's why I talked to my
doctor about VIBERZI...
...a different way
to treat IBS-D.
VIBERZI is a
prescription medication
you take every day
that helps proactively manage
both abdominal pain and
diarrhea at the same time.
So I can stay ahead of
my symptoms.
VIBERZI can cause new or
worsening abdominal pain.
Do not take VIBERZI
if you have no gallbladder,
have pancreas or
severe liver problems,
problems with alcohol abuse,
long-lasting or
severe constipation,
or a bowel or
gallbladder blockage.
Pancreatitis may occur
and can lead to
hospitalization and death.
If you are taking VIBERZI,
you should not take medicines
that cause constipation.
The most common side effects of
VIBERZI include constipation,
nausea, and abdominal pain.
Stay ahead of IBS-D
with VIBERZI.
>> Shepard: HURRICANE MARIA IS
GAINING STRENGTH AS IT'S MOVING
ACROSS THE CARIBBEAN.
AS PUERTO RICANS LOOK AT THE
DAMAGE THAT THE MAYOR OF THE
CAPITOL CITY SAYS SOME PLACES
COULD BE WITHOUT POWER FOR SIX
MONTHS.
MARIA IS BRINGING CATASTROPHIC
FLOODING TO PUERTO RICO.
THE STORM HIT THE ISLAND AS A
CATEGORY FOUR STORM, 155 MILES
AN HOUR SUSTAINED WINDS.
THE STRONGEST HURRICANE
ACCORDING TO THE NATIONAL
HURRICANE CENTER TO HIT PUERTO
RICO IN MORE THAN 80 YEARS.
RESCUE WORKERS TODAY DEALING
WITH DOWNED STREETS AND FLOODING
STREETS AS THEY TRY TO REACH
VICTIMS THAT NEED HELP.
THE STORM DESTROYED HUNDREDS OF
HOMES AND KNOCKED OUT
ELECTRICITY TO THE ISLAND AND
BROUGHT DOWN CELL PHONE TOWERS
AND LEAVING MOST PEOPLE UNABLE
TO CALL FOR HELP OR CALL FOR
FAMILY MEMBERS.
MORE IMAGES TO SHARE IN THE
SLIDE SHOW THIS AFTERNOON.
THIS IS TYPICAL DAMAGE, I'M
TOLD.
A FLOODED GAS STATION ON THE
ISLAND'S EAST COAST.
THE SAME AREA, AMBULANCES
TRAPPED UNDER THE COLLAPSED
ROOF.
THE ROAD LITTERED WITH POLES AND
POWER LINES.
LOOK AT THAT.
THINK HOW LONG IT WOULD TAKE TO
FREE UP THIS ROAD AND FREE UP
THE POWER LINES?
THERE'S A WHOLE ISLAND LIKE
THAT.
HERE'S WHAT'S LEFT OF A HOUSE
NEXT TO THE SOUTHERN COAST.
THE ENERGY MANAGEMENT DIRECTOR
SAID IT WILL BE A HISTORIC
EVENT.
AND THIS IS NEAR PUNTA CANA.
YOU CAN SEE A DAMAGED RESTAURANT
IN THE AREA.
A CATEGORY THREE STORM BY THE
TIME IT BATTERED THAT ISLAND
TODAY WITH WINDS SUSTAINED AT
NEARLY 115 MILES AN HOUR.
FORECASTERS SAY MARIA REGAINED
MAJOR HURRICANE STATUS AS IT
MOVED OFF THE COAST OF THE
DOMINICAN REPUBLIC TODAY.
THE NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER
HERE IN THE U.S. REPORTS THAT
MARIA IS EXPECTED TO BRING
DANGEROUS WINDS, HEAVY WIND TO
THE TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS AND
THE BAHAMAS LATER TODAY.
MORE AHEAD IN THE FORECAST.
WE'RE LOOKING AT THE WHITE
SPREAD DAMAGE IN ST. CROIX AND
THE U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS.
IT WAS A CAT FIVE MONSTER WHEN
IT PASSED OVER-TUESDAY.
THERE'S MORE FLOODING IN
ST. THOMAS.
STEVE HARRIGAN IN SAN JUAN WITH
MORE.
>> A COUPLE OF FEET OF FLOODING
AROUND THESE APARTMENTS.
MANY PEOPLE IN THEIR BALCONIES.
THEY'RE WITHOUT ELECTRIC POWER.
PEOPLE TRUDGING THROUGH THIS
WATER WITH STICKS AS GUIDES.
OLDER PEOPLE GETTING HELP.
IT'S TOUGH TO SEE PEOPLE WALK
THROUGH WITH CHILDREN ON THEIR
BACKS OR CARRYING THEIR ITEMS IN
PLASTIC.
SOME WOMAN OVER HERE CHOP UP
WOOD WITH MACHETES AND HAMMERS
AND BUILD A COOKOUT.
IT'S OUTDOOR LIVING AT THE MOST
PRIMITIVE.
WE'VE SEEN A HYDRANT USED AS A
BATH THIS MORNING, SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: STEVE, ARE THEY
GETTING THE HELP IN THE EARLY
GOING?
>> WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT PEOPLE
INSIDE THEIR APARTMENTS OFTEN
WITH FLOOD WATER AND HOLES IN
THE ROOFS, THEY SAY THEY'RE NOT
GETTING ANYTHING.
IT'S A DO-IT-YOURSELF OPERATION.
IT'S PEOPLE TAKING RUBBISH FROM
HURRICANE IRMA AND TRYING TO USE
IT TO PROP UP A POWER LINE THAT
WAS DOWNED BY HURRICANE MARIA.
USING ONE HURRICANE TO HELP
ANOTHER.
HELP IS ON THE WAY FROM FEMA AND
FROM THE COAST GUARD.
RIGHT NOW MOODS ARE GOOD HERE.
THE PEOPLE ARE RESILIENT.
WITHOUT HELP QUICKLY, THAT COULD
CHANGE, SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: I SUSPECT SO.
STEVE HARRIGAN IN SAN JUAN.
LET'S GET MORE ON THE
HURRICANE'S PATH.
IT'S STILL ON THE MOVE AND HEAD
ADD CROSS THE CARIBBEAN.
CHIEF METEOROLOGIST RICK
REICHMUTH IN THE EXTREME WEATHER
CENTER.
RICK?
>> TURKS AND CAICOS WILL BE SPOT
THAT TAKES THE WORST OF IT.
WINDS 20 TO 50 MILES AN HOUR.
STILL MORE RAIN HERE.
FLOODING.
THE TURKS AND CAICOS, IT WILL
GET THERE CLOSE TONIGHT AND
TOMORROW.
THAT SAID, WE'RE WATCHING
TROPICAL STORM JOSE.
UP HERE ACROSS THE NORTHEAST.
THAT HAS CREATED A WEAKNESS IN
THE ATMOSPHERE.
IT'S GOING TO ALLOW MARIA TO
MOVE TO THE NORTH.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT OUR RELIABLE
COMPUTER GUIDANCE RIGHT NOW,
PULLS THIS UP BETWEEN BERMUDA
AND THE U.S.
AT THIS POINT IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
GOING TO STAY BETWEEN THAT AREA.
IT'S A SLOW-MOVING STORM.
WE'RE GOING TO BE TALKING ABOUT
A WEEK OR SO BEFORE IT GETS INTO
THIS AREA.
MORE PROBLEMS FOR THE COAST.
CERTAINLY BEACH EROSION.
AS LONG AS WE THREAT THIS NEEDLE
BETWEEN BERMUDA AND THE EAST
COAST, I THINK WE'LL BE LOOKING
GOOD.
THE OFFICIAL TRACK FROM THE
NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER SHOWS
THAT.
KEEPING THIS WELL OFFSHORE AND
THEN EVENTUALLY BY THURSDAY TO
FRIDAY OUT TO SEE.
ANY BIG IMPACTS ACROSS THE U.S.
WON'T BE FELT.
>> Shepard: FINGERS CROSSED.
THANKS, RICK.
OFFICIALS IN FLORIDA HAVE
CONFIRMED A TENTH PERSON FROM A
NURSING HOME THERE HAS DIED
AFTER HURRICANE IRMA KNOCKED OUT
AIR CONDITIONING IN THE BUILDING
FOR THREE DAYS.
HEALTH OFFICIALS ARE SUSPENDING
THAT CENTER'S LICENSE SAYING
WORKERS ACTED WITH GROSS MEDICAL
AND CRIMINAL RECKLESSNESS.
WHY DIDN'T THEY CALL 911 WHEN
THE TEMPERATURES SOARED INTO THE
TRIPLE DIGIT AND ELDERLY PEOPLE
LEFT TO COOK.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
(AVO) Lose weight and keep
it off with Contrave.
It's FDA-approved
to help adults who
are overweight or
struggle with obesity.
CONTRAVE is believed to work on
two areas of the brain:
Your hunger center...
I'm so hungry.
(AVO) To reduce hunger. And your
reward system...
Ice cream.
French fries.
(AVO) To help control cravings.
One ingredient in CONTRAVE may
increase suicidal thoughts or
actions in some children, teens,
and young adults in the
first few months.
Serious side effects are mood
changes like depression
and mania, seizures, increased
blood pressure or heart rate,
liver damage, glaucoma, allergic
reactions and hypoglycemia.
Not for patients with
uncontrolled blood pressure,
seizure history, anorexia,
bulimia, drug or alcohol
withdrawl, on bupropion,
opioids, MAOIs, allergy to the
ingredients, or pregnant.
May cause nausea, constipation,
headache and vomiting.
Reduce hunger, help control
cravings with Contrave.
Now you can talk to a doctor
online and get free shipping
at getcontravenow.com
>> Shepard: WORKERS AT THE
NURSING HOME IN FLORIDA AFTER
TEN PEOPLE DIED AFTER HURRICANE
IRMA.
HEALTH OFFICIALS ORDERED THE
FACILITY TO CLOSE.
THIS HAPPENED IN HOLLYWOOD,
FLOOR NORTH OF MIAMI.
NURSING HOME OFFICIALS HAVE
FILED A LAWSUIT DENYING ANY
WRONG DOING.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THE
DETAILS.
TRACE?
>> SHEP, FLORIDA HEALTH
OFFICIALS ARE ACCUSING THE
NURSING HOME OF GROSS CRIMINAL
AND RECKLESSNESS SAYING THE
TRAINED MEDICAL PROFESSIONALS A
TTH
Y CVELMRW OYINHEGL DELAYED
CALLING 911.
THE OFFICIALS SAY A WOMAN SHOWED
UP TO THE HOSPITAL WITH A
TEMPERATURE OF 108.3, BUT AT THE
VERY SAME TIME, SHE WAS DYING AT
THE HOSPITAL, THE NURSING HOME
RECORDED HER TEMPERATURE AT 101.
A 70-YEAR-OLD WOMAN SHOWED UP
WITH A BODY TEMPERATURE OF
109.9.
SHE DIED TEN MINUTES LATER.
JUST HOURS EARLIER, THE NURSING
HOME DESCRIBED HER OF BEING
ALERT, RECORDING HER TEMPERATURE
AT 101.
AN ELLED EARLY MAN ARRIVED AT
THE HOSPITAL WITH A BLUISH LIP
LOOK AND A BODY TEMPERATURE OF
107.
THE STATE OF FLORIDA SAYS THIS
FACILITY CANNOT CONTINUE TO HAVE
ACCESS TO PATIENTS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: NURSING HOME
OFFICIALS, I UNDERSTAND, ARE
FIGHTING BACK, TRACE.
>> YEAH, THEY ARE.
THE FACILITY HAS FILED A LAWSUIT
DENYING ANY WRONG DOING AND
ASKING A JUDGE TO ALLOW THEM TO
REOPEN.
THE NURSING HOME CONTENDS THEY
SPENT CONSIDERABLE TIME ASKING
FOR HELP, SAYING THEY CALLED THE
EMERGENCY LINE AND LEFT MULTIPLE
MESSAGES TO GOVERNOR SCOTT AND
MADE NUMEROUS REQUESTS WITH
FLORIDA POWER AND LIGHT.
REPORTS WITH THE GOVERNOR'S
OFFICE SHOW TWO DOCTORS FROM
SOUTH FLORIDA VISITED THE
RESIDENTS THE DAY BEFORE THE
TRAGEDY AND DID NOT FIND ANYONE
IN DISTRESS.
THE NURSING HOME SAYS ITS
EMPLOYEES TOOK REASONABLE
ACTIONS IN REAL TIME AND THEY'RE
UNFAIRLY BEING CRITICIZED BASED
ONLY ON HINDSIGHT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER,
THANK YOU.
SOMETHING NEW HAS JUST HAPPENED.
POTENTIALLY SOMETHING VERY
IMPORTANT.
FACEBOOK HAS JUST CONFIRMED THAT
IT WILL INDEED SHARE ADS THAT
THE RUSSIANS PURCHASED WITH
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATORS.
THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS OF
ADVERTISEMENTS DURING OUR
POLITICAL SEASON PURCHASED BY
THE RUSSIANS.
THIS IS PART OF LAWMAKERS'
INQUIRY TO RUSSIAN MEDDLING IN
OUR ELECTION AND DETAILS ARE
NEXT.
'Member that
accident I got in,
with the pole, and I had to
make a claim and all that?
Is that whole thing
still draggin' on?
No, I took some pics with
the app and filed a claim,
But, you know how they send you
money to cover repairs and -
-they took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid right away,
But, at the very end
of it all, my agent-
-wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy,
But, if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience,
for any reason...
...they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim
satisfaction guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
WHERE YOU LIVE. IN THE PLACE YOU
CALL HOME. LIFE IS GOOD. BUT FOR
SOME OF US... THERE WAS JUST ONE
THING MISSING. FAST INTERNET.
REALLY FAST INTERNET. IT'S HERE.
INTRODUCING HUGHESNET GEN5, THE
NEXT GENERATION OF SATELLITE
INTERNET. WITH FASTER SPEEDS,
MORE DATA, AND BUILT IN WI-FI.
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF WHAT YOU
LOVE ONLINE. STAY IN TOUCH,
LEARN, SHARE, WATCH VIDEOS, CHAT
WITH FRIENDS, AND GET THINGS
DONE. ENJOY HIGH SPEED INTERNET
AT HOME, WHEREVER YOU LIVE.
THERE HAS NEVER BEEN A BETTER
TIME TO GET AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE
CHOICE FOR SATELLITE INTERNET.
THE NEW HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS HERE,
AND IT'S FASTER THAN EVER.
STANDARD INSTALLATION IS FREE,
SO DON'T WAIT. CALL NOW. OR TEXT
THE PROMO CODE ON YOUR SCREEN TO
35000 TODAY.
>> Shepard: WE GOT BREAKING NEWS
JUST A MOMENT AGO.
THE FACEBOOK CEO, MARK
ZUCKERBERG THAT FACEBOOK JUST
STRUCK A DEAL WITH CONGRESS TO
REACH DETAILS ABOUT ADS THAT THE
RUSSIANS PURCHASED TO INFLUENCE
THE 2016 ELECTION.
MORE THAN 3,000 ADS APPEARED TO
HAVE COME FROM A RUSSIAN LINKED
FIRM.
FACEBOOK REPORTS THEY WILL
HAPPENED OVER THE ADS.
LET'S BRING IN CHAD DAY FROM THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS.
THIS IS A REVERSAL ON FACEBOOK'S
PART.
ZUCKERBERG IS SAYING WE HAVE TO
DO THIS, IT'S VITAL FOR THE
NATION AND ALL OF YOU OTHER
MEDIA COMPANIES YOU NEED TO DO
THE SAME THING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
SO THIS IS A BIG REVERSAL FOR
THEM.
PREVIOUSLY THEY DECIDED THEY
WEREN'T GOING TO TURN OVER THE
CONTENTS OF THE ADS THAT THEY
TRACED BACK TO RUSSIAN FIRMS
THAT WRITE POLITICAL, ON TOPICS
THAT WERE POLITICAL AND SOCIAL
ISSUES TARGETED DURING THE
CAMPAIGN.
A BIG TOPIC OF INTEREST FOR THE
COMMITTEES AND LEADERS OF THE
SENATE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
HAD BEEN TURNING OVER FOR THEM
TO TURN OVER THE CONTENTS TO ARE
YOU VERY THEM AND SEE IF THE ADS
WERE TARGETED AT SPECIFIC
GROUPS.
>> AND HOW THEY MIGHT HAVE BEEN
TARGETED TOWARDS SPECIFIC
GROUPS, WHETHER SOMEBODY LED THE
RUSSIANS TOWARD THAT.
THAT IS THE HEART OF THIS
INVESTIGATION, IS IT NOT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AS THE INVESTIGATIONS ARE
LOOKING AT THE RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN THE ELECTION BUT
LOOKING TO SEE IF THERE IS
ANYBODY ON THE AMERICAN SIDE TO
DIRECT WHERE THE ADS WOULD BE
TARGETED.
ONE OF THE MAIN THING THEY'RE
LOOKING AT, IF THEY'RE TARGETED
AT SPECIFIC GROUPS THAT COULD
DECREASE VOTER TURNOUT FOR
HILLARY CLINTON OR INCREASE
TURNOUT FOR TRUMP.
SO WHAT THE COMMITTEES
PARTICULARLY LOOKED AT, THAT'S
SOMETHING THAT AN AMERICAN
POLITICAL OPERATIVE WOULD KNOW.
SO THAT'S OF PARTICULAR INTEREST
TO THEM AND LOOKING FOR WHETHER
THERE WAS ANY COORDINATION
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
RUSSIANS IS PART OF THIS RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE.
SO FAR THE COMMITTEES HAVE SAID
WE'VE SEEN EVIDENCE OF
COORDINATION BUT THEY HAVEN'T
SAID ANYTHING CONCLUSIVELY.
>> Shepard: WHICH TAKES US BACK
TO PAUL MANAFORT WHO WAS WITH
THE CAMPAIGN FOR A SHORT PERIOD
OF TIME.
AT ANY RATE, IT'S CLEAR TO
INVESTIGATORS THAT HE OFFERED A
PRIVATE BRIEFING TO A RUSSIAN
BILLIONAIRE WITH CLOSE TIES TO
VLADIMIR PUTIN.
IT APPEARS THE FEDS WANT TO KNOW
WHY HE DID THAT AND A LOT ELSE.
>> RIGHT.
SO YOU KNOW, THIS IS AN OFF OF A
BRIEFING FOR A RUSSIAN
BILLIONAIRE WHO HAS BEEN
DESCRIBED AS BEING CLOSE TO
PUTIN.
THIS WAS SOMETHING THAT WAS
DESCRIBED IN AN E-MAIL BETWEEN
POWELL MANAFORT AND A FORMER
WORKER OR FORMER EMPLOYEE OF HIS
A UKRAINIAN NATIONAL THAT WORKED
WITH HIM ON POLITICAL CONSULTING
IN THE UKRAINE.
SO WE DON'T KNOW -- WHAT WE
DON'T KNOW YET, A LOT WE DON'T
KNOW ABOUT THIS POINT, WHETHER
THAT OFFER WENT TO THE RUSSIANS.
THE STORY WAS BROKE YET AND IT
WAS NOTED THERE WERE NO
BRIEFINGS THAT OCCURRED OR
WHETHER THIS OFFER WAS ACTUALLY
PASSED TO THE RUSSIANS.
WHAT WE DO KNOW IS THAT THE
E-MAILS ARE LEGITIMATE AND
ROBERT MUELLER HAS THEM IN HIS
POSSESSION AS WELL AS
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEES.
THEY'LL LOOK AT THIS WHEN THEY
LOOK AT DIRECT TIES OR LINKS
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
RUSSIANS.
>> Shepard: THE BIG PICTURE
QUESTION, WAS SOMEONE WITHIN THE
CAMPAIGN DIRECTING THE RUSSIANS
WHERE TO PLACE THE ADS TO HELP
DONALD TRUMP GET ELECTED AND
HURT HILLARY CLINTON'S CHANCES
TO THAT WE DON'T KNOW THE
ANSWER.
BUT THE SPECIAL PROSECUTOR IS
WORKING ON IT NOW.
CHAD DAY FROM ASSOCIATED PRESS.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Dynamic performance,
Track tuned handling,
and aggressive styling.
The bold Lexus IS.
Lease the 2017 IS Turbo for
$299 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing at
your Lexus dealer.
You totaled your brand new car.
Nobody's hurt,
but there will still be pain.
It comes when your insurance
company says they'll only pay
three-quarters of what
it takes to replace it.
What are you supposed to do?
Drive three-quarters of a car?
Now if you had Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
you'd get your whole car back.
I guess they don't want you
driving around on three wheels.
Smart.
With Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
we'll replace the full
value of your car.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>> Shepard: ON THIS DAY IN 1938,
ONE OF THE MOST DESTRUCTIVE
HURRICANES ON RECORD HIT THE
NORTHEAST.
IT CRASHED INTO NEW YORK'S LONG
ISLAND AND WENT TO CONNECTICUT.
HAD WINDS 186 MILES AN HOUR.
THE STORM DOWNED POWER LINES
WHICH STARTED CATASTROPHIC FIRES
AND FLOODING.
FORECASTERS CALLED IT THE GREAT
NEW ENGLAND HURRICANE THAT HIT
79 YEARS AGO TODAY.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
BREAKING NEWS CHANGES