THIS COMES AFTER THE PRESIDENT
ANNOUNCES A NEW TRAVEL BAN.
IT IS FIRST TWO EFFORTS HAD
LEGAL CATS, BUT THIS THE THIRD
TIME MAY JUST BE THE CHARM FOR
THE PRESIDENT.
REPUBLICAN SENATORS ARE TAKEN
ANOTHER TRY AT CHANGING
OBAMACARE.
THEIR DEADLINE IS THIS WEEK, AND
A COUPLE OF KEY COLLEAGUES SAY
THEY ARE NOT ON BOARD.
WE WILL SEE WHO WILL NEED TO
CHANGE THEIR MIND AND WILL THE
PLAN WERE?
WILL GIVE YOU PUERTO RICO, WILL
AMERICANS NEED HELP AFTER A
TERRIBLE HURRICANE.
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH FOOD, GAS AND
THE CLEANUP EFFORT THAT COULD BE
MEASURED IN MONTHS.
LET'S GET TO IT.
>> BREAKING NEWS.
"SHEPARD SMITH REPORTING" LIVE
FROM THE FOX NEWS DESK.
>> Shepard: TIME IS RUNNING
OUT FOR REPUBLICANS TO GET
SOMETHING DONE BEFORE THEY BRING
IN DEMOCRATS OR MORE
REALISTICALLY, MOVE ON.
CAP A HELL RIGHT NOW ON
HEALTH CARE ALSO PROTESTS OVER
THE REPUBLICAN PLAN AND SOME
PROTESTERS BEING DRAGGED OUT OF
THE HEARING.
THE WHITE HOUSE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS TO SPEAK AT ANY TIME NOW ON
JOBS, BUT WE ARE ALSO WATCHING
TO SEE THE PRESIDENT CONTINUE TO
PUT THE PRESSURE ON HIS OWN
PARTY.
IN HOPES OF AVOIDING ANOTHER
FAILURE ON HEALTH CARE.
SENATE REPUBLICAN YESTERDAY
ADDED MORE MONEY AND USED
RESTRICTIONS AS PART OF THE BILL
KNOWN AS GRAHAM-CASSIDY BILL.
THE ADDITIONAL FUNDING WILL GO
TO STATES LIKE ALASKA, ARIZONA,
KENTUCKY, MAINE, AND TEXAS.
ALL OF THOSE ARE STATES, THAT
HAVE A SENATOR THAT SAID HE OR
SHE IS VOTING NO, OR NOT RIGHT
NOW, OR HAS NOT YET COMMITTED.
WE REPORTED, SO REPUBLICANS CAN
AFFORD TO ONLY LOSE TWO VOTES IN
PASSIVE
IF NOTHING CHANGES, IT IS DEAD
ON ARRIVAL.
SENATOR JOHN McCAIN AND
RAND PAUL HAVE ALREADY SAID THEY
ARE AGAINST.
TED CRUZ OF TEXAS SAID, HE IS
OUT KNOW AT THIS MOMENT.
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS AND MIKE
LEE ARE LEANING NO, AND LISA
MAKOWSKI IS PUBLICLY UNDECIDED
JOHN ROBERTS IS A LIFE OR IS
THERE THIS AFTERNOON AND IN
SPITE THE NOTE COUNTS, THE
WHITE HOUSE IS PUSHING FOR A
VOTE.
>> THEY ARE PUSHING.
THEY ARE TRY TO GET 50 VOTES
BEFORE THE END OF THE WEEK, AS
YOU MENTION.
THEREFORE, MAYBE SIX HOLDOUTS.
YOU LISA MURKOWSKI,
JOHN McCAIN, SUSAN COLLINS OF
MAINE, WAITING FOR THE CBO SCORE
TO COME OUT IN THE NEXT HOUR OR
SO.
RAND PAUL IS AGAINST THIS,
POSSIBLY TED CRUZ AND MIKE LEE
AS WELL.
TWEAKS TO THE PLAN THAT WOULD
GIVE MORE MONEY TO EAT CERTAIN
STATES THE PRESIDENT TWEETING
FROM
ALASKA, ARIZONA, MAINE,
KENTUCKY, OUR BIG IN HEALTH CARE
OF, SEVEN YEARS OF REPEAL AND
REPLACE, SOME SENATORS NOT THER
THERE.
SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS TOLD US
AT A BRIEFING AT THE WHITE HOUSE
THEY ARE PULLING OUT ALL THE
STOPS TO TRY TO GET THIS THING
ACROSS THE FINISH LINE.
LISTEN HERE.
>> WHETHER OR NOT THERE IS A
VOTE, WE SURE HOPE SO.
WE'VE BEEN CALLING ON CONGRESS
TO DO WHAT THEY WERE ELECTED TO
DO.
CERTAINLY WHAT MOST OF THEM HAVE
CAMPAIGNED ON, AND THAT IS TO
REPEAL AND REPLACE OBAMACARE.
WE ARE CONTINUING TO PUSH
FORWARD.
WE KNOW WE CANNOT LIVE WITH THE
OBAMACARE STATUS QUO.
>> THE PRESIDENT ALSO TAKING
JOHN McCAIN OUT TO THE
WOODSHED AFTER HE SAID
DEFINITIVELY THAT HE IS AGAINST
THE GRAHAM-CASSIDY BILL.
LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID ON THE
"RICK AND BUBBA SHOW."
>> YOU LOOK AT WHAT
JOHN McCAIN HAS DONE, A
TREMENDOUS SLAP IN THE FACE OF
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY.
TREMENDOUS.
HE WAS GOOD TO GO ALL WEEK LONG,
ALL MONTH LONG, HE WAS GOOD TO
GO, AND ALL OF A SUDDEN, THUMBS
DOWN.
YOU CAN CALL WHAT YOU WANT THAT
WAS A -- THAT'S THE ONLY REASON
WE DO NOT HAVE IT, BECAUSE OF
JOHN McCAIN.
>> THE PRESENT CONTINUING TO PUT
THAT
HOME SAYING, JOHN McCAIN HAD
NEVER INTENTION TO VOTE FOR THE
BILL, WHICH IS GOVERNOR LOVES.
LET ARIZONA DOWN AND THEN'S WENT
ON TO SAY, DEMOCRATS ARE
LAUGHINGLY SAME, A MOMENT OF
COURAGE.
TELL THAT TO THE PEOPLE OF
ARIZONA WHO RECEIVED 100%
INCREASE.
THE PRESENT IS TALK ABOUT THE
HEALTH CARE COSTS.
>> Shepard: THIS HEALTH CARE
AND VOTE.
THE NUCLEAR CRISIS WITH
NORTH KOREA LIKE NOTHING WE HAVE
SEEN SINCE THE COLD WAR.
THERE'S CLEANUP AND RECOVERY IN
PUERTO RICO, AND IN TEXAS, AND
OF FLORIDA, AND A LONG, LONG
LIST COMING AT THE WHITE HOUSE
KEEPS TWEETING ABOUT FOOTBALL.
>> YES, AND THIS STARTED ON
FRIDAY NIGHT, SHEP, WHEN HE WAS
DOWN IN ALABAMA AT A RALLY FOR
SENATOR LUTHER STRANGE, WHO IS
IN THE FIGHT OF HIS LIFE.
AND TOMORROW NIGHT'S PRIMARY.
THE PRESIDENT ZEROING IN ON
RESPECT FOR THE AMERICAN FLAG
AND GOING ON TO SAY, HE WISHES
THE SUM OF THESE NFL OWNERS, ANY
TIME THE PLAYER TAKES A KNEE
DURING A NATIONAL ANTHEM, WOULD
TELL THOSE SOBS THAT THEY ARE
FIRED.
I ASKED SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS
ABOUT THE COMMENTS, WHETHER THEY
WERE TOO STRIDENT AT THE
BRIEFING A SHORT TIME AGO, GIVEN
THE REACTION THAT THEY PROVOKED
OVER THE WEEKEND.
LET'S LISTEN TO THAT EXCHANGE.
>> DID THE PRESIDENT GO TOO FAR?
>> I THINK IT IS ALWAYS
APPROPRIATE FOR THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITES STATES TO DEFEND OUR
FLAG, DEFEND THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM, AND TO DEFEND
THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO FOUGHT AND
DIED TO DEFEND A.
>> AS HE SAID OVER THE WEEKEND,
SOME 200 PLAYERS OUT OF 1600
EITHER TOOK A KNEE AT THE
VARIOUS GAME OR IN THE CASE OF
THE PITTSBURGH STEELERS,
SEATTLE SEAHAWKS, AND ONE OTHER
TEAM, AND ACTUALLY STAYED INSIDE
THE LOCKER ROOM RATHER THAN
COMING OUT.
FOR THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
ONE NOTABLE EXCEPTION, ALEJANDRO
VILLANUEVA FOR THE PITTSBURGH
STEELERS, WHO DID THREE TOURS OF
DUTY AS AN ARMY RANGER IN
AFGHANISTAN HE WAS THE LONE
PLAYER DURING THAT GAME TO COME
OUT OF THE TUNNEL PUT HIS HAND
OVER HIS HEART AND STAND FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
ROGER THE NFL COMMISSIONER SAID,
THE FRUSTRATION OVER THE VICE OF
RHETORIC THAT WE HEARD FROM
TRUMP.
TOM BRADY, THAT PATRIOT ON THE
RADIO CALLED THE PRESIDENT'S
COMMENTS DIVISIVE AND SAID, HE
DID NOT AGREE WITH WHAT THE
PRESIDENT SAID.
AND NOW NASCAR IS WEIGHING IN ON
ALL OF IT.
OFFICIAL STATEMENTS INCOME IN
SPORTS ARE UNIFYING INFLUENCE IN
OUR SOCIETY, PUTTING PEOPLE OF
DIFFERENT BACKGROUNDS AND
BELIEFS TOGETHER.
I RESPECT FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM HAS ALWAYS BEEN
A HALLMARK OF OUR PRERACE
EVENTS.
THANKS TO THE SACRIFICES OF
MANY, WE LIVE IN A COUNTRY OF
UNPARALLELED FREEDOMS AND CALLUS
LIBERTIES, INCLUDING THE RIGHT
TO PEACEFULLY EXPRESS ONE'S
OPINION.
DESPITE THE FACT THAT TEAM OWNER
SAID HE WANTED HIS TEAM MEMBERS
TO STAND UP FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM, DALE
EARNHARDT JR. TWEETED, ALL
AMERICANS ARE GRANTED RIGHTS TO
PEACEFUL PROTESTS.
THOSE WHO MAKE PEACEFUL
REVOLUTION IMPOSSIBLE WILL MAKE
VIOLENT REVOLUTION INEVITABLE.
QUOTING JFK.
>> Shepard: JOHN, THANK YOU.
THE TOP ADMINISTRATION ANNOUNCED
A NEW BAN, BUT IT'S CLIMATE
NOTHING MORE THAN WINDOW
DRESSING ON MUSLIMS.
HIS TEMPER A BAND ON TRAVELERS
ELECTED TO EXPIRE.
FROM SIX MAJORITY MUSLIM NATIONS
FROM ENTERING UNLESS THEY HAD A
SOUL CARD SO-CALLED BONA FIDE
RELATIONSHIP HERE IN THE U.S.
NOW, SUDAN IS FINE, AND OFF THE
LIST.
IT'S NEIGHBOR CHAD IS NOW ON THE
LIST, AND VENEZUELA.
ALTHOUGH THE RESTRICTIONS APPLY
ONLY TO A GROUP OF GOVERNMENT
OFFICIALS AND THEIR FAMILIES.
THE CHANGES TAKE EFFECT ON
OCTOBER THE 18TH.
THE HOME UNSECURED OFFICIALS SAY
THE EIGHT NATIONS EITHER FAILED
TO SHARING OF INFORMATION WITH
THE UNITED STATES OR DID NOT
TAKE ENOUGH SECURITY PRECAUTIONS
IN MAKING THE ANNOUNCEMENT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID THIS IS ALL
ABOUT SECURITY.
THE PRESIDENT TWEETING, MAKING
AMERICA SAFE IS MY NUMBER ONE
PRIORITY.
WE WILL NOT ADMIT THOSE INTO OUR
COUNTRY THAT YOU CANNOT SAFELY
BET.
NEW TODAY, THE SUPREME COURT
CANCELED ARGUMENTS FOR NEXT
MONTH WITH HIS OLD TROUBLE BAND
AFTER HE ANNOUNCED NEW
RESTRICTIONS, CIVIL RIGHTS
GROUPS SAY THE NEW BAN ISN'T
COVERED, NORTH KOREA AND
VENEZUELA ON THE LIST, THE STILL
AMOUNT TO A MUSLIM BAN.
SIX OF PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
TARGETED COUNTRIES ARE MUSLIM,
THE FACT THAT TRUMP HAS ADDED
NORTH KOREA, WITH FEW VISITORS,
AND
AND A FEW GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS
FROM VENEZUELA, IS DOES NOT
CONCEAL THE REAL FACT THAT IT IS
STILL A MUSLIM BAN.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ORIGINAL STANCE
CANNOT BE CURED BY THROWING
OTHER COUNTRIES ON THE ENEMY
LIST.
BACK TO JOHN ROBERTS AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
JOHN?
>> THE PRESIDENT, SHEP, BELIEVE
THAT BY MODIFYING THE TRAVEL
BAN, IT WILL PASS MUSTER IN THE
COURTS.
YOU BET THEIR ORGANIZATIONS LIKE
THE ACL YOU, WILL GO TO TRY TO
GET STOPPED AS WELL.
THE PRESIDENT BELIEVES THAT BY
WRITING THESE OUT TO INCLUDE
CHAD AND NORTH KOREA INSERTED
OFFICIALS FROM VENEZUELA, A GETS
THEM OUT OF THAT IDEA THAT SO
MANY PEOPLE TALKED ABOUT.
YOU READ THAT STATEMENT FROM THE
ACLU, THIS IS SIMPLY MUSLIM BAN,
IT'S HOPEFULLY ONE THAT CAN
MUSTER IN THE COURTS, BECAUSE
THE RESTRICTIONS ARE TAILORED TO
INDIVIDUAL COUNTRIES.
CERTAINLY, THE WATERFALL OF
CRITICISM CONTINUES TO BE AIMED
AT THE PRESIDENT WHETHER IT IS
ON CAPITOL HILL WITH THE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY FROM
CIVIL LIBERTARIAN GROUPS, YOU
WILL HEAR A LOT ABOUT THIS IN
THE COMING DAYS, SHEP, DESPITE
THE FACT THAT THE SUPREME COURT
PUT ON HOLD THE HEARINGS THAT
WERE SCHEDULED FOR THE TENTH
SAYING, WITH THE NEW TROUBLE
BAND IN PLACE, THOSE HEARINGS
ARE MOOT.
>> Shepard: JOHN ROBERTS AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
LET'S GO TO JAIL, REPORTER WITH
THE ASSOCIATED PRESS
HEALTH CARE.
THAT OVER OR NOT?
THERE ARE SO MANY DIFFERENT
THINGS GOING ON WITH THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THEY ARE PLANNING A NEW TAX
REFORM PLAN THIS WEEK AS WELL.
THEY ARE ASPIRING TO MULTIPLE
DIFFERENT FRONTS RIGHT NOW.
HEALTH CARE, IT STILL SEEMS
THEY'RE CROSSING THE FINGERS
REALLY, REALLY HOPING THAT
THEY'LL BE ABLE TO PULL A COUPLE
OF SENATORS OVER THE LINE AND
SAY THIS BILL.
EVEN THE PRESIDENT HAS
ACKNOWLEDGED HIS COMMENTS THAT
MIGHT NOT HAPPEN THIS TIME
AROUND.
>> Shepard: WHICH OF THOSE
MIGHT BE AVAILABLE FOR THE
PULLOVER AS YOU DESCRIBED?
>> WE WILL HAVE TO SEE A REPORT
SAYS TODAY, BUT IT IS NOT
LOOKING GOOD.
>> Shepard: AND FOR OUR
VIEWERS, THE REPORT WILL BE A
FULL REPORT.
THEY'LL BE SOME GUIDANCE, IT
WILL GET SOMETHING FROM THAT
INHERE FROM THOSE ON
CAPITOL HILL AS A RESULT.
ON THESE OTHER MATTERS, JILL,
LOTS OF DISCUSSION TODAY ABOUT
FOOTBALL, BUT I WOULD RATHER
STICK TO THE REAL ISSUES AT
HAND.
THE NORTH KOREA BACK AND FORTH
REGARDING NUCLEAR WAR, IT SOUNDS
LIKE THE NORTH KOREANS ARE NOW
THREATENING -- THEY ARE
THREATENING TO SHOOT DOWN OUR
JETS IN THAT REGION.
THE WHITE HOUSE -- THEY PLAN TO
SEE MORE ON THIS?
>> IS ESCALATING TO A POINT THAT
AMERICANS NEVER HAVE SEEN.
YET THE FOR MR. SAINT TODAY THAT
THE PRESIDENT'S COMMENTS OVER
WEEKEND HAS COME IS A THREAT OF
WAR AND SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS
SAINT, WE ARE NOT THREATENING
WAR.
WE WILL NOT GO TO WAR WITH KORE
KOREA.
THE PLAN RIGHT NOW NONETHELESS,
THESE ARE VERY SCARY WORDS
COMING FROM PERSONALITIES, WHO
REALLY SEEM TO BE ESCALATING THE
RHETORIC AGAINST ONE ANOTHER.
SPIEL WE HAVE NOT SEEN THIS SORT
OF
THING SINCE THE COLD WAR, AND I
WONDER IF THERE ARE MEETINGS OR
DISCUSSIONS UNDERWAY TO TRY TO
CAMPED ON THE RHETORIC AND ALL
THOSE WITH IT, BECAUSE OUR
UNDERSTANDING WHAT THEY REALLY
WANT IS TO GET TO THE TABLE AND
TALK ABOUT THIS.
SPEAK OUT THERE HAS BEEN SOME
CONVERSATIONS THROUGH
INTERMEDIARIES TAKING PLACE.
PEOPLE AT THE WHITE HOUSE, WHO
ARE CONCERNED ABOUT THIS
ESCALATING RHETORIC FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S TWEETS, ESPECIALLY
THOSE THAT ARE SPECIFICALLY
GOING AFTER KIM JONG UN
PERSONALLY AND CREATING A
PERSONAL WAR BETWEEN THESE TWO
MEN, WHO ARE VERY MUCH
INTERESTED IN STICKING TO THEIR
HEELS.
AS ONE OF THE SITUATIONS, WHERE
THEY ARE VERY FEW GOOD OPTIONS,
AND THE WHITE HOUSE HAS BEEN
THINKING AND CONSIDERING WHAT
THEIR OPTIONS ARE INCLUDING
MILITARY OPTIONS.
>> Shepard: YOU WROTE ON THE
TRAVEL BAN, IS A TRAVEL BAN --
WILL GO THROUGH NOW OR IS THERE
MORE TO COME?
>> WE HAVE TROUBLE BAND 1.0,
2.0, THIS IS 3.0 THAT HE SIGNED
ONE DAY.
WHAT IS DIFFERENT, ESPECIALLY
FROM THE FIRST ONE THAT THEY
PUSH THROUGH JANUARY, IS REALLY
THE AMOUNT OF TIME THAT THE HHS
AND STATE DEPARTMENT HAVE SPENT
COMING UP WITH A STANDARD THAT
THEY USE TO PICK WHICH COUNTRY
WOULD BE IMPLEMENT IT, IMPACTED.
THERE ARE VERY CONCERNED ABOUT
POTENTIAL LEGAL CHALLENGES, AND
WHAT THEY HAVE DONE THIS FOR
MONTHS AND MONTHS GOING THROUGH
ALL OF WHAT THEY THINK ARE THE
REQUIREMENTS THAT THEY WANT FROM
COUNTRIES.
AS PEOPLE COME TO THE
UNITED STATES, THINGS LIKE
WHETHER THOSE COUNTRIES GIVE
THEIR CITIZENS PASSPORTS.
WHETHER THEY REPORTED STOLEN AND
COUNTERFEIT PASSPORTS TO
INTERPOL.
WHETHER THEY SHARE INFORMATION
WITH THE U.S. ABOUT TERRORIST
LINKS.
THE U.S. PUT TOGETHER THAT SET
OF BENCHMARKS, WENT THROUGH
EVERY COUNTRY IN THE WORLD IT'S
A COME HERE THEY ARE.
YOU COMPLY AND COME TO OUR
COUNTRY, OR YOU DO NOT COMPLY,
AND YOU WILL HAVE RESTRICTIONS
PLACED ON YOU.
THE GOVERNMENT SAID, THESE EIGHT
COUNTRIES OF THE EIGHT COUNTRIES
THAT DO NOT LIVE UP TO THOSE
REQUIREMENTS.
>> Shepard: JILL COLVIN,
REPORTER FOR THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS.
HIS THE REPEAL OF OBAMACARE
DEAD?
NOT IF REPUBLICANS CAN HELP IT.
HOW THEY'RE TRYING TOET O GN
AR
ITDBOHEH WLT H TREH EAN. PCA
LA
AT COMING UP AT THE FOX NEWS
DECK ON THIS MONDAY.
♪ ♪
Um... who are you?
I'm Val. The Orange Money
retirement squirrel from Voya.
I represent the money you save
for the future. See?
We're putting away acorns to
show the importance of being
organized.
That's smart. Who's he?
He's the green money you can
spend now. What's up?
Oh you know, gonna pay some
bills, maybe buy a new tennis
racket.
Tennis racket for a squirrel?
He's got a killer backhand.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement, it's time to get
Voya.
SPILL IT MORE NOW ON REPUBLICANS
PUSH TO CHANGE OBAMACARE.
THE PARTY FACING AN UPHILL
BATTLE IS IN SOME OF ITS OWN IT
CENTERS HAVE COME OUT AGAINST
THE GRAHAM CASSIDY PROPOSAL.
REPUBLICANS CONTROL THE SENATE.
52-48, AS REPORTED, THEY CAN
LOSE BUT TO SENATORS IN ORDER TO
BE SUCCESSFUL SINCE ALL
DEMOCRATS SAY THEY WILL VOTE NO.
UNLESS SOMETHING CHANGES, IT
DOES NOT LOOK GOOD FOR THE
G.O.P.'S LATEST EFFORT.
MIKE EMANUEL IS LIVE ON
CAPITOL HILL WITHOUT SENATE
FINANCE COMMITTEE IS HOLDING A
HEARING.
MIKE, WHAT IT'S LIKE THERE, AND
HOW WERE THEY TRYING TO GET
SENATORS TO CHANGE THEIR MIND?
>> SHEP, THEY OFFERED SWEETENERS
OVER THE WEEKEND, MORE SPENDING
TO STATES LIKE ALASKA AND MAINE,
HOPING THEY GET THEM ON BOARD.
GOOD OLD-FASHIONED LEGISLATION
TO GET YES VOTES.
BOTTOM LINE IN THE HALLWAY HERE
OUTSIDE THE COMMITTEE, IT IS
REALLY, REALLY LOUD.
YOU CAN SEE IS PICKING UP A BIT
RIGHT NOW.
ALL THE DISRUPTION HERE, PEOPLE
EXPRESSING THEIR FIRST AMENDMENT
RIGHT.
THE CHAIRMAN MAKING THIS
ANNOUNCEMENT.
>> IF THE HEARING IS GOING TO
INVOLVE INTO A SIDESHOW OR A
FORUM SIMPLY FOR PUTTING PARSON
POINTS ON THE BOARD, THERE IS
ABSOLUTELY NO REASON FOR US TO
BE HERE.
I AM SAYING THIS TO THE BENEFIT
OF MY COLLEAGUES.
LET'S HAVE A CIVIL DISCUSSION.
>> HE REPUBLICANS CLEARLY
LOOKING TO HAVE THIS HEARING
THIS WEEK ON A CRITICAL WEEK FOR
HIS HEALTH CARE REFORM PUSH BY
REPUBLICANS.
IT IS NOT CLEAR HOW FAR IT WILL
GO, BUT THEY'RE GIVING IT THEIR
BEST SHOT.
BOTTOM LINE, THEY'RE TRYING TO
GET THE 58 REPUBLICAN YESES
WHICH FEELS A LOT LIKE JULY,
WHEN THEY KEPT SAYING THEY WERE
GETTING CLOSE, BUT NEVER DID
QUITE GET THERE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: AND IF THEY DO NOT
GIVE 50 REPUBLICANS, DELECTABLE
AND DEMOCRATS, AND I ASSUME THEY
MAY AS WELL FORGET THAT
>> FORGIVE ME.
I'M HAVING TROUBLE HEARING.
IN TERMS OF THE DEMOCRAT SIDE OF
THINGS, WE JUST TALK TO HAWAII
SENATOR, WHO FELT GOOD ABOUT
THINGS, BUT SAID IT IS NOT OVER
TILL IT IS OVER.
UNTIL THESE FILLED BY ME, KEEP
FIGHTING.
ANOTHER KEY DEMOCRAT SAID REJECT
THIS EFFORT BY THE PUBLICANS.
>> NOBODY HAS GOT TO BUY A LEMON
JUST BECAUSE IT IS THE LAST CAR
ON THE LOT.
THIS TRUMP CARE BILL IS A
HEALTH CARE LEMON.
A DISASTER IN THE MAKING.
>> AT THE START OF A VERY
EMOTIONAL WEEK.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WITH
DISABILITIES ARE HERE TODAY
ALONG WITH ACTIVISM PROTESTERS.
SENATORS GETTING AN EAR FULL
FROM FOLKS AS THEY WORK ON
HEALTH CARE.
>> Shepard: I HEAR THEM
SAYING, HEALTH CARE IS A HUMAN
RIGHT.
HAS THIS BEEN GOING ON ALL DAY.
MIKE, HAS THIS BEEN GOING ON ALL
DAY?
DESCRIBED FOR US.
>> I AM SORRY, SHEP.
IT IS HARD TO HEAR.
THERE WERE LINED UP HERE ALL
DAY.
THEY REALLY GOT LOUD AROUND 2:00
OR SO, WHEN SENATORS WERE GOING
IN TO THE VERY ROOM FOR THIS
HEARING.
IT DIED DOWN A LITTLE BIT WHEN
SOME WERE ARRESTED, DISPERSED BY
CAPITOL POLICE.
THEY ARE FIRING UP AGAIN,
PERHAPS WITH THE SENATORS IN THE
HALLWAY OR JUST WANTING TO
EXPRESS THEIR FIRST AMENDMENT
RIGHT OF A SHEP.
>> Shepard: MIKE EMANUEL IN
THE WHOLE OF CONGRESS, THANK YO
THANK YOU.
BRACING FOR THE HEALTH CARE
EFFORTS TO FAIL.
THAT IS A WORD FROM OUR NEXT
GUEST, WHO SAID, THERE IS VERY
SIMPLE REASON THIS BILL CANNOT
PASS.
WHAT IS THAT REASON?
SHE WILL HAVE IT FOR US NEXT.
♪ ♪
Brad.
And then you totaled him.
You two had been through
everything together.
Two boyfriends, three jobs...
you're like
nothing can replace Brad.
Then Liberty Mutual calls...
and you break into
your happy dance.
If you sign up for
Better Car Replacement™,
we'll pay for a car that's
a model year newer
with 15,000 fewer miles
than your old one.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
I count on my
Dell Small Business Advisor
for tech advice.
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪♪
You do all this research
on a perfect car,
then smash it into a tree.
Your insurance company
raises your rates.
Maybe you should've done
more research on them.
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't
raise your rates due to
your first accident.
Switch and you could save $782
on home and auto insurance.
Call
for a free quote today.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>> Shepard: IF YOU ARE THE
G.O.P., AND YOU WANT TO PASS
THIS NEW HEALTH CARE BILL,
BAILEY YOU WANT TO CRUSH
OBAMACARE AND GET RID OF
IT, HOW DO YOU GET ENOUGH
SENATORS ON BOARD TO MAKE IT
HAPPEN?
WHAT DO YOU DO?
THE SEARCH TO A CONGRESSIONAL
REPORTER FOR "POLTICO."
THEY ARE TRYING, WHAT CAN THEY
DO, RACHEL?
SPEAK OUT NOT MUCH MORE
THERE BRACING FOR FAILURE RIGHT
NOW.
THAT IS BECAUSE ON THE ONE SITE,
HAVE CONSERVATIVES WHO WANT TO
TAKE THIS BILL TO THE RIGHT.
TED CRUZ, RAND PAUL, WANTING
LESS REGULATION, BUT THEN YOU
LOSE PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS
PAIRED PEOPLE RELYING ON
MEDICAID ARE VULNERABLE, AND YOU
HAVE A LOT OF MODERATES WHO ARE
HOLDING OUT AND WORRIED ABOUT
SUPPORTING, BECAUSE I THINK IT
WILL HURT PEOPLE WHO RELY ON
THESE PROGRAMS.
TO ADD ON TOP, THE PROTEST THAT
WE'RE SEEING RIGHT NOW, I JUST
DON'T SEE SUSAN COLLINS,
LISA MURKOWSKI, JOHN McCAIN
SAYING THEY WILL BACK THIS.
A LOT OF MY REPUBLICANS
COLLEAGUE SOURCES ARE SAYING,
THIS WILL NOT GO ANYWHERE.
>> Shepard: WHAT MADE THEM
THINK THAT THIS TIME WOULD BE
DIFFERENT?
WHY BRING THIS UP AGAIN TO WHAT
APPEARS AT LEAST FOR NOW TO BE A
FAILURE, IF YOU DID NOT HAVE
SOMETHING TO PLACATE THOSE WHO
ARE VOTING NO?
>> I THINK TWO THINGS.
THE TIME ISSUE.
RIGHT NOW, REPUBLICANS ONLY HAVE
UNTIL THE END OF THE WEEK TO
PASS AN OBAMACARE REPEAL.
ONCE WE HIT SATURDAY, THEY
CANNOT DO THIS ANYMORE, BECAUSE
THEY LOSE THE ABILITY TO
CIRCUMVENT DEMOCRATS AND BYPASS
THE FILIBUSTER IN THE SENATE.
THAT GOES AWAY.
IT DISAPPEARS.
REPUBLICANS ARE HOPING BECAUSE
OF THE TIME PRESSURE, PEOPLE
WOULD FEEL LIKE THEY HAD TO
SUPPORT SOMETHING RIGHT NOW,
EVEN IF THEY DID NOT LIKE
EVERYTHING LEGISLATION LOOK
REPUBLICANS, GRAHAM AND CASSIE,
WERE GOING TO THROW
MORE MONEY AT OPPONENTS.
PUTTING MONEY IN ALASKA, ARIZON
ARIZONA, AND ALSO KENTUCKY
SQUARELY AT SENATORS, WHO ARE
OPPOSED.
THE ISSUE IS, YOU CANNOT BUY
THESE GUYS ARE.
JOHN McCAIN'S COMPLAINT IS NOT
ABOUT MONEY AS MUCH IT IS ABOUT
PROCESS.
HE WANTS MORE COMMITTEE
HEARINGS.
ALSO RAND PAUL, HE HATES THE
IDEA OF SENDING MONEY TO THE
STATES.
THERE SHOULD NOT BE ANY FEDERAL
HEALTH CARE MONEY.
GET RID OF THAT.
THESE ARE THINGS YOU CANNOT
BRIDGE PEOPLE BY, AND
REPUBLICANS, THE TIME IS
TICKING, AND THEY WANT TO DO
SOMETHING, BUT THEY ARE IN A BAD
SPOT RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: AND
PRESIDENT TRUMP TALKING ABOUT
NORTH KOREA ON THE ONE HAND AND
RATCHETING THAT UP AND ON THE
OTHER HAND, ALL THE RACISM WITH
THE NFL.
HE HAS NOT BEEN TWEETING ABOUT
HEALTH CARE AT ALL.
DOES HE CARE ABOUT THIS?
>> WELL, HE CERTAINLY SAYS HE
DOES.
I CAN TELL YOU REPUBLICANS ON
THE HILL ARE VERY UPSET ABOUT
THE FACT THAT HE IS IN A WAR
RIGHT NOW WITH THE NFL.
THEY SAY IT IS A DISTRACTION.
IT THEY COULD REALLY USE HIS
HELP GETTING THIS ACROSS THE
FINISH LINE, AND ANOTHER THING
COMING HERE SUPPOSED TO MAKE A
BIG PUSH ON TAX REFORM.
WE ARE GOING TO SEE THEM PUT OUT
A BUNCH OF DETAILS ON TAX
REFORM.
HE WAS GOING TO GO OUT AND
SUPPORT.
LOOK AT THE FRONT PAGE OF THE
PAPERS RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE SEEING SEEING AGAIN, LIKE
YOU SAID, THE SPATS AND THESE
ARE NOT THINGS THAT REPUBLICAN'S
WANT TO TALK ABOUT.
>> Shepard: REPUBLICANS MAY
NOT WANT IT, RACHEL, BUT THIS
THING, I READ THE EMAIL.
I HAVE TWITTER, I LET THEM TAKE
CARE OF IT.
IT IS VERY CLEAR THAT FOR HIS
BASE, DISSES THE RED MEAT OF ALL
RED MEAT.
THEY ARE ABLE TO RECLAIM THIS?
THEY'RE ABLE TO SAY, THEY WERE
ATTACKING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM,
ATTACKING THE TROOPS, ATTACKING
THE FLAG.
NONE OF WHICH THEY ARE DOING.
THEY'RE NOT DOING ANY OF THAT.
THEY'RE UPSET ABOUT RACIAL
INJUSTICE IN THE COUNTRY, AND
THEY'RE UPSET ABOUT THE THINGS
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID, AND
HE TURNS IT AROUND FOR HIS BASE.
IS THIS ALL A PLAY TO HIS BASE,
AND COULD POSSIBLY BE SO THEY DO
NOT NOTICE, THERE IS NO
HEALTH CARE AND NORTH KOREA IS
THE BIGGEST MESS SINCE THE
COLD WAR?
>> A DISTRACTION HE WANTS RIGHT
NOW, RIGHT?
A PLACE TO A CORNER OF HIS BASE,
FRACTION.
I'LL TELL YOU I'LL TALK TO A
REPUBLICAN ABOUT THIS COUPLE OF
HOURS AGO.
THEY DO NOT SEE THIS HELPFUL AT
ALL.
THESE PROTESTERS WERE A FEW
PLAYERS COME AND THEY'RE BARELY
GETTING ANY HEADLINES, AND THEN
TRUMP ATTACKS THEM, AND ATTACKED
THE NFL, NEVER SINCE THEN, HE
RATCHETED IT UP SO YOU HAVE 200
PLAYERS TAKING A KNEE OR BACK IN
THE LOCKER ROOM, NOT STANDING
FOR THE NATIONAL ANTHEM, AND IT
IS AN UGLY DISPUTE RIGHT NOW.
PEOPLE IN GENERAL DO NOT LIKE IT
WHEN PEOPLE PROTEST THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> Shepard: THEY'RE NOT
PROTESTING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
THAT IS NOT WHAT THEY ARE DOING.
>> IT HAS BECOME MORE ABOUT THE
FLAG, OBVIOUSLY, BECAUSE THE
FOLKS FEEL THE PRESIDENT IS
GOADING BLACK FOOTBALL PLAYERS
AFTER THE CHARLOTTESVILLE
CONTROVERSY A FEW WEEKS LATER.
IT'S BATTLEGROUND FOR
REPUBLICANS.
>> Shepard: RACHEL BADE, GREAT
TO SEE YOU FROM "POLTICO."
KEEP IT UP.
MORE ON THE SHOWDOWN WITH
NORTH KOREA AFTER THE
WHITE HOUSE DISMISSES THE CLAIM
THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
DECLARED WAR ON NORTH KOREA.
THAT IS COMING UP IN 2 MINUTES
PAIRED WHAT WE LEARNED ABOUT THE
MAN WHO POLICE SAY SHOT PEOPLE
INSIDE A CHURCH IN TENNESSEE.
IN THE USHER WHO RISKED HIS LIFE
TO TAKE DOWN THE GOVERNMENT.
THAT IS STRAIGHTAWAY.
♪ ♪
and I know that we have
Accident Forgiveness.
So the incredibly minor
accident that I had tonight...
Four weeks
without the car.
Okay, yep. Good night.
With Accident Forgiveness,
your rates won't go up
just because of an accident.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
(AVO)
When you have type 2 diabetes,
you manage your A1C,
your rates won't go up
just because of an accident.
but you also have a higher risk
of heart attack or stroke.
Non-insulin Victoza®
lowers A1C,
and now reduces
cardiovascular risk.
Victoza® lowers my
A1C and blood sugar
better than
the leading
branded pill.
(AVO)
And for people with
type 2 diabetes
treating cardiovascular disease,
Victoza® is NOW approved
to lower the risk of major
cardiovascular events
such as heart attack,
stroke, or death.
And while it isn't
for weight loss,