Just to know this
is what I'm made of,
this is where
my ancestors came from.
And I absolutely want to know
more about my
Native American heritage.
It's opened up
a whole new world for me.
Discover the story
only your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now at
AncestryDNA.com.
I work
overtime when
I can get it.
I need my blood
sugar to stay
in control.
Weekends
are my time.
I need an insulin
that fits
my schedule.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
(announcer)
Tresiba® is used
to control high blood sugar
in adults with diabetes.
Don't use Tresiba® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during
episodes of low blood sugar,
or if you are allergic
to any of its ingredients.
Don't share needles
or insulin pens.
Don't reuse needles.
The most common side effect
is low blood sugar,
which may cause dizziness,
sweating, confusion,
and headac..
Check your blood sugar.
Low blood sugar can be serious
and may be life-threatening.
Injection site reactions
may occur.
Tell your prescriber
about all medicines you take
and all your medical conditions.
Taking TZDs with insinins
like Tresiba®
may cause serious side
effects like heart failure.
Your insulin dose shouldn't
be changed
without
asking your prescriber.
Get medical help right away
if you have trouble breathing,
fast heartbeat,
extreme drowsiness,
swelling of your face,
toueue, or throat,
dizziness, or confusion.
Ask your health care provider
if you're Tresiba® ready.
Covered by most insurance
and Medicare plans.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
>> Shepard: CONTINUING KOMPL.
LINDSAY GRAHAM RESPONDING TO THE
ANNOUNCEMENT FROM SENATOR JOHN
McCAIN THAT HE WILL VOTE NO ON
THE LATEST REPUBLICAN HEALTHCARE
MAN.
SENATOR GRAHAM IS A CO-SPONSOR
OF THE BILL.
HE WROTE IN A STATEMENT, HIGH
FRIENDSHIP WITH JOHN McCAIN IS
NOT BASED ON HOW HE VOTES BUT
RESPECT FOR HOW HE'S LIVED HIS
LIFE AND THE PERSON HE IS.
I RESPECTFULLY DISAGREE WITH HIS
POSITION NOT TO PROCEED FORWARD.
THE BILL IS ONE VOTE AWAY FROM
FAILING.
WE'RE STIT WAITING TO HEAR WHEN
THE SENATE MAJORITY LEADER,
MITCH McCONNELL, WILL BRING TO
IT FLOOR FOR A VOTE.
U.S. AND RUSSIAN GENERALS COMING
FACE-TO-FACE THIS WEEK,
SOMEWHERE, UNDISCLOSED LOCATION
IN THE MIDDLE EAST FOR
DISCUSSIONS.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM A U.S.
MILITARY SPOKESMAN.
THIS MEETING JUST DAYS AFTER THE
PENTAGON ACCUSED RUSH YAF OF
WOMING U.S.-BACKED FIGHTERS IN
EASTERN SYRIA WITH AMERICAN
SPECIAL FORCES DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
TO THE ACTION.
RUSSIA THREATENED TO RETALIATE
IF ITS TROOPS COME UNDER FIRE
WHILE FIGHTING ALONG SIDE SYRIAN
FORCES.
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS SAY THEY WILL
TARGET AREAS THAT AMERICAN UNITS
OCCUPY IF NECESSARY.
THAT'S A THREAT.
IT'S BRINGING TO THE FOREFRONT
THE REAL POSSIBILITY OF DIRECT
CONFRONTATION BETWEEN THE UNITED
STATES AND RUSSIAN FORCES INSIDE
SYRIA.
WHERE A CIVIL WAR HAS BEEN GOING
ON FOR MORE THAN SIX YEARS.
A PROXY WAR BETWEEN THE UNITED
STATES AND RUSSIA.
JENNIFER GRIFF WIN THE NEWS AT
THE PENTAGON, WHAT THE LATEST ON
THE GROUND SYRIA?
>> THE RUSSIAN MILITARY
ANNOUNCED IT FIRED CRUISE
MISSILES FROM ITS SUBMARINE IN
THE IMMEDIATE TRAINION SEA ON
MILITANT POSITIONS IN WESTERN
SYRIA.
U.S. TROOPS WEREN'T NEARBY.
TENSIONS ARE RUNNING HIGH IN
EASTERN SYRIA AFTER THAT RUSSIAN
GENERAL THREATENED TO ATTACK
AMERICAN TROOPS AND THE MILITIA.
THEY'RE ADVISING RIGHT NOW,
THERE'S A STANDOFF ON THE BANKS
OF THE YOU A FRAY TEASE RIVER
BETWEEN RUSSIAN AND AMERICAN
BACKED FORCES.
BOTH SIDES ARE ESSENTIALLY
EYEBALL-TO-EYEBALL.
THE U.S. MILITARY ACCUSED
RUSSIAN JETS OF BOMBING
U.S.-BACKED FIGHTERS LAST
WEEKEND AS YOU MENTION.
NO U.S. TROOPS WERE HURT.
BUT YESTERDAY, A RUSSIAN GENERAL
WARNLD THE UNITED STATES RUSSIA
WOULD ATTACK IF THE FORCES CAME
UNDER FIRE.
THIS IS A PHOTOGRAPH OF THE
HOTLINE TELEPHONE USED BY THE
U.S. MILITARY TO CALL THEIR
RUSSIAN COUNTERPARTS AND DEACON
FLIKT, IF YOU WILL, IN THE
CROWDED SKIES OVER SYRIA.
IT IS LOCATED THE AIR BASE IN
QATAR WHERE THE U.S. RUNS THE
AIR WAR AGAINST ISIS.
IT IS USED WE'RE TOLD ABOUT A
DOZEN TIMES EACH DAY.
AT THE PENTAGON, HOSTING HIS
POLISH COUNTERPART, DEFENSE
SECRETARY JIM MALTIS WAS ASKED
IF HE WAS WORRIED ABOUT MORE
RUSSIAN AIR STRIKES AGAINST
U.S.-BACKED FIGHTERS AND THEIR
AMERICAN ADVISORS IN SYRIA.
>> NO, I'M NOT WORRIED, WE DEAL
WITH THE RUSSIANS IN A
COLLABORATIVE WAY AND WE'LL SORT
IT OUT.
>> THE U.S. AND RUSSIA ARE
BARRED BY LAW FROM COOPERATING
TOGETHER.
CONGRESS PASSED A LAW AFTER
RUSSIA'S INVASION OF UKRAINE IN
2014.
THAT DIDN'T STOP AMERICAN AND
RUSSIAN GENERALS FROM MEETING
FACE-TO-FACE IN RECENT DAYS, ON
THE GROUND, TO DEFUSE THE
ESCALATING SITUATION.
>> Shepard: WHAT ABOUT THE FIGHT
AGAINST ISIS?
>> ALL EYES ARE ON THE KURDISH
AREAS OF NORTHERN IRAQ WHERE A
CONTROVERSIAL REFERENDUM ON
INDEPENDENT EVENS IS TAKING
PLACE ON MONDAY.
U.S.-BACKED FORCES FIGHTING TO
CLEAR ISIS FROM ITS
SELF-PROCLAIMED CAPITAL IN SYRIA
HAVE CLEARED WE'RE TOLD 70% OF
RA" A.
UP TO 900 ISIS FIGHTERS IN
RACKIA.
IN IRAQ THE OPERATION TO PLIB
RATE ONE OF THE LAST POCKETS
THAT ISIS CONTROLS IN IRAQ.
AS IF THE PENTAGON DOESN'T HAVE
ENOUGH TO KEEP IT'SES ON, RUSSIA
TEST FIRED AN INTERCONTINENTAL
BALLISTIC MISS WILL A 7,500 MILE
RANGE CAPABLE OF HITTING ANY
CITY IN THE UNITED STATES.
PENTAGON OFFICIALS SAY THE U.S.
WAS WARNED ABOUT THE TEST LAUNCH
IN ACCORDANCE A WITH
LONG-STANDING TREATMENTIES.
RUSSIA HAS BEEN USING SYRIA FOR
TESTING.
THAT HAS THE PENTAGON CONCERNED.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
OUR NEXT GUEST IS THE COMMANDER
OF THE AIR WAR AGAINST THE
ISLAMIC STATE, LIEUTENANT
JEFFREY COBRA HARIGIAN HAS
DIRECTED SOME OF THE BIGGEST
EVENTS IN THE FIGHTING INCLUDING
THE NINE-MONTH FIGHT FOR THE
CITY OF MOSUL.
THIS PHOTO FROM MOSUL YESTERDAY.
MUCH OF THAT CITY IS DEVASTATED
FROM THE FIGHTING.
THE GENERAL IS AN AIR FORCE
FIGHTER PILOT WITH MORE THAN 30
YEARS EXPERIENCE.
HE FLIES OVER IRAQ AND SYRIA
NOW, THIS SHOT FROM JUNE AS HE
REFUELED DURING A RISHGS.
THE GENERAL IS ALSO A PURPLE
HEART RECIPIENT N1996 HE WAS
STATIONED IN SAUDI ARABIA WHEN
HE WAS INJURED IN THE BOMBING OF
THE KOBAR TOWERS.
19 AIRMEN DIED IN THAT ATTACK,
SOME 300 OTHERS HURT.
LT. GENERAL JEFFREY COBRA
HARIGIAN, CENTRAL COMMAND, HAN
HONOR TO HAVE YOU.
>> IT'S GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> DOES ANYTHING CHANGE IN
REGARDS TO THE RUSSIANS?
>> STEP ONE IS MANAGE THE DEACON
FLICKS, GET BACK TO THE FIGHT
AGAINST ISIS.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO WORK WITH AND
IN COORDINATION WITH THE TEAM TO
MAKE SURE WE HAVE DEACON FLIKTED
TO GET OF ONE IN THE SIGS FIGHT.
WE'LL GET THE TEAM IN POSITION
TO ENSURE THERE'S NOT A
STRATEGIC MISCOMMUNICATION THAT
CAN OCCUR.
>> Shepard: THE RUSSIANS WERE
FIRING ON OTHERS, OUR SPECIAL OP
FORCES NEARBY.
IT WAS TOO CLOSE.
AND WE SAID, BASICALLY, DON'T DO
IT AND THEY SAID WE'LL FIRE ON
YOU.
DOES THAT CHANGE ANYTHING ON THE
GROUND?
>> WELL, I THINK THE IMPORTANT
PART TO REMEMBER HERE IS WE WILL
PROTECT OUR FORCE.
IT SHOULD BE CRYSTAL CLEAR IN
EVERY AMERICAN'S MIND THAT WE'RE
FOG TO PROTECT OUR FORCE.
WE WORK THROUGH THIS, I THINK
THE PRODUCTIVE CONVERSATION THAT
NEEDS TO OCCUR IS GETTING BACK
TO FIGHTING ISIS, DE-CONFLICTING
OUR FORCES, ENSURING THE
MECHANISM TO DO THAT, WHAT IS
REQUIRED IS A CONTINUED
COVERINGS WITH THE RUSSIANS TO
MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
>> Shepard: WE HAD A MEETING
THAT HAPPENS AT UNDISCLOSED, ALL
THE REST, A MEETING YOU WOULD
HAVE ATTENDED HAD YOU NOT BEEN
HERE.
>> I HAD A REPRESENTATIVE THERE.
AND THAT REPRESENTATIVE GAVE ME
FULL FEEDBACK ON HOW THAT PLAYED
OUT.
AND THERE'S WORK TO BE DONE.
>> I KNOW WE CAN'T KNOW DETAILS,
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW DETAILS.
I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW, IF YOU CAN
TELL US, ARE THINGS GETTING
BETTER.
>> THERE WAS PROGRESS MADE.
IT WILL BE PIECEMEAL AND IT WILL
TAKE TIME.
THE KEY IS AS WE MOVE FORWARD WE
WORK THROUGH DE-CON FLICKS THAT
ALLOWS US TO CONTINUE OUR FIGHT.
AT THE END OF THE DAY WE WANT TO
ENCIRCLE AND ANNIHILATE ISIS
PARTICULARLY IN THE MIDDLE
EUPHRATES RIVER VALLEY.
>> IS THAT WHAT THE RUSSIANS
WANT?
ARE WE ABLE TO COMMUNICATE?
WE'RE NOT ABLE TO COMMUNICATE
TEAM-TO-TEAM, RUSSIANS AND
AMERICANS.
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY HAVE
COMMUNICATED TO US.
PUT AT THE END OF THE DAY AS YOU
KNOW, ACTIONS SPEECH LOUDER THAN
WORDS.
WE HAVE TO WORK OUR WAY THROUGH
THAT, FROM OUR PERSPECTIVE MAKE
SURE THAT OUR AIRMEN, OUR
TEAMMATES ON THE GROUND, OUR
SOLDIERS AND OUR PARTNERS ARE IN
A POSITION TO CONTINUE THAT
FIGHT AGAINST ISIS.
>> Shepard: OUR UNDERSTANDING OF
THINGS IS THAT WE'RE BOMBING
MORE TARGETS IN SYRIA, ISIS
RELATED, THAN IN THE PAST.
IS THAT BECAUSE THERE ARE MORE
TARGETS OR IS IT SOMETHING ELSE?
>> WELL I THINK IT'S COMBINATION
OF WHAT WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO DO TO
DEVELOP TARGETS.
OVER TIME, AS WE'VE SPENT TIME
USING OUR INTELLIGENCE,
SURVEILLANCE, AND RECON SAYS
ASSETS WE HAVE A BETTER
UNDERSTANDING OF THE
ENVIRONMENT.
THE SECOND BIG PIECE IS THE
SIRRIAL DEMOCRATIC FORCES ARE ON
THE MOVE.
IN RA" A, THE GREAT SUCCESS,
ALONG WITH THE MIDDLE EUPHRATES
RIVER VALLEY THAT, DRIVES
ACTIVITY.
>> Shepard: SYRIAN DEMOCRATIC
FORCES.
THAT'S THE ONES WE FIGHT WITH
AGAINST THE GOVERNMENT?
>> YES, SIR.
THAT'S IT.
>> Shepard: ARE THEY GETTING
BETTER AT WHAT THEY DO, AND ARE
THEY -- CAN THEY STAND UP?
>> WOULD I TELL YOU, THEIR
ASYMMETRIC ADVANTAGE IS AIR
POWER.
WE PROVIDE THE CAPABILITY TO
REMAIN ON THE OFFENSIVE.
AND PUT THEMSELVES IN A POSITION
TO SUCCEED.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SEE TODAY.
>> Shepard: THE CRITICS SAID
REPEATEDLY THAT OUR AIR FORCE IS
WORKING FOR IRAN IN THAT MATTER.
>> I WOULD DENY THAT.
>> Shepard: I WOULDN'T SUGGEST
ANYTHING ELSE.
BUT WE CAN SEE WHERE THEY'RE
COMING FROM.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT I THINK IMPORTANTLY, WE ARE
SUPPORTING THE SBS IN THEIR
OPERATION, THE SYRIAN DEMOCRATIC
FORCES, TO DELIBERATE THESE
CITIES IN SYRIA.
THEY HAVE PROVEN EFFECTIVE AT
DOING THAT AND WE'RE SUPPORTING
THEM EVERY DAY AND CONTINUE TO
DO THAT.
>> Shepard: WHEN YOU TAKE OUT
ISIS WHAT HAPPENS THEN?
>> WHAT WE HAVE TO DO IS
FACILITATE THE ABILITY FOR THE
POLITICAL PROCESS TO TAKE PLACE
SO THAT GOVERNANCE CAN OCCUR
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND ALLOW THE
PEOPLE TO GET BACK TO WORK.
THE KIDS TO GET BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> Shepard: THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
FROM EVERYTHING WE SEE IT LOOKS
LIKE SYRIA IS PRETTY WELL
DESTROYED.
>> THAT WILL BE A HEAVY LIFT.
BUT THE SYRIAN DEMOCRATIC FORCES
COMBINED WITH OUR PRECISION
TARGETING HAVE DONE AS MUCH AS
THEY CAN DO TO ENSURE THAT
INFRASTRUCTURE REMAINS STANDING.
GO AHEAD.
>> Shepard: I DIDN'T MEAN TO
INTERRUPT.
I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU ABOUT
IRAQ.
IT APPEARS THAT THERE'S VERY
GOOD PROGRESS THERE.
IN FACT, FROM A LOT OF READING
OVER THE LAST 24 HOURS, IT
SOUNDS LIKE THEY'RE COLLAPSING
MORE QUICKLY THAN HAD BEEN
ANTICIPATED.
>> I COMPLETELY AGREE WITH YOU.
THE WORD I'M USING IS MOMENTUM.
THEY HAVE MOMENTUM.
IT'S BECAUSE THE IRAQIE SKRT
FORCES PROVE THEMSELVES TO BE
VERY CONFIDENT IN WHAT THEY'RE
DOING.
THE SECURITY FORCES.
THEY LEMPLED THE SKILLS THAT WE
BRING TO SUPPORT THEM.
WHAT YOU SEE IS A GROWING
NATIONALISM INSIDE OF IRAQ.
THEY OWN THIS.
THE OTHER PIECE THAT I WOULD
THROW OUT IS WHAT I'VE SEEN ON
THE GROUND IS THEY'VE BEEN
COURAGEOUS, THEY'VE BEEN HEROIC
IN THE FIGHT AND THE PEOPLE
APPRECIATE WHAT THEY'VE DONE TO
LIBERATE THEM.
>> Shepard: I HAVEN'T HEARD THAT
BEFORE, THE OTHER TIMES THAT WE
HAVE ENGAGED OURSELVES WITH
GENERALS OF YOUR ILK HAVE SAID
OTHER THINGS.
THE POINT IS, AS YOU'VE WATCHED
THIS MATURE OVER TIME THE
IRAQIES HAVE BEEN UP FRONT.
WE ARE IN AN ADVISE AND ASSIST
OPERATION.
THAT'S HOW WE SUPPORT THEM.
WHEN YOU COMBINE THE OPERATIONS
WITH THE ASYMMETRIC FORCES OF
THEIR POWER, THEY ARE SUCCEEDING
AND BRINGING IN FORCES THAT
MAINTAIN THE STABILITY TO ALLOW
GOVERNANCE TO OCCUR.
>> Shepard: YOU TALK ABOUT IRAQI
NATIONALISM, THAT'S HARD TO
FIND.
THE KURDS MORE THAN EVER WANT
OUT.
THEY'RE ORGANIZING AND THEY
DON'T WANT TO BE IRAQ, THEY WANT
TO BE KURDISTAN.
>> THE KURDISH REFERENDUM IS
SOMETHING WE'RE ALL CONCERNED
ABOUT.
POLITICALLY THAT WILL BE
SOMETHING THAT WILL NEED TO BE
SORTED OUT.
FROM THE MILITARY PERSPECTIVE WE
WANT TO ENSURE THEIR STABILITY
AND SECURITY THAT FACILITATES
POLITICAL PROGRESS TO BE MADE.
>> Shepard: WILL THERE COME A
TIME WHEN THEY CAN TAKE CARE OF
THEMSELVES?
HOW WILL WE KNOW WHEN THAT IS?
>> THAT'S THE PLAN.
BUT WE HAVE TO ALLOW THAT TO
TAKE TIME.
THAT'S GOING TO TAKE A WHILE FOR
THAT TO OCCUR.
WE WILL LAY OUT METRICS AS WE
MOVE INTO THE NEXT PHASE OF THE
CAMPAIGN, THAT WOULD LAY OUT
WHAT WOULD BE THE APPROPRIATE
TIME FOR US STARTING TO HAND
OVER THE RESPONSIBILITIES
PARTICULARLY FROM A SUPPORT ON
THE MILITARY SIDE PERSPECTIVE.
>> Shepard: WE READ REPORTS THAT
THE AIR FORCE DOESN'T HAVE
ENOUGH BOMBS.
AND WHATEVER YOU READ SOMETHING
LIKE THAT AS A JOURNALIST, YOU
THINK THEY WANT MORE FUNDING.
WE ALSO WANT MORE FUNDING,
EVERYONE DOES.
OR DO WE HAVE A CRITICAL BOMB
SHORTAGE?
>> I'VE BEEN MANAGING THIS FROM
THE DAY I TOOK COMMAND 15 MONTHS
AGO.
IT'S AN ISSUE WE HAVE WORKED
THROUGH CLOSELY WITH THE AIR
FORCE AND DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE.
AND THERE'S A CONCERN OUT THERE,
CLEARLY, AS YOU LOOK AT THE
BUDGET AND ABILITY TO FORECAST
LONG TERM, CONTINUING
RESOLUTIONS DO NOT HELP OUR
ABILITY TO PROCURE THE WEAPONS
IN THE LONG TERM THAT WE NEED.
>> Shepard: YOU NEED A BUDGET.
>> THAT WOULD BE HELP.
>> Shepard: HOW IS WASHINGTON
RESPONDING?
>> I THINK THEY HEAR US BUT I'LL
COME BACK TO THERE IS TALKING
BUT WE NEED TO SEE ACTION TO GET
THE BUDGET RESOLVED.
>> Shepard: DOES THE LACK OF A
BUDGET, JUST CONTINUING
RESOLUTION, MAKE YOUR JOB AND
THE MILITARY JOB HARDER?
>> IT CONCERNS ME.
THE ANSWER TO THAT IN THE SHORT
TERM IS YES.
IT DRIVES US TO HAVE CHALLENGES
THAT WE WOULD BE ABLE TO NOT
HAVE TO DEAL WITH HAD THERE BEEN
A BUDGET.
>> Shepard: YOU HAVE HAD
PROBLEMS WITH SOME PLANES.
THERE'S BEEN TALK OF TAKING THEM
OUT OF THE THE MIX.
WHERE IS THAT?
>> I THINK AT THIS POINT, WE'VE
BEEN ABLE TO WORK THROUGH THAT
AND AS YOU LOOK AT THE RESOURCES
THAT I HAVE, AVAILABLE TO ME,
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO EXECUTE THE
FIGHT EVERY DAY WITHOUT HAVING
TO WORRY ABOUT THOSE ASSETS
BEING PULLED BACK.
>> Shepard: WHEN YOU LOOK AT
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH NORTH
KOREA, THE BACK AND FORTH
RHETORICALLY AND OTHERWISE,
WHAT'S YOURS GREATEST CONCERN?
>> WELL, I THINK AT THE END OF
THE DAY ALL OF US ARE CONCERNED
ABOUT THIS ESCALATING INTO
SOMETHING THAT NO WOULD WANTS TO
HAPPEN.
THAT IS OUT OF MY AREA OF
RESPONSIBILITY.
BUT AS AN AMERICAN, THERE IS A
CONCERN THERE THAT I THINK WE
ALL SHOULD BE WARY OF.
AND HOPE THAT WE CAN FIND A
DIPLOMATIC SOLUTION TO THIS
PROBLEM.
>> Shepard: WHAT KEEPS YOU UP AT
NIGHT?
>> WELL AT THE END OF THE DAY IN
MY AREA OF RESPONSIBILITY, IS
THE POSSIBILITY OF A STRATEGIC
MISCALCULATION.
WE ARE NOT THERE TO FIGHT
RUSSIA.
WE ARE NOT THERE TO FIGHT SYRIA.
OUR JOB IS TO CRUSH ISIS AND
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING EVERY
DAY.
I WORRY THAT WE PUT OUR AIRMEN,
OUR COALITION TEAM, IN A
POSITION WHERE STRATEGIC
MISCALCULATION COULD OCCUR.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE WORKING THIS
DE-CONFLICT.
>> Shepard: YOU USE THAT PHONE
WITH THE RUSSIANS?
>> I DON'T USE INTEREST BUT MY
GUYS DO EVERY DAY.
>> WHAT HAPPENS ON THAT PHONE?
>> THE INTERESTING PART IS I
HAVE SOME YOUNG AIRMEN THAT WE
BRING IN, THAT ARE INTERPRETERS.
SO WE'LL TALK, THEY'LL RESPOND
AND OUR INTERPRETERS, THESE
YOUNG AIRMEN, TRANSLATE FOR US.
IT'S INCREDIBLE THE CONTEXT THAT
THEY GIVE US WITH THEIR
UNDERSTANDING OF THE RUSSIAN
LAYMEN.
IT'S FASCINATING, IT'S BEEN A
LESSON IN LEADERSHIP AS WE WORK
THROUGH NEGOTIATING WITH THE
RUSSIANS ON HOW WE DE-CONFLICT
OUR OPERATIONS.
>> Sandra: IS IT WE'RE HERE,
DON'T GO THERE, OR IS IT BIGGER
PICTURE THAN THAT.
>> ALL OF THE ABOVE.
EVERY DAY, YOU KNOW, IF WE SEE
SOMETHING WE DON'T LIKE WE CALL
THEM.
WE WILL TRY TO MANAGE THE
DE-CONFLICTION, BUT IT'S A
CONVERSATION THAT ENSURES WE'RE
BEING CRYSTAL CLEAR WHAT WE DO.
GENERALLY WE COULD WHAT WE NEED
TO DO TO PROTECT OUR FORCE.
>> Shepard: YOU COMING IN HOT ON
THAT PHONE?
>> OCCASIONALLY, YES, SIR.
>> Shepard: GENERAL, I CAN'T
THANK YOU ENOUGH.
ALL OF THE BEST AND THANK YOU
FOR WHAT YOU DO FOR OUR NATION.
>> IT'S A PLEASURE TO BE HERE.
WHAT YOUR YOUNG AMERICANS ARE
DOING AND WHAT THE COALITION
TEAM IS DOING IS SOMETHING FOR
US ALL TO BE PROUD OF.
>> Shepard: HERE, HERE.
THANK YOU, TO ALL OF YOUR
COLLEAGUES, APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP
DOWNPLAYING THAT RUSSIANS BOUGHT
ARIZONA DURING THE ELECTION.
WHAT ABOUT THE TOTALLY BIASED
AND DISHONEST MEDIA COVERAGE IN
FAVOR OF COOKED HILLARY?
FACEBOOK REVEALED THIS WEEK THAT
FAKE ACCOUNTS BASED IN RUSSIA
BOUGHT AROUND 3,000 POLITICAL
ADS OVER THE PAST COUPLE OF
YEARS.
THE COMPANY ANNOUNCED YESTERDAY
IT WILL TURN OVER THE ADS TO
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATORS
LOOKING INTO RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN THE ELECTION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS ACCUSED
DEMOCRATS OF USING RUSSIA AS AN
EXCUSE FOR LOSING THE ELECTION.
THE KREMLIN SPOKESMAN DECLINED
THAT MOSCOW PLACED ADS ON
FACEBOOK AT ALL AND CLAIMED HIS
PEOPLE DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO DO
THAT.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THE
BACKSTORY.
TELL US MORE ABOUT WHAT FACEBOOK
IS DOING.
>> DURING THE FACEBOOK LIVE
STREAM, THE CEO SAID HE CARES
DEEPLY ABOUT THE DEMOCRATIC
PROCESS AND PROTECTING ITS
INTEGRITY.
BECAUSE OF THAT HE IS
IMPLEMENTING A SERIES OF STEPS
THE COMPANY PLANS ON TAKING TO
ENSURE THAT THIS DOES NOT HAPPEN
AGAIN.
HE ALSO GAVE AN EXPLANATION FOR
HOW IT MIGHT HAVE HAPPENED IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
WATCH.
>> MOST ADS ARE BOUGHT
PROGRAMMATICALLY THROUGH THE
APPS WITHOUT AN ADVERTISER
SPEAKING TO SOME ONE AT
FACEBOOK.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
EVEN WITHOUT OUR EMPLOYEES
DIRECTLY INVOLVED IN THE SALES,
WE CAN DO BETTER.
BY DOING BETTER HE MEANS
FACEBOOK WILL IMPROVE ITS REVIEW
PROCESS, ADD MORE PEOPLE TO THE
SECURITY TEAM, AND START
PARTNERING WITH ELECTION
COMMISSIONS THAT WILL ALSO
INCREASE TRANSPARENCY, REQUIRING
POLITICAL ADVERTISERS TO DECLARE
EXACTLY WHO IS PAYING FOR THE
AD.
ZUCKER BERG SAID THERE WILL
ALWAYS BE BAD PEOPLE IN THE
WORLD AND ENDING ALL
INTERFERENCE ISN'T REALISTIC.
SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT DO THESE ADS
LOOK LIKE?
WHAT WERE THEY ADVERTISING?
>> FACE BECOME SAID THE ADS IN
QUESTION CAME FROM ABOUT 470
PHONY ACCOUNTS.
THE ADS THEMSELVES DID NOT
REFERENCE THE U.S. ELECTIONS,
VOTING, OR ANY CANDIDATE IN
PARTICULAR.
INSTEAD THEY SPREAD, QUOTE,
DIVISIVE SOCIAL AND POLITICAL
MESSAGES AYOS THE IDEOLOGICAL
SPECTRUM, TOPICS OF LGBT
MATTERS, TO RACE, TO GUN RIGHTS.
FACEBOOK SAID THEY TARGETED
CERTAIN PARTS OF THE COUNTRY AND
MAJORITY RAN IN 2015.
AND NOW, THE SENATE INTEL
COMMITTEE WANTS FACEBOOK AND
OTHER SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANIES TO
TESTIFY ABOUT RUSSIA'S
INVOLVEMENT IN THE 2016
ELECTION.
YOU CAN BET THESE ADS WILL
CERTAINLY BE A PART OF THAT
HEARING.
THE COMMITTEE CHAIR SAYS HE'S
VERY INTERESTED IN JUST HOW MUCH
SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANIES ACTUALLY
KNOW ABOUT RUSSIAN ACTIVITIES ON
THEIR VARIOUS SITES.
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER
LIVE, THANK YOU.
VIOLENCE BREAKING OUT IN
NEW YORK CITY DURING A SPEECH BY
THE TURKISH PRESIDENT.
PEOPLE IN THE CROWD PUNCHING A
PROTESTER.
THIS IS NOT THE FIRST TIME THE
TURKISH PRESIDENT SUPPORTERS
HAVE GOTTEN VIOLENT IN THE
UNITED STATES.
THAT'S NEXT.
I count on my
Dell Small Business Advisor
for tech advice.
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪♪
NEW YORK CITY DURING A SPEECH BY
If you have Medicare
Parts A and B
guess what?
You could apply for a
Medicare supplement insurance
plan whenever you want.
No enrollment window.
No waiting to apply.
That means now may be a
great time to shop for an
AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Medicare doesn't
cover everything.
And like all standardized
Medicare supplement
insurance plans,
these help cover some
of what Medicare
doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide.
It could help you find the
AARP Medicare Supplement plan
that works for you.
These types of plans have
no networks,
so you get to choose any
doctor who accepts
Medicare patients.
Rates are competitive,
and they're the only plans
of their kind endorsed by AARP.
Remember -
these plans let you apply
all year round.
So call today.
Because now's the perfect time
to learn more.
Go long.
>> Shepard: OTHER PEOPLE IN THE
CROWD PUNCHES HIM.
WITH THE TURKISH.
.
THAT WAS IN NEW YORK CITY AND
THERE'S VIDEO.
[CROWD NOISE]
STATE DEPARTMENT OFFICIALS SAY
IT DID NOT APPEAR THAT TURKISH
OFFICIALS INVOLVED IN THE FIGHT.
BUT THEY HAVE GOTTEN VIOLENT
WITH PROTESTERS BEFORE.
LAURA ENGLE IS LIVE WITH US.
>> HEY, SHEP.
IT'S NOT ALWAYS CALM WHEN THE
TURKISH PRESIDENT VISITS THE
U.S.
WE KNOW.
AND THAT WAS NO DIFFERENT LAST
NIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT IS IN NEW YORK FOR
THE UNITED NATIONS GENERAL
ASSEMBLY, IN THE MIDDLE OF HILLS
ADDRESS TO THE TURKISH AMERICAN
NATIONAL STEERING COMMITTEE AT A
HOTEL WHEN PROTESTERS ATTEMPTED
TO SHOUT HIM DOWN.
THAT IS WHEN THINGS GOT OUT OF
CONTROL.
VERY QUICKLY.
THE TURKISH PRESIDENT'S ADDRESS
TURNED INTO THIS MELEE WHEN THE
PROTESTER SCREAMED WHY THE
YOU'RE A TERRORIST GET OUT OF MY
COUNTRY."
NOW, AS THE SECURITY DETAIL
START READ MOVING PROTESTERS,
AUDIENCE MEMBERS BEGAN PUNCHING
AND SLAPPING THE PROTESTER AS
SECURITY MOVED IN AND STARTED
TAKING PEOPLE OUT FROM THE ROOM.
A SECURITY ALSO REPORTEDLY
KICKED OUT ONE PERSON WHO
ALLEGEDLY ASSAULTED A PROTESTER.
THOSE INVOLVED SAY THEIR ACTIONS
ARE IN RESPONSE TO VIOLENCE.
TURKEY HAS INFLIKTED ON KURDISH
MUSLIMS INSIDE TURKEY.
PROTESTS HAVE BEEN BREAKING OUT
DURING HIS APPEARANCE AROUND THE
WORLD.
THIS IS HIS VISIT TO ECUADOR IN
THE LAST YEAR.
THEN IN MAY, MEMBERS OF HIS
SECURITY TEAM WERE CAUGHT ON
VIDEO ATTACKING A GROUP OF
PEACEFUL PROTESTERS OUTSIDE THE
TURKISH AMBASSADORS RESIDENCE IN
WASHINGTON.
NINE PEOPLE WERE HOSPITALIZED.
THIS SCENE PROMPTED SECURITY
OFFICIALS WERE INDICTED.
AS FOR YESTERDAY NOBODY WAS
INJURED, IN ARRESTS.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
THE TURKISH PRESIDENT HAS JAILED
THOUSANDS OF POLITICAL OPPONENTS
AND 120 JOURNALISTS, WHO HE
CALLS TERRORISTS.
YOUR WORLD WITH NEIL CAVUTO
BEGINS AFTER THIS.
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
Every year we take
a girl's trip.
Remember Nashville?
Kimchi BBQ.
Amazing Honky Tonk??
I can't believe
you got us tickets.
I did.
I didn't pay for anything.
You never do.
Send me what I owe.
I've got it.
I mean, You did find money
to buy those boots.
Are you serious?
Is that why
you don't like them?
Those boots could
make a unicorn cry.
Yeah, tears of joy.
The Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
The fast, secure and
simple way to send money.
Today, we're out here
with some big news
about type 2 diabetes.
You have type 2 diabetes,
right?
Yes.
So let me ask
you this...
How does diabetes
affect your heart?
It doesn't, does it?
Actually, it does.
Type 2 diabetes
can make you twice
as likely to die
from a cardiovascular event,
like a heart attack or stroke.
And with heart disease,
your risk is even higher.
You didn't know that.
No.
Yeah.
But, wait, there's good news
for adults who have
type 2 diabetes
and heart disease.
JARDIANCE is the only
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit.
JARDIANCE is proven to both
significantly reduce
the chance of dying from a
cardiovascular event
in adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease
and lower your A1C.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy,
faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious
side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting,
stomach pain, tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic reaction
include rash, swelling,
and difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects
are sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE
with a sulfonylurea
or insulin may cause
low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So now that you know all that,
what do you think?
That it's time to think
about JARDIANCE.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE.
And get to the heart
of what matters.
♪
It's not just a car,
it's your daily treat.
♪
Go ahead, spoil yourself.
The ES and ES Hybrid.
Experience amazing.