ONE THAT THEY RIGHTFULLY
SERVE.
>> THANK YOU.
YOU SAID THE PLAN WILL ADD $2.2
TRILLION TO THE DEFICIT.
IS IT WRONG?
>> WE THINK THEY'RE WRONG.
WE THINK THEY'RE WRONG BECAUSE
THE WAY THEY SCORE.
BUT LET'S NOT ARGUE THAT.
WE OFFICIALLY BELIEVE THAT THIS
TAX PLAN WILL HAVE A DRAMATIC
IMPACT ON ECONOMIC GROWTH.
WE KNOW THAT 1% CHANGE IN GDP
WILL ADD $3 TRILLION BACK.
SO IF THEY'RE RIGHT, WE'RE ONLY
GOING TO PAY DOWN $80 BILLION
OF THE DEFICIT.
I'LL LIVE WITH THAT.
>> THANK YOU, GARY.
ON THE CORPORATE SIDE, YOUR
CRITICS SAY ON THE REPATRIATION
OF OVERSEAS ASSETS THAT HISTORY
WOULD SHOW THAT COMPANIES DON'T
ALWAYS USE THE ASSETS WHEN
THEY'RE REWAIT -- REPATRIATED.
HOW CAN YOU GUARANTEE THAT?
>> IF THAT'S OUR WORSE CASE
SCENARIO, COMPANIES USE IT FOR
BUY BACKS AND DIVIDENDS, WHAT
HAPPENS?
THEY BUY BACK SHARES AND
DIVIDENDS WITH GET MORE TAXES ON
GAINS AND DIVIDENDS AND THE
PEOPLE DO WHAT?
THEY REINVESTMENT IN NEW CAPITOL
AND INVESTMENTS.
WE'RE PUTTING ENTICING RULES
INTO THE SYSTEM THAT WILL ENTICE
PEOPLE TO INVEST CAPITAL THE
NEXT FIVE YEARS.
WE'RE GIVING PEOPLE A FIVE-YEAR
WRITE OFF TO EXPENSE.
IF THAT HAPPENS, THAT'S FINE.
WE KNOW THAT MONEY WILL GET
INVESTED IN THE ECONOMY AND
DRIVE WAGES, GROWTH AND
PROSPERITY.
>> YOU'VE BEEN ASKED IT TWICE
AND YOU DIDN'T ANSWER.
I GET YOUR MESSAGE ON THE MIDDLE
CLASS.
THIS TAX PLAN APPEARS IT WILL
BENEFIT THE PRESIDENT AND HIS
FAMILY.
WHY NOT BE CANDIDATE ABOUT THAT?
>> I TOLD YOU IT WILL BENEFIT
THE MIDDLE CLASS.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT AMERICAN
TAXPAYERS CARE ABOUT, WHAT THEY
TAKE HOME.
THEY CARE ABOUT WHAT THEY HAVE
TO SPEND.
THAT'S WHAT THEY CARE ABOUT.
THAT'S WHAT I CARE ABOUT.
I CARE ABOUT -- I BET YOU CARE
ABOUT WHAT YOU PAY IN TAXES.
>> HE'S SAYING HE WON'T BENEFIT.
IT APPEARS THE WAY THIS IS PUT
TOGETHER, HE ACTUALLY WILL.
GETS TO THE IDEA OF WEALTHY
AMERICANS AROUND THE COUNTRY
WHICH PEOPLE DO CARE ABOUT.
CAN YOU --
>> LET ME TAKE YOU THROUGH THE
COMPONENTS THAT YOU'RE OBSESSED
ON FOR A MINUTE.
SARAH WILL YELL AT ME.
I'M TAKING TOO LONG HERE.
YOU TALK ABOUT THE DEATH TAX.
THAT BEING A GREAT BENEFIT.
THE TWO BIGGEST DRIVERS FOR
REPEAL OF THE DEATH TAX ARE THE
NFIB AND THE FARM BUREAU.
THAT'S SMALL BUSINESSES AND
FARMS.
THOSE ARE THE TWO ORGANIZATIONS
THAT SPEND THE MOST TIME
LOBBYING ON THE REPEAL OF THE
DEATH TAX.
DEATH TAX HAS THE BIGGEST EFFECT
ON THEM.
SMALL BUSINESSES AND FARMS.
WEALTHY AMERICANS DO A LOT OF
ESTATE PLANNING.
THEY CAN USE TRUSTS.
THEY CAN USE ALL TYPES OF THINGS
THAT ARE LEGAL WITHIN THE TAX
CODE TO MAKES SURE THEY DON'T
PAY DEATH TAX.
ON THE AMT, I'M NOT GOING TO GET
INTO DEEP, DEEP CALCULATIONS ON
AMT.
BUT IN A BROAD BRUSH LEVEL, WHEN
YOU DO THE AMT, ONCE YOU GET RID
OF THE DEDUCTIONS OF STATE AND
LOCAL TAXES, THAT'S THE BIGGEST
ADD-BACK IN AMT.
AMT IS IRRELEVANT ONCE YOU GET
RID OF THE DEDUCTION OF STATE
AND LOCAL TAXES.
ALL THE THINGS YOU'RE TRYING TO
PULL AT, YOU'RE NOT LOOKING AT
THE PLAN IN ITS ENTIRETY.
THEY DON'T MAKE SENSE ONCE WE
REDO THE PLAN AND SIMPLIFY.
YES.
BE.
>> JUST AS A FOLLOW UP QUESTION
ON THAT.
YOU SAID THAT -- I CITED TO YOU
THE WORRY OF GROUPS LIKE JIM
MARTIN AND THE 60-PLUS SENIORS
ASSOCIATION THAT YOU'RE GOING TO
DRAG OUT REPEAL OF THE DEATH
TAX.
THAT IT WOULDN'T BE IMMEDIATE
AND YOU SAID AT THE TIME IT WAS
IMMEDIATE.
IS THAT FINAL?
IS IT AN IMMEDIATE REPEAL AND GO
OFF THE BOOKS AS SOON AS THE NEW
TAX REFORM PACKAGE IS PASSED?
>> IN OUR OUT LINE, IT'S
IMMEDIATE.
>> THE SAME WITH THE ALTERNATIVE
MINIMUM TAX?
>> IT'S IMMEDIATE.
THE ONLY THING THAT PHASES OUT
IS THE FIVE-YEAR EXPENSING.
IT'S A FIVE-YEAR EXPENSE.
>> SPEAKING OF SMALL BUSINESSES,
LET'S START NEGOTIATING.
YESTERDAY SENATOR SCHUMER SAID
DEMOCRATS MAY BE WILLING TO WORK
SOME KIND OF SMALL BUSINESS TAX
RELIEF INTO WHATEVER COMES OUT
OF THIS.
WHERE DO YOU START NEGOTIATING
ON THAT?
WHAT OFFER DO YOU WANT TO MAKE
TO THE DEMOCRATS?
>> OUR OFFERS -- OUR OPENING
OFFER AND FINAL OFFER ARE ON THE
TABLE.
WE WERE HAPPY TO START AT 25 AND
GO LOWER.
WE'RE HAPPY TO START ON 20 AND
THERE'S THE OPENING OFFER.
HE WANTS TO COUNTER SOMETHING
LOWER, WE'RE NEGOTIABLE.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, GARY.
>> BOSS SAYS I HAVE TO GO.
>> NOW TRY TO BE RESPECTFUL OF
YA'LL'S TIME, WE HAVE TOM
BOSSERT THAT WILL TAKE HURRICANE
RELIEF EFFORTS.
I'LL COME BACK AFTER THAT.
>> THANKS, SARAH.
GOOD AFTERNOON.
AS YOU KNOW, PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
PUT PEOPLE FIRST AND PAPERWORK
SECOND.
HE'S HAD US PULL OUT THE STOPS
AND PULL OUT AS MUCH FEDERAL
RELIEF INTO PUERTO RICO AND THE
VIRGIN ISLANDS AND WE'VE BEEN
DOING THAT TO MEET HIS
OBJECTIVES THE LAST EIGHT DAYS.
I'M HERE TO TAKE QUESTIONS.
I KNOW YOU HEARD REPORTING FROM
SARAH.
>> AND SPECIFICALLY ON THE JONES
ACT, THAT'S BEEN A LOT OF
ATTENTION THE LAST 72 HOURS.
CRITICS SAY THE WHITE HOUSE
SHOULD HAVE MOVED MORE QUICKLY
IN WAIVING THE JONES ACT.
LAWMAKERS AMONG THEM.
WHY IS THAT AN UNFOUNDED
COMPLAINT?
>> OKAY.
IT IS AN UNFOUNDED COMPLAINT.
HERE'S WHY.
THE JONES ACT BRIEFLY STATED IS
A RULE THAT FAVORS FLAGGED
VESSELS, U.S. FLAGGED VESSELS.
IF THERE ARE NOT ENOUGH U.S.
FLAGGED VESSELS, THE CAPACITY IN
OTHER WORDS TO MEET THE NEEDS,
THEN WE WAIVE THE JONES ACT.
IN THIS PARTICULAR CASE, WE HAD
ENOUGH CAPACITY OF U.S. FLAGGED
VESSELS TO TAKE MORE THAN OR TO
EXCEED THE REQUIREMENT AND NEED
OF DIESEL FUEL AND OTHER
COMMODITIES TO PUERTO RICO.
WHAT HAPPENED IS I THINK ALMOST
17 OR 18 DAYS OF BACKLOGGED
DIESEL FUEL NEED TO THE ISLAND.
IT WAS MISREPORTED THAT WE HAD A
CAPACITY PROBLEM AND HAD TO
WAIVE THE JONES ACT.
NOT THE CASE.
THE IDEA IS WE PROVIDED AS MANY
COMMODITIES AS NECESSARY TO THE
ISLAND.
THE CHALLENGE WAS LAND-BASED
DISTRIBUTION.
HOWEVER, LAST NIGHT THE GOVERNOR
CALLED ME A LITTLE AFTER 8:00
AND SAID AT THIS POINT TO ENSURE
THAT THE ADDITIONAL NEEDS ARE
MET AS WE MOVE FORWARD, MIGHT BE
A GOOD IDEA TO PROACTIVELY MAKE
SURE THAT WE PULL OUT THE STOPS
JUST IN CASE THAT CAPACITY
PROBLEM RAN INTO THE REQUIREMENT
PROBLEM.
I TALKED TO THE PRESIDENT.
HE THOUGHT THAT WAS THE RIGHT
THING TO DO.
WAIVED IT RIGHT AWAY.
THAT WAS NOT TOO LATE.
IT WAS NOT EVEN TOO EARLY.
IT WAS JUST THE RIGHT THING
PROACTIVELY.
>> RIGHT NOW, DISTRIBUTION IS
ONE OF THE PROBLEMS.
HOSPITALS ARE NOW UP AND RUNNING
AS NECESSARY TO BRING THE PEOPLE
WHOSE LIVES ARE AT RISK.
WHAT PERCENTAGE OF THE COUNTRY
WOULD YOU SAY YOU HAVE HAD A
CHANCE TO EXPLORE TO SEE HOW
THEY HAVE BEEN IMPACTED BY THIS?
>> YEAH, IT'S HARD TO ANSWER THE
PERCENTAGE OF THE COUNTRY.
IT ANSWER IT THIS WAY.
THROUGH AERIAL SURVEILLANCE,
WE'VE SEEN THE ENTIRETY PUERTO
RICO.
SOME SOUTHWEST AND SOUTHEAST
SECTIONS ARE SPARSE.
THE MOUNTAINOUS INTERIOR IS
WHERE WE'RE TRYING TO GET IN
WITH ROTARY WINGED SUPPORT.
BACK TO THE JONES ACT.
WE HAD ENOUGH CAPACITY IN U.S.
FLAGGED VESSELS TO GET THE
COMMODITIESNER.
WE RAN INTO THE PRIORITY
CHALLENGE OF DISTRIBUTING
LAND-BASED COMMODITIES TO THE
PEOPLE.
THAT'S A CHALLENGE OR FUNCTION
OF TWO PROBLEMS.
FIRST, CAPACITY OF THE LOCALS IN
THE STATE WERE DIMINISHED
BECAUSE THOSE PEOPLE ARE VICTIMS
AS WELL THAT WORK FOR THE STATE
AND THE LOCAL AUTHORITIES.
SECONDLY, THE DEBRIS AND DOWNED
POWER LINES HAD TO BE PUSHED OUT
OF THE WAY.
WE HAVE THE RESOURCES TO DO THAT
NOW.
THAT'S THE CHALLENGE REMAINING.
THE CENTRAL INTERIOR IS GOING TO
BE REVIEWED AND LOOKED A TO MAKE
SURE WE GET THE NEEDS OF THE
PEOPLE MET.
>> HAD THE GOVERNOR NO REQUESTED
PROTECTIVELY A WAIVENER THE
JONES ACT, WOULD YOU HAVE SEEN A
COMPELLING REASON TO SUGGEST IT?
>> MAYBE A HISTORICAL NOTE OF
RELEVANCE, SOMETIMES WE'LL SEE
THE CARRIERS REQUEST THE WAIVER.
SO YOU'LL HAVE FOREIGN-FLAGGED
VESSELS OR U.S. VESSELS CARRIER
COMPANIES CALL US AND SAY PLEASE
WAIVE IT.
THERE'S AN ISSUE.
WE DIDN'T GET ANY CARRIER
REQUESTS.
ONCE THE GOVERNOR CALLS AND SAYS
WE NEED IT, WE SHOULD LISTEN AND
THE PRESIDENT AGREED.
>> IS THIS OVERHYPED IN SIMPLE
TERMS?
>> MISUNDERSTOOD.
SOME CRITICS THINK IT WAS A
PRICE ISSUE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW THE MARKETS
PRICE THESE THINGS.
IT WAS BOUGHT AND PAID FOR BY
THE U.S. TAX PAYNER A
HUMANITARIAN EFFORT AND IT'S A
WISE INVESTMENT TO SAVE LIVES.
IN THIS CASE, WE HAVE THE U.S.
VIRGIN ISLAND CITIZENS, PUERTO
RICAN CITIZENS.
IT'S THE RIGHT THING TO DO.
CAPACITY IS THE ISSUE.
LIFE-SAVING REQUIREMENTS, THAT'S
THE NEED.
WE HAD THE CAPACITY MET.
IN THE MIDDLE.
>> OKAY.
TOM, THE NEED IS IMMEDIATE.
WITH ALL THE CHALLENGES THAT ARE
COMING, WHAT ARE THE
CONVERSATIONS ABOUT WITH AIR
DROPPING IN CERTAIN AREAS?
PEOPLE ARE TALKING ABOUT RUNNING
OUT OF WATER AND FOOD IN HOURS
OR MINUTES.
WHAT IS HAPPENING WITH THAT
CONVERSATION?
ONCE AGAIN, AN ISSUE OF HOUSING.
WE'RE HEARING ABOUT SHIPS,
CRUISE SHIPS.
WHAT ELSE IS GOING ON?
>> SO A NUMBER OF THINGS
HAPPENING.
WITH RESPECT TO DISTRIBUTION OF
COMMODITIES.
THAT IS THE BIGGEST CHALLENGE
RIGHT NOW.
THE RESTORATION OF POWER IS A
BIG CHALLENGE.
I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
ENERGY HERE, ELECTRIC POWER IS
SUPPLYING THE HOSPITALS THAT ARE
PROVIDING MEDICAL CARE TO THE
WOUNDED.
SO THERE'S A DUEL PRIORITY GOING
ON WITH EMERGENCY POWER AND THEN
BLOCKING, CLEARING, PUSHING OUT
THE ROADS TO GET COMMODITIES
DELIVERED.
THERE'S STILL A SHORTFALL THERE.
THAT IS DRIVERS FOR ALL OF THOSE
TRUCKS.
SO WE'RE PUSHING PERSONNEL TO
AUGMENT STATE AND LOCAL
AUTHORITIES TO CONTINUE TO PUSH
THE COMMODITIES.
WHAT YOU SAW TODAY IS SOME
REPORTING OF SOME LOOP FOOTAGE
OF SOME TRUCKS ON PORTS IN
DOCKS.
WE'RE MOVING THE TRUCKS QUICKLY
AND PRIORITIZING WHAT NEEDS TO
COME OFF FIRST SO WE CAN GET
GENERATORS --
>> WOULDN'T AIR DROPS CIRCUMVENT
THAT, HAVING TO REBUILD
INFRASTRUCTURE AND MOVE THINGS
AWAY?
>> IF AIR DROPS ARE UNDER
CONSIDERATION, I'M NOT AWARE OF
IT, BUT I WOULD PROMOTE IT IF
IT'S FASTER GET FOOD AND WATER
TO PEOPLE.
WE HAVE A ONE-STAR GENERAL,
GENERAL KIM, IN PLACE WHO IS IN
CHARGE OF GROUND FORCE
OPERATIONS TO MAKE SURE THERE'S
ONE PERSON IN CHARGE.
IF HE RECOMMENDS AIR DROP, WE
AIR DROP.
>> WE'VE BEEN TOLD THAT THEY
NEED HELICOPTERS TO EVACUATE
PEOPLE FROM REMOTE AREAS.
HE SAYS THERE'S PEOPLE BURYING
FAMILY MEMBERS IN FRONT YARDS.
COMMUNICATIONS ARE BADLY NEEDED.
THEY LOOK AT APOCALYPTIC
CONDITIONS BETWEEN 48 AND 72
HOURS.
THERE'S A LITTLE DISCONNECT FROM
WHAT I'M HEARING HERE AND WHAT
THEY'RE TELLING ME THERE.
CAN YOU EXPLAIN THE DIFFERENCE?
>> YES.
IF THAT'S ACCURATE, IT NEEDS TO
BE REMEDIATED IMMEDIATELY.
I BELIEVE I'M CONFIDENT WE HAVE
ENOUGH RESOURCES MARTIALED AND
DEPLOYED FORWARD.
AS I'VE EXPLAINED IN THE PAST,
WE'VE HAD TO AUGMENT AND CHANGE
OUR BUSINESS MODEL IN THE FIELD.
WE DID THAT THURSDAY.
YOU SAW THE EFFECTS OVER THE
WEEKEND.
WE HAVE TO AUGMENT THE LOCAL AND
STATE AUTHORITIES NOT JUST AT
THE TOP BUT ALL THE WAY OUT
THROUGH THE LOWER LEVEL.
THERE'S FEDERAL OFFICIALS
IDENTIFYING THE REQUIREMENTS AND
AUGMENTING THE STATE LEVEL TO
VALIDATE THOSE REQUIREMENTS.
FROM THE FEDERAL SIDE PROVIDING
THEM.
WE'RE IN EVERY STAGE OF THE
IDENTIFICATION, VALIDATION AND
PROVISION OF REQUIREMENTS AND
DELIVERY OF THEM TO PEOPLE IN
NEED.
A COUPLE THINGS HERE.
PEOPLE SEEING 28 AND 48 HORIZON
PROBLEMS WHERE THEY DON'T SEE
FEED AND WATER.
THAT FOOD AND WATER WILL GET TO
THEM BEFORE THE DEADLINE ARISES.
I HAVE NO DOUBT.
WE HAVE OVER 10,000 PEOPLE THERE
NOW AND THERE'S MORE ON THE WAY
INCLUDING AERIAL SUPPORT.
U.S.S. COMFORT.
THERE'S 12 COAST GUARD CUTTERS,
THREE UNITED STATES NAVY SHIPS.
SIX COMMERCIAL SHIPS WITH
SUPPLIES IN ROUTE.
THIS IS AS OF 5:00 A.M.
THERE'S MORE SINCE.
SEVEN ADDITIONAL SHIPS TO HOUSE
RESPONDERS.
WE HAVE COMMODITIES DISTRIBUTION
EXCEEDING MILLIONS.
SO IT'S ALL MOVING IN TODAY AND
DISTRIBUTION PROBLEM IS BEING
UNCLOGGED.
IF THERE'S SOMEBODY BEING BURIED
IN THE FRONT YARD, THAT'S
TERRIBLE BUT IT'S NOT THE NORM.
RIGHT NOW WE'VE SEEN 16
FATALITIES CONFIRMED FROM THE
STATE AUTHORITIES.
NO FATALITY IS ACCEPTABLE.
IF THAT NUMBER INCREASES, THAT
WILL BE A DEVASTATING BLOW.
WE'RE DOING EVERYTHING WE CAN TO
PREVENT THAT.
LOSS OF LIFE FROM THE STORM IS
ONE THING.
LOSS OF LIFE THAT IS PREVENTIBLE
IS ANOTHER.
>> SENATOR RUBIO JUST BACK FROM
THE ISLAND.
HE SAID THERE'S SIGNIFICANT
LOGISTICAL CONCERNS.
HE SAYS THERE'S NO CLEAR COMMAND
CONTROL BETWEEN LOCAL AND
FEDERAL AGENCIES.
HE SAID IT'S ALL LED BY DOD.
IS THAT OPTION ON THE TABLE?
>> IT'S BEING UNDERTAKEN.
I WAS WITH THE SENATOR IN PUERTO
RICO.
WHAT HE'S IDENTIFYING THERE IS
SOMETHING THAT WE HAD A SOLUTION
FOR.
SO HE'S IDENTIFYING A
TRADITIONAL PROBLEM.
NORMALLY FEMA AND THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT PROVIDE AID TO THE
STATE AND THEY WORK IT OUT WITH
THE LOCAL AUTHORITIES.
WHAT WE'VE IDENTIFIED HERE AS OF
THURSDAY AND YOU SAW IT
IMPLEMENTED OVER THE THE
WEEKEND, A LACK OF CAPACITY
COUPLED WITH THIS SEVERAL
HUNDRED MILES AWAY DIVIDED BY AN
OCEAN ISLAND PROBLEM.
SO WHAT WE'VE DONE IS PROVIDED
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES, LARGELY
GUYS IN GREEN AND FEMALE
EMERGENCY MANAGERS TO STAND NEXT
TO THE MUNICIPALITY LEADERS,
WHETHER THEY'RE MAYORS OR LOCAL
ELECTRIC AUTHORITIES LEADERS AND
BEING AUGMENTED BY FEDERAL
FORCES.
WE'VE ADDRESSED THE CHALLENGES
BY AUGMENTING THEM WITH FEDERAL
STAFF.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WASN'T
NECESSARILY APPARENT TO THE
SENATOR AS HE GOT THERE.
HE IDENTIFIED A PROBLEM.
IT WAS A PROBLEM ALREADY BEING
FIXED.
IT'S ONE HE PROBABLY WASN'T ABLE
TO SEE AT THE MUNICIPAL LEVEL
FOR TWO REASONS.
ONE, HE DIDN'T GET OUT THERE TO
THEM.
AND TWO, THERE WAS A
COMMUNICATION PROBLEM OF GRAVE
IMPORT THAT PERSISTS TO THIS
DAY.
THAT COMMUNICATIONS PROBLEM IS
TIED TO THE ELECTRIC POWER
RESTORATION PROBLEM.
IF I COULD BEFORE I TAKE THE
NEXT QUESTION, LET ME EXPLAIN
WHY AND HOW THE POWER
RESTORATION PROCESS IS
UNFOLDING.
WE PUT THE U.S. ARMY CORPS
ENGINEERS IN CHARGE OF POWER
RESTORATION.
THEY'RE IN CHARGE OF A LOT BUT
NOT EVERYTHING.
THE PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO ARE
STRONG AND COMPETENT.
THEY'RE IN CHARGE AND THAT'S THE
BEST WAY TO HANDLE THINGS.
WHERE THEY HAVE DIMINISHED
CAPACITY, WE'RE TAKING EXTREME
STEPS.
SO A DIRECT FEDERAL ASSISTANCE
ORDER WAS GIVEN.
A MISSION ASSIGNMENT WAS GIVEN.
I'VE HEARD OTHERS ON TV QUIBBLE
WHETHER IT'S A MISSION OR NOT.
MAKE IT CLEAR, THE U.S. ARMY
CORPS OF ENGINEERS HAS BEEN
GIVEN TO RESTORE POWER ON PUERTO
RICO.
HE HAS SOME PRIORITIES.
HIS PRIORITIES ARE TEMPORARY
POWER GENERATION RIGHT NOW.
THAT'S THE BIG DIESEL RUN
GENERATORS SUPPORTING HOSPITALS
AND LIFE-SAVING CAPABILITIES.
TWO, PERMANENT GENERATION.
HE WILL RESTORE THE POWER ON THE
SOUTH OF THE ISLAND.
THREE, TRANSMISSION.
THE BIG POWER LINES.
NEXT, THE CAPILLARY POWER LINES
TO THE HOMES.
I'M SURE THE PEOPLE OF PUERTO
RICO HE SEE THE ARMY CORPS.
>> IF AIR DROPS WOULD HELP, WHY
ARE THEY NOT HAPPENING?
IS IT A MILITARY ISSUE?
>> IT'S MY BELIEF THAT THE STATE
GOVERNMENT AND THE
MUNICIPALITIES HAVE IDENTIFIED
THE FASTEST ROUTE AVAILABLE
BEING GROUND BASED.
IF THAT'S NOT THE CASE, I'M
CONFIDENT BUT I WANT TO MAKE
SURE I DON'T STEP IN BETWEEN
SOMETHING THAT I CAN BE FAR
REMOVED FROM.
IF THE GROUND FORCE COMMANDER
HAS IDENTIFIED AN AIR DROP
MISSION, I ENDORSE IT FROM HERE.
I WOULDN'T QUESTION HIS
JUDGMENT.
IT WAS MY REPORTING FROM EARLIER
TODAY THEY IDENTIFIED THE
FASTEST TO BE THROUGH
GROUND-BASED MEANS BY CLEARING
FIRST AND DELIVERING SECOND.
THEY NEEDED SECURITY FORCES AND
THEY APPLIED THEM.
THERE'S A SECURITY FORCE FOR
EACH OF THE DRIVERS TO FEEL
SAFE.
>> SEVERAL AID FLIGHTS HAVE
GOTTEN OUT OF SOUTH FLORIDA AND
DELIVER FOOD AND WATER WITHOUT
LOGISTICAL PROBLEMS.
THERE'S REPORTS OF MISMANAGEMENT
COMING ALL THE WAY FROM THE
PRESIDENT.
HOW DO YOU RESPOND TO THAT?
>> I'M NOT CERTAIN WHO YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
THERE'S POINT OF CRITICISM TO GO
AROUND.
I'M CONFIDENT --
>> HE SAID THE PROBLEMS THAT
YOU'RE HAVING LOGISTICALLY ARE
OF YOUR OWN MAKING FROM NOT
TAKING ACTION SOONER AND
BRINGING IN THE MILITARY SOONER.
>> FIRST, I THANK THE MAYOR FOR
PROVIDING AID.
HE'S WRONG IN THIS CASE.
I CHALLENGE HIM TO GO DOWN AND
GET A BETTER UNDERSTANDING ON
WHAT WE'VE DONE, WHAT WE'VE BEEN
DOING AND HOW BLOWN AWAY YOU'LL
BE WHEN YOU SEE THE PICTURE.
I'M CERTAIN THE MAYOR HAS HAD
SOME POSITIVE EXPERIENCES.
I WOULDN'T BE CRITICAL
PERSONALLY.
PROBABLY LIKE WITH THE JONES
ACT, HE'S NOT INFORMED ON THE
QUESTION.
>> HOW LONG WILL IT TAKE TO GET
SUPPLIES THROUGH AND WHY IT IS
THERE'S 10,000 CONTAINERS IN THE
PORT OF SAN JUAN?
>> TO MY POINT, WE'RE GETTING A
LOT OF SUPPLIES THROUGH.
MAYBE IT'S MISREPORTING.
>> THE PRESIDENT REFERENCED SOME
OF THE DEBT AND ECONOMIC
PROBLEMS THAT PUERTO RICO HAS
BEEN STRUGGLING WITH FOR SOME
TIME HERE.
WHEN YOU TALKED ABOUT THE LACK
OF CAPACITY, ARE YOU FAULTING
LOCAL OFFICIALS FOR A LACK OF
PREPAREDNESS?
>> NO.
LET ME BE CLEAR.
WHEN I SAY "CAPACITY", I'M
TALKING ABOUT THE CAPACITY
PROBLEM OF PEOPLE BEING VICTIMS
THAT WOULD OTHERWISE BE THE
FIRST RESPONDERS, REPAIRERS AND
MANAGERS OF THE MUNICIPAL
GOVERNMENT FUNCTIONS.
SO WHAT WE'RE DOING IS TRYING TO
RESTORE BASELINE MUNICIPAL
GOVERNMENT FUNCTIONS BECAUSE
THEY HAVE BEEN AFFECTED.
THEIR HOMES ARE DESTROYED AND
FAMILIES PUT IN PERIL.
THAT'S THE CAPACITY PROBLEM I'M
ADDRESSING.
WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT MONEY, THE
ISLAND AUTHORITY IN GENERAL,
PUERTO RICO WAS $72 BILLION IN
DEATH.
THERE'S A RESTRUCTURING
UNDERWAY.
THE CONGRESS WEIGHED IN.
THAT $72 BILLION IS BEING
HANDLED THROUGH BANKRUPTCY
PROCEEDINGS.
>> HOW IS THAT IMPACTING IT?
THE PRESIDENT BROUGHT IT UP.
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT -- I
KNOW THE PRESIDENT BROUGHT IT UP
IN TERMS OF RECOVERY.
HERE'S HOW IT AFFECTS THE
RESPONSE.
IT PUTS THE ISLAND IN A POSITION
WHERE THEY DON'T HAVE THE
FINANCIAL RESOURCES TO MEET THE
COST SHARE REQUIREMENT FOR ALL
OF THESE GOODS AND RESOURCES,
PERSONNEL AND MATERIAL FLOWING.
IN THE PRESIDENT ACKNOWLEDGED
THAT, REALIZED THAT WOULD BE A
PROBLEM AND HE TOOK THE STEP OF
DOING A 100% FEDERAL COST SHARE
ADJUSTMENT TO PAY FOR THIS FROM
DEBRIS REMOVAL, TO DEBRIS
PUSHING, POWER RESTORATION, THE
ARMY CORPS OF ENGINEERS AND ALL
THE EMERGENCY PROTECTIVE
MEASURES, POLICE, FIRE, EMS,
TUCK DRIVERS.
ALL OF THOSE THINGS.
180 DAYS.
SIX MONTHS FOR THE VIRGIN
ISLANDS AND FOR PUERTO RICO
UNTIL WE CAN GET OUR HANDS
AROUND THIS.
ALL OF THOSE FUNCTIONS AND
MISSIONS ARE ALL 100% FEDERAL
COST SHARE.
WE DON'T WANT ANYBODY WORRIED
ABOUT PEOPLE.
WE WANT THEM WORRIED ABOUT
PEOPLE.
TWO MORE QUESTIONS.
>> I WANTED TO FOLLOW UP A
LITTLE BIT AS YOU'RE STARTING TO
ENVISION DOWN THE ROAD.
ANY SORT OF BAILOUT MIGHT BE
PART OF THIS SORT OF BROADER
RECOVERY PACKAGE THAT YOU LOOK
FOR IN THE SUPPLEMENTAL.
ON THAT SUPPLEMENTAL, I KNOW THE
FIRST ONE WILL BE RELATIVELY
SOON.
CAPITOL HILL SAYS IT COULD BE
SOONER.
>> AS MY COLLEAGUE, MR. COHN
ALLUDED TO, WE'RE WILLING TO
NEGOTIATE WITH ACCORDING IF
THERE'S A BETTER IDEA.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO UNDERSTAND
THAT FEMA JUST GOT A $7.1
BILLION APPROPRIATION ON OCTOBER
1.
WE'RE GOING TO ASK FOR THAT IN
THE FORM OF AN EMERGENCY
SUPPLEMENTAL TO PROVIDE MONEY
INTO THE FUNDS THAT DOES THIS
LIFE-SUSTAINING EFFORT AND EVEN
EARLY RECOVERY EFFORTS.
WHETHER WE HAVE TO ADDRESS OR
SHOULD ADDRESS AT THAT POINT THE
EXISTING $72 BILLION OF DEBT AND
HOW IT'S BEEN RESTRUCTURED IS
SOMETHING THAT I'LL HAVE TO TAKE
MY LEAD FROM DEECONOMISTS ON AND
THE BUDGET HAWKS.
I THINK THE BEST IDEA FOR US
WOULD BE TO FOCUS ON PROCESS.
THE ELECTRIC POWER AUTHORITY AND
THE WATER AUTHORITY, THOSE ARE
THE TWO CONCERNING ELEMENTS THAT
HAVE TO BE REBUILD AND UNDER
PROPER MANAGEMENT AND UNDER
PROPER REBUILDING CODES AND
STANDARDS TO MAKE SURE THEY MAKE
IT THROUGH ANOTHER HURRICANE.
WE'RE GOING TO PUT FEDERAL MONEY
IN IT AND DO IT WISELY.
THE PRESIDENT BELIEVES IN THAT.
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE TO ADDRESS
THE DEBT RESTRUCTURING ISSUE IN
THE NEXT GO AROUND.
IF WE DO, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS UP
TO THAT CHALLENGE.
>> THE SUPPLEMENTAL WILL HAVE TO
COME IN THE NEXT TWO TO THREE
WEEKS.
OVER TO DIRECTOR MULVANEY.
>> WHY HAS IT TAKEN EIGHT DAYS
AND A THREE STAR GENERAL --
>> IT DIDN'T REQUIRE A
THREE-STAR GENERAL THREE DAYS
AGO.
WE HAD A THREE-STAR GENERAL FROM
DAY MINUS 8 AND DAY MINUS TWO
AND ALL THE WAY TILL TODAY.
WE FORWARD DEPLOYED A ONE-STAR
GENERAL TO TAKE CARE OF GROUND
FORCE COMMAND ONCE WE REALIZED
THE PROBLEM OF LOGISTICS
DISTRIBUTION HAD OUTSTRIPPED THE
CAPACITY OF THE AFFECTED
MUNICIPAL GOVERNMENT.
THAT THREE-STAR GENERAL WAS
THERE AND RUNNING AND
COORDINATING OPERATIONS AS AN
EXTENSION OF NORAD AND NORTHERN
COMMAND.
WE'VE MADE IMPROVEMENTS TO
MARTIALING OF RESOURCES.
THE THREE-STAR COMMAND STRUCTURE
THAT HE LACKED BACK THEN HAS
BEEN PUT IN PLACE AND HAS BEEN
IN PLACE FOR THIS RESPOND OUT OF
SAN ANTONIO AND AUGMENTED BY A
NORTHERN COMMAND STRUCTURE
THAT'S BEEN PRETTY ROBUST AND
FORWARD LEANING HERE.
THEY'VE DONE VOCAL AUTHORITY AND
NOT WAITING FOR PAPERWORK.
THEY DON'T WAY FOR A GOVERNOR'S
REQUEST.
PERHAPS MISUNDERSTOOD.
NOW THE CHANGE MOVE HERE ON DAY
EIGHT IS TO TAKE THE THREE-STAR
GENERAL AND PUT HIM THERE,
PHYSICALLY IN THE FIELD.
I DON'T ANTICIPATE HE WILL BE
THERE LONG BUT HE HAS TO HAVE
HIS EYES ON IT AND MAKES SURE
HE'S COMFORTABLE WITH THE
INTERACTION WITH HIS FORCES AND
THE GOVERNOR.
IT'S A DIFFERENT BUSINESS PLAN
MODEL IN THE FELLED AND BECAUSE
IT'S UNIQUE AND IT'S AN ISLAND,
1100 MILES AWAY FROM THE NEAREST
LAND IN FLORIDA.
ONCE HE'S SATISFIED OR WOULD
EXPECT THE THREE-STAR GENERAL TO
RECEIVE BACK TO HIS APPROPRIATE
COMMAND STRUCTURE.
FOR NOW HE AND HIS ONE-START
SUBORDINATE COMMAND WILL BE
THERE AND WE'LL GET MORE PEOPLE
THE NEXT COMING DAYS TO TRY TO
ADDRESS THIS SIGNIFICANT PROBLEM
AND SIGNIFICANT NEED.
IF THAT'S OKAY, THAT'S MY LAST
QUESTION.
>> SAN ANTONIO IS THOUSANDS OF
MILES FROM PUERTO RICO.
WAS IT A MISTAKE LOOKING BACK TO
NOT HAVE THIS THREE-STAR GENERAL
ON THE GROUND EARLIER.
>> NOT AT ALL.
THAT DOESN'T EFFECT IT.
THE WAY WE STAGE EQUIPMENT AND
HANDLE AREA COMMAND AND FIELD
OPERATIONAL COMMAND.
THIS IS TEXTBOOK AND IT'S DOWN
WELL.
I HAVE EVERY CONFIDENCE WE'LL
HANDLE IT THE BEST WAY POSSIBLE.
PETER, IF I COULD, JOHN, THAT'S
MY LAST QUESTION.
IF I CAN, I'M GOING TO END BY
SAYING PLEASE SAY A PRAYER FOR
THE PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO AND
THE U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS AND FOR
THE 10,000 PLUS FEDERAL WORKERS
AND VOLUNTEER WORKERS, MEN AND
WOMEN THAT ARE HELPING THOSE IN
NEED.
HONESTLY, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
WILL REQUIRE WEEKS AND MONTHS OF
PATIENCE AS WE RESTORE POWER,
GET FOOD AND WATER AND RETURN TO
NORMALCY.
THANKS FOR YOUR TIME.
PROUD OF PUERTO RICAN PEOPLE AND
THE GOVERNOR HAS OUR CONFIDENCE
AND FAITH.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, TOM.
WE'RE RUNNING LONG TODAY.
I'M JUMP INTO QUESTIONS AND TRY
TO TAKE A FEW BEFORE WE HAVE TO
CUT OFF BEFORE THE DAY.
>> IS THE PRESIDENT TAKING STEPS
TO CRACK DOWN ON TOM PRICE?
>> AS THE PRESIDENT SAID
YESTERDAY, HE'S NOT HAPPY WITH
THE ACTIONS.
WE'RE LOOKING AT THE ISSUE.
THEY'RE CONDUCTING BOTH INTERNAL
AND AN I.G. FULL REVIEW TO BE
CLEAR ALSO, THE WHITE HOUSE DOES
NOT HAVE A ROLE ON THE FRONT END
OF APPROVING PRIVATE CHARTER
FLIGHTS AT THE AGENCIES.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WE'RE
LOOKING INTO FROM THIS POINT
FORWARD AND HAVE ASKED A HALT TO
BE PUT AT HHS ON ANY PRIVATE
CHARTER FLIGHTS MOVING FORWARD
UNTIL THOSE REVIEWS ARE
COMPLETED.
>> DOES SECRETARY PRICE EXPECT
TO KEEP HIS JOB IN THIS
SEPARATION?
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT HAS
ADDRESSED THIS YESTERDAY.
WE ARE GOING THROUGH THIS
PROCESS.
WE'RE GOING TO CONDUCT A FULL
REVIEW AND SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> I HAVE TWO THINGS.
THE FIRST, THE PRESIDENT HAS SIX
TIMES THE LAST COUPLE DAYS SAID
THAT THE SENATOR IS IN THE
HOSPITAL.
THAT'S REFERENCE TO SENATOR
COCHRAN WHO IS NOT IN THE
HOSPITAL AND THE REASON THIS IS
RELEVANT QUESTION IS THE
QUESTION SAID THEY HAVE THE
VOTES FOR THE HEALTHCARE BILL TO
PASS.
CAN YOU TELL US WHAT SENATOR
HE'S REFERRING TO AND IF IT IS
SENATOR COCHRAN, WHY IF THE
VOTES EXIST THE SENATE ISN'T
VOTING ON THAT NOW?
>> LOOK, OUR UNDERSTANDING IS
THE SENATOR WAS PHYSICALLY
UNABLE TO BE HERE THIS WEEK TO
PARTICIPATE IN A VOTE.
WE'RE GLAD THAT HE'S
RECUPERATING.
THE POINT THAT WE'RE MAKING IS
WE HAVE THE VOTES ON THE
SUBSTANCE, BUT NOT NECESSARILY
ON THE PROCESS, WHICH IS WHY
WE'RE STILL CONFIDENT THAT WE
CAN MOVE HEALTHCARE FORWARD AND
GET IT DONE IN THE SPRING.
>> OBVIOUSLY THE PRESIDENT
DIDN'T SUPPORT ROY MOORE IN THE
PRIMARY BUT HE'S MOVED TO WARMLY
EMBRACE HIM SINCE THEN.
WHAT I'M WONDERING, JUDGE MOORE
HAS HAD A A LOT OF CONTROVERSIAL
COMMENTS ABOUT BEING GUY TO
EQUAL TO BEASTALITY AND MUSLIMS
SHOULDN'T SERVE.
WHY SHOULD THOSE COMMENTS NOT
QUALIFIED HIM HIM FROM A
PRESIDENTIAL ENDORSEMENT?
>> AS WE SAID MANY TIMES BEFORE,
I'M NOT GOING TO GET INTO BACK
AND FORTH ON POLITICAL
ENDORSEMENTS FROM THE PODIUM.
I'M NOT GOING TO WEIGH-IN ON A
SPECIFIC RACE AHEAD OF TIME AT
THIS POINT.
MATTHEW?
>> I WANT TO FOLLOW UP ON THAT.
AS YOU MENTIONED, JUDGE MOORE
HOMOSEXUALALITY SHOULD BE
ILLEGAL.
HE SAID KEITH ELLISON SHOULDN'T
BE IN CONGRESS BECAUSE HE'S A
MUSLIM.
WITHOUT ASKING ABOUT THE
SPECIFICS OF THE RACE, DOESN'T
TRUMP SHARE ANY OF THOSE VIEWS
THAT I JUST MENTIONED?
IF NOT, WHY DOES HE THINK THIS
PERSON IS FIT TO BE A U.S.
SENATOR?
>> NOT THAT I'M AWARE OF.
I HAVE NOT TAKEN A DEEP DIVE ON
EVERY COMMENT THAT THE SENATE
NOMINEE HAS MADE.
I CERTAINLY KNOW WHERE THE
PRESIDENT STANDS ON THOSE ISSUES
AND WOULDN'T SEE ANY PARALLEL ON
THE TWO OF THEM ON THAT FRONT.
>> ARE THERE ANY