THE FREIGHTING BEARING
COMMERCIAL SIZE GENERATORS?
YOU SAW HOW THE FOLKS IN THE
HOSPITAL RESPONDED WHEN THE U.S.
MARINES AND THE CBs GOT THE
EMERGENCY GENERATOR WORKING.
THAT BROUGHT POWER AND LIGHT
BACK AND VENTILATORS IN THE
URGENT CARE UNITS AND THE
INTENSIVE CARE UNITS.
POWER IS EVERYTHING.
POWER IS THE BUILDING BLOCK OF
MODERN LIFE.
WITHOUT IT, PUERTO RICO IS
ALREADY IN THE THIRD WORLD THE
WAY THINGS ARE RIGHT NOW.
IT WILL SINK AND SINK UNLESS
THERE'S MASSIVE AID.
I HOPE THE PRESIDENT CAN RALLY
THAT WITH HIS VISIT TUESDAY.
>> Shepard: THANKS, GERALDO.
THANKS SO MUCH.
THE PRESIDENT, BY THE WAY,
CONSIDERING THAT ACT WHICH WOULD
ALLOW OTHER SHIPS TO COME IN
EVEN THOSE OF A FOREIGN FLAG.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
STAY WITH US.
>> Shepard: GOOD AFTERNOON.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THE PRESIDENT IS NOW BEGINNING
TO SPEAK IN INDIANAPOLIS.
HE'S LAYING OUT HIS PLAN FOR
CHANGES IN THE TAX CODE.
WE'RE HOPING FOR SOME SPECIFICS,
SO WE'LL LEARN ABOUT WHAT WILL
HAPPEN WITH YOUR FAMILY IN MIND.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
LIVE FROM INDIANAPOLIS.
>> YOU WANT TAX CUTS.
THAT'S THE ONLY REASON YOU'RE
GOING SO WILD.
IT'S WONDERFUL TO BE BACK IN THE
GREAT STATE OF INDIANA.
WHAT A PLACE.
I WANT TO THANK SENATOR TODAY
YOUNG, SENATOR JOE DONNELLY,
REPRESENTATIVE JACKIE WARLARSKI,
REPRESENTATIVE SUSAN BROOKS AND
REPRESENTATIVE MIKE MESSER FOR
JOINING US TODAY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
I APPRECIATE IT.
[APPLAUSE]
I ALSO WANT TO THANK MEMBERS OF
MY ECONOMIC TEAM, SECRETARY
STEVEN MNUCHIN AND DIRECTOR GARY
COHN FOR JOINING US AS WELL.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
[APPLAUSE]
LET ME BEGIN BY SAYING THAT OUR
HEARTS AND PRAYERS GO OUT TO THE
PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO AND THE
VIRGIN ISLANDS THAT ARE
SUFFERING IN THE WAKE OF ANOTHER
CATASTROPHIC HURRICANE.
THEIR ISLAND WAS VIRTUALLY
DESTROYED.
FEDERAL AGENCIES ARE WORKING
CLOSELY WITH LOCAL PARTNERS TO
HELP THESE COMMUNITIES GET BACK
ON THEIR FEET AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE.
TEXAS, FLORIDA, LOUISIANA ARE
DOING GREAT AND THE RECOVERY
PROCESS IS HAPPENING VERY
QUICKLY.
I WILL BE GOING DOWN TO PUERTO
RICO NEXT WEEK TO GET AN
ON-THE-GROUND BRIEFING ABOUT THE
DISASTER RECOVERY AND TO SEE ALL
OF OUR GREAT FIRST RESPONDERS
AND TO MEET A LOT OF THE PEOPLE
WHO ARE SO AFFECTED BY THESE
STORMS.
WE ARE WITH YOU NOW, I TELL
THEM, AND WE WILL BE THERE EVERY
STEP OF THE WAY UNTIL THIS JOB
IS DONE.
IT IS TRULY CATASTROPHIC WHAT
HAPPENED IN PUERTO RICO.
[APPLAUSE]
AND MASSIVE AMOUNTS OF WATER,
FOOD AND SUPPLIES, BY THE WAY,
ARE BEING DELIVERED ON AN HOURLY
BASIS.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT NOBODY HAS
EVER SEEN BEFORE FROM THIS
COUNTRY.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
AND I'M VERY PROUD OF ALL OF THE
FOLKS THAT HAVE WORKED SO HARD
IN FEMA, ALL OF OUR FIRST
RESPONDERS, ALL OF OUR POLICE
THAT HAVE GONE TO THE ISLAND
BECAUSE THEIR POLICE FORCE HAS
BEEN SO BADLY AFFECTED.
MANY OF THEIR POLICEMEN -- MOST
OF THEIR POLICE PEOPLE HAVE LOST
THEIR HOMES.
IT'S BEEN A TOUGH GO.
BUT WE ARE GOING TO GET IT BACK.
BEFORE WE GO ON TO DISCUSS THE
LARGEST TAX CUT IN OUR COUNTRY'S
HISTORY, I ALSO WANT TO PROVIDE
A BRIEF UPDATE ON HEALTHCARE.
WE HAVE THE VOTES ON
GRAHAM-CASSIDY.
BUT WITH THE RULES OF
RECONCILIATION, WE'RE UP AGAINST
A DEADLINE OF FRIDAY, TWO DAYS.
THAT'S JUST TWO DAYS.
A YES VOTE SENATOR, WE HAVE A
WONDERFUL SENATOR, GREAT, GREAT
SENATOR, WHO IS A YES VOTE, BUT
HE'S HOME RECOVERING FROM A
PRETTY TOUGH SITUATION.
WITH SO MANY GREAT FEATURES,
INCLUDING THE BLOCK GRANTING,
THE MONEY TO THE STATES,
ET CETERA, ET CETERA, OUR
HEALTHCARE PLAN IS REALLY GOING
TO BE SOMETHING EXCELLENT.
IT'S GOING TO BE BETTER MANAGED
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT IT SERVES.
HAVING LOCAL HEALTHCARE
REPRESENTATIVES IS FAR BETTER
THAN HAVING HEALTHCARE MANAGED
FROM WASHINGTON D.C.
NOT EVEN A CONTEST.
[APPLAUSE]
AND MANY, MANY GOVERNORS, AS YOU
ALSO SEE, HAVE AGREED WITH US
AND APPROVED IT AND REALLY LOOK
FORWARD TO RUNNING IT PROPERLY.
BUT AGAIN, BECAUSE THE
RECONCILIATION WINDOW IS ABOUT
TO CLOSE, WE HAVE TO WAIT A FEW
MONTHS UNTIL IT REOPENS BEFORE
WE TAKE A VOTE.
SO WE'RE GETTING ALL OF THE GOOD
SIGNS FROM ALASKA AND THE OTHERS
TO REPEAL AND REPLACE OBAMACARE.
I WAS HOPING THIS WOULD BE PUT
ON MY DESK AFTER WE WON THE
ELECTION, AND I'D COME IN AND
SIGN BUT DIDN'T WORK THAT WAY.
A COUPLE OF PEOPLE THAT I WON'T
SAY ANYTHING.
BUT EARLY NEXT WE'RE WHEN
RECONCILIATION KICKS BACK IN, IN
ANY EVENT, LONG BEFORE THE
ELECTION WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A
VOTE AND WE'RE GOING TO GET THAT
THROUGH AND I THINK WE'LL GET IT
THROUGH EASILY.
BUT SPEAKING OF RECONCILIATION,
THE REPUBLICAN SENATE NEEDS TO
GET RID OF THE FILIBUSTER RULE,
WHICH IS BLOCKING SO MANY GREAT
LEGISLATIVE REFORMS.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE BADLY WANT
AND DESERVE IT.
BY THE WAY, THE DEMOCRATS, THEY
HAD THE OPPORTUNITY, WHICH
HOPEFULLY THEY WON'T FOR MANY,
MANY YEARS.
THEY WOULD GET RID OF IT ON DAY
ONE.
MOST OF YOU KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
I'M TALKING ABOUT.
WE'RE HERE TODAY IN INDIANA TO
ANNOUNCE OUR FRAME WORK TO
DELIVER HISTORIC TAX RELIEF TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
[APPLAUSE]
THIS IS A ONCE IN A GENERATION
OPPORTUNITY.
I GUESS IT'S PROBABLY SOMETHING
THAT I CAN SAY THAT I'M VERY
GOOD AT.
I'VE BEEN WAITING FOR THIS FOR A
LONG TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO CUT TAXES FOR THE
MIDDLE CLASS, MAYBE THE TAX CODE
SIMPLER AND MORE FAIR FOR
EVERYDAY AMERICANS AND WE'RE
GOING TO BRING BACK THE JOBS AND
WEALTH THAT HAVE LEFT OUR
COUNTRY AND MOST PEOPLE THOUGHT
LEFT OUR COUNTRY FOR GOOD.
[APPLAUSE]
WE WANT TAX REFORM THAT IS PRO
GROWTH, PRO JOBS, PRO WORKER,
PRO FAMILY AND YES, TAX REFORM
THAT IS PRO AMERICAN.
[APPLAUSE]
IT'S TIME TO TAKE CARE OF OUR
PEOPLE, TO REBUILD OUR NATION
AND TO FIGHT FOR OUR GREAT
AMERICAN WORKERS.
[APPLAUSE]
INDIANA IS A TREMENDOUS EXAMPLE
OF THE PROSPERITY THAT IS
UNLEASHED WHEN WE CUT TAXES AND
SET FREE THE DREAMS OF OUR
CITIZENS.
THIS STATE HAS CLAIMED A
POWERFUL COMPETITIVE EDGE BUILT
ON LOW TAXES AND LESS
REGULATION, AND ARE WE CUTTING
REGULATION.
[APPLAUSE]
AND BUSINESSES ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY HAVE TAKEN NOTICE.
IN RECENT YEARS, INDIANA HAS
WELCOMED DOZENS OF COMPANIES
FLEEING HIGH TAXES AND HIGH TAX
STATES.
THOUSANDS OF JOBS AND MASSIVE
CAPITAL INVESTMENT HAVE FOLLOWED
MEANING A BETTER QUALITY OF LIFE
FOR THE PEOPLE OF INDIANA.
ALL OF THIS IS POSSIBLE BECAUSE
THE PEOPLE OF THIS STATE HAVE
MADE A DECISION.
THEY CHOSE TO MAKE INDIANA
COMPETITIVE AGAIN.
THEY CHOSE AND THEIR CHOICE WAS
SO IMPORTANT, IT INCLUDED
ELECTING A GOVERNOR WHO YOU MAY
HAVE HEARD OF, WHO SIGNED THE
LARGEST INCOME TAX CUT IN THE
STATE'S HISTORY, OUR VERY
TERRIFIC PERSON AND TERRIFIC
VICE PRESIDENT, MIKE PENCE.
[CHEERS & APPLAUSE]
IT'S TIME FOR WASHINGTON TO
LEARN FROM THE WISDOM OF
INDIANA.
WE NEED WASHINGTON TO PROMOTE
AMERICAN JOBS INSTEAD OF
OBSTRUCTING THEM.
THAT IS WHAT I HAVE BEEN WORKING
TO ACHIEVE EVERY DAY SINCE I
TOOK OFFICE.
THAT IS WHAT I TALKED ABOUT ON
THE CAMPAIGN TRAIL.
ALREADY WE'RE SEEING THE RESULTS
OF AN ECONOMIC POLICY THAT
FINALLY PUTS AMERICA FIRST.
[APPLAUSE]
UNEMPLOYMENT IS AT A 16-YEAR
LOW.
UNEMPLOYMENT FOR AFRICAN
AMERICANS IS NEAR ITS LOWEST
POINT SINCE THE TURN OF THE
MILLENNIUM.
REALLY A FANTASTIC THING TO SEE.
[APPLAUSE]
WAGES ARE RISING.
OPTIMISM AMONG MANUFACTURERS HAS
REACHED ALL-TIME HIGHS.
GDP GROWTH LAST QUARTER REACHED
3% WAY AHEAD OF SCHEDULE.
NOBODY THOUGHT THAT WOULD HAPPEN
FOR A LONG TIME.
[APPLAUSE]
AND THIS QUARTER I BELIEVE WOULD
HAVE BEEN BETTER, BUT THE
HURRICANES WILL HAVE AN IMPACT.
OTHER THAN THAT, IT WOULD HAVE
BEEN IN MY OPINION EVEN BETTER.
YOUR GOVERNMENT IS WORKING FOR
YOU ONCE AGAIN, NOT FOR THE
DONORS, NOT THE SPECIAL
INTERESTS, BUT THE HARD-WORKING
TAX-PAYING CITIZENS OF OUR
COUNTRY.
[APPLAUSE]
AMERICA IS BACK ON THE RIGHT
TRACK, AND I SEE SO MANY RED
HATS "MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN."
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING.
MAKE AMERICA GREAT AGAIN.
[APPLAUSE]
OUR COUNTRY AND OUR ECONOMY
CANNOT TAKE OFF LIKE THEY SHOULD
UNLESS WE DRAMATICALLY REFORM
AMERICA'S OUTDATED COMPLEX AND
EXTREMELY BURDENSOME TAX CODE.
IT'S A RELIC.
HAVE TO CHANGE IT.
WE HAVE TO COMPETE.
COMPETE WITH OTHER COUNTRIES.
THE CURRENT TAX SYSTEM IS A
BARRIER STANDING IN THE WAY OF
AMERICA'S ECONOMIC COMEBACK.
BECAUSE IT CAN BE FAR GREATER
THAN IT'S EVER BEEN.
WE'RE GOING TO REMOVE THAT
BARRIER TO CREATE THE TAX SYSTEM
THAT OUR PEOPLE FINALLY,
FINALLY, FINALLY WANT AND
DESERVE.
FOR SEVERAL MONTHS, MY
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN WORKING
CLOSELY WITH CONGRESS TO DEVELOP
A FRAME WORK FOR TAX REFORM.
OVER THE NEXT FEW MONTHS, THE
HOUSE AND SENATE WILL BUILD ON
THIS FRAME WORK AND PRODUCE
LEGISLATION THAT WILL DELIVER
MORE JOBS, HIGHER PAY AND LOWER
TAXES FOR MIDDLE CLASS FAMILIES
FOR THE WORKING MAN AND WOMAN
AND FOR BUSINESSES OF ALL SIZES.
I LOOK FORWARD --
[APPLAUSE]
I LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING WITH
CONGRESS TO DELIVER THESE
HISTORIC TAX CUTS AND REFORMS TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
THESE TAX CUTS ARE SIGNIFICANT.
THERE'S NEVER BEEN TAX CUTS LIKE
WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
OUR FRAME WORK IS BASED ON FOUR
KEY IDEAS.
FIRST, WE WILL CUT TAXES FOR THE
EVERYDAY HARD-WORKING AMERICANS.
PEOPLE THAT WORK SO LONG, SO
HARD AND THEY HAVE BEEN
FORGOTTEN.
BUT THEY'RE NOT FORGOTTEN
ANYMORE.
I THINK WE PROVED THAT ON
NOVEMBER 8.
[APPLAUSE]
UNDER THIS FRAME WORK, THE FIRST
$12,000 OF INCOME EARNED BY A
SINGLE INDIVIDUAL WILL BE
TAX-FREE.
[APPLAUSE]
AND A MARRIED COUPLE WON'T PAY A
DIME IN TAXES ON THEIR FIRST
$24,000 OF INCOME.
SO A MARRIED COUPLE UP TO
$24,000 CAN SPEND THEIR MONEY ON
THEIR FAMILY, ON THEIR CHILDREN,
WHAT THEY HAVE TO DO.
SO MUCH BETTER.
IN OTHER WORDS, MORE INCOME FOR
MORE PEOPLE WILL BE TAXED AT A
RATE OF ZERO.
[APPLAUSE]
AT THIS 0% RATE, TAXABLE INCOME
WILL BE SUBJECT TO JUST THREE
TAX RATES OF 12%, 25% AND 35%.
JONATHAN BLANTON AND HIS WIFE,
JAMIE, FROM GREENTOWN ARE WITH
US HERE TODAY.
WHERE ARE THEY?
HELLO, JONATHAN.
HOW ARE YOU?
[APPLAUSE]
JONATHAN DOES INDUSTRIAL
JANITORIAL WORK AND JAMIE WORKS
AT AN AUTO COMPANY.
TOGETHER THEY'RE RAISING FOUR
BEAUTIFUL CHILDREN.
LAST YEAR THEY EARNED LESS THAN
$90,000.
UNDER OUR TAX PLAN, THEY WOULD
HAVE SAVED MORE THAN $1,000 AND
COULD BE SUBSTANTIALLY MORE, AND
THAT'S JUST ON FEDERAL TAXES.
SO THEY WOULD HAVE SAVED AT
LEAST $1,000.
MIDDLE INCOME FAMILIES WILL SAVE
MORE MONEY WITH AN INCREASED
CHILD TAX CREDIT FOR CHILDREN
UNDER THE AGE OF 17, WHICH SO
MANY FAMILIES HAVE BEEN CALLING
FOR.
[APPLAUSE]
WE WILL ELIMINATE THE MARRIAGE
PENALTY IN THE EXISTING CREDIT
AND EXPAND ELIGIBILITY TO
INCLUDE EVEN MORE MIDDLE INCOME
FAMILIES.
GREATLY EXPANDED.
WE'RE ALSO EXPANDING THE CHILD
TAX CREDIT BECAUSE WE BELIEVE
THE MOST IMPORTANT INVESTMENT
OUR COUNTRY CAN MAKE IS IN OUR
CHILDREN.
[APPLAUSE]
AND THIS IS JUST ONE MORE
CRITICAL WAY THAT WE'RE
TARGETING RELIEF TO WORKING
FAMILIES.
IN ADDITION UNDER THE FRAME
WORK, THOSE CARING FOR THE
ELDERLY LOVED AND WE LOVE THESE
PEOPLE, BUT WE'RE CARING AND WE
TAKE SUCH CARE OF THE ELDERLY.
OTHER ADULT DEPENDENTS WILL
RECEIVE FINANCIAL RELIEF IN THE
FORM OF A $500 TAX CREDIT.
[APPLAUSE]
WE'RE DOING EVERYTHING WE CAN TO
REDUCE THE TAX BURDEN ON YOU AND
YOUR FAMILY BY ELIMINATING TAX
BREAKS AND LOOP HOLES.
WE WILL ENSURE THAT THE BENEFITS
ARE FOCUSED ON THE MIDDLE CLASS,
THE WORKING MEN AND WOMEN, NOT
THE HIGHEST INCOME EARNERS.
[APPLAUSE]
OUR FRAME WORK INCLUDES OUR
COMMITMENT THAT TAX REFORM WILL
PROTECT LOW INCOME AND MIDDLE
INCOME HOUSEHOLDS.
NOT THE WEALTHY AND
WELL-CONNECTED.
THEY CAN CALL ME ALL THEY WANT.
IT'S NOT GOING TO HELP.
I'M DOING THE RIGHT THING.
IT'S NOT GOOD FOR ME, BELIEVE
ME.
[APPLAUSE]
BUT WHAT IS GOOD FOR ME, NOT
ONLY AS PRESIDENT AND LEGACY,
WHAT IS GOOD FOR ME IS IF
EVERYTHING TAKES OFF LIKE A
ROCKET SHIP LIKE IT SHOULD HAVE
FOR 20 YEARS.
THAT'S GOOD FOR ME.
THAT'S GOOD FOR EVERYONE.
[APPLAUSE]
THAT'S WHAT I THINK IS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
A LOT OF VERY WEALTHY PEOPLE
FEEL THE SAME WAY, BELIEVE ME.
IN FACT, WE'RE ELIMINATING MOST
ITEMIZED DEDUCTIONS THAT
PRIMARILY BENEFIT THE WEALTHIEST
TAXPAYERS.
WE'VE ALSO GIVEN CONGRESS THE
FLEXIBILITY TO ADD AN ADDITIONAL
TOP RATE ON THE VERY HIGHEST
INCOME EARNERS TO PROVIDE EVEN
MORE TAX RELIEF FOR WORKING
PEOPLE.
SECOND, OUR FRAME WORK WILL MAKE
THE TAX CODE SIMPLE, FAIR AND
EASY TO UNDERSTAND.
FINALLY.
AMERICANS WASTE MONEY --
[APPLAUSE]
AMERICANS WASTE A MUCH MONEY.
BILLIONS AND BILLIONS OF DOLLARS
AND MANY HOURS EACH YEAR TO
COMPLY WITH OUR RIDICULOUSLY
COMPLEX TAX CODE.
MORE THAN 90% OF AMERICANS USE
ASSISTANCE TO PREPARE THEIR
TAXES.
UNDER OUR FRAME WORK, THE VAST
MAJORITY OF FAMILIES WILL BE
ABLE TO FILE THEIR TAXES ON A
SINGLE SHEET OF PAPER.
[APPLAUSE]
WE ARE ALSO REPEALING THE
ALTERNATIVE MINIMUM TAX OR AMT.
IT'S ABOUT TIME.
[APPLAUSE]
THE AMT IS ACTUALLY A SHADOW TAX
SYSTEM THAT REQUIRES MANY PEOPLE
TO CALCULATE THEIR TAXES TWO
DIFFERENT WAYS AND PAY THE
HIGHER OF THE TWO AMOUNTS.
YOU'RE ALL FAMILIAR WITH IT.
UNDER OUR FRAME WORK, THE AMT
WILL MAKE EVEN LESSENS BECAUSE
WE'RE REPEALING MANY OF THE
SPECIAL INTERESTS TAX BREAKS
THAT IT WAS DESIGNED TO DEAL
WITH.
WE'RE MAKING OUR TAXES SIMPLE
AGAIN.
WE'RE SIMPLIFYING OUR TAX
SYSTEM.
TO PROTECT MILLIONS OF SMALL
BUSINESSES AND THE AMERICAN
FARMER, WE ARE FINALLY ENDING
THE CRUSHING, THE HORRIBLE, THE
UNFAIR ESTATE TAX OR AS IT IS
OFTEN REFERRED TO AS THE DEATH
TAX.
[CHEERS & APPLAUSE]
THAT MEANS ESPECIALLY FOR ALL OF
YOU WITH SMALL BUSINESSES THAT
ARE REALLY TREMENDOUS
BUSINESSES, YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
LEAVE THEM TO YOUR FAMILY AND
YOUR FAMILY WON'T HAVE TO RUN
OUT AND DO A FIRE SALE TO TRY TO
GET THE MONEY TO PAY THE TAX.
LOSE THE BUSINESS.
ENDS UP GOING OUT OF BUSINESS.
ALL OF THOSE JOBS ARE LOST.
THE FARMERS IN PARTICULAR ARE
AFFECTED.
THEY HAVE WONDERFUL FARMS, BUT
THEY CAN'T PAY THE TAX.
SO THEY HAVE TO SELL THE FARM TO
PEOPLE THAT BUY IT.
DON'T RUN IT WITH LOVE.
THEY CAN'T RUN IT THE SAME WAY.
IT GOES OUT.
SO THAT DEATH TAX IS A DISASTER
FOR THIS COUNTRY AND A DISASTER
FOR SO MANY SMALL BUSINESSES AND
FARMERS AND WE'RE GETTING RID OF
IT.
[APPLAUSE]
NOW IF YOU DON'T LIKE YOUR
FAMILY, IT WON'T MATTER.
BUT FOR THOSE THAT LOVE YOUR
FAMILY, IT MATTERS A LOT.
WITH US TODAY IS KIP THOM, A
FAMILY FARMER FROM LEESBURG.
HI, KIP.
WHO FEARS THAT HIS FAMILY'S
FARMING HERITAGE, BEEN A LONG
TIME.
HOW LONG, KIP?
187 YEARS.
THAT'S PEANUTS.
[APPLAUSE]
WOW.
THAT'S A LONG TIME.
BUT THAT GREAT HERITAGE COULD
COME TO AN END BECAUSE OF THE
DEATH TAX OR THE ESTATE TAX AND
COULD MAKE IT IMPOSSIBLE FOR HIM
TO PASS THAT LEGACY TO HIS
WONDERFUL FAMILY.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO LET THAT
HAPPEN.
WE ARE NOT GOING TO ALLOW THE
DEATH TAX TO STEAL AWAY THE
AMERICAN DREAM FROM THESE GREAT,
GREAT FAMILIES.
MANY OF WHICH ARE IN THIS ROOM
TODAY.
[APPLAUSE]
WE WILL PROTECT OUR FARMERS, OUR
RANCHERS AND OUR SMALL
BUSINESSES, AND WE WILL MAKE
TAXES SIMPLE, EASY AND FAIR FOR
ALL AMERICANS.
OKAY?
[APPLAUSE]
30, WE WILL CUT TAXES ON
AMERICAN BUSINESSES TO RESTORE
OUR COMPETITIVE EDGE AND CREATE
MORE JOBS AND HIGHER WAGES FOR
AMERICAN WORKERS.
[APPLAUSE]
IN INDIANA YOU HAVE SEEN FIRST
HAND THAT CUTTING TAXES ON
BUSINESSES MAKES YOUR STATE MORE
COMPETITIVE AND LEADS TO MORE
JOBS AND HIGHER PAYCHECKS FOR
YOUR WORKERS.
NOW WE WANT TO DO THE SAME THING
FOR AMERICA, MAKING OUR COUNTRY
MORE COMPETITIVE WITH OTHER
NATIONS.
IN MANY CASES, THOSE OTHER
NATIONS ARE TAKING ADVANTAGE OF
NEWS SO MANY WAYS.
THEY SAY THEY'RE FRIENDS.
PERHAPS THEY ARE.
BELIEVE ME, I'M RENEGOTIATING
OUR TRADE DEALS, INCLUDING
NAFTA, INCLUDING MANY OTHER
TRADE DEALS.
[APPLAUSE]
THROUGH REGULATION, ALL YOU HAVE
TO DO IS LOOK AT THE MASSIVE
PIPELINES, DAKOTA ACCESS.
YOU TAKE A LOOK.
48,000 JOBS IMMEDIATELY
APPROVED.
SO WE'RE LETTING THAT HAPPEN.
BUT IN TERMS OF THE TAX AND THE
TAX STRATEGY THAT RONALD REAGAN
USED TO CREATE AN ECONOMIC BOOM
IN THE 80s WHEN OUR ECONOMY TOOK
OFF, THE MIDDLE CLASS THRIVED
AND THE FAMILY INCOME, ALL
FAMILIES, WAS INCREASING MORE
AND MORE AND WAS A BEAUTIFUL
SIGHT TO BEHOLD.
SINCE THEN OTHER NATIONS HAVE A
CONTINUED UNFORTUNATELY OUR
PLAYBOOK.
RAN IT EVEN BETTER THAN WE DID.
I SHOULDN'T SAY EVEN BETTER,
BECAUSE WE DIDN'T RUN IT WELL AT
ALL AND WE LET OTHER NATIONS
COME IN AND TAKE ADVANTAGE OF US
AND TAKE OUR JOBS AWAY AND OUR
BUSINESSES OUT.
WE'RE STOPPING THAT.
YOU CAN SEE IT RIGHT HERE WHAT
WE'VE DONE.
TODAY OUR TOTAL BUSINESS TAX
RATE IS 60% HIGHER THAN OUR
AVERAGE FOREIGN COMPETITOR IN
THE DEVELOPED WORLD.
THAT'S NOT GOOD.
WE HAVE SURRENDERED OUR
COMPETITIVE EDGE TO OTHER
COUNTRIES BUT WE'RE NOT
SURRENDERING ANYMORE.
UNDER OUR FRAME WORK, WE WILL
DRAMATICALLY CUT THE BUSINESS
TAX RATE SO THAT AMERICAN
COMPANIES AND AMERICAN WORKERS
CAN BEAT OUR FOREIGN COMPETITORS
AND START WINNING AGAIN.
[APPLAUSE]
WE WILL REDUCE THE CORPORATE TAX
RATE TO NO HIGHER THAN 20%.
WAY DOWN FROM 35 AND 39.
[APPLAUSE]
WHICH IS SUBSTANTIALLY BELOW THE
AVERAGE OF OTHER INDUSTRIALIZED
NATIONS.
THIS IS A REVOLUTIONARY CHANGE
AND THE BIGGEST WINNERS WILL BE
THE EVERYDAY AMERICAN WORKERS AS
JOBS STARTS POURING INTO OUR
COUNTRY AS COMPANIES START
COMPETING FOR AMERICAN LABOR AND
AS WAGES START GOING UP AT
LEVELS THAT YOU HAVEN'T SEEN IN
MANY YEARS.
[APPLAUSE]
WHEN OUR COMPANIES MOVED TO
OTHER COUNTRIES, IT'S OUR LOYAL
AMERICAN WORKERS THAT GET HURT.
WHEN COMPANIES STAY IN AMERICA
AND COME TO AMERICA, IT'S OUR
WONDERFUL WORKERS THAT REAP THE
REWARDS.
I JUST LEFT THE UNITED NATIONS
LAST WEEK AND I WAS TOLD BY ONE
OF THE MOST POWERFUL LEADERS OF
THE WORLD THAT THEY'RE GOING TO
BE ANNOUNCING IN THE NOT TOO
DISTANCE FUTURE FIVE MAJOR
FACTORIES IN THE UNITED STATES
BETWEEN INCREASING AND NEW.
FIVE.
YOU'LL BE HEARING ABOUT THAT
VERY SOON.
AND I SAID THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
HE SAID, YOU KNOW WHAT?
IT'S STARTING TO HAPPEN IN THE
UNITED STATES.
IT'S STARTING TO HAPPEN.
SO I JUST WANT TO LET YOU KNOW
THAT.
I PROMISED I WOULDN'T SAY WHO.
I'LL KEEP MY WORD.
OKAY?
UNLESS YOU FORCE ME.
MEMBERS OF BOTH PARTIES --
HAPPENS TO BE IN THE AUTOMOBILE
INDUSTRY.
MEMBERS OF BOTH PARTIES SHOULD
AGREE THAT WE NEED A TAX CODE
THAT KEEPS JOBS IN OUR COUNTRY
AND BRINGS JOBS BACK TO OUR
COUNTRY.
[APPLAUSE]
AROUND FOR THE MILLIONS OF SMALL
BUSINESSES AND FARMS THAT FILE
THEIR TAXES AS SOLE PROPRIETORS,
WE WILL CAP THE TAX RATE THEY
PAY AT 25%.
MUCH LOWER.
BIG DIFFERENCE.
THIS WILL BE THE LOWEST TOP
MARGINAL INCOME TAX RATE FOR
SMALL AND MID SIZE BUSINESSES
THIS COUNTRY IN MORE THAN 80
YEARS.
TO GIVE BUSINESSES EVEN MORE
REASON TO BOOTH THEIR INVESTMENT
IN AMERICA, FOR THE NEXT FIVE
YEARS OUR FRAME WORK WILL ALLOW
TO FULLY WRITE OFF -- LISTEN TO
THIS -- THE COST OF EQUIPMENT IN
THE YEAR THEY BUY IT.
THAT IS BIG.
[APPLAUSE]
AND THAT'S INSTEAD OF HAVING TO
TAKE DEDUCTIONS AND DEDUCT THE
COST OVER A LONG PERIOD OF TIME.
THAT'S CALLED INCENTIVE.
THIS WILL BE TREMENDOUSLY
IMPORTANT TO HELP AMERICAN
BUSINESSES AFFORD THE HEAVY
INDUSTRIAL MACHINERY AND OTHER
CAPITAL INVESTMENTS THEY NEED TO
GROW BIG AND GROW STRONG.
JOINING US TODAY IS JOHN GANNON,
THE OWNER OF A CUSTOM WOOD
FENCING AND CONSTRUCTION COMPANY
IN INDIANAPOLIS.
JOHN IS THE FATHER OF NINE
CHILDREN AND RECENTLY CELEBRATED
HIS 35th WEDDING ANNIVERSARY.