YOU WHEN IT HAPPENS.
IT'S BEEN A BUSY HOUR.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
MORE NEWS NOW.
HERE'S SHEP.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST, 3:00 IN PUERTO RICO
WHERE HURRICANE MARIA HAS BEEN
PUNISHING THAT ISLAND WITH
POWERFUL WINDS.
>> WE'VE BEEN SEEING STRONG
WINDS WELL OVER 100 MILES FOR
TWO HOURS HERE, STRONG ENOUGH TO
CAUSE VISIBLE DESTRUCTION.
WE'VE SEEN TREES SNAPPED, PARTS
OF WELL-MADE STRUCTURES
COLLAPSE.
>> Shepard: AS STEVE CAN ATTEST,
IT'S A CATASTROPHIC STORM.
ONE OF THE STRONGEST TO EVER HIT
AMERICAN SOIL AND THE
DESTRUCTION COULD BE WIDESPREAD.
WE'RE TRACKING THE HURRICANE.
PLUS, IN MEXICO CITY, CRIES OF
ANGUISH AT THE SITE OF A SCHOOL
COLLAPSED IN THE EARTHQUAKE.
PARENTS STILL WAITING TO FIND
OUT WHAT HAPPENED TO THEIR KIDS.
RESCUERS WORKING THROUGH THE
NIGHT, SEARCHING FOR SURVIVORS.
WE'LL GO THERE LIVE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SET TO MEET WITH
THE BRITISH PRIME MINISTER.
THE LEADER OF OUR STRONGEST
ALLY.
WE'RE EXPECTING THAT IN THIS
HOUR.
LET'S GET TO IT.
WE'RE TRACKING TWO DEADLY
NATURAL DISASTERS.
THE DANGEROUS HURRICANE MAKING
ITS WAY ACROSS THE CARIBBEAN AND
THE EARTHQUAKE IN MEXICO.
WE'LL GO LIVE TO MEXICO CITY IN
JUST A MOMENT.
BUT HURRICANE MARIA HAS KILLED
ANYBODY PEOPLE ACROSS THE
CARIBBEAN.
TODAY IT MADE LANDFALL AS ONE OF
THE STRONGEST TO HIT PUERTO RICO
AND ST. CROIX.
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR SAYS
PUERTO RICANS HAVE NOT
EXPERIENCED AN EVENT OF THIS
MAGNITUDE IN THEIR MODERN
HISTORY.
HERE'S A LOOK AT THE STORM FROM
SPACE AS THE CORE MOVES OVER
PUERTO RICO.
THE HURRICANE MADE LANDFALL AS A
CATEGORY FOUR.
THE STORM ON THE SOUTHEAST COAST
OF THE ISLAND WITH SUSTAINED
WINDS OF 155 MILES AN HOUR.
THE NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER
WARNING OF LIFE THREATENING
WINDS AND STORM SURGE AND RAIN
OVER PUERTO RICO IN ST. CROIX
TODAY.
WATER LEVELS COULD RISE UP TO
NINE FEET ON PUERTO RICO WITH
LARGE AND DESTRUCTIVE WAVES.
THE DANGEROUS WINDS ARE EXPECTED
TO CONTINUE FOR 24 HOURS.
PUERTO RICAN OFFICIALS SAY
DOZENS OF COMMUNITIES WILL HAVE
TO BE REBUILD.
THEY SAY THE STORM COULD
"DECIMATE" THE ISLAND'S POWER
COMPANY.
IN ONE NEIGHBORHOOD ON PUERTO
RICO'S NORTHERN COAST, THE MAYOR
SAID FOUR OUT OF FIVE HOMES ARE
DESTROYED.
THE STORM HAS SNAPPED PALM
TREES, PEELED OFF ROOFTOPS.
PEOPLE IN THE CAPITOL OF
SAN JUAN ARE REPORTING
WIDESPREAD FLOODING.
SOME IN HIGH RISE APARTMENTS.
ONE WOMAN THAT LIVES IN SAN JUAN
TOLD THE "MIAMI HERALD" THAT HER
HOUSE WAS TREMBLING.
THE RAIN HORIZONTAL AND ALL THE
TREES ON THE GROUND.
SHE SAID THE WINDS ARE LIKE
SOMETHING OUT OF A HORROR MOVIE.
WE'RE ALSO GETTING A LOOK AT THE
DEVASTATION ON THE SMALL ISLAND
OF DOMINIC DiNATALE --
DOMINIQUE.
THE STORM HIT AND BLEW AWAY THE
MAYOR'S ROOF.
HERE'S A LOOK AT THE DAMAGE IN
ST. CROIX, ONE OF THE U.S.
VIRGIN ISLANDS.
THE HURRICANE SIDE SWIPED THE
ISLAND.
KNOCKING OVER TREES, TOPPLING
POWER LINES AND CAUSING SEVERE
FLOODING.
OFFICIALS IN ST. CROIX WARNED
PEOPLE TO STAY AWAKE MOST OF THE
NIGHT AND KEEP THEIR SHOES ON IN
CASE THEY NEEDED TO RUN.
FORECASTERS SAY HURRICANE FORCE
WINDS EXTEND 60 MILES FROM THE
EYE OF MARIA.
THEY SAY THE CENTER OF THE STORM
IS EXPECTED TO CROSS OVER THE
COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
TONIGHT BEFORE MOVING TO THE
TURKS AND CAICOS AND THE
BAHAMAS.
I WANT TO GET STRAIGHT TO STEVE
HARRIGAN WHO IS LIVE IN SAN JUAN
FOR US THIS AFTERNOON.
STEVE, LOOKS LIKE THINGS HAVE
CALMED DOWN.
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE NOW?
>> SHEPARD, THE WIND HAS CALMED
CONSIDERABLY, UNDER 50 MILES PER
HOUR THAT MEANS THE POLICE AND
FIRST RESPONDERS CAN GO OUT.
EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK HERE, IT'S A
WET MISS AND IT'S NOT GETTING
BETTER SOON.
WHERE I'M STANDING NOW, CHUNKS
OF BUILDINGS, SATELLITE DISHES,
BALCONIES, PIECES OF WALL, HOLES
IN BUILDINGS.
THAT WAS 145 MILES PER HOUR
WINDS EARLIER THIS MORNING.
WE JUST MOVED AROUND TO A
NEIGHBORHOOD.
IF YOUR HOUSE IS MADE OF WOOD
WITH A METAL ROOF, JUST GONE.
SOME HOUSES WE SAW ON THE STREET
GONE.
TO MOVE AROUND HERE, IT'S
STREAMLY DIFFICULT.
IF YOU'RE AN AVERAGE CITIZEN IN
PUERTO RICO RIGHT NOW, YOU MIGHT
NOT HAVE A ROOF.
YOU PROBABLY HAVE STRUCTURAL
DAMAGE WHEREVER YOU LIVE AND YOU
DEFINITELY DO NOT HAVE
ELECTRICITY.
A SITUATION THAT COULD LAST FOR
WEEKS OR MONTHS, SHEPARD.
>> GOING FORWARD, FLOODS AND
MUDSLIDES.
>> IT'S NOT OVER YET.
THE WINDS WERE DRAMATIC AND
POSSIBLY DEADLY.
WE DON'T KNOW THE RESULTS YET.
WE SAW POWER CREWS OUT ON FOOT
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T GET ANYWHERE.
THERE'S SO MANY DOWNED POWER
LINES AND DOWNED BRANCHES.
THEY WERE WALKING TO TRY TO
ASSESS THE DAMAGE.
AS FAR AS THE MUDSLIDES GO,
ESPECIALLY IN THE CENTRAL
MOUNTAINOUS PART OF THE COUNTRY
THAT IS LIKELY WHEN YOU GET
10-15 INCHES OF RAIN.
FEMA HAS PREPOSITIONED HERE.
WE'LL SEARCH AND RESCUE AND A
LOT OF RECOVERY.
>> Shepard: THANKS, STEVE.
LET'S GET TO RICK REICHMUTH IN
THE EXTREME WEATHER CENTER, THIS
IS AWFUL.
>> A HORRIBLE FORM.
MAKING LANDFALL 6:15 A.M.
MAYBE A LITTLE BRIGHT NEWS,
ANOTHER GOING OVER LAND DURING
THE DAYLIGHT HOURS.
ALMOST EVERY RECORD IN PUERTO
RICO AT RECORD FLOOD STAGE.
ALL OF THEM GOING UP INCREDIBLY
FAST.
UNFORTUNATELY, CUTTING A CROSS
DIAGONALLY ACROSS THE ISLAND.
EVERYBODY FEELING THE IMPACTS OF
THIS STORM, THIS IS THE FUTURE
RADAR.
THE RUSSIA ARE THE HURRICANE
FORCE WINDS STAYING TO THE NORTH
OF THE NORTH SIDE OF THE IDEA OF
THE D.R.
HOPEFULLY TO THE EAST OF TURKS
AND CAICOS THAT GOT DEVASTATED
BY IRMA A COUPLE WEEKS AGO.
THEN IT CONTINUES TO PULL TO THE
NORTH.
MOST OF THE MODELS MAKE THIS
NORTH WARD TURN HERE.
THIS IS GOOD NEWS FOR THE
SOUTHEASTERN PART OF THE U.S.
WHICH WE THOUGHT WOULD HAVE A
DISTRICT IMPACT, THIS IS
FOLLOWING A SIMILAR TRAJECTORY
AS TO WHAT THE HURRICANE JOSE
HAS DONE.
PULLING TO THE MID-ATLANTIC AND
AROUND PARTS OF THE NORTHEAST.
WE'LL BE ADDING IMPACTS ACROSS
PARTS OF THE NORTHEAST WEDNESDAY
AND THURSDAY AS THE STORM PULLS
OFF TO THE NORTH.
THAT SAID, TOO EARLY TO SAY WHAT
THE IMPACTS ARE.
DO WE HAVE A DISTRICT HIT
SOMEWHERE?
MAYBE ON THE OUTER BANKS?
IT'S A POSSIBILITY.
SOMEWHERE FARTHER IN FROM NEW
YORK CITY UP AROUND PARTS OF THE
NORTHEAST, TOO EARLY TO SAY WHAT
WE DO KNOW, ENVIRONMENTAL
CONDITIONS ARE LESS FAVORABLE
FOR A STRONG HURRICANE.
THE WATER TEMPERATURES COME DOWN
AS WELL.
ALL GUIDANCES HAVE A WEAKER
STORM.
BUT TUESDAY, A STORM OFF THE
SHORE OF THE MID-ATLANTIC, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT A SEASON, RICK.
CAN YOU IMAGINE LIVING THROUGH
THIS THING?
NO LIGHTS, NO WAY TO GET HELP,
NO IDEA WHETHER YOUR HOME WILL
STAND UP OR FALL DOWN AROUND
YOU.
WE'LL SPEAK WITH A WOMAN RIDING
OUT THE STORM, HIDING IN HER
CLOSET.
THAT'S COMING UP FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK ON THIS WEDNESDAY
AFTERNOON.
Ugh. Heartburn.
Sorry Ma'am.
No burning here.
Try Alka-Seltzer
Heartburn relief
gummies.
They don't taste
chalky and work fast.
MMMM. Incredible.
Can I try?
She doesn't
have heartburn.
Alka-Seltzer heartburn
relief gummies.
Enjoy the relief.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
>> Shepard: MORE ON HURRICANE
MARIA AS IT BATTERS PUERTO RICO.
OFFICIALS SAY THE EXTREMELY
DANGEROUS STORM KNOCKED OUT
POWER TO THE ENTIRE ISLAND.
BLEW OUT WINDOWS IN SAN JUAN.
LET'S TURN TO JENNIFER GONZALEZ
COLON NOW.
SHE'S PUERTO RICO'S RESIDENT
COMMISSIONER.
THE ISLAND'S REPRESENTATIVE IN
CONGRESS AND RIDING OUT THE
STORM IN A CLOSET EAST OF
SAN JUAN.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> RIGHT NOW, I'M FINE.
WAITING UNTIL THE WINDS GETS
OVER THE ISLAND.
WE ARE STILL HAVING WINDS MORE
THAN 60 MILES PER HOUR.
SO OFFICIALS ARE ASKING PEOPLE
TO REMAIN AT THEIR HOMES BECAUSE
IT'S NOT SAFE YET TO GET OUT OF
THE HOUSES.
THERE'S A LOT OF FLOODING IN
MANY AREAS.
WE RECEIVED BETWEEN 12 TO 35
INCHES OF RAIN DURING THIS DAY.
THE WINDS BEGAN AT 1:00 A.M. IN
THE MORNING.
WE'RE STILL HAVING THE SEVERE
CONDITIONS AND SEVERE WINDS
ACROSS THE ISLAND.
ONE OF THE MAIN ISSUES IS THAT
THE RIVERS OVERFLOWED THEIR
BANKS.
SO IT'S REALLY SCARY.
WE NEVER HAD THIS KIND OF
HURRICANE BEFORE.
OF COURSE, THE WHOLE ISLAND IS
WITHOUT POWER.
>> Shepard: HOW ARE YOU TALKING
TO US?
>> I HAVE EXTRA BATTERIES FOR MY
CELL PHONE BECAUSE IT'S THE ONLY
WAY TO HAVE COMMUNICATION.
ACTUALLY, A LOT OF COMMUNICATION
TOWERS WENT DOWN AND ARE OFF
LINE.
A LOT OF THE PEOPLE ON THE
ISLAND DO NOT HAVE COMMUNICATION
AT THIS TIME.
SO THAT'S MAYBE THE REASON SOME
PEOPLE THAT ARE IN THE STATES
ARE CALLING THEIR FAMILIES AND
PEOPLE AND FRIENDS IN PUERTO
RICO AND THEY'RE NOT ANSWERING,
BECAUSE OF THAT.
>> Shepard: REPRESENTATIVE
GONZALEZ COLON, THERE'S SO MANY
PUERTO RICANS, THERE'S SO MANY
CONCERNED ABOUT THE AREA OUTSIDE
OF THE CAPITOL.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW FROM THE
NEIGHBORHOODS?
WERE PEOPLE EVACUATED
EFFICIENTLY?
>> YES, STILL, A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE STILL HERE BECAUSE OF THE
FLOODING AND THE RIVERS OUT OF
THEIR BANKS.
THIS IS THE MAIN PROBLEM WE HAVE
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S NOT SAFE TO GET OUT OF THE
HOUSES.
IN SAN JUAN, A LOT OF PEOPLE
LOST THEIR HOMES IN THE AREAS
HIT HARD.
A LOT OF PEOPLE LOST THEIR HOMES
BECAUSE OF THE HEAVY WINDS.
ESPECIALLY PEOPLE WITH WOODEN
HOUSES.
THOSE WOODEN HOUSES ARE ALMOST
GONE IN MANY AREAS OF THE
ISLAND.
I'M SPEAKING WITH YOU.
I'M STILL HAVING HEAVY WINDS IN
MY OWN HOUSE.
THE HOUSE JUST TREMBLED DURING
THIS SITUATION.
>> Shepard: CONGRESS WOMAN, FOR
OUR VIEWERS WATCHING ACROSS THE
48 AND AROUND THE WORLD THIS
AFTERNOON, WHAT CAN PEOPLE DO TO
HELP YOU AND THE PEOPLE OF
PUERTO RICO?
WHAT IS THE MOST URGENT NEED?
HOW CAN WE HELP?
>> THE MOST URGENT NEED IS
RESTORING THE POWER ON THE
ISLAND.
FOR THAT MATTER, I ASK DIRECTLY
VICE PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE LAST
NIGHT.
HE CALLED ME.
I ASKED HIM DIRECTLY AND SOME
OTHER CABINET MEMBERS TO SEND
ELECTRIC TEAMS TO THE ISLAND TO
HELP US RESTORE THE POWER GRID.
THE SECOND ONE, THE GOVERNOR OF
PUERTO RICO, HELP FOR THOSE
PEOPLE THAT LOST THEIR
BELONGINGS.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A LONG TIME
TO RECOVER THE INFRASTRUCTURE OF
THE ISLAND.
ROADS, BRIDGES AND MANY
HOSPITALS HAVE BEEN HIT DIRECTLY
BY THIS HURRICANE.
YOU'LL HAVE THAT.
ALSO IN THE HOTELS AND METRO
AREA.
SO WE STILL DON'T KNOW THE FULL
EXTENT OF THE DAMAGE OF THIS
MONSTER HURRICANE LEFT US HERE.
>> Shepard: IW K TNOHERETAT GES
F AARHEORRE T VERY YOUNG AND
THE VERY OLD.
IT'S A GOOD TIME TO REMEMBER
THAT PUERTO RICANS ARE AMERICANS
JUST LIKE ALL OF US.
THEY DIE ON THE BATTLEFIELD AND
SALUTE THE SAME FLAG.
I KNOW THIS NATION AND THE
GENEROUS PEOPLE OF AMERICA WILL
RESPOND AS THEY ALWAYS DO.
ALL THE BEST, CONGRESSWOMAN.
WE'RE THINKING ABOUT YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
AS YOU SAID, THERE'S FOUR
MILLION AMERICAN CITIZENS HERE.
FIVE MILLION PUERTO RICANS IN
THE MAINLAND.
IT'S THE THIRD TIME IN LESS THAN
A MONTH THAT A HURRICANE
LANDFALL ON THE U.S. SOIL.
IN OUR CASE, TWICE.
IRMA AND WITH MARIA.
WE'VE BEEN MANAGING PEOPLE FROM
ST. THOMAS, THE U.S. VIRGIN
ISLANDS, THE BRITISH VIRGIN
ISLANDS, GIVING SHELTER TO THEM.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO NEED A LOT OF
HELP.
I WANT TO THANK VICE PRESIDENT
MIKE PENCE AND FEMA DIRECTOR FOR
THEIR CALLS AND THEIR DILIGENCE.
THEY'RE ALREADY ON THE ISLAND,
FEMA, WORKING WITH THE GOVERNOR,
WORKING WITH THE TEAMS.
WE MAY NEED A LOT OF HELP TO
HELP THE ISLAND RECOVER.
>> Shepard: WE'LL BE SPEAKING TO
BROCK LONG IN JUST A MOMENT FROM
FEMA.
THANKS, REPRESENTATIVE
GONZALEZ-COLON.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: A NINTH PATIENT HAS
DIED AFTER HURRICANE IRMA TURNED
A FLORIDA NURSING HOME INTO AN
OVEN.
THAT'S THE WORD OF POLICE FROM
HOLLYWOOD.
COPS THERE SAY THE LATEST VICTIM
HAD BEEN 93 YEARS OLD.
THIS COMES NEARLY A WEEK AFTER
RESCUERS FOUND ELDERLY PATIENTS
SWELTERING IN THAT FACILITY.
THE STORM KNOCKED OUT THE AIR
CONDITIONING.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE STAFF
DIDN'T CALL 911 FOR THREE DAYS.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE LAUNCHED A
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION NOW.
THE CENTER'S ADMINISTRATOR HAS
SAID THAT STAFFERS DILIGENTLY
PREPARED FOR THE IMPACT OF
HURRICANE IRMA.
YET WHEN THE AIR CONDITIONING
WENT OUT ON ELDERLY AND
INFIRMED, THEY DID NOT CALL 911
FOR THREE DAYS.
WE'RE WATCHING THE AFTERMATH OF
ANOTHER NATURAL DISASTER.
ONE THAT BROKE DURING THIS HOUR
YESTERDAY.
CREWS ARE DIGGING THROUGH THE
REMAINS OF A SCHOOL LOOKING FOR
ANYBODY THAT MAY HAVE SURVIVED
YESTERDAY'S DEVASTATING
EARTHQUAKE IN MEXICO.
PARENTS WAIT FOR WORD ON THEIR
CHILDREN.
AGONIZING HOURS GO BY.
FIREFIGHTERS, POLICE,
VOLUNTEERS, RESCUE DOGS WERE ON
SCENE.
WE'LL TAKE YOU THERE AFTER THIS.
(VO) Pro Plan Bright Mind
Adult 7+ promotes alertness and
mental sharpness in dogs
7 and older.
(Ray) The difference has been
incredible.
She is much more aware. She
wants to learn things.
(VO) Purina Pro Plan Bright
Mind. Nutrition that performs.
Approaching Medicare
eligibility?
Don't put off checking out your
Medicare options until 65.
Now is a good time to get the
ball rolling.
Medicare only covers about
eighty percent of
Part B medical costs.
The rest is up to you.
That's where AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plans
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company come in.
Like all standardized Medicare
supplement insurance plans,
they could help save you in
out-of-pocket medical costs.
Taking informed steps really
makes a difference later.
That's what it means to
GO LONG™.
Call now and request this free
Decision Guide
and explore the range of AARP
Medicare Supplement Plans.
All plans like these let you
choose any doctor or hospital
that accepts Medicare patients.
These are the only Medicare
supplement insurance plans
endorsed by AARP.
Call now and request your free
Decision Guide...
and start gathering the
information you need
to help you GO LONG™.
>> Shepard: EVEN BEFORE THIS
STORM, PUERTO RICO HAD A
CRUMBLING INFRASTRUCTURE AND
TENS OF BILLIONS IN DEBT.
THIS WILL COMPOUND THE PROBLEMS.
POWER LINES ALL OVER PUERTO
RICO.
TWO WEEKS AGO, HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDING WITHOUT ELECTRICITY.
NOW ALL OF PUERTO RICO IS
WITHOUT POWER RIGHT NOW.
THESE HURRICANES CAUSING MORE
PROBLEMS FOR AN ISLAND THAT HAS
SPENT YEARS IN FINANCIAL CRISIS.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THIS ONE
FOR US.
TRACE?
>> SHEP, THE ECONOMY IS
EXTREMELY DIRE.
PUERTO RICO IS A PUERTO RICO --
POOR ISLAND TO BEGIN WITH.
THEY HAVE BILLIONS IN UNFUNDED
PENSIONS TO TEACHERS AND
GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEES.
WHEN YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT AN
ISLAND WITH FIVE MILLION PEOPLE,
THAT IS ASTOUNDING.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF PUERTO
RICO'S BEST AND BRIGHTEST LEAVE
THE ISLAND EACH YEAR FOR BETTER
JOBS IN THE U.S.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THE STATE OF
EMERGENCY IN PUERTO RICO
DECLARED BY PRESIDENT TRUMP
COULD MEAN A LOT OF FEDERAL
DOLLARS FLOWING INTO THE ISLAND,
WHICH COULD BOOST THE ECONOMY AT
LEAST TEMPORARILY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE, THE STORMS
HAVE SHOWN HOW BAD SOME OF
PUERTO RICO'S INFRASTRUCTURE
PROBLEMS ARE.
>> RIGHT.
WE TALK ABOUT THE ISLAND BEING
WITHOUT POWER.
10% IS ALREADY WITHOUT POWER
FOLLOWING HURRICANE IRMA WHICH
DIDN'T HAVE A DIRECT HIT.
THE NUMBER 1 CLIENT IS THE WATER
COMPANY.
SO NO POWER MEANS NO WATER, NO
SEWER.
UNLIKE HERE IN THE U.S., THE
CELL PHONE PROVIDERS IN PUERTO
RICO RELY SOLELY ON THE PUBLIC
POWER GRID.
SO COMMUNICATIONS ARE ALSO VERY
LIMITED AND THE ISLAND'S POWER
AUTHORITY IS MASSIVELY IN DEBT.
SO TURNING THE LIGHTS BACK ON
COULD TAKE SEVERAL MONTHS.
WHEN IT COMES TO INFRASTRUCTURE,
IT GETS WORSE.
RETAINING WALLS AND BUILDINGS
ARE WEAK.
IN SOME CASES, THEY'RE DANGEROUS
BY YEARS OF DEFERRED MAINTENANCE
AND MEDICAL FACILITIES ARE
UNDERFUNDED AND COULD BE
OVERWHELMED BY THE STORM.
>> Shepard: THANKS, TRACE.
UPDATING THE TOP STORY.
THE FEDS FACING ANOTHER HUGE
CLEANUP.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THE HEAD OF
FEMA ABOUT RESPONSE AND WE'LL
WATCH FOR HURRICANE MARIA'S NEXT
MONTH.
FIRST, ANTHONY WIENER SOON TO
LEARN HIS SENTENCE FOR SEXTING
WITH A TEENAGE GIRL.
TODAY PROSECUTORS LAYING OUT HOW
LONG THEY WANT HIM IN PRISON.
DETAILS AHEAD.
>> A FOX REPORT NOW.
HEADLINES FROM THE FOX NEWS
DECK.
THE FIGHT TO LIBERATE RAQQA IN
SYRIA IS IN ITS FINAL STAGES.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM U.S.-BACKED
FIGHTERS THAT SAY THEY CONTROL
90% OF THE CAPITOL IN SYRIA.
THE U.S. HAS HUNDREDS OF TROOPS
ON THE GROUND FOR SUPPORT.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS URGING A
FORMER JUDGE TO SEND ANTHONY
WIENER TO PRISON FOR 27 MONTHS.
WIENER PLEADED GUILTY TO SENDING
OBSCENE TEXTS TO A 15-YEAR-OLD
GIRL.
HIS SENTENCING SET FOR MONDAY.
DEFENSE LAWYERS CLAIM THE TEEN
WAS THE AGGRESSOR AND MAY WANTED
TO HAVE GATHERED MATERIAL FOR A
BOOK.
WATCH THIS.
A SINKHOLE SWALLOWING A HOME
NEAR ORLANDO.
THE HOMEOWNER SAID IT WAS TIME
TO GET OUT OF DODGE WHEN SHE
HEARD THE HOUSE CREEKING AND
CRACKING AND NOTICED THE BATHTUB
SINKING INTO THE GROUND.
♪♪
So, I was at Mom and Dad's
and found this.
CD's, Baseball cards...
Your old magic set?
And this wrestling ticket...
Which you still owe me for.
Seriously?
$25?
I didn't even want to go.
Ahhh, your diary.
"Mom says it's totally
natural..."
$25 is nothing.
Abracadabra, Bro.
The Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
The fast, secure and simple way
to send money.
>> Shepard: AT LEAST 225 PEOPLE
CONFIRMED DEAD IN MEXICO AND
DOZENS OF HOMES DESTROYED AFTER
THE EARTHQUAKE THAT STRUCK 25
HOURS AGO.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO OFFICIALS ON
SCENE.
DRONE VIDEO SHOWS CREWS WORKING
AT A SCHOOL IN MEXICO.
ONE OF THE SEARCH AND RESCUE
MISSIONS ARE UNDERWAY RIGHT NOW.
VIDEO SHOWS RESCUERS PULLING
CHILDREN FROM WHAT REMAINS OF
THE SCHOOL.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
>> THERE YOU GO.
A LIVE LOOK AT THE SCHOOL WHERE
RESCUES ARE UNDERWAY RIGHT NOW.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR ANYBODY ELSE
THAT MAY HAVE SURVIVED AND SEEM
TO BE ONE PERSON MAY BE ALIVE IN
THERE.
THE QUAKE HIT YESTERDAY SOUTH
AND ET OF M