because it has two
rechargeable batteries.
That means you can
always be charging,
even while you're cleaning.
With Duo Clean, MultiFLEX,
and powerful suction
so you can go, and
go, and go again.
Welcome to hassle-free
runtime with Shark.
>> I'M JULIE BANDERAS WITH A FOX
REPORT.
A STAMPEDE KILLING 220 PEOPLE IN
INDIA.
IT HAPPENED IN THE MORNING RUSH
HOUR AT A TRAIN STATION IN
MUMBAI.
A RAILWAY SPOKESPERSON SAYS
THERE WAS A RAINSTORM AND A HUGE
CROWD OF PEOPLE TRAMPLED EACH
OTHER AS THEY TRIED TO STAY DRY.
TWO WOMEN ARE ALIVE AFTER A CAR
PLUNGED OFF A MOUNTAIN ROAD IN
CALIFORNIA.
A HELICOPTER MANAGED TO HOIST
THEM TO SAFETY WITH A GOOD
SAMARITAN.
AN OFF DUTY OFFICER SAW THEM.
AND IN PARIS, THE 300 MILLIONth
VISITOR TO THE EIFFEL TOWER.
[VO] QuickBooks introduces
Rodney.
He has a new business teaching
lessons.
Rodney wanted to know how his
business was doing...
...so he got QuickBooks.
It organizes all his accounts,
so he can see his bottom line.
Ahhh...that's a profit.
Know where you stand instantly.
Visit QuickBooks-dot-com.
People would ask
me in different
countries that
we traveled,
what is your
nationality and
I would always
answer Hispanic.
So when I got my Ancestry DNA
results it was a shocker.
I'm everything.
I'm from all nations.
I would look at forms
now and wonder
what do I mark?
Because I'm everything.
And I marked other.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
>> Trace: PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
TOM PRICE IS BECOMING A
DISTRACTION FROM THE UNVEILING
OF THE TRUMP TAX PLAN.
THE
PRESIDENT HAS SAID WE'LL SEE
WHETHER PRICE KEEPS HIS JOB
AFTER TAKING EXPENSIVE CHARTER
FLIGHTS WHEN CHEAPER COMMERCIAL
FLIGHTS WERE AVAILABLE.
PRICE TOLD FOX NEWS THAT HE
LOOKS FORWARD TO REGAINING TRUST
OF THE PRESIDENT AND THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE BUT HE GOT THE
GO-AHEAD TO TAKE THOSE TRIPS.
LISTEN.
>> WHAT WERE YOU THINKING AT
THOSE MOMENTS?
THESE FLIGHTS WERE CLEARLY TO
PLACES THAT HAD COMMERCIAL AIR
POSSIBILITIES.
>> THESE TRIPS WERE APPROVED
THROUGH THE NORMAL PROCESS.
IT WAS DEEMED APPROPRIATE AND
THAT THAT WAS THE NECESSARY WAY
TO BE ABLE TO MAKE MY OTHER
OBLIGATIONS WITHIN THE
DEPARTMENT.
>> PRICE OFFERED TO PAY $52,000
TO COVER THE COST OF HIS SEATS
ON THE PLANE.
POLITCO ESTIMATES THE TOTAL COST
WAS $400,000.
WE SHOULD NOTE IF HE PAYS THE
$51,000, THAT'S NO GUARANTEE
THAT HE WILL KEEP HIS JOB.
THE PRESIDENT IS ABOUT TO SPEAK.
WE'RE WAITING ABOUT 15 SECONDS
FROM NOW.
LET'S HEAR THE PRESIDENT ON TOP
PRICE.
>> WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
WE HAVE -- HE'S A VERY FINE MAN.
WE'LL MAKE A DECISION SOMETIME
TONIGHT.
HE'S A VERY FINE MAN.
AS FAR AS PUERTO RICO IS
CONCERNED, THAT'S BEEN GOING
REALLY WELL.
IT'S BEEN TOTAL DEVASTATION.
WE HAVE OVER 10,000 PEOPLE IN
PUERTO RICO RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE GETTING TRUCK DRIVERS
BECAUSE THE PEOPLE FROM PUERTO
RICO, THE DRIVERS JUST AREN'T
THERE.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR THEIR HOMES.
THEY HAVE OTHER PROBLEMS.
LIKEWISE WITH THE POLICE FORCE.
BUT I THINK IT'S GOING REALLY
WELL CONSIDERING.
RICK SCOTT, GOVERNOR WAS FLORIDA
WAS THERE.
HE'S GOING TO GET INVOLVED ALSO
WITH PUERTO RICO.
AND WE'VE MADE TREMENDOUS
STRIDES.
VERY TOUGH SITUATION.
A BIG QUESTION IS, WHAT
HAPPENS -- WE HAVE TO REBUILD.
IF YOU LOOK AT IT, THE
ELECTORATE IS GONE, THE ROADS
ARE GONE, THE TELECOMMUNICATIONS
ARE GONE.
THE REAL QUESTION IS WHAT WILL
HAPPEN LATER.
IT'S A TOUGH SITUATION.
THE LOSS OF LIFE IS ALWAYS
TRAGIC.
BUT IT'S BEEN INCREDIBLE THE
RESULTS THAT WE'VE HAD WITH
RESPECT TO LOSS OF LIFE.
PEOPLE CAN'T BELIEVE HOW
SUCCESSFUL THAT HAS BEEN
RELATIVELY SPEAKING.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> I CAN'T HEAR YOU, JOHN.
>> THE GOVERNOR OF PUERTO RICO
HAS BEEN UNBELIEVABLY GENEROUS
WITH HIS STATEMENTS.
HE'S BEEN PRAISING OUR EFFORTS.
THIS IS A VERY DIFFICULT -- THIS
IS A TOTAL DEVASTATION.
WHEN YOU LOOKS AT TEXAS AND WHEN
YOU LOOK AT FLORIDA, YOU KNOW,
IT'S A WHOLE DIFFERENT LEVEL.
NOBODY HAS EVER SEEN.
WHEN YOU HAVE A CATEGORY FIVE
WIFE OUT AN ISLAND LIKE THIS.
YOU HAVE NOTHING.
YOU DON'T HAVE THE ROADS, YOU
DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
YOU DON'T HAVE THE PEOPLE TO
OPERATE THE EQUIPMENT.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE HUNDREDS OF
TRUCK DRIVERS BEING BROUGHT IN
TO THE ISLAND TO OPERATE THE
TRUCKS.
BECAUSE THOSE PEOPLE HAVE LOST
THEIR HOMES.
SO THEY'RE UNABLE TO DO IT.
AND THE POLICE HAVE LOST THEIR
HOMES.
SO THEY'RE UNABLE TO DO IT.
IT'S A TOUGH SITUATION, JOHN.
>> WAS IT TOO EARLY TO SAY
PUERTO RICO WAS A GOOD STORY?
>> I HAVEN'T HEARD THAT.
WHAT I CAN TELL YOU, WE'VE DONE
AN INCREDIBLE JOB CONSIDERING
THERE'S NOTHING TO WORK WITH.
A VERY BIG QUESTION IS WHAT ARE
WE GOING TO
DO WITH THE POWER
PLANT?
THE POWER PLANT HAS BEEN WIPED
OUT.
IT'S NOT LIKE LET'S GO BACK AND
FIX IT.
THAT'S WHAT I DO.
I'M A GOOD CONSTRUCTION GUY.
YOU DON'T GO BACK AND FIX IT.
THERE IS NOTHING.
THE POWER GRID IS GONE.
SO WE HAVE A LOT OF BIG
DECISIONS.
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT THE DOLLARS
ARE REALLY TREMENDOUS.
I'M BE TALKING WITH THE
DEMOCRATS AND WE'LL BE TALKING
TO CONGRESS ABOUT WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO DO A LITTLE BIT LONGER
TERM.
MEANTIME, WE'VE SAVED A LOT OF
LIVES.
WE'VE DONE A REALLY GOOD JOB.
NOW WE'RE BRINGING THE PEOPLE
FOR DISTRIBUTION.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> IN CUBA?
YOU KNOW, THE PROBLEM WE'VE HAD
IN CUBA.
WE'LL BE COMING OUT WITHING?
.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> WE'RE LOOKING AT PUERTO RICO.
THAT'S A VERY, VERY BIG THING
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
YOU KNOW, WE'RE SPENDING
HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS RIGHT NOW.
IT'S A TERRITORY.
THESE ARE GREAT PEOPLE.
I KNOW THE PEOPLE VERY WELL.
THEY'RE GREAT PEOPLE.
THERE'S A MASSIVE INVESTMENT.
YOU'RE REBUILDING ALL OF IT.
AT SOME POINT, AS YOU KNOW,
THERE'S HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS --
A TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF MONEY
ALREADY INVESTED IN PUERTO RICO
BY OTHERS BEFORE THE STORMS.
THAT MONEY HAS BEEN IN SERIOUS
TROUBLE.
SO NOW ON TOP OF IT, A LOT OF
OTHER MONEY.
SO A LOT OF -- LOOK, A DECISION
HAS TO BE MADE.
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO?
PUERTO RICO WAS FLATTENED.
A BIG DECISION COMES AS TO WHAT
WE'RE GOING TO DO.
I'M THERE TO HELP.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> WE HAVE GREAT SECRETARIES AND
WE HAVE SOME THAT OWN THEIR OWN
PLANES, AS YOU KNOW.
THAT SOLVES THAT.
BUT WE PUT IT AN ORDER NO MORE
PLANES.
LOOK AT PAST ADMINISTRATIONS.
LOOK AT THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
AND TAKE A LOOK AT THE AMOUNT OF
TIME THAT THEY SPENT IN THE AIR,
THEY SPENT A LOT OF TIME IN THE
AIR.
BUT I FELT VERY BADLY BECAUSE
SECRETARY PRICE IS A GOOD MAN.
BUT WE'RE LOOKING INTO IT AND
WE'RE LOOKING TO IT STRONGLY.
>> DO YOU CONSIDER IT A FIREABLE
OFFENSE?
>> WE'LL TAKE A LOOK.
I'LL ANNOUNCE SOMETHING IN THE
NEAR FUTURE.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> I HAVE A GREAT CABINET.
WE SAVE HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF
DOLLARS THROUGH NEGOTIATIONS.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN EXAMPLE.
WITH THE F-35 FIGHTER PLANE, ME,
MYSELF, I'VE SAID HUNDREDS OF
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN
NEGOTIATING.
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS I
DON'T LIKE SEEING ANYBODY EVEN
HAVE A QUESTION ABOUT FLYING.
I JUST DON'T WANT TO DO THAT.
WE'RE SAVING TREMENDOUS AMOUNTS
OF MONEY NO MATTER WHERE WE GO.
LOOK AT WHAT WE'VE DONE IN
FLORIDA OR TEXAS.
WE'VE DONE THAT FOR RELATIVELY
LITTLE COMPARED TO WHAT OTHER
PEOPLE DO.
SO I DON'T LIKE TO SEE THAT
HAPPEN.
I THINK IT'S A SHAME.
AS A HUMAN BEING, TOM PRICE IS A
VERY GOOD MAN.
I CAN TELL YOU THAT.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> THAT'S UNACCEPTABLE.
>> I'VE HAD FOUR MEETINGS FROM
THE FED CHAIRMAN AND I'LL BE
MAKING A DECISION OVER THE NEXT
TWO OR THREE WEEKS.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> WE ARE -- FIRST OF ALL, BROCK
HAS DONE A FANTASTIC JOB AT
FEMA.
ELAINE DUKE IS ACTING AND SHE'S
WORKING VERY HARD.
YOU KNOW, I THINK WHAT FEMA HAS
DONE HAS BEEN INCREDIBLE BETWEEN
ALL OF THESE HURRICANES AND
DOING SO WELL.
BUT WE'LL BE MAKING THAT
DECISION PROBABLY WITHIN A
MONTH.
HOMELAND SECURITY.
YES.
>> YOU SAID YOU SPOKE TO JERRY
JONES AND OTHER OWNERS.
>> I'VE SPOKEN TO OTHER OWNERS.
I REALLY THINK IT'S COMING
TOGETHER.
I NOTICED LAST NIGHT OR I WAS
TOLD -- I DIDN'T SEE IT, BUT I
HEARD EVERYBODY STOOD FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
THAT SHOWS RESPECT FOR OUR
COUNTRY, OUR FLAG AND FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
SO YOU KNOW, I'M VERY HAPPY.
I HEARD THAT.
AND THEY SHOULD STAND.
YOU HAVE TO STAND.
IT'S OUR NATIONAL ANTHEM.
I SPOKE TO NUMEROUS TEAM OWNERS.
I DID SPEAK TO JERRY.
YES.
THANK YOU.
>> Trace: YOU CAN SEE THE
PRESIDENT --
>> I WAS DISAPPOINTING.
I DIDN'T LIKE IT COSMETICALLY OR
OTHERWISE.
I WAS DISAPPOINTED.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS AN
ADMINISTRATION THAT SAVES
HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS
ON RENEGOTIATING THINGS, ON NEW
TRADE DEALS.
YOU'LL SEE THE RESULTS SOON.
WE'RE RENEGOTIATING NAFTA,
RENEGOTIATING SO MANY DIFFERENT
THINGS AND MAKING BETTER DEALS.
YOU'LL BE SEEING OTHER THINGS
COME UP.
I DON'T LIKE TO SEE SOMEBODY
THAT PERHAPS SAYS THE PERCEPTION
THAT IT WASN'T RIGHT.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> I DON'T WANT TO SAY BUT WE'LL
BE ANNOUNCING SOMETHING TODAY.
>> DO YOU EXPECT HIS
RESIGNATION?
>> WE'LL BE
TODAY.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> I'M NOT AWARE OF THAT.
I MEAN, I HEARD IT WAS VERY
MINISTERIAL.
I'M NOT AWARE OF IT.
ANYTHING ELSE, JOHN?
GO AHEAD.
HE ALWAYS TREATS ME SO NICELY.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO ANNOUNCE
SOMETHING WITH TOM PRICE TODAY?
>> PROBABLY TODAY SOMEBODY WILL
BE ANNOUNCED.
I THINK HE'S A VERY FINE PERSON.
I CERTAINLY DON'T LIKE THE
OPTICS.
WE RENEGOTIATE DEALS.
AS AN EXAMPLE, THE F-35 FIGHTER
PLANES.
I'VE SAVED HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS.
I DON'T LIKE THE OPTICS OF WHAT
YOU JUST SAW.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> BAD THINGS HAPPENED IN CUBA.
VERY BAD THINGS.
YOU'LL SEE WHAT IS HAPPENING IN
CUBA.
THEY DID SOME BAD THINGS IN
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> PROBABLY SOMETIME TODAY.
>> DO YOU FEEL PRESSURE --
>> I'M NOT HAPPY.
I CAN TELL YOU.
I'M NOT HAPPY.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE REST OF YOUR
CABINET?
>> Trace: WE WERE TOLD THE
PRESIDENT WOULD SPEAK BETWEEN 5
AND 7 MINUTES AND HE SPOKE ABOUT
TEN MINUTES AS HE GOT OFF MARINE
ONE.
YOU HEARD THE HEADLINES THERE.
HE SAID AS FAR AS TOM PRICE IS
CONCERNED, HE WOULD DECIDE
PRICE'S FATE SOMETIME TONIGHT.
PRICE FLEW ON GOVERNMENT PLANES
TO THE TUNE OF $500,000.
HE SAID HE WOULD PAY $51,000 OR
A LITTLE OVER THAT TO PAY FOR
HIS SEAT.
NOW THE PRESIDENT DECIDES WHAT
HE PLANS TO DO ABOUT SECRETARY
PRICE.
THE LION'S SHARE OF THE NEWS
CONFERENCE WAS ABOUT PUERTO RICO
AND THE DEVASTATION DOWN THERE
AND THE GOVERNMENT'S RESPONSE TO
THAT.
LET'S GET TO GERALDO RIVERA WHO
IS IN SAN JUAN, PUERTO RICO.
WE SPOKE 24 HOURS AGO.
IN THAT TIME, HAS THERE BEEN
IMPROVEMENT IN GETTING THE GOODS
AND SUPPLIES TO THE INLAND
AREAS?
>> THERE HAS BEEN SOME
IMPROVEMENT, TRACE.
IF I CAN JUST REFERENCE THE
PRESIDENT'S REMARKS.
I THINK THAT PEOPLE ARE LOOKING
FOR GOOD GUYS OR BAD
GUYS.
THEY'RE LOOKING TO PLACE BLAME.
THE PARTISANS TO THE LEFT ARE
BLAMING TRUMP.
THE PARTISANS TO THE RIGHT ARE
BLAMING THE INCOMPETENT PUERTO
RICAN GOVERNMENT.
I THINK THE REALITY -- THE
PRESIDENT -- I DON'T DISAGREE
WITH ANYTHING HE SAID REPORTING
PUERTO RICO.
THE PERSONS OR THE TWO PEOPLE
MOST TO BLAME ARE IRMA AND
MARIA.
THE TWO HISTORIC DEVASTATING
HURRICANES THAT HIT THIS ISLAND
WITHIN A PERIOD OF TWO WEEKS AND
KNOCKED IT TO ITS KNEES.
THE DEVASTATION ACCURATELY
PORTRAYED IS STEM TO STERN, EAST
TO WEST, NORTH TO SOUTH.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S A PERSON
IN THIS 3.4 MILLION RESIDENTS OF
THIS ISLAND WHO HAS BEEN LEFT
UNAFFECTED.
THE SOUTH SIDE WHERE THE
GOVERNMENT HAS NOT YET MADE
THEIR SURVEYS, WHO HAVE BROUGHT
DIRECT ASSISTANCE, IS STILL
DEVASTATED.
ROADS BLOCKED EVERYWHERE.
IF YOU NEED TO PLACE BLAME AT
ALL, I THINK IT'S ON THE FAILURE
OF THE ELECTRICAL POWER SYSTEM.
THE ELECTRICAL GRID.
YOU KNOW, I WAS HERE SEPTEMBER A
YEAR AGO WHERE THE ELECTRIC
POWER GRID WENT OUT FOR THREE
DAYS BECAUSE OF A FIRE IN A
SINGLE POWER PLANT.
IRMA KNOCKED OUT 70% OF THE
POWER GRID THAT WAS NOT YET
RESTORED WHEN MARIA CAME AND
KNOCKED OUT THE REST OF IT.
THAT'S WHY THEY CAN'T PUMP THE
GAS OUT OF GROUND OR THE WATER
OUT OF THE GROUND OR CAN'T RUN
ELEVATORS OR AIR CONDITIONING.
THAT'S WHY HOSPITALS ARE RELYING
ON EMERGENCY GENERATORS.
THERE IS NO POWER.
THE BANKRUPT AND THE PRESIDENT
REFERRED TO THIS, TRACE,
DIRECTLY, THE BANKRUPT PUERTO
RICO ELECTRIC POWER AUTHORITY,
PREPA, THEY'RE $36 BILLION IN
DEBT.
THEY'RE RESPONSIBLE FOR POOR
MAINTENANCE AND AN OLD SYSTEM.
WHERE THE CABLES AND POLES ON
THIS ISLAND, THERE ARE OUTAGES
ON EVERY SINGLE BLOCK.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE HUNDREDS AND
HUNDREDS OF POLE MEN, LINEMEN TO
PUT TELEPHONE POLES IN TO STRING
IT UP.
THAT'S WHY THERE'S NO CELL PHONE
SERVICE.
THERE'S NO INTERNET.
THAT'S WHY THE PANIC HAS BEEN
GRIPPING THE PUERTO RICAN
PEOPLE.
THE PRESIDENT IS DOING THE RIGHT
THING.
HE'S RIGHT, THIS IS WHERE THE
RUBBER MEETS THE ROAD, TRACE.
REMEMBER, THE POWER AUTHORITY,
$6 BILLION IN DEBT AND BANKRUPT.
HOW MUCH IS THE UNITED STATES
WILLING TO PAY TO HELP THE
PUERTO RICAN PEOPLE STAY AWAY
FROM SLIDING INTO THE THIRD
WORLD?
RIGHT NOW PUERTO RICO IS IN THE
DARK AGES.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE SOMETHING OF
THE SCALE OF THE MARTIAL PLAN
THAT REBUILT EUROPE AFTER THE
CHAOS AND THE ASHES AND THE
DESTRUCTION OF WORLD WAR II.
I SAY CALL IT THE TRUMP PLAN IF
THAT'S WHAT IT TAKES.
HE BUILT THESE IMPRESSIVE
BUILDINGS AND THE HOTELS AND SO
FORTH.
IF THE PRESIDENT IS COMMITTED TO
RAISING MULTIBILLIONS OF DOLLARS
TO REBUILD THIS JUNK, TO STRING
ELECTRIC POWER FROM TOWN TO
TOWN.
THERE'S NOTICE WRONG WITH THE
POWER PLANTS.
THAT'S THE IRONY.
THE POWER PLANTS ARE FINE.
IT'S THE GRID.
IT'S THE POWER CABLES
THEMSELVES.
THE LINES THEMSELVES THAT HAVE
NOT AND COULD NOT AND NEVER
COULD WITHSTAND 150, 160, 170
MILES AN HOUR WINDS, TRACE.
>> Trace: AND A KEY TO THIS
WHOLE THING, GERALDO, WHO WILL
PAY FOR WHAT DOWN THERE.
GREAT WORK IN SAN JUAN, PUERTO
RICO.
THANKS, GERALDO.
WE JUST HEARD PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAID HE WILL DECIDE TONIGHT IF
HIS HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES
SECRETARY TOM PRICE IS IN OR OUT
AFTER HE USED TAXPAYER MONEY FOR
EXPENSIVE CHARTER FLIGHTS.
OUR POLITICAL PANEL WEIGHS IN
NEXT.
If you're approaching 65,
now's the time to get
your ducks in a row.
To learn about Medicare,
and the options you have.
You see, Medicare doesn't
cover everything -
only about 80% of your
Part B medical expenses.
The rest is up to you.
So if 65 is around the corner,
think about an
AARP Medicare Supplement
Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like all standardized Medicare
supplement insurance plans,
they help cover some of
what Medicare doesn't pay.
And could save you in
out-of-pocket medical costs.
So don't wait.
Call to request your free
Decision Guide.
And gather the information now
to help you choose a plan later.
These types of plans let
you pick any doctor
or hospital that takes
Medicare patients.
And there's a range of
plans to choose from,
depending on you needs
and your budget.
So if you're turning 65 soon,
call now and get started.
Because the time to think
about tomorrow...is today.
Go long.
WHERE YOU LIVE. IN THE PLACE YOU
CALL HOME. LIFE IS GOOD. BUT FOR
SOME OF US... THERE WAS JUST ONE
THING MISSING. FAST INTERNET.
REALLY FAST INTERNET. IT'S HERE.
INTRODUCING HUGHESNET GEN5, THE
NEXT GENERATION OF SATELLITE
INTERNET. WITH FASTER SPEEDS,
MORE DATA, AND BUILT IN WI-FI.
NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF WHAT YOU
LOVE ONLINE. STAY IN TOUCH,
LEARN, SHARE, WATCH VIDEOS, CHAT
WITH FRIENDS, AND GET THINGS
DONE. ENJOY HIGH SPEED INTERNET
AT HOME, WHEREVER YOU LIVE.
THERE HAS NEVER BEEN A BETTER
TIME TO GET AMERICA'S NUMBER ONE
CHOICE FOR SATELLITE INTERNET.
THE NEW HUGHESNET GEN 5 IS HERE,
AND IT'S FASTER THAN EVER.
STANDARD INSTALLATION IS FREE,
SO DON'T WAIT. CALL NOW. OR TEXT
THE PROMO CODE ON YOUR SCREEN TO
35000 TODAY.
>> WE'LL SEE.
WE HAVE -- HE'S A VERY FINE MAN.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A DECISION
SOMETIME TONIGHT.
HE'S A VERY FINE MAN.
>> Trace: THAT'S PRESIDENT TRUMP
TALKING ABOUT HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES SECRETARY TOM PRICE AND
THE DECISION IF TOM FIRED WILL
BE FIRED TONIGHT.
LET'S BRING IN OUR PANEL, CAPRI
IS HERE FROM THE AMERICAN
UNIVERSITY AND BRAD BLAKEMAN, A
FORMER ADVISER TO GEORGE W.
BUSH.
YESTERDAY IF YOU ASKED ME IF TOM
PRICE STAYS OR GOES, I WOULD SAY
HE GOES.
>> BUT STANDARD OPERATING
PROCEDURE ON FRIDAY, THE
PRESIDENT IS COMPLIMENTING HIM
ON HIS PAST SERVICE BUT I DON'T
THINK HE WILL BE STICKING
AROUND.
THAT CREATES ANOTHER CHALLENGE
FOR THE WHITE HOUSE, GETTING
ANOTHER SECRETARY IF PRICE WERE
TO GO CONFIRMED BY THE SENATE.
IN LIGHT OF HEALTHCARE BEING THE
NUMBER 1 ISSUE AFTER TAXES FOR
THE PRESIDENT TO BE TACKLING.
>> Trace: DO YOU AGREE, CAPRI,
THAT THE $51,000 PAY BACK IS NOT
GOING TO CUT IT?
>> I CERTAINLY THINK THERE'S ANY
TIME THERE'S AN EXORBITANT
AMOUNT OF TAX DOLLARS FOR AN
UNJUSTIFIABLE USE, $500,000,
$51,000, I'D SURMISE THAT
$51,000 IS USED TO PAY BACK THE
TRAVEL OF SECRETARY PRICE'S
WIFE.
THIS COMES ON THE HEELS OF
SECRETARY MNUCHIN UTILIZING A
GOVERNMENT PLANE TO GO TO
KENTUCKY AND HANG OUT AT FORT
NEXT AND MAYBE SEE THE ECLIPSE.
SO I THINK PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
TWO CHOICES AT THIS POINT.
ONE, EITHER ASK HIM, DEMAND HE
PAY BACK THE FULL AMOUNT OF
MONEY FOR THE TAX DOLLARS AND
CREATE A POLICY WHEREBY NO
MEMBER THAT DOESN'T HAVE ANY
JURISDICTION INTERNATIONALLY IS
UTILIZING THESE PLANES OR HE
LETS THEM GO.
THE OTHER THING THAT MAYBE HE'S
DOING IS UTILIZING PRESIDENT
TRUMP --
>> Trace: LET ME GET BRAD IN
HERE.
WE HAVE TO GO.
THIS WAS THE GUY HEAD OF THE
REPUBLICAN STUDY COMMITTEE.
THIS IS ABOUT GOVERNMENT
SPENDING.
SO I HAVE ONE SECONDS FOR YOU.
GO AHEAD.
>> AND IN WASHINGTON, YOU HAVE
TO DO AS I SAY.
AND NOT AS I DO.
YOU HAVE TO CHANGE.
YOU HAVE TO MEAN WHAT YOU SAY
AND DO WHAT YOU ASK OTHER PEOPLE
TO EXPECT FROM YOU.
THAT'S THE BOTTOM LINE.
>> Trace: RIGHT.
BRAD, CAPRI, THANKS BOTH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Trace: I'M TRACE GALLAGHER IN
FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
"YOUR WORLD" IS NEXT WITH NEIL.
NEIL WILL TELL YOU ABOUT THE DOW
IN THREE SECONDS.
d tonight...
Four weeks
without the car.
Okay, yep. Good night.
With Accident Forgiveness,
your rates won't go up
just because of an accident.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
Your brain is an amazing thing.
But as you get older,
it naturally begins to change,
causing a lack of sharpness,
or even trouble with recall.
Thankfully, the breakthrough in
Prevagen helps your brain
and actually improves memory.
The secret is an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
(AVO)
When you have type 2 diabetes,
you manage your A1C,
but you also have a higher risk
of heart attack or stroke.
Non-insulin Victoza®
lowers A1C,
and now reduces
cardiovascular risk.
Victoza® lowers my
A1C and blood sugar
better than
the leading
branded pill.
(AVO)
And for people with
type 2 diabetes
treating cardiovascular disease,
Victoza® is NOW approved
to lower the risk of major
cardiovascular events
such as heart attack,
stroke, or death.
And while it isn't
for weight loss,
Victoza® may
help you lose some weight.
(AVO)
Victoza® is not for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not take Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza® and get
medical help right away
if you get symptoms of a serious
allergic reaction such as rash,
swelling, difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Gallbladder problems have
happened in some people.
Tell your doctor right away
if you get symptoms.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting,
decreased appetite,
indigestion, and constipation.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,