TERMS OF SUPPORTING THE GOVERNOR
AND OUR RECOVERY.
LIKE I SAID EARLIER, WE'RE
ADDING ADDITIONAL CONVOYS TO DO
DISTRIBUTION INTO THE MORE
REMOTE AREAS OF THE ISLAND.
WE FEEL CONFIDENT THAT WILL
STAY.
>> IS THERE MARTIAL LAW IN
PUERTO RICO?
>> NOT TO MY KNOWLEDGE.
WE HAVE HEARD NOTHING FROM THE
GOVERNOR TO DECLARE MT'S ABOUT
ALLOCATING THE RESOURCES THAT
YOU HAVE CURRENTLY ON THE
ISLAND.
SO FOR SECURITY PURPOSES, THE
NATIONAL GUARD THAT HAS ALREADY
BEEN THERE FOR A VERY LONG TIME
AND ACTIVATED, PROVIDING
SECURITY FORCES WHAT WE'RE
BRINGING IN IS JUST GOING TO
BOLSTER EVERYTHING ON TOP OF
THAT.
>> IT'S BEING COMPARED TO
HURRICANE KATRINA-LIKE
DEVASTATION.
IS IT THAT BAD?
WHAT YOUR ASSESSMENT?
>> EVERY HURRICANE IS UNIQUE.
ONE OF THE DIFFICULTIES IN THE
VIRGIN ISLANDS AND IN PUERTO
RICO IS THE TOTAL -- BECAUSE
THEY'RE SMALLER ISLANDS, THE
TOTAL DEVASTATION.
IN THE VIRGIN ISLANDS AND IN
PUERTO RICO, WE HAD ZERO POWER.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A LONG TIME
TO RESTORE THE POWER GRID.
WE DON'T HAVE THE ADJACENT AREAS
FROM WHICH TO DEPLOY LIKE WE DID
IN KATRINA.
I'LL TELL YOU ONE THING THAT IS
WORKING, THE FORWARD-LEANING OF
THE PRESIDENT AND DECLARING A
DISASTER DECLARATION VERY EARLY
AND THE GOVERNOR AND ASKING FOR
HELP AND FEMA BEING ON THE
GROUND.
I THINK IT'S VERY DIFFERENT
RESPONSE.
>> DOES THE ADMINISTRATION PLAN
TO ASK CONGRESS FOR ANOTHER
SUPPLEMENTAL KICKING IN?
>> WE DON'T HAVE A DOLLAR
FIGURE.
WE'RE WORKING WITH THE NEEDS.
WE BELIEVE WE WILL NEED
ADDITIONAL BEYOND THE OCTOBER 1
INCREMENTS.
>> LET ME TELL YOU WHAT WE HAVE
TAKEN ACTION TO THIS POINT.
YOU KNOW, PUERTO RICO HAS POWER
ON THE ISLAND.
I SPOKE TO THE DIMINISHED
CAPACITY TO GET THAT BACK.
WHEN I SAY "DIMINISHED
CAPACITY", THE POWER WORKERS,
THE FIRST RESPONDERS ARE
DISASTER SURVIVORS.
THEY MAY HAVE LOST EVERYTHING.
WE RECOGNIZE THAT WE HAVE ASKED
THE ARMY CORPS OF ENGINEERS TO
BASICALLY TAKE OVERSIGHT AND
MANAGEMENT OF NOT ONLY THE
EMERGENCY POWER RESTORATION AND
THE INITIAL PART OF REBUILDING
THE ENTIRE GRID.
THE ENTIRE REBUILD OF THE GRID,
THAT'S A LONG PROCESS.
IF WE DO IT, WE GOT TO DO IT
RIGHT.
WE DON'T WANT TO WIND UP HAVING
THIS SAME DISCUSSION TEN, 20, 30
YEARS FROM NOW.
>> SO THE ARMY CORPS OF
ENGINEERS --
>> THEY'RE ON THE ISLAND, YES.
>> ARE THERE ANY LESSONS THAT
WE'VE LEARNED BY THESE BIG
STORMS THAT WE'RE GETTING BETTER
AT ADDRESSING?
SECOND QUESTION VERY QUICKLY IS
THERE ANY FEAR BESIDES CLIMATE
CHANGE --
>> WE'RE FOCUSED ON RESPONSE AND
COVERRY.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING AT DHS
AND FEMA.
WHAT WE HAVE LEARNED IS NOT
LOSING ANY TIME.
ON HARVEY AND THIS HURRICANE,
MARIA, THE PRESIDENT DECLARED
THE DISASTER BEFORE THE EYE HIT
LANDFALL THAT IS ABSOLUTELY
CRITICAL TO ALLOWING US TO COME
IN AND SUPPORT OF THE GOVERNOR
BEFORE THE DISASTER REALLY HITS.
TO ME THAT HAS BEEN A
GAME-CHANGER.
>> I THINK THE LAST 35 DAYS HAVE
BEEN A GUT CHECK FOR AMERICANS
THAT WE DON'T HAVE A TRUE
CULTURE OF PREPAREDNESS IN THIS
COUNTRY.
WE HAVE WORK TO DO.
WHETHER IT'S IN EDUCATION, BEING
READY.
IT'S NOT JUST SAYING, HEY, HAVE
THREE DAYS OF SUPPLIES READY TO
GO.
IT'S GREATER THAN THAT IT'S THE
FINANCES AND ABILITY TO OVERCOME
EMERGENCIES.
WE HAVE TO HIT THE RESET BUTTON
STARTING AT A YOUNG AGE AND
FILTERING UP.
>> ONE LAST QUESTION.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> PUERTO RICO WAS HURT BEFORE
THE DISASTER HIT.
THE PRESIDENT HAS PROVIDED FOR
100% REIMBURSEMENT OF ALL THE
MAJOR RESPONSE EFFORTS BY THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT FOR THE FIRST
180 DAYS THAT WILL GET US TO A
POINT THAT WE CAN REASSESS.
THANK YOU ALL.
>> THANK YOU, FOLKS.
>> Shepard: SO PUERTO RICO NEEDS
A LOT OF HELP AND A LOT OF TIME
AHEAD.
GERALDO IS LIVE AT THE AIRPORT.
I'VE BEEN READING ABOUT THIS.
I'M HEARING IT'S A MESS THERE.
>> IT IS A MESS.
JAMMED.
MAIN TERMINAL IS JAMMED, SHEP,
WITH PEOPLE DESPERATE TO GET OUT
OF PUERTO RICO.
AT THE URGING OF THE GOVERNOR,
HE SAYS ANYBODY THAT DOESN'T
HAVE TO BE HERE SHOULD LEAVE.
THE PROBLEM IS THERE'S BEEN SO
FEW FLIGHTS OUT.
UNITED AIRLINES STEPPED UP TO
THE PLATE AMID STORIES OF PRICE
GOUGING AND FLIGHTS CANCELLED
FOR A WEEK OR TWO EVEN, UNITED
HAS PUT ON A 777 FLIGHT THAT WAS
LEAVING FOR CHICAGO.
I'VE BEEN ON AN AIRCRAFT CARRIER
THE LAST COUPLE HOURS.
I DON'T KNOW IF THE 777 TOOK
OFF.
UNITED OFFERED FREE OF CHARGE TO
GET PEOPLE OUT OF HERE.
THE GOVERNOR WANTS PEOPLE
BRINGING SUPPLIES, DESPERATELY
NEEDED.
TO ME, IT'S ALMOST MIND BOGGLING
HOW SLOW THE RELIEF EFFORT HAS
BEEN.
THERE'S BEEN ONE RELIEF FLIGHT
ALL DAY YESTERDAY.
THEY WERE TRYING TO SWAP OUT THE
AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLERS HERE AT
THE SAN JUAN AIRPORT.
JUST DOESN'T SEEM THAT THE PEDAL
HAS BEEN PUT TO THE METAL IF YOU
GET MY MEANING.
THIS IS A CATASTROPHE WITH FOOD
SUPPLIES ARE SHORT, BUT WITH NO
WATER AND NO POWER, EVERYONE IS
USING GENERATORS.
THE GENERATORS NEED FUEL.
SO YOU HAVE THE SIX TO EIGHT
HOUR LINES AT THE AIRPORT, SHEP.
IT'S MELANCHOLY AND DEPRESSING.
YOU WANT THIS RELIEF MACHINE TO
GET UP AND GOING.
THE KIDS IN THE WHITE HERE ARE
FROM THE MORE MORMON CHURCH.
THESE ARE NEW YORK FIREFIGHTERS.
THEY JUST GOT HERE.
WHAT IS NEEDED, IT'S LIKE THE
OLD SONG, YOU NEED LINEMEN FROM
THE COUNTY.
GLEN CAMPBELL SONG.
YOU NEED TELEPHONE POLES, WE
NEED PEOPLE THAT KNOW HOW TO PUT
THE GRID BACK IN ACTION.
WE NEED PEOPLE THAT CAN --
IMAGINE IF YOU LEFT IN A
12-STORY CONDO AND YOU HAVE NO
WATER AND ELECTRICITY.
EVERY TIME YOU FLUSH THE TOILET,
YOU NEED A GALLON OF WATER.
WHERE THE HELL YOU GOING TO GET
IT?
THE SITUATION IS GETTING MORE
AND MORE DIRE.
I JUST APPRECIATE WHAT I HEARD
ABOUT THE COMMONWEALTH GETTING
TOGETHER TO MOUNT A REAL
EFFECTIVE RELIEF EFFORT.
BUT BECAUSE THIS DOESN'T HAVE
THE DRAMA OF THE WINDS BLOWING
AND THE FLOODS CREEPING UP, YOU
KNOW -- MY FEAR IS THE PEOPLE
DON'T RECOGNIZE THIS IS A SLOWLY
UNFOLDING HUMAN CATASTROPHE, A
DISASTER FROM ONE END TO THE
OTHER.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: A LOT OF CONCERNS
ABOUT THE VERY OLD AND THE VERY
YOUNG.
HOW THEY WILL REFRIGERATE FOOD
AND MEDICINE AND HOW THEY CAN
SURVIVE.
DO WE NEED TO BE THINKING OF A
BIGGER PLAN?
>> WHAT I WOULD DO, SHEP -- YOU
HURT ME WITH THAT QUESTION.
WHAT I WOULD DO, YOU NEED SHIPS
FULL OF GENERATORS.
YOU NEED -- PEOPLE WANT TO SEND
ICE.
THE ICE WILL MELT.
THE FOOD WILL SPOIL.
THE OLD-TIMERS WITH THEIR
MEDICINE, THEY NEED IT THREE
TIMES A DAY, NEED IT
REFRIGERATED.
WE JUST LEFT THE AIRCRAFT
CARRIER, THE HELICOPTER CARRIER
RUN BY THE NAVY.
MARINES ARE NOW ASHORE.
THEY'RE VISITING HOSPITALS AND
BRINGING GENERATORS TO THEM.
THAT'S THE KIND OF
PRACTICINGMATIC AID THAT THEY
NEED HERE.
THEY DON'T NEED GOOD WISHES.
EVEN MONEY DOESN'T IT.
WE NEED TO GET THE ISLAND BACK
ON THE GRID.
IT'S IN THE DARK AGES NOW, SHEP.
>> Shepard: FOR THE GENERATORS
YOU NEED FUEL IS.
THERE ENOUGH OF THAT?
IS THERE A POSSIBILITY OF
MOUNTING A HUGE GENERATOR RELIEF
SHIP AS YOU MENTIONED?
>> AS FAR AS I KNOW, BY THE WAY
THE
TIME I GOT ON THE AIRCRAFT
CARRIER BEFORE I LOST COMS WITH
THE MAIN AIRPORT, THE BIG HARBOR
HERE AT NIGHT IS NOT
OPERATIONAL.
YOU NEED BULK HERE.
THERE'S 3.4 MILLION PEOPLE.
IT'S ONE THING IF A DISASTER
STRIKES.
3.4 MILLION PEOPLE, MANY ELDERLY
BECAUSE OF THE FINANCIAL CRISIS
HERE.
MANY OF THE ABLE-BODIED, THE
STRONG MIDDLE CLASS HAVE GONE TO
FLORIDA ALREADY OR NEW YORK.
THEY SAW IRMA COMING.
THEY SAW JOSE AND NOW MARIA.
WHAT IS LEFT IS THE OLD FOLKS.
I'M GETTING ALL OF THESE TEXTS.
I CAN READ YOU TEXTS I'M GETTING
FROM FAMILY IN THE BRONX.
SOME OF MY RELATIVES, OTHERS IN
THE OTHER PARTS OF THE COMMUNITY
THEY HAVE NOT HEARD FROM YET.
I THINK THEY'RE OKAY.
BUT THEY ARE OUT OF TOUCH.
THE CELL SERVICE -- THERE'S NO
CELL SERVICE HERE.
IT'S VERY, VERY SPOTTY.
VERY FRUSTRATING.
THERE'S NO COORDINATION.
WHEN I GO ON THE ROADS THIS LONG
AFTER THE HURRICANES AND STILL
SEE TELEPHONE POLES SITTING
ACROSS THE HIGHWAY OR BIG ROAD
SIGNS CRUSHED INTO THE MIDDLE
LANE OF A THREE-LANE HIGHWAY, MY
POINT HERE, SHEP, IS THAT THIS
IS AN EXTREMELY DIRE SITUATION
THAT UNLESS IT'S GOING TO BECOME
THE KIND OF SCREWED UP RESPONSE
THAT KATRINA WAS, WE HAVE TO SEE
PRACTICAL RESULTS AND THE
PRACTICAL RESULTS ARE PUT SOME
PEOPLE BACK ONLINE.
GET SOME TEMPORARY CELL TOWERS
UP.
RATHER THAN THE BIG C-5s AND THE
C-130s AND THE C-17 SITTING ON
THE TARMAC, WHY AREN'T THE SKIES
FILLED WITH COMMERCIAL AIRLINERS
BRINGING STUFF, SUPPLIES IN?
THIS HAS BEEN -- I'M NOT
CRITICIZING ANYBODY.
DON'T GET ME WRONG HERE.
BUT THIS -- THAT'S WHY I WANT
USE THE TERM BUNGLED RESPONSE
BUT IT'S BEEN AN UNEVEN
RESPONSE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: GERALDO WITH THE
FACTS ON THE GROUND.
THEY NEED GENERATORS.
GET THEM GENERATORS.
THE DEATH OF AN AMERICAN STUDENT
IN NORTH KOREA IS MORE SERIOUS
THAN WE NEW.
THE PARENTS OF OTTO WARMBIER
TALK ABOUT THE FIRST TIME THEY
SAW THEIR SON AND THEIR
REALIZIZATION THAT HE WOULD
NEVER BE THE SAME.
(AVO)
When you have type 2 diabetes,
you manage your A1C,
but you also have a higher risk
of heart attack or stroke.
Non-insulin Victoza®
lowers A1C,
and now reduces
cardiovascular risk.
Victoza® lowers my
A1C and blood sugar
better than
the leading
branded pill.
(AVO)
And for people with
type 2 diabetes
treating cardiovascular disease,
Victoza® is NOW approved
to lower the risk of major
cardiovascular events
such as heart attack,
stroke, or death.
And while it isn't
for weight loss,
Victoza® may
help you lose some weight.
(AVO)
Victoza® is not for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not take Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza® and get
medical help right away
if you get symptoms of a serious
allergic reaction such as rash,
swelling, difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Gallbladder problems have
happened in some people.
Tell your doctor right away
if you get symptoms.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting,
decreased appetite,
indigestion, and constipation.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may cause kidney problems.
Ask your doctor
about Victoza®.
>> Shepard: THE PARENTS TELL US
HE WAS BLIND AND DEAF, HOWLING
AND JERKING VIOLENTLY.
THE FATHER OF OTTO WARMBIER SAID
THAT WAS THE CONDITION OF HIS
SON WHEN HE ARRIVED IN THE
UNITED STATES AFTER MORE THAN A
YEAR IN CAPTIVITY IN NORTH
KOREA.
OTTO WARMBIER WAS ARRESTED FOR
ALLEGEDLY STEALING A PROPAGANDA
POSTER FROM A HOTEL.
THEY LATER SENTENCED HIM TO 15
YEARS OF HARD LABOR FOR THAT.
NORTH KOREAN OFFICIAL SAYS HE
SLIPPED INTO A COMA AFTER TAKING
A SLIPPING PILL AND GOT
BOTULISM.
HIS PARENTS SAY THEY TORTURED
HIM.
>> SHEP, THE PARENTS ARE HEART
BROKEN.
THEY SAID THEY HAD THREE MONTHS
TO COME TOGETHER AND DO SOME
HEALING.
THEY ACKNOWLEDGED THEY WERE NOT
PREPARED TO SEE WHAT THEY SAW.
HERE'S FRED WARMBIER'S
HEART-RENDERING TAKE ON WHAT IT
WAS LIKE TO SEE HIS SON AT THE
AIRPORT.
YOU'LL HEAR HIM TALKING ABOUT
CINDY, GRETA AND AUSTIN.
>> WE WERE IN A WAITING ROOM
WITH THE MEDICAL TEAM AS THE
PLANE ARRIVED.
IT WAS DETERMINED THE MEDICAL
TEAM WOULD GO ON THE PLANE
BEFORE OUR FAMILY.
THEY WENT ON THE PLANE, FIVE
MINUTES OR SO LATER, THEY CAME
DOWN AND SAID IT WAS TIME FOR
OUR FAMILY TO GO TO THE PLANE.
IT WAS MYSELF, CINDY, AUSTIN AND
GRETA.
WE WALKED OVER TO THE PLANE.
THE ENGINES ARE STILL HUMMING.
THEY JUST LANDED.
WE WALKED UP THE STEPS.
WHEN WE GET HALFWAY UP THE
STEPS, WE HEARD THIS HOWLING
INVOLUNTARILY, UNHUMAN SOUND.
WE WEREN'T CERTAIN WHAT IT WAS.
WE CLIMBED TO THE TOP OF THE
STEPS AND WE LOOKED IN AND OTTO
WAS ON THE STRETCHER ACROSS IN
THE PLANE.
HE WAS JERKING VIOLENTLY MAKING
THESE INHUMAN SOUNDS.
CINDY AND GRETA RAN OFF THE
PLANE.
AUSTIN AND I WALKED OVER TO
OTTO.
OTTO HAD A SHAVED HEAD.
HE HAD A FEEDING TUBE COMING OUT
OF HIS NOSE.
HE WAS STARING BLANKLY INTO
SPACE JERKING VIOLENTLY.
HE WAS BLIND.
HE WAS DEAF.
WE LOOKED AT HIM AND TRIED TO
COMFORT HIM.
LOOKED LIKE SCENE HAD TAKEN A
PAIR OF PLIERS AND REARRANGED
HIS BOTTOM TEETH.
WITHIN TWO DAY OF BEING HOME,
HIS FEVER SPIKED TO 104 DEGREES.
HE HAD A LARGE SCAR ON HIS RIGHT
FOOT.
NORTH KOREA IS NOT A VICTIM.
THEY'RE TERRORISTS.
>> THEY DESTROYED HIM.
>> THEY PURPOSELY AND
INTENTIONALLY INJURED OTTO.
>> NORTH KOREA HAS DENIED CLAIMS
THAT OTTO WARMBIER WAS TORTURED
OR TREATED CRUELLY SAYING HE WAS
DEALT WITH ACCORDING TO DOMESTIC
LAWS AND INTERNATIONAL
STANDARDS.
U.S. INTELLIGENCE REPORTS SAY
WARMBIER WAS BADLY BEATEN IN
CUSTODY, SHEP.
>> Shepard: IT SEEMS LIKE IN THE
EARLY GOING, TRACE, HEAR IT FROM
THE FAMILY, THEY THOUGHT HE
WOULD FULLY RECOVER BEFORE
THEY -- REALITY SET IN.
>> THEY DID.
WHEN THE WARMBIERS WERE WAITING
ON THEIR SON'S PLANE TO ARRIVE
BACK IN THE UNITED STATES, THEY
THOUGHT HI WOULD BE IN A
MEDICALLY INDUCED COMA AND WITH
THE BEST DOCTORS AND A LOT OF
LOVE, THAT HE WOULD COME OUT OF
IT.
HERE'S CINDY WARMBIER TALKING
ABOUT HOW SHE AND HER DAUGHTER
REACTED TO THE FIRST SCENE OF
OTTO AND HIS CONDITION.
>> WHEN GRETA RAN OFF THE PLANE
AND I WAS SO WORRIED BECAUSE SHE
WAS SCREAMING.
OUR IMAGE OF OTTO AS YOU KNOW IS
OF SOMEONE JUST WONDERFUL.
BEAUTIFUL INSIDE AND OUT TO SEE
HOW HE CAME HOME WAS TOO MUCH
FOR US.
I ALMOST -- I GOT IT TOGETHER.
I RODE IN THE AMBULANCE WITH
HIM.
I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO BE ALONE
ANYMORE.
HE HAD BEEN ALONE FOR WAY TOO
LONG.
WE STAYED WITH HIM.
LOVED HIM AS BEST WE COULD.
NO PARENT SHOULD HAVE GONE
THROUGH WHAT WE WENT THROUGH.
THE FACT THAT OTTO WAS ALONE ALL
THAT TIME WITH NO ONE TO COMFORT
HIM IS UNEXCUSABLE.
WHATEVER HAPPENED, I MEAN, WHY
WOULD YOU DO THIS?
>> OTTO WARMBIER TIED LESS THAN
A WEEK AFTER RETURNING TO THE
UNITED STATES.
DOCTORS SAID HE WAS IN THE STATE
OF UNRESPONSIVE WAKEFULNESS AND
SUFFERED A NEUROLOGICAL INJURY
THAT LIKELY OCCURRED SHORTLY
AFTER HE WAS SENTENCED TO 15
MONTHS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER LIVE
FOR US.
THANK YOU, TRACE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FORMER ADVISER
ROGER STONE SPEAKING TO
REPORTERS AFTER HE TESTIFIED
ABOUT RUSSIAN MEDDLING IN THE
ELECTION.
HE SAID HE TOLD LAWMA
>> FORMER DONALD TRUMP CAMPAIGN
ADVISER ROGER STONE SAYS THERE'S
NOT ONE SHRED OF EVIDENCE.
AND THAT'S A QUOTE.
ROGER STONE APPEARED IN FRONT OF
MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE TODAY.
THE PANEL IS INVESTIGATING
MOSCOW'S MEDDLING IN THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL CAMPAIGN.
LET'S BRING IN JUDGE ANDREW
NAPOLITANO.
ROGER STONE.
>> ROGER STONE'S COMPLAINT IS
THAT THE ALLEGATIONS AGAINST HIM
WERE PUBLIC, BUT HIS ANSWERS ARE
NOT BECAUSE HE BEGGED THE
COMMITTEE TO INTERROGATE HIM IN
PUBLIC RATHER THAN BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS.
THE POLICY OF THE COMMITTEE IS
TO INTERROGATE BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS AND DECIDE IF THEY WANT TO
DO IT IN PUBLIC.
SO WE KNOW OF HIS CERTAIN AND
LOUD AND ARTICULATE AND FORCEFUL
DENIALS IN HIS OPENING STATEMENT
BECAUSE HE RELEASED THAT.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT QUESTIONS
THEY ASKED HIM.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
TENNESSEE, THIS IS FROM POLITCO.
THIS IS FROM NASHVILLE.
BOB CORKER WILL NOT RUN FOR
RE-ELECTION.
HE'S JUST MADE THE ANNOUNCEMENT
SAYING WHEN I RAN FOR THE SENATE
IN 2006, I COULDN'T IMAGINE TO
SERVE MORE THAN TWO TERMS.
HE'S NOT RUNNING AGAIN.
ONE OTHER MATTER IS THIS MATTER
OF E-MAILS.
THERE'S MEMBERS OF THE TRUMP
TRANSITION TEAM WHEN THEY GOT --
THE ELECTION HAPPENED AND THE
SWEARING IN HAPPENED AND THE
INAUGURATION HAPPENED, THEY
CONTINUED TO USE PRIVATE E-MAIL
FOR CORRESPONDENCE.
NO EVIDENCE THAT THERE'S
ANYTHING CLASSIFIED ON THAT BUT
BRINGS UP THE OLD HILLARY
CLINTON THINGS --
>> MAKES YOU WONDER WHY THE
WHITE HOUSE WASN'T CONCERNED
ABOUT THIS WITH ALL OF THE
PROBLEMS THIS PRODUCED DURING
THE CAMPAIGN.
SO IF THERE WAS CLASSIFIED
MATERIALS ON IT, IT'S A SERIOUS
ISSUE.
WE HAVE OF NONE.
>> Shepard: NONE AT ALL.
>> WHEN YOU WORK FOR THE
GOVERNMENT, THE GOVERNMENT OWNS
YOUR E-MAILS EVEN ON THOSE ON
YOUR PERSONAL ACCOUNT.
SO TECHNICALLY THAT'S KEEPING
GOVERNMENT PROPERTY.
IF YOU SURRENDER IT OVER, IT'S
OVER WITH.
IT'S A BIT OF A BLACK EYE FOR AN
ADMINISTRATION THAT MADE A BIG
DEAL ABOUT IT.
>> Shepard: LOCK HER UP.
>> YES.
>> Shepard: THAT'S DIFFERENT.
SHE HAD A PRIVATE E-MAIL SERVER.
THERE'S MORE TO IT FROM MY
UNDERSTANDING ABOUT IT, ONCE YOU
GET INTO OFFICE OR YOU SERVE IN
THE GIFT AND YOU GET SOMETHING
ON YOUR G MAIL, YOU TAKE THAT G
MAIL AND FORWARD IT TO YOUR
GOVERNMENT ACCOUNT.
COULD BE OVERSIGHT.
WHO KNOW WHAT IT IS BUT WORTH
BRINGING UP.
>> SEEMS TO BE CAUGHT BEFORE ANY
DAMAGE WAS DONE.
ONE CANNOT OVERLOOK THE IRONY.
>> FOR THIS BOB CORKER SEAT IN
TENNESSEE, AN IMPORTANT MEMBER
DOWN THERE, RAN AGAINST HAROLD
FORD JR. FROM 2006.
>> HE WAS THE HARSHEST
REPUBLICAN CRITIC OF THE
PRESIDENT WHEN HE CALLED HIM UP
STABLE.
>> HE'S NOT RUNNING AGAIN.
THAT WILL LEAVE AN OPENING THERE
IN THE STATE OF TENNESSEE FOR
MANY MILLIONS BATTLE.
>> I THINK HAROLD FORD WILL BE
MOVING BACK TO TENNESSEE
QUICKLY.
>> YOU THINK SO?
>> YES.
>> Shepard: HAROLD FORD.
MIGHT GIVE HIM A CALL AND SEE
WHAT HE'S DOING.
POLITICS INTERESTING.
THANKS, JUDGE.
>> ALWAYS A PLEASURE.
>> Shepard: THEY'LL SHUT THINGS
DOWN ON WALL STREET.
WE'RE A LITTLE DOWN NOW.
JUST OFF A FEW POINTS.
NEIL CAVUTO WITH THE BEST IN
BUSINESS AS THE FOX NEWS CHANNEL
DAYTIME ROLLS ON IN JUST THREE
MINUTES.
Hi. So I just got off the phone
with our Allstate agent,
and I know that we have
Accident Forgiveness.
So the incredibly minor
accident that I had tonight...
Four weeks
without the car.
Okay, yep. Good night.
With Accident Forgiveness,
your rates won't go up
just because of an accident.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
your rates won't go up
just because of an accident.
♪♪
When food is good
and clean and real,
it's ok to crave.
And with Panera catering,
there's more to go around.
Panera.
Food as it should be.