AS CANDIDATE COULD TAKE THAT IF
HE WAS STILL A REPUBLICAN THE
PRESIDENT WOULDN'T ENDORSE HIM?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO GET INTO THE
HYPOTHETICALS THAT A CANDIDATE
MAY OR MAY NOT HAVE OVER THE
TIME THAT THE PRESIDENT IS THE
PRESIDENT.
I KNOW WHERE THE PRESIDENT
STANDS ON CERTAIN ISSUES.
THAT'S WHAT I CAN SPEAK ABOUT,
NOT SOMEBODY THAT IS A CANDIDATE
FOR ANOTHER OFFICE THAT IS NOT
HERE.
>> I DIDN'T GET -- TOM DID NOT
CALL ON ME.
I'M GOING TO ASK A QUESTION I
WANT TO UNDERSTAND.
HE MENTIONED IN RESPONSE TO WHAT
SENATOR RUBIO WAS SAYING ASKING
THE PENTAGON TO BE IN CHARGE,
THAT THE PENTAGON IS IN CHARGE
OF A LOT BUT NOT
IN CHARGE AND WHAT THE RESPONSE
IS.
>> WE'RE CONTINUING TO WORK WITH
STATE OFFICIALS INCLUDING
GOVERNOR WHO AS TOM SAID WE HAVE
CONFIDENCE IN, BUT WE'RE
SUPPLEMENTING AND AUGMENTING
THAT WITH FEDERAL RESOURCES
INCLUDING OVER 10,000 FEDERAL
EMPLOYEES AND ONE STAR GENERAL
THERE ON THE GROUND.
>> WHY IS NOT ONE ENTITY IN
CHARGE?
HE SAID MANY PEOPLE WERE IN
CHARGE OF DIFFERENT THINGS.
WHY IS ONE PERSON NOT IN CHARGE?
>> I BELIEVE ONE PERSON IS IN
CHARGE OF DIFFERENT PARTS OF
THIS PROCESS.
THE GOVERNOR IS STILL THE
GOVERNOR OF PUERTO RICO.
WE'RE CONTINUING TO WORK WITH
THEM, BEING IN CONSTANT CONTACT
AND WE HAVE ONE PERSON IN CHARGE
OF THE FEDERAL COMPONENT OF
THAT.
THAT WOULD BE THE ONE-STAR
GENERAL ON THE GROUNDWORKING
WITH STATE OFFICIALS.
>> I KNOW YOU SAID THE WHITE
HOUSE DOESN'T APPROVE CHARTER
FLIGHTS AHEAD OF TIME.
GENERALLY SPEAKING, GIVEN THE
FOCUS OF THE PRESIDENT ON COST
SAVINGS, LIKE YOU SAID, NOT JUST
DRAINING THE SWAMP AND WANT
PEOPLE TO SPEND MONEY IN BETTER
WAYS, IS A GUIDANCE ABOUT FLYING
COMMERCIAL AND HOW THEY SHOULD
BE TRAVEL SOMETHING.
>> WE'RE LOOKING INTO THAT WHEN
IT COMES TO MILITARY AIRCRAFT.
THAT'S A PART WHERE THE WHITE
HOUSE DOES PLAY A ROLE.
ON THAT FRONT, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION HAS ACTUALLY
AUTHORIZED FAR FEWER FLIGHTS FOR
SENIOR GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS THAN
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION DID
DURING THE SAME TIME PERIOD DID.
SO WE'RE LOOKING AT WAYS TO
BRING THAT BACK UNDER THE PLACES
WHERE THE WHITE HOUSES THAT THAT
DIRECT CONTROL AND AUTHORITY,
WHICH IS UNDER MILITARY AIRCRAFT
WHICH WE CUT BACK SIGNIFICANTLY.
>> ON THE GROWING WAR OF
COMMENTS, I KNOW YOU DON'T WANT
TO TALK ABOUT FROM THE RACE.
BUT FROM THE PODIUM DO YOU WANT
TO CONDEMN THE SENTIMENTS THAT
THE PRESIDENT DOES NOT SHARE?
>> I WOULD CERTAINLY SAY WE
DON'T AGREE WITH THOSE COMMENTS
IN TERMS OF WHETHER OR NOT I'M
GOING TO GET IN THE BACK AND
FORTH OVER ANOTHER CANDIDATE,
WE'RE HERE TO FOCUS ON THE
PRESIDENT.
>> ONE MORE QUESTION ON
SECRETARY PRICE'S FLIGHT.
ON ONE OF THOSE FLIGHTS,
KELLYANNE CONWAY WAS FLYING WITH
HIM ON THE PRIVATE FLIGHT.
ARE YOU LOOKING AT THAT
SPECIFICALLY TO SEE --
>> I DIDN'T SAY WE WERE NOT
AWARE.
I SAID WE DON'T AUTHORIZE THOSE
PRIVATE CHARTER FLIGHTS.
WE'RE DOING AN INTERNAL REVIEW
AT HHS OF ALL PRIVATE CHARTER
FLIGHTS AS WELL AS AN I.G.
REVIEW THAT WILL BE CONDUCTED OF
ALL OF THEM.
JULIE?
>> AS THE PRESIDENT IS WATCHING
THIS COVERAGE IN PUERTO RICO, IS
HE SATISFIED WITH WHAT HE SEES
AS A RESPONSE THERE?
IS HE SATISFIED IN WHAT HE'S
HEARING FROM HIS ADVISERS OR
WOULD HE LIKE TO SEE THINGS
MOVING ALONG FASTER AS PEOPLE ON
THE GROUND HAVE ASKED FOR?
>> THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO
CONTINUE TO DO EVERYTHING WE CAN
TO PROTECT THE SAFETY AND
SECURITY OF THE PEOPLE BOTH AT
THE U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS AND
PUERTO RICO.
TOM SPOKE IN DEPTH ABOUT THAT
PROCESS.
THAT'S OUR FOCUS AND THAT'S WHAT
WE'RE CONTINUING TO DO.
PEOPLE FIRST, PAPERWORK SECOND.
THE PRESIDENT HAS EMPOWERED ALL
OF HIS AGENCIES TO GO FORWARD
WITH THAT MINDSET.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO DO.
>> I SAW THAT THE PRESIDENT WAS
HERE WITH AN EVENT FOR THE FIRST
LADY.
DID HE HAVE A CHANCE TO TALK
ABOUT THE ISSUE OF HIS PRIVATE
JET OR HAS HE HAD A ONE-ON-ONE
CONVERSATION ABOUT THAT?
WHEN YOU SAID THE WHITE HOUSE
ORDERED A HALT ON THAT, IS THAT
ADMINISTRATIONWIDE, EVERY AGENCY
OR --
>> SPECIFIC TO HHS.
I DON'T KNOW THAT THEY SPOKE
TODAY.
I KNOW THAT THEY HAVE SPOKEN
ABOUT THIS ISSUE PREVIOUSLY.
I DON'T BELIEVE THE PRESIDENT
SAW THE SECRETARY AT ANY POINT
TODAY THOUGH.
>> FOLLOWING UP ON THAT.
DOES ANYONE BELIEVE THAT THEY
WERE EMPOWERED TO GO ON PRIVATE
JETS?
WE HAVE THE HHS SECRETARY, THE
EPA ADMINISTRATOR, THE TREASURY
SECRETARY TOOK A FLIGHT ON A
PRIVATE JET AND AN ITINERARY
AVAILABLE COMMERCIALLY?
IS THERE SOMETHING THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS SAID --
>> NOT AT ALL.
THE PRESIDENT IS CLEAR ABOUT HIS
POSITION BY STATING VERY CLEARLY
THAT HE IS NOT THRILLED WITH THE
AIRPLANE USE AT THIS POINT.
>> TWO THINGS.
I JUST WANT TO UNDERSTAND THE
REVIEW PROCESS HERE OF PRICE AND
OTHERS.
THERE'S AN I.T. REVIEW.
IS THERE A WHITE HOUSE
COMPONENT?
IS ANYONE --
>> FOR HHS SPECIFICALLY, THEY'RE
CONDUCTING AN INTERNAL REVIEW AS
WELL AS AN I.G. REVIEW.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS LOOKING AT
MORE OF AN OVERALL NOT SPECIFIC
TO THAT DEPARTMENT BECAUSE
THERE'S ALREADY TWO REVIEWS
TAKING PLACE THERE.
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID HE WOULD
DONATE PERSONAL FUNDS TO HARVEY
RELIEF.
DID HE MAKE ANY DONATION TO
PUERTO RICO?
>> I HAVEN'T TALKED TO HIM
SPECIFICALLY ABOUT THAT.
HE DIDN'T MAKE A DONATION TO
HARVEY RELIEF.
HE MADE A DONATION TO RELIEF
ORGANIZATIONS.
THE RED CROSS AND MANY OTHERS
THAT ARE A PART OF ALL OF THE
HURRICANES THAT WE'VE
EXPERIENCED THE LAST SEVERAL
WEEKS.
SO THOSE ORGANIZATIONS ARE NOT
LIMITED TO A SPECIFIC, NOR ARE
THE DONATION AS SPECIFIC STORM.
THEY GO TO THOSE ORGANIZATIONS
THAT ARE HELPING AGGRESSIVELY
AND INTENSELY IN THE RECOVERY
EFFORTS IN THE U.S. VIRGIN
ISLANDS AND PUERTO RICO AS WELL.
>> WE SAW STEVE SCALISE WITH
THAT EMOTIONAL REMARKS IN THE
HOUSE CHAMBER TODAY.
DID THE PRESIDENT SPEAK TO HIM
TO WELCOME HIM BACK?
>> I KNOW THEY DID SPEAK TODAY.
I DON'T HAVE MANY DETAILS.
I KNOW HE CERTAINLY WELCOMED HIM
BACK AND REMINDED HIM THAT WE
WILL CONTINUE TO KEEP HE AND HIS
FAMILY IN OUR PRAYERS.
>> AND GIVEN THE DISASTER IN
PUERTO RICO, IS THE PRESIDENT
DELAYING HIS TRIP?
>> AS OF RIGHT NOW, WE FEEL
COMFORTABLE WITH THE PRESIDENT
TAKING A TRIP.
IF THERE WAS ANY INDICATION THAT
IT WOULD HALT RELIEF EFFORTS, WE
WOULD RECONSIDER AND PULL THAT
TRIP BACK.
BUT RIGHT NOW IT WOULD BE
HELPFUL FOR HIM TO BE THERE.
>> HAS JARED KUSHNER OR ANY
OTHER STAFF MEMBER TAKEN A
PRIVATE PLANE RIDE SINCE THEIR
JOINING THIS ADMINISTRATION OR
BE GIVEN ACCESS IN SOME FORT TO
RIDE ALONG WITH SOMEBODY ELSE?
>> I'M NOT SURE ABOUT THOSE TWO
SPECIFIC INDIVIDUALS.
I HAVE TO LOOK.
>> I'D LIKE TO ASK ABOUT CUBA.
THERE'S RECORDEDLY WITHDRAW OF
FAMILY AND STAFF THERE.
>> AT THIS POINT, I'M NOT GOING
TO GET AHEAD OF ANY POTENTIAL
ACTION THAT MAY TAKE PLACE
THERE.
I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING NEW TO
ADD.
>> CUBA SAYS IT WARNED THE U.S.
AGAINST TAKING ANY HASTY ACTIONS
IN RESPONSE TO THESE INCIDENTS
TARGETING DIPLOMATS.
HOW DOES THE U.S. RESPOND TO
THAT?
>> WE HAVEN'T TAKEN ANY ACTION
RIGHT NOW.
WHEN WE DO THAT WE'LL LET YOU
KNOW.
I CAN ASSURE YOU OUR GOAL IS ON
THE FOCUS OF WHAT IS BEST FOR
THIS COUNTRY, NOT WHAT IS BEST
FOR CUBA.
JOHN.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID THAT
PLAYERS THAT KNEEL DURING A
NATIONAL ANTHEM OUGHT TO BE
FIRED.
YOU YOURSELF HAVE SAID FROM THE
PODIUM IN RESPONSE TO A VERY
CRITICAL TWEET BY AN ESPN ANCHOR
THAT THAT INDIVIDUAL OUGHT TO BE
FIRED.
YOU SAID IT WAS A FIREABLE
OFFENSE, WHICH BRINGS ME TO
SECRETARY PRICE.
HIS EXTENSIVE USE BY THESE
PRIVATE JETS, WHY IS THAT NOT A
FIREABLE OFFENSE IS MY FIRST
QUESTION AND HAS HE OFFERED TO
REIMBURSE THE GOVERNMENT IN ANY
WAY FOR HIS USE OF THOSE PRIVATE
JETS?
>> I THINK THAT'S SOMETHING THAT
WE WOULD DETERMINED ONCE THE
REVIEWS ARE COMPLETE.
IN TERMS OF REIMBURSEMENT, I'M
NOT SURE.
I'LL GET BACK TO YOU.
>> ON THE ISSUE -- WE'RE
UNDERSTANDING THAT MANY OF THE
NFL PLAYERS ARE STILL VERY UPSET
WITH THIS BACK AND FORTH --
>> I THINK SO ARE MANY
AMERICANS.
MORE AMERICANS THAN NFL PLAYERS.
>> CAN I FINISH MY QUESTION?
>> SURE.
>> MANY NFL PLAYERS ARE VERY
UPSET.
MANY PEOPLE HAD DIFFERENT IDEAS
AND OPINIONS ON THIS.
WHEN THE PRESIDENT WEIGHED IN,
THE NFL SAID WE'RE GOING TO BE
UNITED.
THERE'S AN ANTICIPATION THAT IT
COULD GROW EVEN MORE SEE THIS
WEEKEND.
WHAT IS THE PRESIDENT
ANTICIPATING, WHAT SHOULD WE
EXPECT HIM TO SAY ABOUT THIS?
IT'S NOW THE NFL AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT.
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT HAS
MADE VERY CLEAR.
THIS SHOULDN'T BE ABOUT THE NFL
BEING AGAINST THE PRESIDENT.
THIS SHOULD BE ABOUT OUR COUNTRY
COMING TOGETHER TO SUPPORT THE
FLAG, THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
THERE'S NOTHING WRONG WITH
HAVING PRIDE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THIS PRESIDENT HAS BEEN VERY
CLEAR ON THAT AND HE'S NOT GOING
TO BACK AWAY FROM THAT.
>> IT'S NOT ABOUT HAVING PRIDE.
THEY SAID THEY'RE PATRIOTS, THEY
LOVE THIS COUNTRY BUT THEY'RE
CHALLENGING THE SYSTEM AND
THEY'RE LOOKING AT HISTORY LIKE
THE CHALLENGE OF THE SYSTEM WHEN
IT CAME TO WOMENS RIGHTS ISSUES
AS WELL AS CIVIL RIGHTS.
WHAT DOES THE PRESIDENT SAY WHEN
YOU LOOK AT HISTORY AND SEE HOW
PEOPLE LOVE THIS COUNTRY AND
WANTED TO CHALLENGE THE SYSTEM
TO MAKE IT BETTER?
>> IF WE'RE GOING TO LOOK AT
HISTORY, WE SHOULD LOOK AT THE
THOUSANDS OF AMERICANS THAT HAVE
GIVEN THEIR LIFE TO PROTECT THAT
FLAG, THAT ANTHEM.
WE SHOULD BE CELEBRATING THOSE
PEOPLE.
I GAVE YOU A CHANCE TO ANSWER.
WE SHOULD BE LOOKING AT EVERY
WAY WE CAN TO CELEBRATE OUR
COUNTRY, BRING IT TOGETHER, NOT
LOOKING AT WAYS TO DIVIDE IT.
THE PRESIDENT IS TALKING ABOUT
WHAT WE'RE FOR, NOT ABOUT WHAT
WE'RE AGAINST.
CERTAINLY THIS ADMINISTRATION
WILL ALWAYS BE FOR PROTECTION
AND CELEBRATION OF THE FLAG AND
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO CHANGE.
>> TO CLARIFY ON THAT.
>> I DON'T THINK THERE'S MUCH TO
CLARIFY.
I THINK IT WAS BLACK AND WHITE
THERE.
>> PEOPLE ARE VERY DIVIDED ON
THIS ISSUE.
IT'S A RACIAL ISSUE FOR SOME
PEOPLE.
THE QUESTION IS, WHEN THE
MILITARY ISSUE IS BROUGHT IN,
THE MILITARY GOES AND FIGHTS FOR
THE FREEDOMS OF THIS NATION.
THESE PLAYERS ARE SAYING THEY'RE
THANKFUL FOR THE MILITARY
SERVICE TO ALLOW --
>> WE ALL ARE.
>> IS THERE SOME TYPE OF
CONFUSION HERE OR IS THIS US
VERSUS THEM KIND OF SCENARIO?
>> THIS SHOULDN'T BE.
IT'S NOT AN US VERSUS THEM.
THIS SHOULD BRING OUR COUNTRY
TOGETHER.
THESE ARE SYMBOLS OF WHAT OUR
COUNTRY STAND FOR AND SHOULD BE
THE OPPOSITE OF WHAT THAT IS.
THIS SHOULD BE A UNIFYING MOMENT
WHEN THE NATIONAL ANTHEM PLAYS.
ALL AMERICANS SHOULD SALUTE THE
FLAG AND THE ANTHEM AND BE A
PART OF THE PROCESS.
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID HE
BELIEVED NFL TEAM OWNERS ARE
AFRAID OF THEIR PLAYERS.
WHAT DOES HE MEAN BY THAT?
>> PROBABLY THE BACKLASH OF THE
PLAYERS AND THE STANCE THEY'RE
MAKING.
NOT WANTING TO CREATE THAT
CONFLICT WITHIN THEIR TEAM.
THE PRESIDENT IS HERE TO LEAD
THE COUNTRY.
HE FEELS VERY STRONGLY ABOUT
THIS AS DO MOST AMERICANS
BECAUSE THEY CERTAINLY AGREE
WITH HIM AS WE'VE SEEN NOT JUST
IN THE PUBLIC SUPPORT BUT ALSO
IN PUBLIC POLLING ON THAT VERY
SPECIFIC ISSUE.
>> [QUESTION INAUDIBLE]
>> I BELIEVE THEY SPOKE
YESTERDAY MORNING ON THIS
MORNING.
WE'LL HAVE A READ OUT OR THAT.
>> FOLLOW UP JUST QUICKLY ON THE
NFL THING.
I MAY NOT BE THE BRIGHTEST GUY
IN THE ROOM.
>> YOU SAID IT.
>> MY QUESTION --
>> NOBODY ELSE ARGUED EITHER.
>> I REALLY DON'T UNDERSTAND.
I UNDERSTAND THAT HE'S SAYING
YOU SHOULDN'T STAND UP.
IF A GUY IS SITTING THERE GOING
I DON'T WANT TO STAND UP, HE
STILL RECOGNIZES HE HAS A FIRST
AMENDMENT RIGHT NOT TO, YES?
IT'S HIS OPINION.
OR IS HE ASKING TO US CARVE OUT
AN EXCEPTION TO THE FIRST
AMENDMENT FOR FREEDOM OF
EXPRESSION?
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN VERY
CLEAR AND HE FEELS STRONGLY WHEN
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM PLAYS,
PEOPLE SHOULD STAND UP.
>> I HAVE A SECOND QUESTION.
THE SECOND QUESTION WAS IN
REGARDS TO THE PRIVATE E-MAILS.
THAT HAVE GONE OUT.
HAS THE PRESIDENT AND HIS STAFF
ON THAT, IS HE CONCERNED ABOUT
THEM USING PRIVATE E-MAILS FOR
PUBLIC BUSINESS?
>> THE WHITE HOUSE HAS BEEN
CLEAR AND INSTRUCTION ALL STAFF
TO FULL PLY COMPLY WITH
PRESIDENTIAL RECORDS ACTS.
ALL STAFF HAS BEEN BRIEFED ON
THE NEED TO PRESERVE THOSE
RECORDS AND WE'LL CONTINUE TO DO
SO.
BRIAN?
LAST QUESTION.
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF TIME.
>> HE TALKED ABOUT SENATOR
COCHRAN AND THE HEALTHCARE VOTE.
HE SAID THAT SENATOR COCHRAN WAS
NOT ABLE TO BE HERE THIS WEEK.
SENATOR COCHRAN WAS GOING TO
COME IF THERE WAS A VOTE.
WAS THE WHITE HOUSE NOT AWARE?
>> THAT WAS OUR UNDERSTANDING,
AS I SAID.
THE SENATOR WAS PHYSICALLY
UNABLE TO BE HERE THIS WEEK.
WE'RE GLAD THAT WASN'T THE CASE.
THANKS SO MUCH.
WE'LL BE IN THE OFFICE THE REST
OF THE DAY AND HAPPY TO ANSWER
QUESTIONS.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE WRAPPING UP
THEIR DAILY BRIEFING.
ALMOST AN HOUR LONG.
I'M TRACE GALLAGHER IN FOR
SHEPARD SMITH.
WE HAD SARAH SANDERS AND WE ALSO
HAD THE WHITE HOUSE HOMELAND
SECURITY ADVISER AS WELL AS THE
CHIEF ECONOMIC ADVISER HANDLING
VARIOUS TOPICS.
A LOT OF QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
CRISIS GOING ON IN PUERTO RICO
AFTER HURRICANE MARIA.
THE WHITE HOUSE DEFENDED ITS
DECISION TO WAIT TO WAIVE THE
JONES ACT AND LET MORE SHIPS
DELIVER SUPPLIES.
THE ISLAND IS DEVASTATED.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT POWER BEING
OUT ALMOST EVERYWHERE.
PEOPLE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH FOOD,
WATER.
THEY DON'T HAVE ENOUGH CASH.
THE JONES ACT BANS FOREIGN SHIPS
FROM TRANSPORTING SUPPLIES
BETWEEN THE U.S. PORTS.
JUST YESTERDAY THE PRESIDENT
SAID THIS WERE ENOUGH AMERICAN
SHIPS TO DELIVER AID TO PUERTO
RICO BUT THE WHITE HOUSE SAID
THE PRESIDENT MADE THE DECISION
AFTER A REQUEST FROM THE
ISLAND'S GOVERNOR.
LET'S BRING IN JOHN ROBERTS LIVE
AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
JOHN, THE WHITE HOUSE IS TRYING
TO REALLY MAKE THE POINT HERE
THAT THEY HAVE ENOUGH SHIPS TO
BRING THE GOODS AND SUPPLIES TO
AND FROM PUERTO RICO.
WHAT THEY DON'T HAVE IS THE
ABILITY TO DISTRIBUTE THOSE
GOODS ACROSS THE ISLAND.
>> YEAH.
GOOD AFTERNOON TO YOU, TRACE.
I TALKED WITH PEOPLE FROM THE
NATIONAL SECURITY COUNCIL ABOUT
THIS IN DEPTH THIS MORNING.
THE BIG PROBLEM IS THAT SO MANY
OF THE ROADS IN PUERTO RICO ARE
IMPASSABLE.
THEY HAVE BULLDOZERS IN THE
STREETS NOW.
THEY HAVE BACKHOES TRYING TO
CLEAR THEM.
THAT'S WHY THEY HAVE HAD THAT
BACKLOG IN PORTS AND PLACES LIKE
SAN JUAN IN TERMS OF NOT GETTING
THE CONTAINERS FULL OF SUPPLIES
OUT.
THE NSC WAS FIRM ABOUT THIS IDEA
THAT THEY'VE HAD NO PROBLEM WITH
CAPACITY IN TERMS OF GETTING
THINGS TO THE ACTUAL ISLAND.
THE PRESIDENT HAD NOT DECLARED
ANY KIND OF WAIVER FOR THE JONES
ACT BECAUSE OF THE FACT THEY HAD
ENOUGH SHIPS TO GET SUPPLIES IN.
WHEN THE GOVERNOR CALLED THE
WHITE HOUSE YESTERDAY AFTERNOON
TO ASK FOR THE WAIVER, THE WHITE
HOUSE THOUGHT IT WAS PRUDENT TO
DO SO.
I ASKED TOM BOSSERT ABOUT THAT
AS TO WHETHER OR NOT IF THEY
DIDN'T HAVE THAT REQUEST FROM
THE GOVERNOR, WHETHER THEY WOULD
HAVE LOOKED FOR A WAIVENER THE
JONES ACT.
LET'S WATCH THAT EXCHANGE.
>> HAD THE GOVERNOR NOT
REQUESTED PROTECTIVELY A
WAIVENER THE JONES ACT, WOULD
YOU HAVE SEEN A COMPELLING
REASON TO INITIATE --
>> I WASN'T RECOMMENDING TO THE
PRESIDENT THAT HE WAIVE THE
JONES ACT UNTIL I GOT THE
GOVERNOR'S REQUEST.
WHEN THE GOVERNOR CALLS AND SAYS
I SEE ON THE HORIZON, I THINK WE
SHOULD LISTEN TO HIM.
>> SO THE NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL THOUGHT THERE WAS NO
PROBLEM IN TERMS OF CAPACITY.
THEY ACTED OUT OF CAUTION WHEN
THEY GOT THAT REQUEST FROM THE
GOVERNOR AS WELL AS TOM BOSSERT
SAYING THE PRESIDENT WILL SEEK
AN EMERGENCY SUPPLEMENTAL TO
PROVIDE MORE RELIEF FOR PUERTO
RICO.
>> STAND BY.
I WANT TO GET TO GERALDO.
I'M NOT SURE IF YOU HEARD JOHN
ROBERTS' CONVERSATION THERE.
IS THERE AN IMPROVING SYSTEM IN
PLACE NOW OF TRYING TO GET THE
SUPPLIES, THE WATER, THE FOOD
ACROSS THE ISLAND?
>> I DO NOT SEE IT, TRACE.
I HAVE TO BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I'D LOVE TO REPORT THAT
EVERYTHING WAS FLOWING FREELY,
THAT EVERYBODY WAS COORDINATED,
THAT EVERYBODY WAS GETTING
RELIEF WHERE THEY NEED TO.
THAT IS NOT THE CASE.
THE RELIEF EFFORT HAS BEEN
CHAOTIC, IT'S BEEN SPOTTY, IT'S
BEEN UNDERWHELMING TO SAY THE
LEAST.
THERE'S AD HOC ACTS WHERE THEY
APPEAR TO BE DOING THE RIGHT
THING.
BEHIND ME IS THE VESSEL
ADVENTURE OF THE SEAS, THE ROYAL
CARIBBEAN CRUISE SHIP THAT HAS
BEEN SENT TO EVACUATE EMPLOYEES
OF THE ROYAL CARIBBEAN COMPANY.
THERE'S EVACUEES, TOURISTS
IDENTIFIED BY THE MINISTRY OF
TOURISM STRANDED IN THEIR
HOTELS.
EVEN HERE THE SITUATION WAS
CHAOTIC.
PEOPLE SCRAMBLING, ELBOWING EACH
OTHER, FIGHTING.
THIS IS ONE MOM THAT CAN RELATE
HER EXPERIENCES ON THE PIER HERE
TRYING TO GET ON THE ADVENTURE
OF THE SEAS.
>> PEOPLE ARE FIGHTING FOR
WATER, FIGHTING FOR DIAPERS, FOR
PAMPERS FORKS ANYTHING THEY CAN
FIND.
WE DON'T HAVE WATER, RUNNING
WATER.
WE DON'T HAVE ELECTRICITY.
WE NEED HELP, A LOT OF HELP.
WE'RE NOT HONESTLY -- THERE'S NO
HELP COMING FOR US YET.
THAT'S WHY SHE AND THE OTHER
2,000 WERE LEAVING ON THIS
VESSEL.
THIS IS AN ISLAND IN DIRE NEED,
TRACE, AS YOU HAVE BEEN
REPORTING.
IT'S BEEN DEVASTATING NORTH TO
SOUTH.
THEY ARE PEOPLE THAT HAVE NOT
HAD FRESHWATER OR POWER NOW.
IT'S OVER A WEEK SINCE THIS
HURRICANE HIT.
IT CAME ON THE HEELS OF
HURRICANE IRMA.
PUERTO RICO IS A DYSFUNCTIONAL
PLACE IN THE BEST OF TIMES, A
BANKRUPT GOVERNMENT.
NOW THEY HAVE FINALLY, TRAILS,
APPOINT ADD THREE-STAR GENERAL
TO COORDINATE.
THAT'S WHAT IS SORELY NEEDED
HERE ON THE GROUND IN PUERTO
RICO.
THEY CALL THIS THE ISLAND OF
ENCHANTMENT.
THIS IS AN ISLAND THAT HAS BEEN
CURSED BY NATURE.
IT HAS BEEN HIT BY THESE TWO
DEVASTATING HURRICANES.
NOW PEOPLE ARE SCRAMBLING JUST
TO SURVIVE, TRACE.
>> HELP IS ON THE WAY, GERALDO.
COMING UP, MORE ON REPORTS THAT
THE HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES
SECRETARY TOOK COSTLY CHARTER
FLIGHTS INSTEAD OF CHEAPER
COMMERCIAL ONES.
WHAT SECRETARY TOM PRICE IS
SAYING ABOUT WHETHER HE WILL
KEEP HIS JOB AND THE RESPONSE
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE IS NEXT.
If you have Medicare
Parts A and B
guess what?
You could apply for a
Medicare supplement insurance
plan whenever you want.
No enrollment window.
No waiting to apply.
That means now may be a
great time to shop for an
AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Medicare doesn't
cover everything.
And like all standardized
Medicare supplement
insurance plans,
these help cover some
of what Medicare
doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide.
It could help you find the
AARP Medicare Supplement plan
that works for you.
These types of plans have
no networks,
so you get to choose any
doctor who accepts
Medicare patients.
Rates are competitive,
and they're the only plans
of their kind endorsed by AARP.
Remember -
these plans let you apply
all year round.
So call today.
Because now's the perfect time
to learn more.
Go long.
>> WELL, PRESIDENT TRUMP'S TOP
HEALTH OFFICIAL SHOWING
CONFIDENCE EVEN AFTER THE
PRESIDENT SAID HE'S NOT HAPPY
WITH HIM, HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES SECRETARY TOM PRICE
REPORTEDLY TOOK DOZENSES OF
EXPENSIVE CHARTER FLIGHTS WHEN
CHEAPER FLIGHTS WERE AVAILABLE.
HERE'S SECRETARY PRICE ON A NEWS
CONFERENCE ON THE UPCOMING FLU
SEASON.
>> YOU THINK YOU'RE GOING TO BE
FIRED?
>> I STILL THINK WE HAVE THE
CONFIDENCE OF THE PRESIDENT AND
WE WORK ON IMPORTANT ISSUES LIKE
FLU VACCINATION.
>> LET'S BRING IN JOSH GERSTEIN,
THE SENIOR REPORTER FOR POLITCO.
A COUPLE TIMES THE PRESIDENT HAS
GIVEN THE COULD SHOULDER TO
PEOPLE WHEN IT CAME TO SEAN
SPICER AND STEVE BANNON AND
WHOEVER.
BUT THIS HAS TO BE ONE OF THOSE
THINGS HE'S ON THIN ICE.
>> IT LOOKS THAT WAY.
USUALLY THE WHITE HOUSE IS
COMBATIVE WHEN THERE'S QUESTIONS
RAISED ABOUT ONE OF THE CABINET
MEMBERS OR A SENIOR OFFICIAL.
THEY HAVEN'T CAVED IN ON THE
ISSUES BEFORE.
SO TO HAVE THE PRESIDENT SAY
WE'LL SEE, THE WHITE HOUSE
SAYING THEY'RE GOING TO HAD THIS
TRAVEL WHILE THEY DO A REVIEW.
SARAH SANDERS IN THE BRIEFING WE
SAW DIDN'T SAY THE PRESIDENT HAD
FULL CONFIDENCE IN SECRETARY
PRICE.
SHE SAID THE REVIEW IS UNDERWAY.
THE WORDS "WE'LL SEE" LINGER IN
THE AIR ART THIS POINT.
>> WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF IT?
YOU THINK HE SURVIVES OR NO?
>> I THINK IT'S VERY POSSIBLE HE
MAY HAVE TO GO.
WHAT THE WHITE HOUSE HAS TO LOOK
AT, THEY'RE NOT INTERESTED IN
DOING MAJOR SURGERY ON THEIR
CABINET.
ARE OTHER PEOPLE IN TROUBLE LIKE
THE EPA CHIEF, SCOTT PRUITT WHO
APPARENTLY TOOK SOME CHARTER
TRAVEL AS WELL.
KELLYANNE CONWAY WAS ON ONE OF
THE FLIGHTS WITH PRICE.
THEY WANT TO MAKE SURE IF THEY
HAVE TO LANCE THIS BOIL, IT'S
NOT AS SERIOUS A PROBLEM THAT
WOULD SPREAD ACROSS THE CABINET
OR THE ADMINISTRATION.
>> I WANT YOUR TAKE ON TAXES.
WE HEARD FROM GARY COHN, THE
WHITE HOUSE ECONOMIC ADVISER
SAYING BASICALLY THE TAXES ARE
ABOUT LOWERING THE RATES AND
GETTING RID OF LOOP HOLES.
SEEMS LIKE THEY'RE HAVING A HARD
TIME SELLING THIS TO THE MIDDLE
CLASS.
HE'S SAYING YEAH, MIDDLE CLASS,
YOU'RE GOING TO SAVE $1,000.
BUT THEY'RE HAVING A HARD TIME
MARKETING IT.
>> IT'S VERY TRUE.
PEOPLE ARE SUSPICIOUS THAT
THEY'RE GOING TO GET A TAX CUT
THAT SOMEONE ELSE ALWAYS GETS
THE TAX CUT.
THE ISSUE OF THE STATE AND LOCAL
TAXES BEING DEDUCTIBLE ON THE
FEDERAL RETURN IS A THORNY ONE.
I NOTICED COHN DESCRIBED THAT AS
A LOOP HOLE.
AND UPPER MIDDLE CLASS PEOPLE
FROM THE HIGHER INCOME, HIGHER
TAXING STATES LIKE NEW YORK,
CONNECTICUT, CALIFORNIA ARE NOT
GOING TO VIEW THAT DEDUCTION AS
A LOOP HOLE AND WILL PUT UP A
BIG FIGHT, DEMOCRATS AND
REPUBLICANS.
>> I GOT TO GO HERE, JOSH.
IS THIS THING COME DOWN TO THE
WIRE?
DOES THIS STAND A CHANCE OF
PASSING AT ALL?
>> I THINK IT DOES.
THE REPUBLICANS NEED A WIN HERE.
IT'S VERY, VERY TOUGH TO PASS
TAX REFORM LEGISLATION.
NOBODY HAS MADE AN ATTEMPT TO DO
IT IN 30 YEARS AND THERE'S GOOD
REASON WHY.
>> THERE'S GOOD REASON BUT THEY
NEED A VICTORY.
JOSH GERSTEIN FROM POLITCO.
THANKS.
>> I'M TRACE GALLAGHER IN FOR
SHEPARD SMITH.
"YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL CAVUTO IS
NEXT.
The day after chemo might mean
a trip back to
the doctor's office,
just for a shot.
But why go back there,
when you can stay home...
...with Neulasta Onpro?
Strong chemo can put you
at risk of serious infection.
Neulasta helps
reduce infection risk
by boosting your
white blood cell count,
which strengthens
your immune system.
In a key study,
Neulasta reduced the risk
of infection from 17% to 1%...
...a 94% decrease.
Applied the day of chemo,
Neulasta Onpro is designed to
deliver Neulasta the next day.
Neulasta is for
certain cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta
if you're allergic to
Neulasta or Neupogen
(filgrastim).
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries,
and capillary leak syndrome
have occurred.
Report abdominal or
shoulder tip pain,
trouble breathing
or allergic reactions
to your doctor right away.
In patients with
sickle cell disorders,
serious, sometimes
fatal crises can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
So why go back there?
If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.