COUNTRY AND KILLED SOME 10,000
PEOPLE.
SOME MORE PICTURES NOW IN THE
SLIDE SHOW THAT THIS FIRST
ONE -- THE FIRST PICTURE HERE
SHOWING SOMEBODY GIVING WATER TO
A MAN WHO IS TRAPPED UNDER A
COLLAPSED BUILDING.
AND HERE, A CAR CRUNCHED UNDER
PART OF THE COLLAPSED SCHOOL
WE'VE BEEN SHOWING YOU.
ANOTHER IMAGE SHOWS FIRST
RESPONDERS WORKING TO REMOVE A
MASSIVE PILE OF DEBRIS.
ST INCREDIBLE THE WORK THEY'RE
DOING WITH SO MANY BUILDINGS
DAMAGED OR DESTROYED, THIS
FAMILY AND MANY OTHERS WERE
PREPARING TO SLEEP ON THE
STREETS LAST NIGHT AS THEY
WAITED FOR AFTER SHOCKS.
MANY RACED TO HELP RESCUERS.
HERE'S A STREET CLOWN THAT
SHOWED UP TO OFFER WHATEVER
ASSISTANCE HE COULD.
IN THIS INSTANCE, A WOMAN
HOLDING UP A SIGN FOR SILENCE SO
FIRST RESPONDERS CAN LISTEN FOR
THOSE BURIED UNDER THE CONCRETE
AND STEEL.
THERESA MAY MEETING WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE PRIME
MINISTER MAY FROM THE UNITED
KINGDOM AND HER REPRESENTATIVES
WHO ARE PEOPLE THAT WE KNOW VERY
WELL THROUGH RECENT TRADE
NEGOTIATIONS.
I HAVE TO SAY WE'LL BE DOING A
LOT OF TRADING WITH THE UNITED
KINGDOM.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
WE HAVE GOTTEN TO KNOW EACH
OTHER OVER THE LAST YEAR.
IT'S A REAL HONOR TO HAVE YOU
HERE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
GOOD TO BE HERE.
AS YOU SAY, WE'VE HAD MANY
DISCUSSIONS BETWEEN
REPRESENTATIVES AND OURSELVES ON
A WHOLE VARIETY OF ISSUES,
INCLUDING TRADE WHICH THERE BE
IMPORTANT FOR US AND OTHER
ISSUES, FOREIGN POLICY ISSUES,
SECURITY AND DEFENSE
RELATIONSHIP, WHICH IS THE
CLOSEST THAT WE HAVE.
GREAT THAT THAT CONTINUES.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: PLEASANTRIES BUT NO
QUESTIONS ANSWERED TODAY.
LIVE PICTURES FROM MEXICO CITY
WHERE STREET RESCUES ARE
UNDERWAY, A SPLIT SCREEN HERE ON
THE RIGHT.
YOU CAN SEE THE STREETS OF THE
CITY AND ON THE LEFT IS THE SPOT
WHERE THEY'RE SEARCHING FOR ANY
POSSIBLE SURVIVORS FROM THE
SCHOOL THAT COLLAPSED THERE.
OUR CORRESPONDENT, JONATHAN HUNT
IS IN MEXICO CITY NEAR A
COLLAPSED BUILDING WHERE WE'RE
HEARING THERE MAY BE PEOPLE
TRAPPED THERE AS WELL, JONATHAN?
>> YEAH, SHEP.
WE JUST ARRIVED IN MEXICO CITY
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO.
WE APOLOGIZE FOR THE
COMMUNICATIONS.
WE'RE GETTING YOU A PICTURE AT
THIS POINT.
LET ME PAINT THE PICTURE FOR
YOU.
I'M STANDING IN FRONT OF WHAT
WAS A FIVE-STORY APARTMENT
BUILDING.
EACH STORY OF THE BUILDING
PANCAKED DOWN ON TO EACH OTHER
RIGHT NOW.
SO IT NOW STANDS WHAT WOULD HAVE
BEEN ABOUT TWO STORIES HIGH.
ALTHOUGH FIVE CRUSHED INTO EACH
OTHER.
WE'RE TOLD THERE WAS LIKE 40
APARTMENTS IN THAT BUILDING.
RESCUERS ARE SWARMING AROUND IT
RIGHT NOW TRYING TO FIND ANYBODY
THAT STILL MAY BE ALIVE IN THE
RUBBLE.
THEY'VE BEEN BRINGING OUT A
NUMBER OF BODIES TO THE BODIES
OF TWO CHILDREN FOR INSTANCE
BROUGHT OUT A SHORT TIME AGO.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
HERE.
A LOT OF OFFICIAL REFUGEE
WORKERS OBVIOUSLY.
I HAVE TO SAY ONE OF THE
STRIKING THINGS WHEN YOU ARRIVE
IN MEXICO CITY IS THE NUMBER OF
VOLUNTEERS, THE NUMBER OF
ORDINARY MEXICAN CITIZENS
RUSHING TO HELP.
WE DROVE HERE FROM THE AIRPORT,
SHEP, IN THE LAST FEW MINUTES.
LITERALLY HUNDREDS OF PICKUPS,
MOTOR BIKES GETTING ALONG AS
FAST AS THEY CAN.
THOSE PICKUP TRUCKS OF MOTOR
BIKES LOADED WITH PEOPLE JUST
WANTING TO HELP.
THEY'RE CARRYING SHOVELS,
ANYTHING THAT MAY BE OF USE AS
THEY TRY TO PERFORM THE RESCUES
AROUND THIS CITY RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE IN THE SOUTHERN PART OF
THE CITY, WHICH IS WARDS WHERE
THE SCHOOL IS THAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
THAT IS ONE OF THE MOST INTENSE
SCENES BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY
CHILDREN STILL UNACCOUNTED FOR.
THAT DIGGING WILL GO ON
OBVIOUSLY UNTIL THEY HAVE
ACCOUNTED FOR EVERYBODY WHO MAY
HAVE BEEN IN THAT SCHOOL.
THE SAME WITH THE BUILDING I'M
STANDING IN FRONT OF RIGHT NOW.
THE SAME WITH ALL OF THE 40 OR
SO BUILDINGS THAT COLLAPSED HERE
IN MEXICO CITY.
THE PRESIDENT HAS DECLARED
THREE DAYS OF MOURNING.
IT'S RIGHT NOW A RESCUE
OPERATION.
THE FOCUS IS FINDING PEOPLE
UNDER THIS RUBBLE WHO MAY STILL
BE ALIVE.
WE'RE TOLD, AS YOU LOOK AT THE
PICTURES OF THE SCHOOL, THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL AND THE
SOUTHERN PART OF MEXICO CITY,
THAT THEY FOUND ONE YOUNG GIRL
ALIVE.
THEY'RE DOING THEIR BEST TO GET
TO HER.
OBVIOUSLY IT IS A VERY, VERY
DIFFICULT OPERATION.
A VERY DANGEROUS OPERATION.
WHEN RESCUE WORKERS GO IN TO
PERFORM THE OPERATIONS AS WE SAW
A FEW YEARS AGO IN HAITI,
THEY'RE PUTTING THEIR LIVES AT
RISK.
ONE WRONG MOVE, ONE WRONG PIECE
OF CONCRETE OR ONE PIECE OF
TIMBER MOVES AND MORE OF THE
BUILDING CAN COME DOWN
ENDANGERING THE LIVES OF THE
RESCUE WORKERS.
IT'S A TENSE, DIFFICULT
OPERATION, SHEP.
>> Shepard: JONATHAN HUNT IN
MEXICO CITY.
LIVE REPORTS THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
BACK TO CONTINUING COVERAGE OF
HURRICANE MARIA PUMMELLING
PUERTO RICO AND ST. CROIX AND
OTHERS.
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT NOW DEALING
WITH ITS THIRD NATURAL DISASTER
IN LESS THAN A MONTH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS APPROVED AN
EMERGENCY DECLARATION FOR PUERTO
RICO AND THE VIRGIN ISLANDS.
THE MONSTER STORM COULD COST
BILLIONS IN DAMAGE ACROSS THE
CARIBBEAN.
THAT'S ON TOP OF THE DEVASTATION
THAT HURRICANE IRMA HAS JUST
LEFT BEHIND.
LET'S GO TO BROCK LONG NOW FROM
FEMA WHO BRIEFED PRESIDENT TRUMP
BY PHONE ON HURRICANE MARIA.
SIR, NICE TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
HOW IS THE BRIEFING?
>> THE PRESIDENT REMAINS VERY
ENGAGED AND HIS MESSAGE IS TAKE
CARE OF PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING.
WE KEPT 3,200 STAFF ON THE U.S.
VIRGIN ISLANDS AND PUERTO RICO.
THAT IS INCIDENT MANAGEMENT
TEAMS TO MEDICAL TEAMS TO SEARCH
AND RESCUE TEAMS.
THEY'RE STARTING TO DEPLOY OUT
AS THE STORM -- ELEMENTS OF THE
STORM PASS THROUGH.
AND THEN WE'RE PREPARED TO OPEN
UP AIRPORTS AND THE SHIPPING
PORTS TO CONTINUE WITH MORE
TEAMS AND COMMODITIES COMING IN
UP.
>> Shepard: WHAT KIND OF REPORTS
SPECIFICALLY ARE YOU GETTING
FROM THE TEAMS FANNING OUT?
>> SO IN THE VIRGIN ISLANDS AS
THE SYSTEM PASSED TO THE SOUTH
OF THE ISLANDS LAST NIGHT, THE
WINDS EXPANDED AND THEY
BASICALLY -- THEY HAD UP TO
ABOUT 137 MILES PER HOUR WINDS.
SO THEY HAVE A LOT OF ROOF
DAMAGE.
THEY DO HAVE DAMAGE TO THEIR
CRITICAL INFRASTRUCTURE.
THE POWER IS OFF.
THEY EXPERIENCED SOME DAMAGE TO
HOSPITALS, WHICH WERE ALREADY
WORKING WITH THE GOVERNOR TO
ALLEVIATE SOME OF THOSE IMPACTS.
PUERTO RICO UNFORTUNATELY,
THEY'RE UNDER FLASH FLOOD
WARNINGS IN THE COMMONWEALTH.
THEY HAVE 100% OF THE POWER OFF.
VIRGIN ISLANDS AND PUERTO RICO
HAVE FRAGILE POWER SYSTEMS.
THE GOAL IS LIFE SAFETY, LIFE
SUSTAINING MISSIONS BY GETTING
COMMODITIES IN.
FIRST TO PUSH OUT DEBRIS TO OPEN
THE ROADS AND PROVIDE EMERGENCY
POWER TO THE INFRASTRUCTURE TO
GET IT BACK UP AND TRY TO
RESTORE ROUTINE.
>> Shepard: LOOKING ACROSS THE
EXPAND OF ALL THAT YOUR
DEPARTMENT IS DEALING WITH, IT'S
HARD TO FATHOM HOW DIFFICULT IT
MUST BE TO GET THROUGH THIS.
YOU HAVE TO BE STRETCHED THIN
RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
I WOULDN'T SAY WE'RE STRETCHED
THIN.
THESE GUYS BACK HERE ARE
INCREDIBLY DEDICATED.
THEY'VE BEEN RUNNING FOR 30 DAYS
AT THIS POINT.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO MEET THE
DEMANDS.
WE SIGNED UP FOR THIS JOB AND
DEDICATED TO HELPING THE
GOVERNORS ACHIEVE THEIR RESPONSE
GOALS AND HELP PEOPLE.
>> Shepard: FOR PEOPLE AT HOME
SAYING I WANT TO HELP BUT NOT
SURE HOW TO DO IT, WHAT DO YOU
TELL THEM?
>> RIGHT NOW THE BEST WAY IS TO
GO TO NVOAD.ORG.
THAT WILL GIVE YOU BASICALLY A
WHOLE LIST OF OPTIONS TO
VOLUNTEER AND DONATE.
THEN ONCE WE WORK WITH THE
GOVERNORS, THERE WILL BE OTHER
OPPORTUNITIES TO SUPPORT
VOLUNTEER AND DONATIONS TO EACH
ONE OF THE TERRITORIES.
>> Shepard: WE'RE WITH YOU.
CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
FEMA ADMINISTRATOR BROCK LONG.
TALK TO YOU SOON.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
HE THINKS HE HAS A GOOD SHOT AT
BROKERING PEACE IN THE MIDDLE
EAST.
THE PRESIDENT MET WITH THE
PALESTINIAN LEADER TODAY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID HE MADE UP
HIS MIND ABOUT THE IRAN NUCLEAR
DEAL ONE DAY AFTER CALLING IT AN
EMBARRASSMENT.
SO WHAT IS THE DECISION?
BY THE WAY, THE IRANIAN
PRESIDENT HAS SHOT BACK.
THAT IS NEXT.
I work
overtime when
I can get it.
I need
my blood sugar
to stay
in control.
So I asked
about Tresiba®.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
Tresiba®
is a once-daily,
long-acting
insulin
that lasts even
longer than
24 hours.
I need to cut my A1C.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
Tresiba® works
like my body's insulin.
Releases slow
and steady.
Providing
powerful
A1C reduction.
My week?
Hectic.
My weekends?
My time.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
I can take Tresiba®
any time of day.
So if I sleep in,
and delay my dose,
I take it as soon as I can,
as long as there's at least
8 hours between doses.
Once in use,
Tresiba® lasts
8 weeks,
with or without
refrigeration,
twice as long
as the Lantus® Pen.
(announcer)
Tresiba® is used
to control high blood sugar
in adults with diabetes.
Don't use Tresiba® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during
episodes of low blood sugar,
or if you are allergic
to any of its ingredients.
Don't share needles
or insulin pens.
Don't reuse needles.
The most common side effect
is low blood sugar,
which may cause dizziness,
sweating, confusion
and headache.
Check your blood sugar.
Low blood sugar can be serious
and may be life-threatening.
Injection site reactions
may occur.
Tell your prescriber
about all medicines you take
and all your medical conditions.
Taking TZDs with insulins
like Tresiba®
may cause serious side
effects like heart failure.
Your insulin dose shouldn't
be changed
without
asking your prescriber.
Get medical help right away
if you have trouble breathing,
fast heartbeat,
extreme drowsiness,
swelling of your face,
tongue or throat,
dizziness or confusion.
Ask your health care provider
if you're Tresiba® ready.
Covered by most insurance
and Medicare plans.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪♪
People would ask
me in different
countries that
we traveled,
what is your
nationality and
I would always
answer Hispanic.
So when I got my Ancestry DNA
results it was a shocker.
I'm everything.
I'm from all nations.
I would look at forms
now and wonder
what do I mark?
Because I'm everything.
And I marked other.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
>> Shepard: LIVE IN MEXICO CITY.
SOUTHERN PART OF THE CITY.
SO MANY BUILDINGS THAT HAVE A
COLLAPSED ACROSS THE GREAT CITY.
THIS SCHOOL IS OF URGENT
CONCERN.
MORE THAN 30 KIDS AND TEACHERS
FOR THAT MATTER ARE UNACCOUNTED
FOR.
25 CONFIRMED DEAD.
NOW THE RACE TO FIND SOMEONE
ALIVE.
THEY RESCUED ONE GIRL TODAY.
WE DON'T KNOW THE PARTICULARS OF
HER CONDITION.
WE KNOW THAT SHE'S ALIVE AND WE
KNOW THEY BELIEVE THEY'RE
HEARING SOUNDS INSIDE.
THEY'RE DOING EVERYTHING THEY
CAN TO GET IN THERE AND SAVE
ANYBODY POSSIBLE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE'S MADE A
DECISION ON WHETHER TO PULL THE
UNITED STATES OUT OF THE
HISTORIC NUCLEAR DEAL WITH IRAN.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT DECISION
IS HIS TO KNOW FOR NOW.
>> HAVE YOU DECIDED TO STAY OR
LEAVE?
>> I HAVE DECIDED.
>> WHAT IS YOUR DECISION?
>> I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
>> Shepard: HE WILL LET US KNOW.
HE MADE A COMMENT WITH A MEETING
WITH MAHMOUD ABBAS.
THE PRESIDENT'S COMMENT ON THE
IRAN DEAL AFTER HE CALLED IT AN
EMBARRASSMENT DURING A SPEECH TO
THE UNITED NATIONS GENERAL
ASSEMBLY.
THE PRESIDENT OF IRAN TOOK A
SHOT BACK.
>> IT WILL BE A PERIOD OF
DISAGREEMENT IN THE WORLD OF
POLITICS.
THE WORLD WILL HAVE LOST A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY.
BUT SUCH UNFORTUNATE BEHAVIOR
WILL NEVER IMPEDE IRAN'S COURSE
OF PROGRESS AND ADVANCEMENT.
>> Shepard: ROGUE NEWCOMERS TO
THE WORLD OF POLITICS.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JOHN ROBERTS IS
HERE.
THAT'S TO BE EXPECTED.
>> THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
DISCUSSIONS AROUND THE JCP,
JOINT COMPREHENSIVE PLAN OF
ACTION.
THE CONVERSATIONS ARE CAN THE
DEAL BE REOPENED.
THE UNITED STATES IS ONE OF SIX
SIGNATORS TO THE DEAL.
IF YOU CAN'T GET A BETTER DEAL,
IS THE PRESIDENT BETTER TO PULL
OUT.
AS A CANDIDATE, THE PRESIDENT
SAID HE WAS GOING TO SCRAP THE
DEAL.
BUT THE PRESIDENT HAS
RECERTIFIED THAT IRAN IS
COMPLYING WITH THE DEAL AS
ANOTHER DEADLINE COMES UP AS
SOME ARE SAYING THE PRESIDENT
WILL CONSIDER THE DECISION.
THE WHITE HOUSE'S VIEW OF THE
DEAL, IT ONLY DEALS WITH IRAN
AND THE NUCLEAR PROGRAM AND
DOESN'T DEAL WITH THE SUPPORT
FOR TERROR, BASHAR AL-ASSAD.
YESTERDAY HE SAID AT THE U.N.,
THE IRANIAN RESPOND TODAY BY
SAYING THE FOLLOWING.
>> IGNORANT, ABSURD AND HATEFUL
RHETORIC FILLED WITH
RIDICULOUSLY BASELESS
ALLEGATIONS.
>> ABSURD HATEFUL RHETORIC.
WE REPORT, YOU DECIDE.
THE PRESIDENT HAS TAKEN SOME
OTHER STEPS WITH REGARDS TO IRAN
OUTSIDE OF THE FRAME WORK OF THE
NUCLEAR AGREEMENT UNILATERALLY
IMPOSED SANCTIONS.
IF HE DECIDED TO STAY IN THE
IRAN NUCLEAR DEAL, THE WHITE
HOUSE COULD TAKE MORE STEPS TO
REIGN IN IRAN'S BAD BEHAVIOR.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
>> AND THEY TALKED ABOUT THE
MIDEAST PEACE DEAL.
>> THE PRESIDENT MET WITH
MAHMOUD ABBAS AND THE KING OF
JORDAN.
HE MET WITH THE ISRAELI PRIME
MINISTER.
THE PRESIDENT HAS A LOT INVESTED
IN THIS.
HIS SON-IN-LAW, JARED KUSHNER IS
THE POINT PERSON ON THIS.
THEY HAVE MADE A NUMBER OF
VISITS TO THE REGION.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS YESTERDAY.
THE PRESIDENT HOLDING OUT HOPE
THAT SOMETHING MAY BE POSSIBLE.
LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID THIS
MORNING.
>> WE'RE AT A VERY IMPORTANT
JUNCTURE.
A SMALL PERIOD OF TIME AND WE'RE
GOING TO SEE WHAT WE CAN DO.
SO MANY PEOPLE HAVE TALKED ABOUT
IT AND IT'S NEVER HAPPENED.
WE'RE FIGHTING VERY HARD.
>> HE'S OPTIMISTIC.
SHOULD WE GO THROUGH THE LIST OF
PRESIDENTS THAT WERE HOPEFUL AND
CAME AWAY WITH NOTHING.
>> Shepard: IT'S A LONG ONE.
>> IT IS.
>> Shepard: MICHAEL CROWLEY FROM
POLITCO.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, MICHAEL.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT IS THE
REPORTING WHERE WE ARE IN THIS.
PULLING OUT HAS ENORMOUS
CHALLENGES.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
SOME CRITICS OF THE DEAL, SOME
THAT OPPOSED IT AT THE TIME THAT
IT WAS SEALED WITH SEVERAL
COUNTRIES AS JOHN POINTED OUT,
EVEN SOME OPPONENTS OF DOING
THAT NOW SAY IT'S TOO LATE.
THE COST OF UNDOING THIS DEAL
ARE MUCH GREATER THAN TO OPPOSED
THE DEAL.
IRAN GOT A LOT OF FINANCIAL
BENEFITS.
AS SOON AS THE DEAL WAS STRUCK
IN JULY 2015, IRAN GOT BILLIONS
OF IMMEDIATE PAY-OFF.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN CLAW THAT
BACK.
IN FACT, CIA DIRECTOR MIKE
POMPEO SPOKE TO BRET BAIER.
BRET SAID YOU WERE A STRONG
CRITIC.
AND POMPEO SAID THINGS LOOK
DIFFERENT NOW BEING ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE DESK AND THE
ENVIRONMENT HAS CHANGED.
THE DEAL IS SIGNED.
IRAN GOT THE BENEFITS.
THOSE THAT DIDN'T LIKE THE DEAL
ARE CAUTIOUS ABOUT BLOWING IT UP
RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: WILL THERE REAL
INDICATORS THAT THEY'RE CHEATING
OR IS THE CONSENSUS THAT THINGS
ARE GOING AS WELL AS COULD BE
EXPECTED?
>> YOU KNOW, I GUESS WHAT YOUR
DEFINITION OF CHEATING IS.
THE INTERNATIONAL A COMIC ENERGY
AGENCY INSPECTORS THAT HAVE BEEN
GOING TO IRAN AND HAVE THIS VERY
SPECIFIC CHECKLIST OF TECHNICAL
METRICS SAY THAT IRAN IS NOT
CHEATING.
THEY'RE IN COMPLIANCE.
THERE WAS ONE INCIDENT IRAN GOT
A LITTLE ABOVE THE AMOUNT OF
HEAVY WATER THEY WERE SUPPOSED
TO HAVE ON HAND.
IF YOU TALK THE PEOPLE THAT
ARE -- FOLLOW THIS CLOSELY, THEY
SAY IT'S NOT THAT BIG OF A DEAL.
THE IAEA SAYS THEY'RE IN
COMPLIANCE.
THERE'S A GROUP OF PEOPLE, TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS,
CONSERVATIVE, ISRAELI OFFICIALS
SAY IT'S THE WRONG WAY TO THINK
ABOUT IT.
THAT IT'S BROADER THAN THIS.
IRANIAN BEHAVIOR YOU HAVE TO
LOOK AT.
ARE THEY BECOMING MORE OF A
CIVILIZED NATION THAT OBEYS THE
SORT OF RULES OF THE ROAD
INTERNATIONALLY.
THE ANSWER TO THAT IS NO.
THE DEAL SORT OF OBLIGATED IRAN
TO BEHAVE BETTER IN THEIR
NEIGHBORHOOD AND THEREFORE
THEY'RE NOT HONORING WHAT SOME
TRUMP OFFICIALS HAVE CALLED THE
SPIRIT OF THE DEAL.
THE FRIENDS THAT SERVED UNDER
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID THE DEAL
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IRANIAN
BEHAVIOR, THE METRICS, THE
RESEARCH, THE URANIUM ON HAND.
THAT'S THE OPINION RIGHT NOW.
>> MICHAEL CROWLEY FORE POLITCO.
THANK YOU.
>> THANKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THE TOP REPUBLICAN
IN THE UNITED STATES SENATE SAYS
HE PLANS TO MOVE AHEAD WITH THE
LATEST GOP HEALTHCARE PLAN.
BUT HE CAN LOSE ONLY ONE MORE
REPUBLICAN VOTE AND STILL PASS
THE BILL.
TODAY THE FORMER PRESIDENT
BARACK OBAMA WEIGHED IN ON THIS
MATTER.
ON THE BATTLE OVER HIS OWN
HEALTHCARE LAW.
WE'LL GO LIVE TO CAPITOL HILL
AND WE'RE CONTINUING TO WATCH IN
MEXICO CITY WHERE THE SEARCH IS
ON FOR SURVIVORS A DAY AFTER THE
QUAKE HIT WITH SO MANY WONDERING
WITH BUILDINGS COLLAPSED ALL
OVER THE COUNTRY, HOW HIGH THE
DEATH TOLL MAY BE.
stimate.
I just snapped a photo
and got an estimate in 24 hours.
My insurance company
definitely doesn't have that...
You can leave worry behind when
Liberty Stands With You™
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
♪ (Music plays throughout) ♪
♪  ♪
WHERE YOU LIVE. IN THE PLACE YOU
CALL HOME. THERE'S ROOM TO GROW.
FRESH AIR. FREEDOM. THERE WAS
JUST ONE THING MISSING, FAST
INTERNET. REALLY FAST INTERNET.
IT'S HERE. INTRODUCING HUGHESNET
GEN5. THE NEXT GENERATION OF
SATELLITE INTERNET. WITH FASTER
SPEEDS, MORE DATA, AND BUILT IN
WIFI. NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
WHAT YOU LOVE ONLINE. STAY IN
TOUCH, LEARN, SHARE, WATCH
VIDEOS, CHAT WITH FRIENDS, AND
GET THINGS DONE. ENJOY HIGH
SPEED INTERNET AT HOME, WHEREVER
YOU LIVE. THERE'S NEVER BEEN A
BETTER TIME TO GET AMERICA'S
NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR SATELLITE
INTERNET. THE NEW HUGHESNET GEN5
IS HERE, AND IT'S FASTER THAN
EVER. STANDARD INSTALLATION IS
FREE, SO DON'T WAIT. CALL NOW OR
TEXT (PROMO CODE) TO THIRTY-FIVE
THOUSAND, TODAY.
>> Shepard: THE SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER MITCH McCONNELL INTENDS
TO BREAK THE LATEST GOP
HEALTHCARE BILL TO THE SENATE
FLOOR TO A VOTE NEXT WEEK.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM HIS
SPOKESMAN.
WHEN RAND PAUL ALREADY PLEDGING
TO VOTE NO AND WITH NO SUPPORT
FROM DEMOCRATS AT ALL, THE GOP
CAN AFFORD TO LOSE BY ONE MORE
VOTE.
AND THERE ARE PEOPLE ON THE
FENCE.
THE CHIEF CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MIKE EMANUEL WITH
THE NEWS.
HI, MIKE.
>> PLANS TO VOTE NEXT WEEK ARE
DESIGNED TO TURN UP THE PRESSURE
ON UNDECIDED REPUBLICANS.
>> IT'S BEEN THE MOST FUN THING
I'VE WORKED ON, THE MOST
CHALLENGING THING I'VE WORKED ON
AND WE'RE A POINT TO TAKE THE
BILL UP NEXT WEEK.
TO MY REPUBLICAN COLLEAGUES, IF
YOU HAVE A BETTER IDEA, NOW IS
THE TIME.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE IT UP
NEXT WEEK?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE'RE GOING TO THE FLOOR WITH A
REPEAL AND REPLACE PROPOSAL THAT
IS FEDERALISM.
EVERYBODY GETS TO LOOK AT IT,
STUDY IT.
>> A LOT OF FOCUS ON THREE
REPUBLICAN SENATORS THAT KILLED
HEALTHCARE REFORM IN JULY.
SUSAN COLLINS, JOHN McCAIN AND
ALASKA'S LISA MURKOWSKI.
>> THE INITIAL ANALYSIS ON THE
IMPACT OF THE STATE OF MAINE OF
THEIR BILL IS THAT IT WOULD
RESULT TO MAINE RECEIVING A
BILLION DOLLARS LESS IN FEDERAL
FUNDING FOR HEALTHCARE OVER THE
NEXT DECADE.
>> MEETINGS CONTINUE ON CAPITOL
HILL TRYING TO ADDRESS THE
CONCERNS OF GOP SENATORS
SCHLEPP?
>> Shepard: THERE WAS A
BIPARTISAN EFFORT TO TRY TO
IMPROVE OBAMACARE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT?
>> IT FELL APART LAST NIGHT.
YOU HAD SENATOR LAMAR ALEXANDER
AND PATTY MURRAY TRYING TO WORK
ON A BIPARTISAN FIX BY THE END
OF THE MONTH.
TOP DEMOCRATS ARE EXPRESSING
DISAPPOINTMENT.
>> IT'S UNFORTUNATE.
WE HAD A CHANCE TO DO SOMETHING
IMPORTANT, HISTORIC, BIPARTISAN
THAT WOULD HAVE BUILT ON THE
HEALTHCARE SYSTEM THAT WE HAVE
IN THIS COUNTRY.
NOW WE'RE MOVING TO ANOTHER
PARTISAN APPROACH.
NO CBO SCORE, NO HEARINGS.
GETTING READY TO REPEAT WHAT WE
DID A FEW MONTHS AGO.
>> FORMER PRESIDENT OBAMA
WEIGHED IN THIS AFTERNOON
CALLING THE LATEST ATTEMPT TO
SCRAP OBAMACARE AGGRAVATING.
>> ALL OF THIS IS BEING DONE
WITHOUT ANY ECONOMIC OR
ACTIONARY OR PLAIN COMMON SENSE
RATIONALE.
IT FRUSTRATES.
IT'S CERTAINLY FRUSTRATING TO
HAVE TO MOBILIZE EVERY COUPLE
MONTHS TO KEEP OUR LEADERS FROM
INFLICTING REAL HUMAN SUFFERING
ON OUR CONSTITUENTS.
>> IT'S NOT ENTIRELY CLEAR IF
REPUBLICANS WILL GET TO 50 YES
VOTES, SHEP.
>> Shepard: MIKE EMANUEL AT THE
ROTUNDA ON THE HILL.
THANK YOU.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
If you've been struggling
with belly pain
and constipation,
and you're overwhelmed
by everything you've tried--
all those laxatives,
daily probiotics,
endless fiber--
it could be wearing on you.
Tell your doctor
what you've tried,
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults
with IBS
with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help relieve
your belly pain
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.
Do not give LINZESS
to children less than six
and it should not be given
to children
six to less than eighteen.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS
if you have a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop
unusual or severe
stomach pain,
especially with
bloody or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe,
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor
right away.
Other side effects
include gas,
stomach-area pain
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
Experience the Lexus RX
with Advance Safety...
Standard.
Lease the 2017 RX 350 for
$399 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing at
your Lexus dealer.
>> Shepard: WE'VE BEEN WATCHING
ALMOST CONSTANTLY AS THEY WORK
FEVERISHLY TO SAVE ANYBODY
BURRED IN THAT SCHOOL IN
SOUTHERN MEXICO CITY.
WE'LL HAVE UPDATES THROUGHOUT