IN YOUR JOURNEY.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
WE'RE STAYING ON THE NEWS ALL
DAY LONG, PARTICULARLY MEXICO
CITY WHERE THEY'RE TRYING TO
RESCUE KIDS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST, 3:00 IN THE EAST I
AND 2:00 P.M. IN MEXICO CITY.
TEAMS SAY THEY HAVE SPOKEN WITH
ONE GIRL TRAPPED BENEATH A
BUILDING.
SHE TOLD THEM THERE'S MORE
SURVIVORS WITH HER.
NOW WITH THE WRECKAGE SHIFTING
AND GROANING AND MORE AFTER
SHOCKS POSSIBLE, CREWS ARE
RISKING THEIR LIVES TO TRY TO
GET THOSE KIDS TO SAFETY.
HURRICANE MARIA ROARING ACROSS
THE CARIBBEAN NOW LEAVING BEHIND
ABSOLUTE DESTRUCTION.
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS IN PUERTO
RICO NOW GETTING AN IDEA OF JUST
HOW MUCH THEY LOST WHEN THE
STORM SCOURED THEIR ISLAND.
WINDS SO POWERFUL, THEY RIPPED
CONCRETE BALCONIES OFF OF WALLS
AND NOW MARIA HEADED FOR THE
TURKS AND CAICOS AND THE
BAHAMAS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ANNOUNCING BOLD
NEW MEASURES TARGETING THE
NUCLEAR NATION OF NORTH KOREA.
HE SAYS THEY'RE AIMED AT CUTTING
OFF CASH TO KIM JONG-UN AND HIS
WEAPONS PROGRAM.
MORE DETAILS EXPECTED IN A LIVE
EVENT IN JUST MOMENTS.
SO LET'S GET TO IT.
BREAKING NEWS THIS HOUR.
FIRST, THE TREASURY SECRETARY
STEVE MNUCHIN ABOUT TO BRIEF
REPORTERS ON THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S LATEST MOVE TO
CUT OFF NORTH KOREA'S CASH FLOW.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ANNOUNCING HIS
NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER HOURS AGO.
IT GIVES THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT
MORE POWER TO GO AFTER PEOPLE
THAT DO BUSINESS WITH KIM
JONG-UN'S GOVERNMENT.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS IT WILL LEAVE
THE DICTATOR WITH LESS MONEY FOR
HIS NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
>> NORTH KOREA'S NUCLEAR WEAPONS
AND MISSILE DEVELOPMENT IS A
GRAVE THREAT TO PEACE AND
SECURITY IN OUR WORLD AND IT IS
UNACCEPTABLE THAT OTHERS
FINANCIALLY SUPPORT THIS
CRIMINAL ROGUE REGIME.
OUR NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER WILL CUT
OFF SOURCES OF REVENUE THAT FUND
NORTH KOREA'S EFFORTS TO DEVELOP
THE DEADLIEST WEAPONS TO HUMAN
KIND.
>> Shepard: THE PRESIDENT MAKING
THE ANNOUNCEMENT WITH THE
LEADERS OF SOUTH KOREA AND
JAPAN.
THE PRESIDENT HELD SEPARATE
MEETINGS WITH EACH LEADER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP PRAISING CHINA
FOR REPORTEDLY TELLING ITS BANKS
TO STOP DOING BUSINESS WITH
NORTH KOREA.
THE REUTERS NEWS AGENCY SAID
THAT MESSAGE CAME FROM CHINA'S
CENTRAL BANK, WHICH MAKES IT
SIGNIFICANT.
ANALYSTS SAY IT WOULD BE A MAJOR
BLOW TO NORTH KOREA BECAUSE
CHINA IS ITS CLOSEST ALLY.
THE EXECUTIVE ORDER ALSO COMES
JUST A COUPLE OF DAYS AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FIRST SPEECH
TO THE U.N.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THE UNITED
STATES WOULD TOTALLY DESTROY
NORTH KOREA IF IT HAD TO, BUT
HOPEFULLY HE SAID IT WON'T BE
NECESSARY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ALSO SAID KIM
JONG-UN OR ROCKETMAN, AS HE
CALLS HIM THESE DAYS IS ON A
SUICIDE ANYTHING.
NOW NORTH KOREA'S FOREIGN
MINISTER HAS SPOKEN BACK.
>> IF THEY THOUGHT THEY COULD
SCARE US WITH A SOUND OF A DOG
BARKING, IT'S A SILLY DREAM.
>> Shepard: SOUND OF A DOG
BARKING.
THE FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS HE
PITY'S PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
ADVISERS.
DESPITE THE RHETORIC, PRESIDENT
TRUMP DID NOT RULE OUT TALKING
WITH THE NORTH KOREANS.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, IS DIALOGUE
STILL POSSIBLE WITH NORTH KOREA?
>> Shepard: BREAKING RIGHT NOW,
THE TREASURY SECRETARY STEVE
MNUCHIN IS TALKING ABOUT THE NEW
ORDER.
LET'S LISTEN LIVE FROM NEW YORK
CITY.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NEW
EXECUTIVE ORDER SIGNIFICANTLY
EXPANDS TREASURIES, AUTHORITIES
TO TARGET THOSE WHO ENABLE THIS
REGIME'S ECONOMIC ACTIVITY
WHEREVER THEY ARE LOCATED.
FOR TOO LONG, NORTH KOREA HAS
EVADED SANCTIONS AND USED THE
INTERNATIONAL FINANCIAL SYSTEM
TO FACILITATE FUNDING FOR
WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION AND
BALLISTIC MISSILE PROGRAMS.
NO BANK IN ANY COUNTRY SHOULD BE
USED TO FACILITATE KIM JONG-UN'S
DESTRUCTIVE BEHAVIOR.
THIS NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER WILL
AUTHORIZE TREASURY TO IMPOSE A
RANGE OF SANCTIONS LIKE
SUSPENDING U.S. CORRESPONDENT
ACCOUNT ACCESS TO ANY FOREIGN
BANK THAT KNOWINGLY CONDUCTS OR
FACILITATES SIGNIFICANT
TRANSACTIONS TIED TO TRADE WITH
NORTH KOREA.
THESE SANCTIONS WILL BE
FORWARD-LOOKING AND APPLIED TO
BEHAVIOR THAT OCCURS FOLLOWING
TODAY WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
SIGNED THE EXECUTIVE ORDER.
FOREIGN FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS
ARE NOW ON NOTICE THAT GOING
FORWARD, THEY CAN CHOOSE TO DO
BUSINESS WITH THE UNITED STATES
OR WITH NORTH KOREA, BUT NOT
BOTH.
THIS NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER ENABLES
TREASURY TO FREEZE ASSETS OF
ANYONE CONDUCTING SIGNIFICANT
TRADE IN GOODS, SERVICES OR
TECHNOLOGY WITH NORTH KOREA.
IT ALSO ALLOWS TO US FREEZE
ASSETS OF ACTORS SUPPORTING
NORTH KOREA'S TEXTILE, FISHING,
AND TECHNOLOGY INDUSTRIES.
WE CALL ON ALL COUNTRIES AROUND
THE WORLD TO JOIN US BY CUTTING
OFF ALL TRIED AND FINANCIAL TIES
TO NORTH KOREA IN ORDER TO
ACHIEVE A DE-NUCLEARIZED KOREAN
PENINSULA.
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP STATED IN HIS
SPEECH TO THE U.N., IT'S TIME
FOR ALL NATIONS TO WORK TOGETHER
TO ISOLATE KIM JONG-UN'S REGIME
UNTIL IT CEASES ITS HOSTILE
BEHAVIOR.
WE WILL WORK WITH OUR ALLIES AND
PARTNERS TO STOP FROM USING THE
GLOBAL FINANCIAL SYSTEM TO
FURTHER KIM'S RECKLESS BEHAVIOR.
THANK YOU AND I'D BE HAPPY TO
TAKE A FEW QUESTIONS.
>> CAN YOU EXPLAIN HOW THIS WILL
AFFECT -- WHAT KIND OF
DISCUSSIONS YOU AND YOUR COUNTER
PARTS HAVE HAD ABOUT THIS?
>> LET ME COMMENT.
I HAD A VERY PRODUCTIVE
CONVERSATION EARLY THIS MORNING
WITH GOVERNOR JOE AT THE PBOC,
THE PEOPLE'S BANK OF CHINA AND
HOW WE'RE GOING TO WORK
TOGETHER.
THIS ACTION IS DIRECTED AT
EVERYONE.
IT'S IN NO WAY DIRECTED AT
CHINA.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING
CLOSELY WITH THEM.
>> MR. SECRETARY, CAN I READ A
QUICK SECTION OF THE E.O.?
NO AIRCRAFT IN WHICH A FOREIGN
PERSON HAS AN INTERESTED HAS
LANDED AT A PLACE IN NORTH
KOREA, MAY LAND IN THE UNITED
STATES AFTER DEPARTURE FROM
NORTH KOREA.
THEN SIMILAR APPLICATIONS TO
SHIPS.
ANY IDEA ON HOW MANY SHIPS OR
AIRCRAFT WOULD BE HAVE BEEN
AFFECTED IN PICK A YEAR?
SO WE CAN GET A SENSE OF THE
SCALE OF THE IMPACT.
>> AGAIN, ANOTHER IMPORTANT
ASPECT OF THE E.O. BESIDES FOR
US BEING ABLE TO BLOCK FINANCIAL
TRANSACTIONS.
WE'LL WORK CLOSELY WITH THE
COAST GUARD AND OTHERS ON THIS.
I'M NOT PREPARED TO GIVE YOU A
NUMBER.
IT'S VERY SIGNIFICANT.
FURTHER, WE CAN PUT ACTIONS
AGAINST PORTS AS WELL.
>> A COUPLE QUESTIONS.
FIRST ONE, WHY WILL THIS ROUND
OF SANCTIONS WORK WHEN OTHERS
HAVE FAILED?
>> AGAIN, LET ME BE CLEAR.
I DON'T THINK OTHER SANCTIONS
HAVE FAILED.
THESE SANCTIONS ARE SIGNIFICANT.
NOT ONLY DOES IT ALLOW US TO
SANCTION INDIVIDUALS OR
ENTITIES, BUT IT ALLOWS US TO
FREEZE OR BLOCK ANY TRANSACTIONS
WITH ANY FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS
ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD THAT
FACILITATES ANY TRANSACTIONS
WITH THE BLOCKED PERSON.
>> DO THESE SANCTIONS INCLUDED A
PLAN TO TARGET NORTH KOREAN
BUSINESSES AROUND THE WORLD?
>> YES, IT DOES.
>> ANY FUTURE SANCTIONS?
>> I WON'T COMMENT ON FUTURE
SANCTIONS.
WE'LL REVIEW ALL OPTIONS.
>> DOES THIS REPRESENT A
REJECTION OR A MOVING PATH TO
THE U.N. SECURITY COUNCIL?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK IN ANY WAY.
WE APPRECIATE THE U.N. SECURITY
COUNCIL RESOLUTION AND THE
UNANIMOUS SUPPORT TO THAT.
THIS GOES BEYOND IT.
AS I'VE MENTIONED, THIS ALLOWS
US TO BLOCK ANY FINANCIAL
INSTITUTION THAT DOESN'T
FOLLOW-THROUGH ON THE U.N.
SANCTIONS OR ADDITIONAL
SANCTIONS.
>> WHEN DO YOU EXPECT TO MAKE
DESIGNATIONS --
>> WE'LL DO DESIGNATIONS ON A
ROLLING BASIS.
THIS STARTS TODAY.
IT'S FORWARD LOOKING, NOT
BACKWARDS LOOKING.
>> CAN YOU SAY MORE ABOUT YOUR
DISCUSSIONS WITH THE CENTRAL
BANK OF CHINA?
WHAT DO YOU UNDERSTAND --
>> AGAIN, THOSE CONVERSATIONS
ARE CONFIDENTIAL.
AS I SAID, I HAD A VERY
PRODUCTIVE CONVERSATION WITH
THEM THIS MORNING.
>> PIGGYBACKING ON THAT, THE
TIMELINE, HAS THERE BEEN
PREVIOUS NEGOTIATIONS WITH THE
BANK OF CHINA?
>> NO, THERE WERE NO PREVIOUS
DISCUSSIONS.
THE FIRST TIME WE DISCUSSED IT
WAS THIS MORNING.
I CALLED THEM TO ALERT THEM OF
THIS IN ADVANCE GIVEN THEIR
CLOSE COOPERATION WITH US.
>> THANK YOU.
SO I WANT TO ASK PART OF THE
SAME QUESTION.
THAT CHINA HAD GIVEN SOME
INDICATION 1 1/2 WEEKS AGO OF
SOME ACTIONS.
WHAT DID THEY TODAY IS SEPARATE
FROM WHAT THEY INDICATED
EARLIER --
>> I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE
COMMENTS ABOUT WHAT THEY DID
EARLIER.
WHAT THEY DID TODAY IS I ASSUME
AS A RESULT OF OUR CONVERSATION.
>> CAN I ASK --
>> LET'S COME BACK TO YOU SO WE
CAN GET OTHER PEOPLE.
>> CAN YOU -- DO YOU BELIEVE
THAT CHINA'S ACTIONS TODAY
REDUCE THE NEED FOR FURTHER
SECONDARY SANCTIONS ON CHINESE
ENTITIES --
>> I JUST COMMENTED WE LOOK
FORWARD TO WORKING WITH THEM AS
WELL AS ALL OF OUR PARTNERS.
WHAT IS IMPORTANT ABOUT THIS IS
THE ADDITIONAL AUTHORITIES THE
TREASURY HAS.
>> CAN YOU PUT THIS IN THE
CONTEXT OF THE PRESIDENT'S
SPEECH EARLIER IN THE WEEK WHEN
HE TALKED ABOUT MORE MILITARY
ACTION?
HOW DO THESE THINGS WORK
TOGETHER AND WHAT DO YOU EXPECT
NORTH KOREA TO DO IN RESPONSE?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO COMMENT ON
WHAT I EXPECT NORTH KOREA TO DO.
OBVIOUSLY WHAT WE'VE SAID IS THE
OBJECTIVE, FOR THEM TO STOP
THEIR MISSILE TESTS AND GIVE UP
THEIR NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT HAS BEEN
IN THE WORKS FOR A WHILE.
I ALLUDED TO THIS ABOUT TWO
WEEKS AGO, THAT I HAD BEEN
DISCUSSING THIS WITH THE
PRESIDENT AND THIS IS ALL PART
OF THE PRESIDENT'S STRATEGY AT
THE U.N. THIS WEEK.
>> SECRETARY TILLERSON SAID IT
TOOK AWHILE FOR THE LAST ROUND
OF SANCTIONS TO HAVE AN IMPACT
OR FOR NORTH KOREA TO BE ABLE TO
FEEL THEM IS.
THERE A TIMELINE THAT YOU'RE
LOOKING AT IN WHICH CASE --
>> AGAIN, THERE'S NO TIME LINE.
THIS IS FORWARD ACTION ON THIS.
AGAIN, I WOULD EMPHASIZE THAT WE
HOPE THAT THERE'S VOLUNTARY
COOPERATION, BUT TO THE EXTENT
THAT WE HAVE TO CUT OFF BANKS
FROM THE BANKING SYSTEM IN THE
UNITED STATES, WHICH OBVIOUSLY
WOULD BE SIGNIFICANT, WE NOW
HAVE THOSE TOOLS TO DO THAT.
>> DO YOU RECALL ANY OTHER
COUNTRIES, CENTRAL BANKS --
>> I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE ANY
COMMENTS ON CONFIDENTIAL
DISCUSSIONS WITH OTHER
COUNTRIES.
AGAIN, I'M CONFIRMING THAT I DID
SPEAK TO THEM THIS MORNING.
I'M NOT GOING TO COMMENT ON
OTHER DISCUSSIONS THAT ARE
CONFIDENTIAL.
>> THE PRESIDENT EARLIER THANKED
PRESIDENT XI FOR HIS ACTIONS.
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE ENOUGH?
DID YOU CALL ON RUSSIA --
>> AGAIN, WE'LL CALL ON RUSSIA
TO DO MORE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND PRESIDENT XI
HAVE HAD PRODUCTIVE
CONVERSATIONS AND WE APPRECIATE
THE WAY THEY'RE WORKING WITH US.
I'M GOING TO TAKE ONE MORE.
>> I'D FOLLOW UP ON MY INITIAL
QUESTION.
YOU SAID THIS WAS NOT TARGETED
AT CHINA SPECIFICALLY.
BUT CHINA IS THE LARGEST TRADING
PARTNER WITH NORTH KOREA.
SO CAN YOU SPELL OUT HOW THIS
WILL AFFECT THEM AND HOW IT WILL
AFFECT THE U.S. AND THEIR
RELATIONSHIP WITH CHINA WITH
REGARD TO NORTH KOREA?
>> AS I EMPHASIZED EARLIER, THIS
IS TARGETED AT NORTH KOREA AND
ANYBODY THAT WANTS TO DO TRADE
OR BUSINESS WITH THEM.
WE APPRECIATE THE RELATIONSHIP
WITH CHINA AND LOOK FORWARD TO
WORKING WITH THEM.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
>> Shepard: STEVE MNUCHIN
DISCUSSING THE NEW SANCTIONS BY
THE PRESIDENT THROUGH NORTH
KOREA WITH PARTNERSHIP IT WOULD
APPEAR FROM A NUMBER OF NATIONS.
HE WOULDN'T BE SPECIFIC ABOUT
DISCUSSIONS.
BIG PICTURE WITH THE SANCTIONS
AND THE NATIONSIN CGOM THEOGRET
W
TSTHE GOAL?
JOHN ROBERTS TRAVELLING WITH THE
PRESIDENT IN NEW YORK AND IN THE
STUDIO WITH US TODAY.
BIG PICTURE?
>> BIG PICTURE, THIS IS DESIGNED
TO GET KIM JONG-UN TO THE
NEGOTIATING TABLE.
THE PRESIDENT WAS ASKED, IS
THERE STILL ROOM FOR DIALOGUE?
HE SAID WHY NOT.
ALL OF THIS THAT YOU'VE HAVE
SEEN IS DESIGNED TO TRY TO GET
KIM JONG-UN TO THE NEGOTIATING
TABLE TO TALK ABOUT NOT JUST
FREEZING IT BUT TO GIVE IT UP.
THE PRESIDENT'S GOAL IS TO
DENUCLEARIZE THE KOREAN
PENINSULA.
IT MEANS FREEZING IT AND ROLLING
IT BACK TO NOTHING.
ONE OF THE BIG DEVELOPMENTS IS
THE FACT THAT CHINA FINALLY
STEPPED UP TO THE PLATE.
LISTEN TO WHAT THE PRESIDENT
SAID CHINA DECIDED TO DO TODAY.
>> CHINA, THEIR CENTRAL BANK,
HAS TOLD THEIR OTHER BANKS, A
MASSIVE BANKING SYSTEM, TO
IMMEDIATELY STOP DOING BUSINESS
WITH NORTH KOREA.
I THANK PRESIDENT XI OF CHINA
FOR THE BOLD MOVE HE MADE TODAY.
THIS IS A SOMEWHAT UNEXPECTED
MOVE AROUND WE APPRECIATE IT.
>> RIGHT NOW THE PRESIDENT IS
SPEAKING WITH PRESIDENT ERDOGAN
FROM TURKEY.
THEY'RE HAVING A BILATERAL
MEETING AND THE POOL IS THERE.
LET'S WATCH.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
A GREAT HONOR AND PRIVILEGE.
HE'S BECOME A FRIEND OF MINE.
I WANT TO INTRODUCE PRESIDENT
ERDOGAN OF TURKEY.
HE'S RUNNING A VERY DIFFICULT
PART OF THE WORLD.
HE'S INVOLVED VERY STRONGLY AND
HE'S GETTING HIGH MARKS FRANKLY.
HE'S ALSO BEEN WORKING WITH THE
UNITED STATES.
WE HAVE A GREAT FRIENDSHIP.
AS COUNTRIES WE'RE AS CLOSE AS
WE HAVE EVER BEEN.
A LOT OF THAT HAS TO DO WITH THE
PERSONAL RELATIONSHIPS.
SO PRESIDENT, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
A GREAT HONOR TO HAVE YOU HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
THANK YOU.
[SPEAKING TURKISH].
>> Shepard: THE TURKISH PRIME
MINISTER EDWARD SPEAKING WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
ERDOGAN, A VERY COMPLICATED
RELATIONSHIP.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> WE ARE GETTING TOGETHER WITH
YOU AS A DELEGATION AND WE WILL
COME BACK TO BILATERAL
MEETINGS-WE'LL ASSESS THE
CURRENT RELATIONSHIPS BETWEEN
THE UNITED STATES AND TURKEY AND
HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO DISCUSS
REGIONAL DEVELOPMENTS AS A
WHOLE.
I WOULD LIKE TO ONCE AGAIN THANK
YOU FOR THIS OPPORTUNITY.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
MR. PRESIDENT.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, WHEN IS THE
LAST TIME YOU SPOKE WITH PAUL
MANAFORT.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: A DIFFICULT SET OF
CIRCUMSTANCES HERE WITH THE
PRIME MINISTER ERDOGAN.
HE'S JAILED PEOPLE BY THE
THOUSANDS FOR SPEAKING OUT
AGAINST HIS GOVERNMENT.
HE'S JAILED MORE THAN 120
JOURNALISTS, DENOUNCED AROUND
THE WORLD.
THERE'S A WIDELY-HELD BELIEF
THAT HE'S TURNING WHAT APPEARED
TO BE A COUNTRY ON THE WAY TO
DEMOCRATIZATION INTO SOMETHING
AKIN TO A DICTATORSHIP.
>> THE PROBLEM HERE, HE'S A NATO
MEMBER AND TURKEY IS THE GATEWAY
FROM TURKEY TO THE MIDDLE EAST.
YOU SAID IT'S A COMPLICATED
RELATIONSHIP.
A DIPLOMATIC WAY OF PUTTING UP.
>> Shepard: I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU
RESOLVE IT.
SEEING HIM UP THERE, AS A
JOURNALIST IT AFFECTS YOU THE
SAME WAY IT DOES ME.
IT'S A SCARY PROPOSITION WHAT IS
HAPPENING IN TURKEY, IT'S
AGAINST EVERYTHING WE BELIEVE IN
THE UNITED STATES.
>> IT IS.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS PRESIDENT,
THIS NATION NEEDS TO HAVE A
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM BECAUSE OF
WHERE HIS COUNTRY IS AND WHERE
THEY REPRESENT.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE LINES THAT YOU
HAVE TO HOLD YOUR NOSE TO DEAL
WITH THE PEOPLE YOU HAVE TO DEAL
WITH.
THAT'S PROBABLY THE CASE IN THIS
POINT.
BACK TO WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT
PRIOR TO GOING HERE, CHINA.
THE MOVE THAT CHINA MADE IN
TERMS OF THE CENTRAL BANK
TELLING CHINESE BANKS, DON'T DO
ANY BUSINESS WITH NORTH KOREA
ANYMORE, THAT'S BIG.
THE PRESIDENT SAID CHINA NEEDS
TO STEP UP TO THE PLATE.
WHEN I SPOKE WITH THE PRESIDENT
LAST THURSDAY, I ASKED HIM ABOUT
NORTH KOREA AND CHINA.
HE SAID THEY'RE PLANNING SOME
MOVES WITH CHINA HE COULDN'T
TELL US ABOUT.
IT WOULD CLEARLY SEEM THIS IS
IT.
WHY IT'S SO IMPORTANT IS BECAUSE
THIS DOESN'T WORK WITHOUT
CHINA'S COOPERATION AND CHINA
TAKING STRINGENT MEASURES.
ALWAYS LOTS OF POSSIBILITIES FOR
CHEATING, BUT MAYBE THIS IS A
STEP DOWN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
>> Shepard: CHINA HAS BEEN CLEAR
TO SAY FROM THEIR PERSPECTIVE,
WE'VE DONE WHAT WE CAN DO.
THE WORLD IS PUSHING US.
>> THE CHINESE CAN DO MORE THAN
THEY'VE BEEN DOING.
>> Shepard: OBVIOUSLY.
I WONDER IF THIS IS A CHANGE.
>> IT WOULD APPEAR TO BE A
CHANGE.
ALTHOUGH THERE'S ROOM FOR
CHEATING.
IS THIS CHINA JUST SAYING THIS
IS WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO OR IS
THIS CHINA DOING WHAT THEY SAY
THEY'RE GOING TO DO?
>> Shepard: THE U.S.,
SANCTIONING BANKS, THIS IS A
WIDE EXPANSION?
>> IT BROADENS THE TARGET
ENVIRONMENT.
THERE WAS ONE CHINESE BANK BEING
SANCTIONED.
THIS LAST TARGETED INDIVIDUALS
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
THE FACT THAT THEY'RE LOOKING AT
NORTH KOREA AND GOING TO TARGET
THE NORTH KOREAN TEXTILE
INDUSTRY AND THE FISHING
INDUSTRY.
OTHER SMALLER INDUSTRIES THAT
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
DEFENSE MINISTRY, THIS IS TRYING
TO PUT A CHOKE HOLD ON NORTH
KOREA.
THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID HE
DOESN'T WANT TO SETTLE FOR
ANYTHING SHORT OF
DENUCLEARIZATION OF THE
PENINSULA.
THERE COULD BE WIGGLE ROOM
THERE.
I DON'T THINK NORTH KOREA WOULD
FREEZE IT UP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JOHN
ROBERTS.
GORDON CHANG WROTE THE BOOK ON
NORTH KOREA.
HE'S OUR GUEST LIVE NEXT.
WILL THIS WORK?
THAT'S NEXT.
When my doctor told me
I have age-related macular
degeneration, AMD,
he told me to look at this
grid every day.
And we came up with a plan
to help reduce
my risk
of progression,
including PreserVision
AREDS 2.
My doctor said
PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
the National Eye
Institute recommends
to help reduce
the risk of progression of
moderate to advanced AMD
after 15 years
of clinical studies.
PreserVision
AREDS 2.
Because my eyes
are everything.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
Approaching Medicare
eligibility?
Don't put off checking out your
Medicare options until 65.
Now is a good time to get the
ball rolling.
Medicare only covers about
eighty percent of
Part B medical costs.
The rest is up to you.
That's where AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plans
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company come in.
Like all standardized Medicare
supplement insurance plans,
they could help save you in
out-of-pocket medical costs.
Taking informed steps really
makes a difference later.
That's what it means to
GO LONG™.
Call now and request this free
Decision Guide
and explore the range of AARP
Medicare Supplement Plans.
All plans like these let you
choose any doctor or hospital
that accepts Medicare patients.
These are the only Medicare
supplement insurance plans
endorsed by AARP.
Call now and request your free
Decision Guide...
and start gathering the
information you need
to help you GO LONG™.
>> Shepard: NEW SANCTIONS ON
NORTH KOREA WITH CHINESE HELP.
LET'S GO TO GORDON CHANG, AUTHOR
OF "NUCLEAR SHOW DOWN: NORTH
KOREA TAKES ON THE WORLD."
GORDON, THANK YOU.
>> THANKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: A BIT OF A MUTED
RESPONSE.
SOMETHING ABOUT DOGS BARKING.
YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> YEAH, THIS IS EXTREMELY
SIGNIFICANT.
WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP DID AND
WHAT TREASURY SECRETARY MNUCHIN
IS NOW DOING IS SHUTTING OFF THE
MONEY TO THE NORTH KOREAN
REGIME.
EVERY BANK GETS A FREE PASS FOR
WHAT THEY DID IN THE PAST WITH
THEIR RELATIONS WITH PYONGYANG.
WHAT MNUCHIN SAID, LOOK, GOING
FORWARD, IF A BANK VIOLATES U.S.
LAW, IT WILL BE DESIGNATED.
YOU HEARD THAT WORD
"DESIGNATION" IN THE PRESS
CONFERENCE.
THAT'S UNDER 311 OF THE PATRIOT
ACT.
IF A BANK IS SO DESIGNATED, IT'S
CUT OFF FROM THE GLOBAL
FINANCIAL SYSTEM BECAUSE IT CAN
NO LONGER TRANSACT BUSINESS IN
DOLLARS.
WHAT THE NORTH KOREANS NOW WILL
DO IS TRY TO TRANSACT BUSINESS
IN OTHER CURRENCIES, WHAT THE
UNITED STATES IS GO AROUND THE
WORLD AND MAKE SURE THEY CAN'T
USE OTHER CURRENCIES.
>> Shepard: THE NORTH KOREANS
DIDN'T SAY MUCH.
THEY WAIT AWHILE.
YOU WONDER IF THEY WON'T WAIT
UNTIL ALL OF THESE WORLD LEADERS
GO BACK TO THEIR HOMES.
>> OH, ABSOLUTELY.
THE LAST THING THEY WANT TO DO
IS ENGAGE IN A PROVOCATION THAT
GIVES UP TRUMP TO TALK TO OTHER
WORLD LEADERS.
I EXPECT THE NORTH KOREANS TO BE
QUIET A WORK OR SO.
YOU HEARD WHAT NORTH KOREA SAY
ABOUT THE WORDS OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP, LIKE A DOG BARKING.
THEY'RE SEEING THAT THE U.S. CAN
EXERT PRESSURE ON THEIR PRIMARY
BACKER.
NORTH KOREA IS IN A WORLD OF
HURT.
>> Shepard: JOHN ROBERTS REPORTS
THE BIG PICTURE IS TO GET NORTH
KOREANS TO THE NEGOTIATING
TABLE.
DOES THIS HELP?
>> OBVIOUSLY NEGOTIATIONS ARE
THE PREFERRED WAY OF SOLVING
THIS.
I BELIEVE WE SHOULD START THE
DISCUSSIONS ONLY WHEN THE NORTH
KOREANS UNDERSTAND THAT THEY
HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO DISARM.
IF WE START THEM EARLIER THAN
THAT, THEY WILL USE THEM TO
DELAY TO PERFECT THEIR MISSILES
AND NUKES.
THAT'S WHAT WE DID IN THE
SIX-PARTY TALKS IN THE
ADMINISTRATION OF GEORGE W.
BUSH.
WE DON'T WANT TO DO THAT AGAIN.
THE PRESIDENT, OUR PRESIDENT
UNDERSTANDS THAT, AND I THINK
WE'LL SEE MAXIMUM PRESSURE,
MAXIMUM ENGAGEMENT, WHICH IS THE
BUZZ PHRASE IN WASHINGTON.
IT MIGHT WORK THIS TIME IF THE
ADMINISTRATION IS ABSOLUTELY
DETERMINED TO CARRY FORWARD ON
THIS.
>> Shepard: SHORT ON TIME.
LESS LIKELY OR MORE LIKELY TO
GET ANOTHER MISSILE TEST?
>> THERE WILL BE ANOTHER MISSILE
TEST.
THE NORTH KOREANS NEED TO
IMPROVE THEIR CAPABILITIES.
THEY WANT A DETERRENT.
THEY WANT TO SELL THESE THINGS
TO THE IRANIANS, THIS IS WHERE
WE COME IN.
THE IRANIANS PAY THE NORTH
KOREANS $2 BILLION TO $3 BILLION
A YEAR.
WHAT MNUCHIN IS DOING WILL CUT
OFF THAT FLOW OF CASH IF HE'S
SUCCESSFUL.
WE HAVE TO BE CONCERNED THAT THE
NORTH KOREANS DON'T SWITCH TO
OTHER CURRENCIES.
THE ONE CURRENCY WE CAN'T
CONTROL IS THE CHINESE CURRENCY.
>> GORDON CHANG FROM WASHINGTON.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: THERE'S BREAKING
NEWS FROM THE EARTHQUAKE IN
MEXICO.
MOMENTS AGO, WORD THAT THERE ARE
NO CHILDREN STILL ALIVE IN THAT
SCHOOL THAT COLLAPSED THERE
AFTER TUESDAY'S POWERFUL
EARTHQUAKE.
THAT CAME FROM THE MEXICAN NAVY.
EARLIER REPORTS HAD INDICATED
THAT UP TO SIX CHILDREN MIGHT BE
ALIVE IN THE RUBBLE.
THE ASSOCIATED PRESS QUOTING AN
OFFICIAL FROM THE MEXICAN NAVY
SAYS THERE MAY STILL BE AN ADULT
ALIVE IN THE WRECKAGE.
THEY BELIEVE THERE IS, BUT NO
CHILDREN.
THE PILE OF WRECKAGE SHIFTED
DRAMATICALLY THIS MORNING.
WORKERS HAVE BEEN TRYING TO PROP
IT UP WITH IRON BEAMS.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW MANY SETS OF
HUMAN REMAINS MAY BE UNDERNEATH.
A SEARCH AND RESCUE TEAM FROM
LOS ANGELES IN MEXICO TO HELP, A
PHOTO OF THEM HERE ON A CARGO
PLANE.
THE U.S. AMBASSADOR TO MEXICO
SAYS THEY HAVE EXPERTS AND TONS
OF EQUIPMENT.
MEXICAN OFFICIALS SAY SO FAR THE
QUAKE HAS KILLED 245 PEOPLE AND
INJURED MORE THAN 2,000.
OUR CHIEF CORRESPONDENT,
JONATHAN HUNT IS LIVE AT THE
SCHOOL.
JONATHAN?
>> SHEP, IT'S A VERY TENSE SCENE
HERE AT THE SCHOOL RIGHT NOW.
THE SCHOOL IS ABOUT 50 YARDS OR
SO BEHIND ME.
IT'S A HIVE OF ACTIVITY AND
REMAINS SO.
RUBBLE BEING BROUGHT OUT FROM
THE SCENE, LOADED ON TO THE
TRUCKS YOU CAN SEE HERE.
AS WE COME LEFT AND DOWN A BIT,
YOU CAN SEE THE SUPPLY TENTS.
THESE ARE SET UP TO SUPPORT THE
RESCUE WORKERS IN THEIR HUNDREDS
IF NOT THOUSANDS OF VOLUNTEER
CIVILIANS DOING WHAT THEY CAN DO
HELP IN THIS VERY INTENSE RESCUE
EFFORT, SHEP.
WE HAVE BEEN GETTING CONFLICTING
REPORTS ALL DAY AS YOU JUST
POINTED OUT ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
THERE MAY BE ANY SURVIVORS
UNDERNEATH THE RUBBLE OF THAT
SCHOOL AND WHETHER, IF THERE
ARE, THEY ARE CHILDREN OR
ADULTS.
THE LATEST AS YOU SAID FROM THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS, HEARING FROM
THE MEXICAN NAVY, WHICH IS ONE
OF THE INSTITUTIONS INVOLVED IN
THE RESCUE EFFORT, THAT THEY DO
NOT BELIEVE THERE ARE ANY
SURVIVING CHILDREN.
THEY DO BELIEVE THERE MAY BE AN
ADULT ALIVE.
WE HAVE HEARD DIRECTLY FROM OUR
SOURCES CLOSER IN TO THE SCHOOL
THAT A HEAT-SEEKING CAMERA HAS
PICKED UP A SIGNAL THAT MAY
INDICATE THAT THERE MAY BE
SOMEBODY ALIVE.
I WANT TO CAUTION EVEN WITH THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS HEARING THIS
FROM THE MEXICAN NAVY, THERE'S
SO MANY CONFLICTING REPORTS
FLOATING AROUND WHO MAY OR MAY
NOT BE ALIVE UNDERNEATH THAT
RUBBLE.
IT'S DIFFICULT TO TAKE ANYTHING
WITH ANY CERTA