THE OFFICER SNEAKING OUT AS HE
TRIED TO
BYSTANDERS TRIED TO HELP.
HE OPENED THE DOOR AND GOT THE
SNAKE OUT.
AMERICA'S NEWS HEADQUARTERS
SIGNING OFF.
I'M SANDRA SMITH.
HERE'S TRACE.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP PUSHING HIS
TAX PLAN AND MAKING BIG
PROMISES.
>> A GIANT BEFORE MASSIVE, THE
BIGGEST EVER IN OUR COUNTRY TAX
CUT.
>> BUT AFTER SETBACKS IN
CONGRESS ON HEALTHCARE, WILL
REPUBLICANS GET ANYTHING PASSED?
WHAT WOULD IT MEAN FOR YOU?
WE'LL TALK TO CHRIS WALLACE FROM
"FOX NEWS SUNDAY."
AND THE PRESIDENT PUSHING BACK
CLAIMS ON A SLOW RESPONSE IN
PUERTO RICO.
EVEN AS WE HEAR ABOUT NEW
STORIES ABOUT SUFFERINGFTER
THE DEADLY STORM.
GERALDO RIVERA IS LIVE.
AND A NEW WARNING FOR ANYBODY
THINKING ABOUT A TRIP TO CUBA.
AMERICANS GETTING SICK IN A
SERIES OF BIZARRE ATTACKS.
THE FEDS SAY THEY STILL DON'T
KNOW WHO IS TARGETING AMERICANS.
THAT'S AHEAD THIS HOUR ON
"SHEPARD SMITH REPORTING."
I'M TRACE GALLAGHER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP PRAISING THE NEW
TAX PLAN AND PRAISING THE
BIGGEST TAX CUT HISTORY.
HE ALSO PROMISED TO MAKE THE TAX
CODES SIMPLE, EASY AND FAIR AND
HE SAYS THE U.S. NEEDS TO
ENCOURAGE COMPANIES TO STAY IN
AMERICA.
>> ONE TEAM, ONE PEOPLE AND ONE
GREAT AMERICAN FAMILY.
THIS CAN BE REMEMBERED AS THE
MOMENT WE TOOK CONTROL OF OUR
DESTINY AND CHOSE A FUTURE OF
AMERICAN PATRIOTISM, PROSPERITY
AND PRIDE.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE AND
REPUBLICAN LEADERS HAVE RELEASED
A FRAME WORK FOR OVERHAULING THE
TAX CODE BUT STILL MISSING A FEW
DETAILS.
IT CALLS FOR DOUBLING THE AMOUNT
THAT ISN'T TAXED FOR $12,000 FOR
INDIVIDUALS AND $24,000 FOR
MARRIED COUPLES.
HE WOULD REDUCE THE NUMBER OF
TAX BRACKETS TO THREE, 12%, 25%
AND 35%.
STILL NO WORD ON WHAT INCOME
LEVELS FALL UNDER EACH BRACKET.
THE PLAN WOULD GET RID OF THE
ESTATE TAX, WHICH CRITICS CALL
THE DEATH TAX.
SOME DEMOCRATS SAY THE PLAN
DOESN'T DO ENOUGH FOR THE MIDDLE
CLASS.
SENATE MINORITY LEADER CHUCK
SCHUMER CALLED IT A SWEEPING TAX
CUT FOR MILLIONS AND
BILLIONAIRES.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS PLAN DOES NOT
BENEFIT THE WEALTHY.
JOHN ROBERTS IS LIVE FOR US AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
JOHN?
>> TRACE, GOOD AFTERNOON TO YOU.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN MAKING
THIS CASE FOR WEEKS NOW.
NOW HE HAS MORE MEAT ON THE BONE
IN TERMS OF WHAT YOU TALKED
ABOUT THERE.
THE ACTUAL PROPOSAL.
HE WAS TALKING ABOUT THE TAX CUT
ON INDIVIDUALS.
TODAY HE WENT TO THE NATIONAL
ASSOCIATION OF MANUFACTURERS IN
D.C. FOR THEIR CONVENTION AND
OUTLINED TO THEM WHAT ALL OF
THIS WOULD MEAN FOR
CORPORATIONS.
HERE'S WHAT IT WOULD MEAN.
THE PRESIDENT IS PROPOSING TO
CUT THE CORPORATE TAX FROM AN
AVERAGE OF 35% DOWN TO 20%.
THE SMALL BUSINESS TAX RATE AND
THIS WOULD INCLUDE S CORPS,
PASS-THROUGHS, SO
PROPRIETORSHIPS AND LLCS TO MAX
OUT AT 25% AND IMMEDIATE FULL
EXPENSES OF CAPITAL EXPENDITURES
FOR FIVE YEARS.
IF YOU WERE TO BUY A NEW TRUCK
OR EQUIPMENT OR A BACKHOE,
COMPUTERS, YOU CAN WRITE IT ALL
IMMEDIATELY AND DO THAT FOR A
PERIOD OF FIVE YEARS.
SO FOR COMPANIES THAT ARE TRYING
TO RETOOL OR EXPAND, THAT WOULD
BE AN ENORMOUS BOON FOR THEM.
HERE'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT SAID
IN TERMS OF WHAT HE WANTS THIS
TO DO FOR THE COUNTRY.
LISTEN HERE.
>> THIS IS A REVOLUTIONARY
CHANGE.
THE BIGGEST WINNERS WILL BE
EVERY DAY WORKING FAMILIES AS
JOBS START POURING INTO OUR
COUNTRY.
WHEN COMPANIES LEAVE OUR SHORES,
IT'S AMERICAN WORKERS THAT GET
HURT.
THEY GET FIRED.
WHEN COMPANIES STAY IN AMERICA
AND MOVE TO AMERICA, IT'S OUR
WONDERFUL WORKERS THAT REAP THE
BENEFITS AND THE REWARDS.
>> DEMOCRATS THOUGH DON'T LIKE
THIS PLAN TOO MUCH.
YOU MENTIONED CHUCK SCHUMER AT
THE TOP.
HE SAID CUTTING TAXES FOR THE
WEALTHIEST AMERICANS AND GIANT
CORPORATIONS LEADS TO BIGGER CEO
BONUSES, MORE STOCK BUY-BACKS
AND DIVIDENDS FOR SHAREHOLDERS,
NOT JOBS AND HIGHER WAGES.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS IF YOU MAKE
AMERICA A GOOD PLACE TO DO
BUSINESS, COMPANIES WILL STAY
HERE AS OPPOSED TO MOVING THEIR
MANUFACTURING PROCESSES OR
HEADQUARTERS OVERSEAS.
THAT WILL ATTRACT MORE
INVESTMENT FROM OVERSEAS AND
THAT WILL BENEFIT AMERICAN
WORKERS.
TRACE?
>> JOHN ROBERTS STAY WITH US FOR
A MOMENT IF YOU WOULD.
THE PRESIDENT CONTINUING TO
DEFEND HIS ADMINISTRATION'S
RESPONSE TO THE DEVASTATION IN
PUERTO RICO.
DURING HIS TAX EVENT, THE
PRESIDENT STARTED TALKING ABOUT
THE CRISIS AFFECTING MORE THAN
THREE MILLION AMERICANS.
HE SAYS THE U.S. WILL NOT REST
UNTIL THE PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO
ARE SAFE.
>> WE WANT TO TAKE IN A MASSIVE
FEDERAL MOBILIZATION TO ASSIST
PUERTO RICO.
NOW VIRTUALLY EVERYTHING HAS
BEEN WIPED OUT AND WE WILL HAVE
TO REALLY START ALL OVER AGAIN.
WE'RE LITERALLY STARTING FROM
SCRATCH.
>> PEOPLE IN THE U.S. TERRITORY
LIVING WITHOUT ELECTRICITY,
DRINKING WATER, FOOD AND MEDICAL
SUPPLIES.
SOME SAY THEY'RE STILL WAITING
FOR AID.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS THOUSANDS OF
TROOPS AND FEDERAL RELIEF
WORKERS ARE THERE.
HE ALSO SAYS THE U.S. IS SENDING
TRUCK DRIVERS TO HELP GET THE
SUPPLIES TO PEOPLE INLAND.
THE PRESIDENT POINTED OUT THIS
COMMENT FROM THE ISLAND'S
GOVERNOR THAT TOLD NEIL CAVUTO
THE PRESIDENT IS DOING WHAT HE
CAN.
>> HAS THE AMERICAN RESPONSE
BEEN SATISFACTORY TO YOU?
>> YES, IT HAS, NEIL.
I WANT TO CLARIFY THESE TWO
POINTS THAT SOMETIMES THAT SEEM
CONTRADICTORY.
NUMBER 1, WE DO NEED MORE AID
BUT THE PRESIDENT AND THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS DONE
EVERYTHING THAT THEY CAN, THAT
WE HAVE ASKED THEM TO DO AND
WE'VE GOTTEN THOSE RESULTS.
>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION ALSO
FACING BACKLASH OVER COMMENTS
FROM THE ACTING HOMELAND
SECURITY SECRETARY, ELAINE DUKE.
YESTERDAY TOLD REPORTERS THE
FEDERAL RELIEF EFFORT IS A GOOD
NEWS STORY.
THAT'S A QUOTE.
THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN CALLED THE
STATEMENT IRRESPONSIBLE.
SHE SAID IT'S A PEOPLE ARE DYING
STORY.
LET'S GET BACK TO JOHN ROBERTS
IN THE WHITE HOUSE.
JOHN?
>> AND THE ACTING DHS SECRETARY
WAS ASKED ABOUT THAT YESTERDAY,
TRACE.
SAYING THAT PEOPLE ON THE GROUND
THERE ARE SAYING THAT THEY'RE ON
THE VERGE OF A CATASTROPHE
THERE.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS THEY'RE
DOING EVERYTHING THEY CAN TO GET
AS MUCH AID TO PUERTO RICO AS
QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
THE BIG PROBLEM HAS NOT BEEN
CAPACITY TO GET GOODS AND
SERVICES THERE.
IT'S TO GET THEM FROM THE PORT
CITIES OUT TO THE AREAS OF THE
COUNTRY THAT HAVE BEEN SO HARD
HIT.
THEY SAY DEBRIS CLOGS THE
ROADWAYS.
OFTEN ONLY ONE WAY IN AND ONE
WAY OUT.
THE PRESIDENT AS HIS HELICOPTER
IS ARRIVING HERE KEEPS SAYING
THEY'RE DOING A GOOD JOB AND
GETTING GOOD REVIEWS.
THE PRESIDENT TWEETING GOVERNOR
ROSELLA SAID EVERY TIME WE HAVE
SPOKEN, THEY HAVE DELIVERED.
THE FACT IS THAT PUERTO RICO HAS
BEEN DESTROYED BY TWO
HURRICANES.
BIG DECISIONS WILL HAVE TO BE
MADE AS TO THE COST OF
REBUILDING.
FOR THE MOMENT IN TERMS OF
DEBRIS CLEARING, THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT IS PICKING UP 100% OF
THE COST.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT THERE
WILL NEED TO BE SOME DIFFICULT
CONVERSATIONS AHEAD TO FIGURE
OUT HOW AND WHO WILL PAY TO
BUILT PUERTO RICO.
LISTEN HERE.
>> ULTIMATELY, THE GOVERNMENT OF
PUERTO RICO WILL HAVE TO WORK
WITH US TO DETERMINE HOW THIS
MASSIVE REBUILDING EFFORT WILL
END UP BEING ONE OF THE BIGGEST
EVER, WILL BE FUNDED AND
ORGANIZED.
AND WHAT WE WILL DO WITH THE
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF EXISTING
DEBT ALREADY ON THE ISLAND.
WE WILL NOT REST, HOWEVER, UNTIL
THE PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO ARE
SAFE.
>> FLORIDA GOVERNOR RICK SCOTT
WAS HERE AWHILE AGO.
OF COURSE, HIS STATE WAS PICKING
UP FROM HURRICANE IRMA.
HE'S ALSO VERY MUCH INVOLVED
WITH HELPING OUT THE PEOPLE OF
PUERTO RICO.
HE SAID THE LOGISTICS FOR
HELPING OUT PUERTO RICO
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT FROM
FLORIDA OR FROM TEXAS.
BECAUSE IT'S AN ISLAND, VERY
MOUNTAINOUS WITH LIMITED ACCESS
TO MANY AREAS MEANS THERE'S MANY
PROBLEM THAT THEY DIDN'T DEAL
WITH IN EITHER FLORIDA, TEXAS OR
LOUISIANA.
HE REITERATED THIS IDEA THAT
THEY HAVE TO GET MORE PEOPLE IN
THERE AS WELL AND METHODS TO GET
THOSE SUPPLIES FROM THE PORT
CITIES OUT TO THE HARDEST HIT
AREAS.
LISTEN TO RICK SCOTT HERE.
>> I TALKED TO THE PRESIDENT
ABOUT IT.
I TOLD HIM, OF COURSE, THE
BIGGEST ISSUE RIGHT NOW IN
PUERTO RICO IS WE NEED MORE
TRUCK DRIVERS AND WE NEED MORE
TRUCKS.
WE HAVE TO GET EVERYTHING OUT OF
THE PORT, WHETHER IT'S THE FUEL,
THE WATER.
THE BIGGEST THING IS THE FUEL.
THEIR ISSUE IS DIFFERENT FROM
FLORIDA.
WE HAD A PROBLEM OF GETTING FUEL
IN TO THE PORTS.
THEY HAD THE FUEL.
THEY HAVE TO GET IT OUT OF THE
PORTS.
>> AGAIN, THE PROBLEM IS GETTING
STUFF OUT OF THE PORTS.
THE U.S. SENATE IS GOING TO HAVE
ITS CHANCE TO WEIGH-IN ON THIS.
THEY'LL BE MEETING WITH THE FEMA
ADMINISTRATOR, BROCK LONG
MONDAY.
SEE HOW THAT GOES, TRACE.
>> YEAH, THEY HAD A LOT OF
VOLUNTEERS IN TEXAS AND FLORIDA.
VERY FEW IN PUERTO RICO BECAUSE
EVERYBODY IS AFFECTED.
JOHN ROBERTS, LIVE FOR US.
THANK YOU.
MORE NOW ON HOW THE U.S.
MILITARY IS RESPONDING TO THE
CRISIS IN PUERTO RICO.
DEFENSE OFFICIALS SAY THEY'RE
PUTTING A THREE-STAR ARMY
GENERAL IN CHARGE OF THE
RECOVERY EFFORT.
LUCAS TOMLINSON IS LIVE AT THE
PENTAGON.
LUCAS?
>> GOOD AFTERNOON, TRACE.
ABOUT TWO HOURS AGO, THE
HOSPITAL SHIP COMFORT SET SAIL
FROM MORE FOLK AND WILL ARRIVE
IN PUERTO RICO TUESDAY.
>> MY ORDERS ARE A MINIMUM OF 30
DAYS.
YOU KNOW, AGAIN, THOSE ARE
DECISIONS THAT ARE MADE MUCH
ABOVE OUR LEVEL.
WHAT WE'LL DO IS WE'LL GO OUT
THERE AND HIT THE GROUND RUNNING
OR HIT THE DECK PLATES RAINING
AS WE SAY IN THE NAVY AND WE'LL
KEEP MOVING UNTIL SOMEBODY TELLS
US THAT WE'RE NO LONGER NEEDED.
>> SOME CRITICS SAID THE SHIP
WOULD HAVE LEFT SOONER BUT
CAPTAIN ROBINSON SAID TWO DAYS
AGO, THERE WERE LESS THAN 100
PEOPLE ON BOARD.
NOW THERE'S OVER 800 DOCTORS AND
CREW.
THE COMFORT DEPLOYED TO SOUTH
AMERICA AND TREATED OVER 120,000
PEOPLE.
THE SHIP HAS SIX EMERGENCY ROOMS
AND HUNDREDS OF BEDS.
TODAY THE U.S. MILITARY SAYS ONE
HOSPITAL IN PUERTO RICO IS FULLY
FUNCTIONAL.
NOW THE ARMY CORPS OF ENGINEERS
HAS COMPLETED A DAMAGE
ASSESSMENT ON THE MAIN DAM AND
HAS ISSUED A FLASH FLOOD WATCH
BECAUSE ANOTHER 1-3 INCHES OF
RAIN IS EXPECTED THIS WEEKEND.
THE PENTAGON PLACED JEFFERY
BUCHANAN, A THREE-STAR GENERAL
IN PUERTO RICO.
HE ARRIVED YESTERDAY.
HIS DEPUTY, RICHARD KIM ARRIVED
TO ESTABLISH A HEADQUARTERS.
THEY WILL FOCUS ON LOGISTICS,
MUDSLIDES AND FAILING
STRUCTURES.
A SHORT TIME AGO I HEARD FROM AN
OFFICER FROM THE 35th ARMY
SIGNALS BATTALION IN PUERTO RICO
AND HELPING SET UP SATELLITE
COMMUNICATIONS WHICH HAVE ALSO
BEEN HAMPERED ON THE ISLAND.
TRACE?
>> YEAH, THEY NEED THOSE CELL
TOWERS AND COMMUNICATIONS.
LUCAS TOMLINSON LIVE AT THE
PENTAGON.
AHEAD, WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THE
PUERTO RICAN DISASTER RESPONSE
AND THE PRESIDENT'S TAX PLAN.
WILL HE HAVE BETTER LUCK GETTING
THAT THROUGH CONGRESS THAN HE
DID WITH HEALTHCARE?
"FOX NEWS SUNDAY" ANCHOR CHRIS
WALLACE JOINS US LIVE NEXT.
lder.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
♪ The sun'll come out
tomorrow... ♪
For people with Heart Failure,
tomorrow is not a given.
But ENTRESTO is a medicine
that helps make more
tomorrows possible.
♪ Tomorrow, tomorrow... ♪
♪ I love ya, tomorrow ♪
In the largest Heart Failure
study ever,
ENTRESTO helped
more people stay alive
and out of the hospital
than a leading Heart Failure
medicine.
Women who are pregnant
must not take ENTRESTO.
It can cause harm or death
to an unborn baby.
Don't take ENTRESTO
with an ACE inhibitor
or aliskiren.
If you've had angioedema
while taking an ACE
or ARB medicine,
don't take ENTRESTO.
The most serious side effects
are angioedema,
low blood pressure...
...kidney problems,
or high potassium in your blood.
♪ Tomorrow, tomorrow I love
ya, tomorrow ♪
Ask your heart doctor
about ENTRESTO.
And help make tomorrow possible.
♪ You're only a day away. ♪
Remember that accident I got in
with the pole, and I
had to make a claim
and all that?
Is that whole thing
still dragging on?
No, I took some pics
with the app and...
filed a claim, but...
You know how they send you
money to cover repairs and...
They took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid
right away, but...
at the very end of
it all, my agent...
Wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy.
But if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience
for any reason,
they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim Satisfaction
Guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
REPUBLICAN LAWMAKERS SAY THEY'RE
FOCUSES ON THEIR TAX PLAN AFTER
THE SENATE FAILED TO PASS OF
HEALTHCARE BILL.
PAUL RYAN SAID IT WAS
FRUSTRATING.
SO WILL THEY HAVE BETTER LUCK
WITH TAXES THAN HEALTHCARE?
LET'S BRING IN "FOX NEWS SUNDAY"
ANCHOR CHRIS WALLACE.
GREAT TO SEE YOU, CHRIS.
IT'S FUNNY.
A LOT OF THIS STUFF IS MARKETING
WHEN IT COMES TO POLITICS.
DID LAUGH WHEN GARY COHN, THE
WHITE HOUSE ECONOMIC ADVISER WAS
AT THE PRESS BRIEFING SAYING THE
AVERAGE RETURN FOR MIDDLE CLASS
AMERICANS WILL BE ABOUT $1,000.
SO YOU CAN REMODEL YOUR KITCHEN.
THE INTERNET WENT CRAZY AND
SAID, YOU KNOW, $1,000?
HAS HE WATCHED HGTV?
YOU CAN'T EVEN BUY A DISHWASHER
FOR $1,000.
GIVES YOU THAT, YOU KNOW, NOTION
THEY'RE HAVING A TOUGH TIME
MARKETING HOW TO REALLY GET THIS
TAX PLAN, YOU KNOW, TO THE HEART
OF THE MATTER AND GET IT SOLD TO
PEOPLE.
>> YEAH, A COUPLE THINGS GARY
COHN SAID.
HE ALSO SAID THE AVERAGE MIDDLE
INCOME FAMILY MAKES $100,000.
I WAS STUNNED BY THAT.
THE MEDIAN INCOME FAMILY IN THIS
COUNTRY MAKES $55,000.
SO AGAIN, IT RAISES QUESTIONS AS
TO WHETHER OR NOT THE WHITE
HOUSE UNDERSTANDS.
LET ME SAY, IF HE HAS A GUY TO
DO A KITCHEN FOR $1,000, I WANT
THAT CONTRACTOR RIGHT AWAY.
THEY'LL HAVE A TOUGH TIME WITH
THIS.
EVERYBODY SAYS WELL, TAX REFORM
IS EASIER BECAUSE THAT'S THE
REPUBLICAN MONTRA.
TAX CUTS.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE SIZABLE TAX
CUTS HERE.
LET ME GIVE YOU ONE EXAMPLE.
ONE OF THE WAYS IN WHICH THE
ADMINISTRATION WANTS TO PAY FOR
WHAT WILL BE ABOUT A $5 TRILLION
CUT IN REVENUE OVER THE NEXT TEN
YEARS IS BY DOING AWAY WITH THE
DEDUCTION THAT PEOPLE GET FOR
PAYING YOUR STATE AND LOCAL
TAXES.
FOLKS IN HIGH TAX STATES LIKE
CALIFORNIA OR NEW YORK OR A
BUNCH OF OTHER STATES, THEY
DON'T LIKE THAT BECAUSE OF THE
FACT THAT IT MEANS THAT THAT'S A
DEDUCTION THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
GET.
NOW, THERE'S 33 REPUBLICANS
REPRESENTING THOSE HIGH TAX
STATES.
THE REPUBLICANS COULD ONLY
AFFORD IN THE HOUSE TO LOSE 22.
SO THIS MEANS THE HIGH TAX STATE
REPUBLICANS OBVIOUSLY A LOT OF
THEM ARE BLUE STATES THAT MOSTLY
HAVE DEMOCRATS, BUT THERE'S SOME
REPUBLICANS, THEIR VOTERS WILL
LOSE A BIG AND IMPORTANT TAX
DEDUCTION.
THEY'RE CONCERNED.
THEY'LL WANT EITHER SOMETHING IN
COMPENSATION FOR THAT OR TO HAVE
THAT PULLED BACK.
THAT IS A TRILLION DOLLARS OF
ADDED REVENUE TO THE GOVERNMENT
ENDING THAT DEDUCTION.
YOU TAKE THAT AWAY, THIS BECOMES
AN EVEN BIGGER LOSS TO THE
TREASURY.
>> Trace: WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF
PAUL RYAN'S RANT WHERE HE'S
SAYING THERE'S NOT ENOUGH STUFF
GETTING DONE.
HE SAID THE 274 BILLS AS OF
SEPTEMBER 22 HAVE PASSED THE
HOUSE AND NOT GETTING THE SAME
IN THE SENATE.
HE'S SAYING THEY NEED TO DO
MORE.
IS IT A FAIR ASSESSMENT OR
SAYING THE HOUSE IS PASSING
THESE THINGS KNOWING THE SENATE
WILL FIX THEM, SO IT'S NOT
REALLY FAIR TO LAY IT ON THE
SENATE?
IS THAT FAIR FROM PAUL RYAN --
>> HE'S CLEARLY RIGHT.
THEY ARE PASSING A LOT OF THINGS
IN THE HOUSE.
THEY'RE GETTING BOTTLED UP OR
NOT PASSED OR DEFEATED IN THE
SENATE.
BUT HAVING SAID THAT, THE HOUSE
AND THE SENATE ARE TWO DIFFERENT
BODIES WITH TWO DIFFERENT SETS
OF RULES.
FIRST OF ALL, EXCEPT FOR BUDGET
RECONCILIATION AND MOST FOLKS
KNOW BY NOW THAT THAT IS ONE
BILL A YEAR THAT YOU CAN PASS
WITH 51 VOTES, YOU NEED A SUPER
MAJORITY, 60 VOTES, BECAUSE THEY
CAN THREATEN THE FILIBUSTER TO
STOP IT.
SO THE RULES ARE DIFFERENT.
THERE'S DIFFERENT BALANCE OF
POWER.
THEY HAVE A 22-VOTE MAJORITY IN
THE HOUSE.
THE REPUBLICANS DO.
THEY HAVE A TWO-VOTE MAJORITY IN
THE SENATE.
THE MARGIN FOR ERROR IS MUCH
SMALLER IN THE SENATE.
WE SAW THAT WITH THE OBAMACARE
DEFEAT.
IT'S NOT THAT MITCH McCONNELL
AND THE SENATORS ARE SITTING ON
THEIR HANDS.
THEY HAVE DIFFERENT RULES AND
THEY HAVE A MUCH MORE NARROW
MAJORITY.
AS A RESULT, RYAN IS RIGHT.
MUCH LESS IS GETTING PASSED IN
THE SENATE.
>> YOU KNOW, BELOW YOU, CHRIS,
THERE'S A PROMOTION FOR SEAN
HANNITY.
RUSH LIMBAUGH WAS ON
LAST NIGHT
AND AGAIN TONIGHT.
HE SAYS IF THE REPUBLICANS WOULD
COME TOGETHER FOR THREE MONTHS
AND STAND BEHIND THE PRESIDENT
AND GET BEHIND HIS BILLS, THEY
WOULD ACTUALLY OWN POLITICS FOR
THE NEXT TWO DECADES.
NEWT GINGRICH CAME ON LATER AND
AGREED WITH THAT.
WHAT IS YOUR ASSESSMENT OF THAT
TAKE?
>> AGAIN, THAT'S ONLY FOR THE
BUDGETS RECONCILIATION MATTERS.
EVERYTHING ELSE IN THE SENATE,
THEY CAN'T PASS WITH JUST
REPUBLICAN VOTES IN THE SENATE.
THEY NEED EIGHT DEMOCRATS.
THEY GOT 52 REPUBLICANS, THEY
NEED EIGHT DEMOCRATS.
BUT YOU COULD ARGUE IN THE CASE
OF OBAMACARE REPEAL AND REPLACE
AND IF THEY CAN PASS A BUDGET
RESOLUTION IN THE CASE OF TAX
REFORM, IF THEY GOT TOGETHER,
THEY COULD GET THINGS DONE AND
PUSH THE TRUMP AGENDA.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT WE'VE SEEN
THIS IN OBAMACARE, I THINK WE'LL
SEE IT IN TAX REFORM AS WELL,
THERE'S NOT ONE REPUBLICAN
PARTY.
THERE'S A HUGE SPLIT IN THE
WE SAW THAT IN 2010 WHEN YOU HAD
THE TEA PARTIERS WIN, HUGE
VICTORY FOR REPUBLICANS BUT THEY
DIDN'T HAVE TO GOVERN.
THEY WERE RUNNING AGAINST THE
PRESIDENT WHO WOULD VETO A LOT
OF THEIR MEASURES.
NOW THEY HAVE TO GOVERN.
SO THE SPLITS THAT WERE COVERED
UP, NOW WITH THE REPUBLICAN
PRESIDENT WE CAN SEE THERE
THEY'RE.
THEY'RE THERE BIG TIME ON
HEALTHCARE AND SEE IT TO SOME
DEGREE ON TAX REFORM AS WELL.
GOVERNING IS A LOT TOUGHER THAN
JUST BEING AGAINST AND OPPOSING.
>> Trace: YEAH.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ON SOCIAL MEDIA
MADE THAT POINT TO NEWT
GINGRICH.
THANKS, CHRIS.
>> THANK YOU, TRACE.
>> Trace: THIS WEEKEND ON "FOX
NEWS SUNDAY," CHRIS WILL HAVE
THE LATEST ON THE DISASTER
RESPONSE IN PUERTO RICO WITH
FEMA ADMINISTRATOR BROCK LONG.
HE WILL TALK ABOUT THE TAX PLAN
WITH MICK MULVANEY.
THAT'S THIS SUNDAY ON YOUR LOCAL
FOX STATION AND A SPECIAL TIME
AT 8:00 A.M. EASTERN.
THAT'S BECAUSE OF FOOTBALL.
IT WILL REPLAY ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL LATER IN THE DAY.
DON'T TRAVEL TO CUBA.
THAT'S THE WARNING FROM THE
STATE DEPARTMENT.
THEY'RE ALSO PULLING HALF OF
THEIR STAFF OUT OF HAVANA.
THAT STORY NEXT.
>> Trace: THE U.S. IS PULLING
DIPLOMATS AND THEIR FAMILIES OUT
OF CUBA AFTER MYSTERIOUS SONIC
ATTACKS AGAINST AMERICANS ON THE
ISLAND.
THAT'S WHAT A STATE DEPARTMENT
OFFICIAL CONFIRMS TO FOX NEWS.
THE ASSOCIATED PRESS REPORTED
THE STATE DEPARTMENT ORDERED
MORE THAN HALF OF ITS STAFFERS
TO LEAVE THE UNITED STATES.
THE U.S. IS WARNING AGAINST
TRAVELLING TO CUBA.
INVESTIGATORS SAY 21 AMERICAN
DIPLOMATS AND FAMILY MEMBERS
HAVE COME DOWN WITH A STRANGE
DISEASE OR SYMPTOMS INCLUDING
BRAIN DAMAGE, HEARING LOSS AND
CONCUSSIONS.
ACCORDING TO A.P., ONE VICTIM
DESCRIBED WAKING UP IN A HOTEL
ROOM TO A BLARING NOISE THAT
WENT AWAY WHEN HE GOT OUT OF
BID.
WHEN FBI AGENTS SEARCHED HOTEL
ROOMS, THEY SAID THEY COULDN'T
FIND ANY DEVICES.
CUBAN OFFICIALS HAVE INSISTED
THEY HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
INCIDENTS.
JOSH LEDERMAN IS A FOREIGN
AFFAIRS REPORTER THAT COVERS
NATIONAL SECURITY FOR THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS.
HE CO-WROTE TODAY'S ARTICLE ON
THE U.S. PULLING DIPLOMATS OUT
OF CUBA.
JOSH, GREAT TO SEE YOU.
YOU LOOK AT THE RELATIONS
BETWEEN CUBA AND THE UNITED
STATES AND RIGHT NOW THEY'RE
PAPER THIN AND THIS IS NOT ABOUT
TO HELP.
>> THEY WERE DELL CUT TO BEGIN
WITH FOR SURE.
THIS WILL MAKE IT HARDER FOR
THAT WARMING OF RELATIONS THAT
TOOK FORM IN 2015 TO CONTINUE.
CUBA SPENT THE LAST COUPLE WEEKS
PLEADING WITH THE UNITED STATES
NOT TO DO WHAT IT DID TODAY.
SAYING DON'T BE HASTY.
YOU HAVE NO EVIDENCE THIS WAS
UNITED STATES.
THE U.S. DECIDED TODAY THAT YES,
THAT'S TRUE.
THE U.S. ISN'T POINTING THE
FINGER AT CUBA BUT CUBA HAS BEEN
UNABLE TO ASSURE THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT THAT DIPLOMATS ARE
SAFE ON CUBAN SOIL AND THE U.S.
HAS TO TAKE SIGNIFICANT ACTIONS
TO PROTECT NOT ONLY AMERICAN
DIPLOMATS BUT TOURISTS THAT
COULD BE HARMED BY THIS.
>> SURE.
THEY'RE EXTRAPOLATING SAYING
IT'S NOT JUST THE U.S. ENVOYS.
IF YOU TRAVEL TO CUBA AND YOU'RE
IN HAVANA, THEN, YOU KNOW, YOU
HAVE THE SAME RISK.
AND THE QUESTION BECOMES IF YOU
LOOK AT CUBA'S RESPONSE AND I
KNOW THEY'RE DENYING THIS, JOSH,
BUT THERE'S NOT THIS ALL HANDS
ON DECK MENTALITY TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF WHO IS RESPONSIBLE FOR
THESE ATTACKS.
>> WELL, THE U.S. HAS ACTUALLY
PRAISED CUBA'S WELLINGNESS TO
INVESTIGATE THIS.
MANY OFFICIALS FLIED DOWN TO
HAVANA TO DO SOME SEARCHES WHAT
THE CUBANS HAVE NOT BEEN ABLE TO
DO IS GET TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS
AND SAY IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
IT'S CONSIDERED THE
RESPONSIBILITY OF A HOST COUNTRY
TO PROTECT DIPLOMATS, MAKE IT A
HOSPITABLE ENVIRONMENT AND IN
THE ABSENCE OF CUBA BEING ABLE
TO SAY WE ARE NOT GOING TO BE
EXPERIENCING THESE THINGS
HAPPENING TO AMERICAN DIPLOMATS
IN THE FUTURE, THE U.S. HAS SAID
THIS IS NOT SUFFICIENT.
>> Trace: YEAH, PROTECT
DIPLOMATS AND TOURISTS.
LOOK AT THE ANALOGY OF MEXICO.
MANY SAY THERE'S CORRUPTION DOWN
THERE.
BUT WHEN SOMETHING HAPPENS IN A
TOURIST PART OF THE COUNTRY,
THEY'RE ALL OVER IT.
IF WORD GETS OUT THAT MEXICO IS
NOT SAFE, THE TOURISM INDUSTRY
GOES CAPUT.
AND NOW THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING.
MAYBE IT'S NOT SAFE IN CUBA AND
CUBA CAN'T -- ALL THEY'RE
TRYING, THEY CAN'T GET A HANDLE
ON WHO IS BEHIND THIS.
>> CERTAINLY POTENTIAL EFFECTS
ON THE TOURISM INDUSTRY IN
HAVANA, WHICH IS A LIFE LINE FOR
THE CUBAN ECONOMY COULD BE
IMMENSE.
I WOULDN'T RUSH TO SAY THAT CUBA
ISN'T DOING THINGS THAT THEY
SHOULD BE DOING TO INVESTIGATE
THIS.
WE HAVE TO KEEP IN MIND, THE
BEST U.S. LAW ENFORCEMENT
INTELLIGENCE, THE TOP PEOPLE
THAT INVESTIGATE THESE CRIMES
FOR THE UNITED STATES HAVE NOT
BEEN ABLE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT'S
GOING ON.
SO IF THE U.S. CAN'T FIGURE IT
OUT, IT MAKES SENSE THAT THIS IS
SO PERPLEXING THAT IT'S BEEN
DIFFICULT FOR THE CUBANS TO GET
A HANDLE ON AS WELL.
>> Trace: THAT'S A FAIR
ASSESSMENT, JOSH.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> THANKS A LOT.
>> Trace: WELL, NO MATTER HOW
BAD THE ECONOMY TANKED IN PUERTO
RICO, THE ISLAND'S AGRICULTURE
INDUSTRY HAD BEEN A BRIGHT SPOT
UNTIL NOW.
HURRICANE MARIA STRIPPING
FIELDS, KILLING LIVESTOCK AND
LEADING FARMERS AND THEIR
FAMILIES FACING A VERY UNCERTAIN
FUTURE.
WE'RE LIVE ON THE GROUND IN
SAN JUAN COMING UP.