UNEMPLOYMENT RATE HAS DROPPED
AND WORK FORCE IS AT A 3 1/2
YEAR HIGH.
THIS UNDERSCORES THE NEED FOR
CONGRESS TO WORK WITH US TO GROW
THE ECONOMY AND CREATE JOBS.
THE IMPORTANCE OF PASSING TAX
RELIEF FOR AMERICAN WORKERS AND
BUSINESS CANNOT BE OVERSTATED.
WE HAVE A ONCE IN A GENERATION
OPPORTUNITY TO CREATE A TAX CODE
THAT IS SIMPLE, FAIR AND EASY TO
UNDERSTAND.
THAT MEANS GETTING RID OF THE
LOOP HOLES THAT BENEFIT THE
WEALTHIEST AMERICANS AND
LOWERING TAXES ON THE MIDDLE
AMERICANS AND BUY THE GREAT
PRODUCTS MADE BY AMERICAN
MANUFACTURERS.
TODAY THE PRESIDENT SIGNED A
PROCLAMATION DECLARING OCTOBER 6
NATIONAL MANUFACTURING DAY.
THIS HONORS THE MEN AND WOMEN
THAT CREATE THE PRODUCTS THAT
POWER OUR COMMUNITIES, IMPROVE
OUR LIVES AND DEFEND OUR NATION.
THE PEOPLE WHO HAS THE PRESIDENT
SAYS BELIEVE IN THOSE BEAUTIFUL
WORDS "MADE IN THE U.S.A."
IN ADDITION TO THE 14 WORKERS
THE PRESIDENT HOSTED IN THE OVAL
OFFICE DURING TODAY'S
PROCLAMATION SIGNING, MORE THAN
500,000 PEOPLE AROUND THE
COUNTRY ARE PARTICIPATING IN
THOUSANDS OF EVENTS RELATED TO
MANUFACTURING DAY.
AMONG THEM, NUMEROUS MEMBERS OF
THE PRESIDENT'S CABINET AND
OTHER SENIOR OFFICIALS.
OUR TAX PLAN WOULD LEAD TO A
GREAT MANUFACTURING BOON.
WE WOULD CUT TAXES ON BUSINESSES
OF ALL SIZES AND RESTORE THEIR
COMPETITIVE EDGE TO CREATE MORE
JOBS AND HIGHER WAGES FOR OUR
WORKERS.
OUR PLAN WOULD ALLOW THEM TO
BRING BACK TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS
OVERSEAS.
THE PRESIDENT WILL BE BACK OUT
ON THE ROAD BUILDING SUPPORT FOR
THIS PLAN, WHICH IS REALLY A
JOBS BILL.
HE WILL BE IN PENNSYLVANIA
MONDAY AND WE'LL HAVE MORE
DETAILS COMING SOON.
WITH THAT, WE'LL KICKOFF FRIDAY
WITH QUESTIONS.
WE'LL START NOW IS.
KIND OF FUN.
WE SHOULD DO THIS MORE OFTEN AND
NOT JUST SAVE IT FOR FRIDAYS.
JOHN DECKER.
>> THANK YOU, SARAH.
THE BODY OF ANOTHER U.S. SOLDIER
HAS JUST BEEN DISCOVERED BY
LOCAL FORCES IN NIGER WHICH
BRINGS TO FOUR THE TOTAL NUMBER
OF GREEN BERETS THAT WERE KILLED
WEDNESDAY IN NIGER.
SO FAR THERE'S NO RESPONSE TO
THIS BY THE PRESIDENT, NO TWEET
FROM THE PRESIDENT, NO STATEMENT
FROM THE PRESIDENT.
CAN WE EXPECT SOME SORT OF
REPRISAL BY THE U.S. MILITARY IN
NIGER AS RELATES TO WHAT
HAPPENED WEDNESDAY?
>> I MADE A STATEMENT ON BEHALF
OF THE ADMINISTRATION YESTERDAY
IN THE OPENING.
OBVIOUSLY ANY TIME ONE OF THE
MEMBERS OF OUR GREAT MILITARY
ARE INJURED, WOUNDED OR KILLED
IN ACTION, THAT IT'S CERTAINLY
SOMETHING THAT WE TAKE VERY
SERIOUSLY.
OUR THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS ARE
WITH THOSE INDIVIDUALS.
WE'RE CONTINUING TO REVIEW AND
LOOK INTO THIS.
AS WE HAVE MORE DETAILS, WE'LL
LET YOU KNOW.
CECILIA?
>> CAN YOU CLARIFY THE
PRESIDENT'S COMMENTS?
WAS HE REFERRING TO MILITARY
ACTION WHEN HE SAID "CALM BEFORE
THE STORM?"
>> AS WE SAID MANY TIMES BEFORE,
THE PRESIDENT HAS AS I HAVE FROM
THIS PODIUM ON QUITE A FEW
OCCASIONS, WE'RE NEVER GOING TO
SAY IN ADVANCE WHAT THE
PRESIDENT WILL DO.
AS HE SAID LAST NIGHT IN
ADDITION TO THE COMMENTS, YOU'LL
HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE.
>> HOW SERIOUSLY SHOULD AMERICAN
ADVERSARIES FOR THAT MATTER TAKE
THESE COMMENTS?
>> I THINK YOU CAN TAKE THE
PRESIDENT PROTECTING THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE ALWAYS EXTREMELY
SERIOUS.
HE'S BEEN VERY CLEAR THAT THAT'S
HIS NUMBER 1 PRIORITY.
IF HE FEELS THAT ACTION IS
NECESSARY, HE WILL TAKE IT.
STEVE?
>> WHEN THE PRESIDENT SAID HE
WANTS HIS MILITARY LEADERS TO
GIVE THEM MILITARY OPTIONS
FASTER, DOES HE FEELS LIKE
THEY'RE INTENTIONALLY
SLOW-WALKING THESE OPTIONS TO
HIM?
>> NO, NOT AT ALL.
AS YOU KNOW, HE'S A PERSON THAT
LIKES TO TAKE ACTION AND TAKE IT
QUICKLY.
I DON'T THINK YOU SHOULD READ
INTO ANYTHING BEYOND THAT.
HE WANTS OPTIONS ON THE TABLE SO
HE CAN MAKE QUICK DECISIONS.
>> IS THAT A GENERAL COMMENT OR
DID HE MEAN A SPECIFIC COUNTRY?
>> A GENERAL COMMENT.
NOTHING SPECIFIC THAT WAS IN
REFERENCE TO.
>> I HAVE TWO QUESTIONS.
ONE ON THE SOLDIER THAT WAS
KILLED IN NIGER AND THE OTHER ON
DACA.
WHEN WAS THE PRESIDENT MADE
AWARE THERE WAS A FOURTH SOLDIER
MISSING IN ACTION?
WHEN DID HE BECOME AWARE THAT
THAT SOLDIER HAD BEEN KILLED AND
DISCOVERED BY LOCAL FORCES?
>> I BELIEVE THE NOTIFICATION
WAS YESTERDAY.
I'D HAVE TO GET CLARIFICATION ON
THE SPECIFIC TIMING OF WHEN THAT
TOOK PLACE.
>> WHEN WAS THE PRESIDENT MADE
AWARE THAT THAT SOLDIER'S BODY
WAS FOUND?
AGAIN, I KNOW THAT IT WAS PRETTY
SOON AFTER THAT HAD BEEN
DISCOVERED.
AS FAR AS AN EXACT TIME, I CAN'T
GIVE YOU THAT.
I KNOW CHIEF KELLY KEPT HIM
UPDATED ON THAT SITUATION AS IT
EVOLVED.
>> AND ON DACA, THE PRESIDENT
WELCOMED HISPANIC AMERICAN
LEADERS TO THE WHITE HOUSE.
HE DID NOT MENTION HIS POSITION
TO END DACA DURING HIS REMARKS
THERE.
HE DID NOT RENEW HIS CALL FOR
CONGRESS TO PROTECT THOSE THAT
WILL BE VULNERABLE FOR
DEPORTATION IN MARCH.
WHY DID HE NOT BRING THAT UP?
>> LOOK, HE'S BEEN CLEAR.
THERE'S NO REASON TO CONTINUE TO
REITERATE THE SAME POSITION THAT
HE'S HELD.
HE CALLED ON CONGRESS TO ACT ON
IT.
YOU CAN EXPECT IN THE COMING
DAYS THAT HE WILL LAY OUT HIS
RESPONSIBLE IMMIGRATION REFORM.
YOU CAN COUNT ON THAT TO HAPPEN
VERY SOON.
THAT'S ALL PART OF THE PROCESS
MOVING FORWARD.
HE HASN'T BEEN UNCLEAR ABOUT
WHAT HIS POSITION IS ON THAT
FRONT.
APRIL?
>> SARAH, GOING BACK TO THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM, WHEN THE
PRESIDENT DEALS WITH WORLD
MATTERS LIKE THIS, ALL OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE.
HAS THIS WHITE HOUSE EXHAUSTED
DIPLOMACY?
FOR HIM TO SAY THE CALM BEFORE
THE STORM, LISTENING TO WHAT HE
HAD TO SAY.
>> WE'RE CONTINUING TO PUT
MAXIMUM ECONOMIC AND DIPLOMATIC
PRESSURE ON COUNTRIES LIKE NORTH
KOREA.
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO DO
THAT.
AT THE SAME TIME, THE PRESIDENT
WILL KEEP ALL OF HIS OPTIONS ON
THE TABLE.
OUR POSITION HAS NOT CHANGED.
IT'S BEEN VERY CONSISTENT.
>> IS NORTH KOREA THE STORM?
>> THAT'S AN EXAMPLE.
WE HAVE A LOT OF BAD ACTORS.
NORTH KOREA, IRAN.
SEVERAL EXAMPLE THERE'S.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT THE
CONTRACEPTION WAIVER.
THE ACLU ANNOUNCED A LAWSUIT.
THEY SAID THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS PAYING FOR
WOMEN TO PAY FOR THEIR RELIGIOUS
BELIEFS.
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT CANNOT
AUTHORIZE DISCRIMINATION IN THE
NAME OF RELIGION OR OTHERWISE.
WHAT IS YOUR RESPONSE?
>> I WOULD NEVER GET THE ACLU TO
TAKE ANY OF MY TALKING POINTS.
THE PRESIDENT BELIEVES THE
REASON TO PRACTICE ONE'S FAITH
IS A FUNDAMENTAL RIGHT IN THIS
COUNTRY.
THAT'S ALL TODAY WAS ABOUT.
OUR FEDERAL GOVERNMENT SHOULD
PROTECT THAT RIGHT.
AS LONG AS DONALD TRUMP IS
PRESIDENT, HE WILL.
>> FOR THE ACLU, WHAT WOULD YOU
SAY TO THE WOMEN OUT THERE OR
THE FAMILIES OUT THERE THAT NOW
HAVE TO PAY MORE OUT OF THEIR
POCKET TO GET CONTRACEPTION
COVERAGE THAT THEY CHOOSE AND
THAT THEY DESIRE?
>> THIS IS A PRESIDENT THAT
SUPPORTS THE FIRST AMENDMENT,
SUPPORTS THE FREEDOM OF
RELIGION.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHY THAT
SHOULD BE AN ISSUE.
THE SUPREME COURT HAS VALIDATED
THIS DECISION ON MANY TIMES
OVER.
THE PRESIDENT IS SOMEBODY THAT
BELIEVES IN THE CONSTITUTION.
IF PEOPLE DON'T LIKE WHAT THE
CONSTITUTION SAYS, TALK TO
CONGRESS ABOUT CHANGING IT.
>> GIVEN THE LAWSUITS THAT THE
ACLU HAS FIRED, IS THE
ADMINISTRATION PREPARED TO
DEFENSE THIS CONTRACEPTION
MANDATE BACK TO THE SUPREME
COURT IF NEED BE?
>> THE SUPREME COURT MADE CLEAR
WHAT THE POSITION IS.
IT SUPPORT WHAT'S THIS
ADMINISTRATION HAS DONE.
>> BUT THIS WILL BE A LEGAL
FIGHT --
>> IF IT DOES, IT SHOWS THAT
THIS STRAIGHT IS ON THE RIGHT
SIDE OF THE LAW.
>> AND ON THE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM ISSUE.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO
PRESERVE --
>> AS LONG AS YOU DON'T ASK THE
SAME QUESTION.
>> IT'S A FOLLOW UP.
YOU SAID THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO
PRESERVE AN ELEMENT OF SURPRISE.
IF HE WANTS TO PRESERVE AN
ELEMENT OF SURPRISE, WHY WOULD
HE DANGLE HINTS ABOUT HIS
ACTIONS IN THE FIRST PLACE.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE HE DID.
HE DIDN'T TALK ABOUT ANY
SPECIFIC ACTIONS AT ALL.
MATTHEW?
>> TWO QUESTIONS.
FIRST FOLLOWING UP ON THE HHS
CHANGE.
DOES THE WHITE HOUSE HAVE ANY
ESTIMATES OF HOW MANY PEOPLE
COULD LOSE ACCESS TO BIRTH
CONTROL UNDER THIS CHANGE?
>> I'M NOT AWARE.
I'D REFER YOU TO HHS FOR
SPECIFICS.
>> THE PRESIDENT REPEATED
EARLIER TODAY THAT THE U.S. IS
THE HIGHEST TAX NATION IN THE
WORLD.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
SO WHY DOES HE KEEP MAKING THAT
STATEMENT?
WHY DOES HE STICK TO THAT
TALKING POINT?
>> THERE ARE SPECIFIC SECTORS IN
THE COUNTRY THAT ARE AMONG THE
HIGHEST TAXED IN THE WORLD AND
WE'LL BE HAPPY TO PROVIDE THAT
DATA.
JOHN?
>> I HAVE TWO QUESTIONS, SARAH.
THERE'S RUMORS THAT PRIME
MINISTER SABRIS WILL COME HERE
ON THE 17th, MEET WITH THE
PRESIDENT AND THEN MEET WITH THE
VICE PRESIDENT ON THE 18th.
WE'VE HAD NO CONFIRMATION.
IS THE PRIME MINISTER INVITED
AND IS HE COMING TO MEET THE
PRESIDENT AND VICE PRESIDENT?
>> HE IS.
I BELIEVE THAT DATE IS CORRECT.
THE 17th, I BELIEVE, THAT HE
WILL BE HERE.
>> THE OTHER THING, THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS HAD A VACANCY
WITHOUT A PERMANENT SECRETARY OF
HOMELAND SECURITY FOR TWO
MONTHS, WHICH IS A RECORD FOR
THAT POSITION NOT OPERATING WITH
A PERMANENT SECRETARY.
ARE WE GOING TO HAVE AN
ANNOUNCEMENT ON A CHOICE FOR
PERMANENT SECRETARY WITHIN DAYS
NEXT WEEK PERHAPS?
AND RUMORS ARE CONSISTENT, HE
WILL MAKE ELAINE DUKE THE
PERMANENT SECRETARY.
TRUE OR FALSE?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO GET AHEAD OF
ANY ANNOUNCEMENT THAT THE
PRESIDENT MAY MAKE ABOUT A
PERMANENT PERSON.
I WILL SAY ACTING SECRETARY DUKE
IS VERY COMPETENT, HAS MANAGED
THE DEPARTMENT WELL IN A TOUGH
AND TRYING TIME GIVEN THE
HURRICANE SEASON WE'VE HAD AND
CERTAINLY HAVE NOT WANTED TO
MAKE BIG SHIFTS IN LEADERSHIP
DURING THIS TIME.
WHILE THERE'S SO MUCH GOING ON
THERE, IN TERMS OF A TIMETABLE,
WE'LL KEEP YOU POSTED WHEN WE
HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
>> THAT'S WHAT YOU JUST SAID
ABOUT SECRETARY DUKE, THE
TESTIMONY YOU GAVE AS THE
PRESIDENT'S OPINION OF HER AS
WELL.
>> YES.
HE'S HAPPY WITH THE JOB THAT
SHE'S DONE AS THE ACTING
SECRETARY.
>> SENAOR CORNYN SAID THE
IMMIGRATION PRINCIPLES WOULD BE
HARMFUL TO DACA.
DACA SHOULD BE KEPT SEPARATE
ABOUT ANY ILLEGAL IMMIGRATION.
WHAT IS THE WHITE HOUSE'S
RESPONSE TO THAT?
ARE YOU GUYS COMMITTED TO
ATTACHING LEGAL IMMIGRATION TO
THE DACA DEBATE?
>> WE WANT TO MAKE SURE WHATEVER
WE PUT FORWARD IS A RESPONSIBLE
IMMIGRATION REFORM AND NOT ONE
PIECE OF THIS PROCESS DEALT WITH
SEPARATELY.
WE NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT WE'RE
ADDRESSING ALL THE PROBLEMS SO
WE'RE NOT DEALING WITH THIS
AGAIN IN TWO, FOUR, FIVE, SIX
YEARS BUT PUTTING FORWARD A VERY
THOROUGH AND FULL PLAN.
THAT'S WHAT YOU'LL SEE COMING
FROM THE ADMINISTRATION IN VERY
SHORT ORDER.
FRED?
>> THANK YOU, SARAH.
TWO WEEKS.
FIRST, THERE'S A VIEW ON PAYDAY
LENDING.
>> NOT THAT I'M AWARE OF.
>> JUST TO FOLLOW UP ON THAT
TOPIC.
THERE'S BEEN SOME HOUSE
REPUBLICANS WHO BELIEVE THAT
THERE'S ALREADY CAUSE FOR FIRING
RICHARD.
GOING BACK TO HIS HANDLING OF
THE WELLS FARGO CASE.
WHY HASN'T THE PRESIDENT -- HAS
HE APPROVED OF THE JOB HE'S DONE
SO FAR?
>> WHEN WE HAVE PERSONNEL
ANNOUNCEMENTS, WE'LL KEEP YOU
POSTED.
THAT'S TWO ALREADY.
I'M MOVING ON.
MARGARET?
>> TWO QUICK QUESTIONS.
THERE'S BEEN SOME RUMORS ABOUT
THE FUTURE OF SECRETARY REX
TILLERSON TODAY.
CAN YOU CONTINUE TO SAY THE
PRESIDENT REMAINS CONFIDENT IN
HIM AS SECRETARY OF STATE?
>> HE DOES.
AS HE SAID YESTERDAY OR TWO DAYS
AGO AS I SAID YESTERDAY, NOTHING
HAS CHANGED DESPITE WHAT YOU MAY
READ IN THE MEDIA OR WATCH ON
TV.
I WOULD CERTAINLY TRUST THE
PRESIDENT IN MY COMMENTS FAR
ABOVE THOSE OF OTHER REPORTERS.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU, THE
PRESIDENT CAN MOVE MARKETS,
CAUSE MISCALCULATIONS.
YOU MENTIONED NORTH KOREA, IRAN
WITH CALM BEFORE THE STORM.
AN IMPLICATION THAT THERE'S SOME
SORT OF FORECASTING OF A
MILITARY ACTION.
CAN YOU CLARIFY IF WE'RE
INTERPRETING THINGS CORRECTLY?
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN SPECIFIC ABOUT
ANYTHING.
I'VE ALSO TALKED ABOUT THE FACT
THAT WE'RE CONTINUING TO PUT
MAXIMUM ECONOMIC AND DIPLOMATIC
PRESSURE ON COUNTRIES LIKE NORTH
KOREA.
I'M SAYING THAT ALL OPTIONS ARE
ON THE TABLE AS THEY HAVE BEEN
AND WE'RE NOT GOING TO ANNOUNCE
WHAT ACTIONS WE'LL BE TAKING
UNTIL THAT MOMENT COMES.
>> WHY DID HE SAY THAT?
>> CAN YOU BE MORE SPECIFIC
ABOUT THE PRESIDENT BEING OPEN
TO LEGISLATION BANNING BUMP
STOCKS?
>> AS I SAID YESTERDAY, WE WANT
TO BE PART OF THAT CONVERSATION.
WE WANT MORE INFORMATION.
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO DO
THAT OVER THE COMING DAYS.
THAT'S THE CURRENT POSITION.
HASN'T CHANGED SINCE YESTERDAY.
>> THANK YOU, SARAH.
TWO QUESTIONS IF I CAN.
>> WHY NOT?
>> I ASKED YOU ABOUT SENATOR
CORKER.
>> JUST NOT THREE.
>> JUST TWO.
I ASKED YOU ABOUT SENATOR CORKER
AND THE COMMENTS HE MADE A FEW
WEEKS BACK.
EARLIER THIS WEEK HE SAID THAT
SECRETARY TILLERSON, MATTIS AND
KELLY ARE BASICALLY WHAT IS
KEEPING THE COUNTRY SEPARATED
FROM CHAOS AND HE SAID THERE'S
OTHER PEOPLE IN THE WHITE HOUSE
THAT AREN'T PUTTING FORTH
POLICIES IN A COHERENT FASHION.
DO YOU HAVE ANY RESPONSE?
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT IS THE
ONE THAT IS KEEPING THE WORLD
FROM CHAOS.
HE HAS AN INCREDIBLE TEAM AROUND
HIM HELPING LEAD THAT EFFORT.
HE'S HAD TREMENDOUS
ACCOMPLISHMENTS ON THE
INTERNATIONAL STAGE BY WORKING
WITH ALLIES AND CONFRONTING
ENEMIES.
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO DO
THAT WITH THE TEAM AS THE
PRESIDENT LEADING THAT EFFORT.
>> IS GENERAL KELLY --
>> I'M COME BACK.
>> GETTING BACK TO THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM COMMENTS.
THERE'S A THEORY IN WASHINGTON
AND FORGIVE ME IF YOU'VE BEEN
ASKED ABOUT IT BEFORE, THAT THE
PRESIDENT SUBSCRIBES TO THIS MAD
MAN THEORY, THAT IF HE MAKES A
LOT OF UNSETTLING OFF-PUTTING
COMMENTS THAT SORT OF THROW
PEOPLE OFF, THAT HE LIKES TO
KEEP HIS ADVERSARIES GUESSING.
THAT'S THE POINT OF MAKING
COMMENTS LIKE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM AND SO FORTH.
WHAT IS YOUR SENSE OF THAT?
IS THERE ANYTHING TO THAT?
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT
ADDRESSED THIS HIMSELF.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO LAY OUT HIS
GAME PLAN FOR OUR ENEENEMIES.
IF YOU'RE ASKING, IS THE
PRESIDENT TRYING TO DO THAT?
ABSOLUTELY.
>> HE'S TRYING TO THROW PEOPLE
OFF?
>> I WON'T SAY HE'S TRYING TO
THROW PEOPLE OFF BUT HE'S NOT
TRYING TO BROADCAST OR TELEGRAPH
HIS EXACT ACTIONS.
I THINK WE'VE SEEN WHAT A
FAILURE IT IS WHEN AN
ADMINISTRATION DOES THAT AND
THIS IS A PRESIDENT THAT WILL DO
IT DIFFERENTLY AND DO IT BETTER.
>> JUST A FOLLOW UP.
SO WHEN PEOPLE ARE -- THEY SORT
OF CATCH THEIR BREATH IN THIS
TOWN, WHEN THEY SORT OF HOLD
THEIR BREATH IN THIS TOWN, WHEN
HE SAYS SOMETHING LIKE THAT, YOU
HAVE A SMILE ON YOUR FACE.
IS THAT SOMEWHAT SATISFY
SOMETHING.
>> NO.
I PICTURE PEOPLE IN THIS TOWN
HOLDING THEIR BREATH.
THAT MIGHT BE A WELCOME SURPRISE
FOR MOST OF AMERICA.
GO AHEAD.
>> SARAH, ONE MORE THING TO PICK
UP ON WHAT MARGARET WAS TRYING
TO GET AT.
LET ME PUT IT TO YOU THIS WAY.
CAN YOU EXCLUDE THE POSSIBILITY
THAT THE PRESIDENT WAS ACTUALLY
JUST BEING MISCHIEVOUS?
THAT HE WAS MESSING WITH THE
PRESS A LITTLE BIT WHEN HE MADE
THAT COMMENT.
>> I WOULDN'T SAY HE'S MESSING
WITH THE PRESS.
I SAY WE HAVE SOME SERIOUS WORLD
ISSUES HERE.
I THINK NORTH KOREA, IRAN BOTH
CONTINUE TO BE BAD ACTORS AND
THE PRESIDENT IS SOMETHING THAT
WILL ALWAYS LOOK FOR WAYS TO
PROTECT AMERICANS.
HE'S NOT GOING TO DICTATE WHAT
THOSE ACTIONS MAY LOOK LIKE.
I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANYTHING
BEYOND THAT THAT I CAN ADD ON
THAT FRONT.
>> AND ANOTHER QUESTION ON IRAN.
A COUPLE DAYS AGO SENATOR TOM
COTTON GAVE A SPEECH IN WHICH HE
SAYS THEY BELIEVES THE BEST
OUTCOME WOULD BE TO HAVE
CONGRESS REIMPOSE SANCTIONS.
WE WOULD USE THIS PERIOD OF 120,
90 DAYS TO RENEGOTIATE SEVERAL
TERMS OF THE DEAL.
DOES THE WHITE HOUSE THINK THAT
THAT SOUNDS LIKE APPLAUSABLE AND
GOOD WAY TO DO WITH THE IRAN
NUCLEAR DEAL?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO GET AHEAD OF
THE PRESIDENT'S ANNOUNCEMENT ON
THE DECISION HE HAS.
WHAT I CAN TELL YOU, THE
PRESIDENT ISN'T LOOKING AT ONE
PIECE OF THIS.
HE'S LOOKING AT ALL OF THE BAD
BEHAVIOR OF IRAN, NOT JUST THE
NUCLEAR DEAL AS BAD BEHAVIOR.
THE BALLISTIC MISSILE TESTING,
DESTABILIZING OF THE REGION,
NUMBER 1 STATE SPONSOR OF
TERROR, ELICIT NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
HE WANTS TO LOOK FOR A BROAD
STRATEGY THAT ADDRESSES ALL OF
THOSE PROBLEMS.
THAT'S WHAT HIS TEAM IS FOCUSED
ON AND THAT'S WHAT HE WILL ROLL
OUT TO ADDRESS THAT AS A WHOLE
IN THE COMING DAYS.
STEVE?
>> IS IT THE PRESIDENT'S WISH --
>> AGAIN, I'M NOT GOING TO GET
INTO THE DETAILS OF THE
PRESIDENT'S DECISION UNTIL HE
MAKES THAT.
>> SARAH, ABOUT CUBA.
CBS NEWS IS REPORTING THAT THE
STORY IS GOING TO A NEW LEVEL.
THERE'S AMERICANS THAT DON'T
WORK FOR THE GOVERNMENT THAT
SAYING THEY'RE SUBJECT TO THESE
ATTACKS.
THERE'S A HANDFUL OF AMERICANS
THAT HAVE REPORTED THESE
SYMPTOMS.
WHAT IS GOING ON HERE?
HOW IS THE WHITE HOUSE VIEWING
THIS?
HOW ARE WE GOING TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF IT?
>> SOMETHING THAT WE TAKE
SERIOUSLY.
WE'RE CONTINUING TO INVESTIGATE.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT IS TAKING
THE LEAD ON THIS EFFORT AND
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO LOOK
INTO THIS UNTIL WE GET SOME REAL
ANSWERS.
>> JUST TO DRILL DOWN ON WHAT
YOU SAID YESTERDAY ABOUT THE
PRESS.
SAYING THAT WE OWE IT -- I DON'T
THINK ANYBODY DISAGREES THAT WE
SHOULD BE ACCURATE.
BUT DO YOU AND THE PRESIDENT
BELIEVE THE PRESIDENT HAS A
RESPONSIBILITY TO BE AS TRUTHFUL
AND HONEST AND HAS HE DONE IT
AND THOSE SURROGATES THAT HAVE
USED ALTERNATIVE FACTS AND WOULD
THEY NOT DO THAT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE ALL COME HERE EVERY DAY TO
GIVE YOU THE BEST AND MOST
ACCURATE INFORMATION THAT WE
CAN.
APRIL?
>> GOING BACK TO THE ANSWER
ABOUT LEADERSHIP AND THE
PRESIDENT.
IS GENERAL KELLY PART OF THAT
LEADERSHIP TEAM WITH THE
PRESIDENT AS HE'S LEADING IN
THIS WHITE HOUSE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> DOES THE PRESIDENT HAVE
CONFIDENCE IN GENERAL KELLY?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> TODAY IS FRIDAY.
CAN WE EXPECT A RESIGNATION
TODAY?
>> I DON'T THINK SO, APRIL.
DAVID?
>> SINCE WE LAST HEARD FROM YOU,
THE FORM PRODUCER HARVEY
WINESTEIN HAS BECOME THE SUBJECT
OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT
ALLEGATIONS.
AND THERE'S BEEN SOME DEMOCRATS
THAT HAVE HAD DONATIONS.
IT'S BEEN SUGGESTED THAT LATINOS
IN HOLLYWOOD WOULD BE DEPORTED
IF THE PRESIDENT IS ELECTED.
DOES THE PRESIDENT THESE THE
DONATIONS SHOULD GO BACK?
>> THAT'S A DECISION FOR THE
INDIVIDUALS TO MAKE.
WHETHER OR NOT THAT IS MONEY
THAT THEY WANT TO TAKE, THAT'S
UP TO THEM.
THAT'S NOT A DECISION FOR US TO
MAKE.
>> ONE MORE -- I'M SORRY.
WHY HASN'T THE PRESIDENT FIRED
THE IRS HEAD?
HE TALKED ABOUT THE SCANDAL.
WHY DOES HE STILL HAVE A JOB?
>> I'LL HAVE TO ASK HIM AND GET
BACK TO YOU.
>> LAS VEGAS QUESTION.
THE PRESIDENT TALKED ABOUT THE
POLICE AND THEIR RESPONSE AFTER
THE MASS SHOOTINGS.
NEVADA --
>> CAN YOU SPEAK UP A LITTLE
BIT?
>> NEVADIANS CREDIT FEDERAL
MONDAY PROGRAMS TO TRAIN THEM TO
DEAL WITH TERRORIST ATTACKS TO
DEAL WITH THE GREAT RESPONSE.
YOU HAVE CUTS IN THOSE PROGRAMS
IN YOUR BUDGET PLANS?
ARE YOU RETHINKING THAT?
>> I THINK AT THIS POINT WE'RE
CONTINUING TO MOVE FORWARD.
IF THERE'S A MOMENT WHERE WE
FEEL LIKE THE SAFETY AND
SECURITY OF AMERICAN CITIZENS
MAY BE AT RISK BECAUSE OF CUTS,
I THINK WE WOULD HAVE TO
RE-VISIT IT AT THAT TIME.
JIM?
>> SARAH, THE NATION LOST 33,000
JOBS IN SEPTEMBER.
I WAS CURIOUS WHAT THE
PRESIDENT -- HOW THE PRESIDENT
FEELS ABOUT THAT AND HE'S
STEPPING UP HIS EFFORTS TO
CONVINCE CONGRESS TO PASS MAJOR
TAX RETURNS BECAUSE OF THIS
SURPRISING JOB LOSS IN
SEPTEMBER.
>> I THINK TODAY'S REPORT SHOWS
THE DEVASTATING IMPACT OF THE
HURRICANE SEASON.
WHILE MANY DISPLACED WEREN'T
ABLE TO WORK, THE ECONOMY
REMAINS EXTREMELY STRONG.
THE PEOPLE CONTINUE TO HAVE
JOBS, WHICH IS WHY THE
UNEMPLOYMENT RATE FELL.
I THINK ONE THING TO REALLY KNOW
AND SOMETHING THAT THIS
ADMINISTRATION WANTS TO FOCUS ON
CERTAINLY MOVING INTO THE
FUTURE, I THINK TAX REFORM PLAY
AS BIG ROLE IN THIS.
ONE OF THE BIG IDENTIFIERS THAT
I THINK WE SHOULD LOOK AT IS THE
DROP IN THE UNEMPLOYMENT RATE,
INCLUDING NEW LOADS FOR AFRICAN
AMERICANS, TEENS AND WOMEN,
WHICH IS CERTAINLY A GREAT STEP
FORWARD IN THIS PROCESS.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
REPEATEDLY SAID THAT WE SHOULD
LET OBAMACARE IMPLODE.
THERE'S A NEW REPORT IN "THE
WASHINGTON POST" THAT SET THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP PERSONALLY
DIRECTED ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS TO DENY A REQUEST FROM
REPUBLICAN GOVERNOR OF IOWA TO
FIX THE OBAMACARE MARKET IN THAT
STATE.
IS THAT TRUE?
>> I'M NOT AWARE OF THAT
SPECIFIC DIRECTIVE.
SO I'D HAVE TO CHECK INTO THAT
AND GET BACK TO YOU.
>> IF IT IS TRUE --
>> I'M NOT GOING TO COMMENT ON
HYPOTHETICALS WHERE I DON'T HAVE
THE INFORMATION IN FRONT OF ME.
>> I WANT TO ASK YOU ABOUT THE
IRAN RECERTIFICATION PROCESS.
REGARDLESS OF WHAT THE PRESIDENT
DECIDES, WHEN HE MAKES THIS
DECISION NEXT WEEK, WOULD YOU
RATHER NOT HAVE TO DO THIS EVERY
90 DAYS AFTER THAT?
>> AGAIN, AS I SAID EARLIER,
WE'RE LOOKING AT SOMETHING THAT
IS A BROAD STRATEGY, DOESN'T
JUST ADDRESS ONE PART OF I RAN'S
BAD BEHAVIOR AND ADDRESSES A
WIDE RANGE OF ISSUES.
SO THAT WOULD BE OUR FOCUS.
HOPEFULLY THEY WOULD BEGIN TO
NOT BE A BAD ACTOR AROUND WE
WOULDN'T HAVE TO DO THIS AT ALL.
OUR GOAL WOULD BE TO ADDRESS A
NUMBER OF FACTORS, NOTICE JUST
ONE OR TWO THING.
PETER?
>> A SECOND QUESTION.
THE PRESIDENT INDICATED THAT HE
WANTED PAKISTAN TO GO AGAINST
AGENTS OF CHAOS.
THE FOREIGN MINISTER WAS HERE IN
THE WHITE HOUSE THIS WEEK TO
MEET GENERAL McMASTER.
HAVE YOU SEEN ANY CHANGE IN
PAKISTANI BEHAVIOR?
>> NOTHING SPECIFIC THAT I CAN
WEIGH INTO AT THIS TIME.
WE'LL KEEP YOU POSTED.
>> WILL THE PRESIDENT CAMPAIGN
FOR THE CANDIDATE IN VIRGINIA?
>> I'M NOT GROG TO WAY INTO
SPECIFIC RACES AND THE ACTIONS
WE MAY OR MAY NOT TAKE.
THAT'S A GREAT PLACE TO END THIS
FOR FRIDAY.
I HOPE EVERYBODY HAS A GREAT
REST OF THE FRIDAY AND A GOOD
WEEKEND.
THANKS, GUYS.
>> Shepard: THE WHITE HOUSE
PRESS SECRETARY, SARAH SANDERS
WRAPPED UP THE BRIEFING.
THAT STARTED AFTER PRESIDENT
TRUMP WITH A WINK AND A WARNING
AFTER REMAINING WHAT HE MEANT
WHEN HE CALLED A MEETING WITH
THE MILITARY LITERS THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
WHAT DID YOU MEAN BY THAT?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: THE PRESIDENT MADE
THE ORIGINAL COMMENT LAST NIGHT
AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
AT THAT TIME HE WAS MEETING WITH
HIS MILITARY LEADERS TO TALK
ABOUT MAJOR FOREIGN POLICY
ISSUES, INCLUING IRAN, NORTH
KOREA AND ISIS.
LISTEN.
>> THIS IS THE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM.
>> WHAT STORM IS THAT,
MR. PRESIDENT?
>> THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING.
>> WHAT STORM, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Shepard: YOU'LL FIND OUT.
WE WERE HOPING TO FIND OUT MORE
AT THE WHITE HOUSE BRIEFING
TODAY.
KRISTIN FISHER IS LIVE IN THE
BRIEFING ROOM.
WE DID NOT.
>> WE DID NOT FIND OUT ANY
ANSWERS TO THAT QUESTION.
THAT HAS BEEN THE MILLION DOLLAR
QUESTION ALL DAY HERE IN
WASHINGTON AND AROUND THE WORLD.
WHAT WAS PRESIDENT TRUMP
REFERRING TO WHEN HE SAID THAT
THIS IS THE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM.
YOU KNOW, REPORTERS IN THIS ROOM
ASK THAT QUESTION ABOUT AS MANY
TIMES AS YOU COULD POSSIBLY ASK
THE PRESS SECRETARY.
THEY ASKED HER, YOU KNOW, WAS
THIS INTENDED TO KEEP OUR
ADVERSARIES GUESSING?
PERHAPS WAS PRESIDENT TRUMP
BEING MISCHIEVOUS OR MAYBE HE
JUST MESSING WITH THE PRESS.
HERE'S EXACTLY WHAT SHE SAID.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> AS WE SAID MANY TIMES BEFORE,
I KNOW THE PRESIDENT HAS, AS I
HAVE FROM THIS PODIUM ON QUITE A
FEW OCCASIONS, WE'RE NEVER GOING
TO SAY IN ADVANCE WHAT THE
PRESIDENT IS GOING TO DO.
AS HE SAID LAST NIGHT IN
ADDITION TO THOSE COMMENTS,
YOU'LL HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE.
I THINK YOU CAN TAKE THE
PRESIDENT PROTECTING THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE ALWAYS EXTREMELY
SERIOUS.
HE'S BEEN VERY CLEAR THAT'S HIS
NUMBER 1 PRIORITY.
IF HE FEELS THAT ACTION IS
NECESSARY, HE WILL TAKE IT.
>> WAS HE REFERRING TO NORTH
KOREA?
WAS HE REFERRING TO SUPERIOR IS
FIGHTERS IN NIGER AFTER THE LOSS
OF GREEN BERETS THIS WEEK OR
MAYBE IRAN?
WE JUST DON'T KNOW.
AS THE WHITE HOUSE PRESS
SECRETARY MADE CLEAR, SHE'S NOT
GOING TO GIVE MORE DETAILS.
SHE WILL LEAVE THAT UP TO HIM,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: KRISTIN, THE WHITE
HOUSE TALKING ABOUT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S NEW LIMITS ON
MANDATORY BIRTH CONTROL COVERAGE
UNDER THE AFFORDABLE CARE ACT OR
OBAMACARE.
THE NEW POLICY LETS EMPLOYERS
REFUSE FREE CONTRACEPTIVES BY
CLAIMING A RELIGIOUS OR MORAL
OBJECTION.
THE AMERICAN CIVIL LIBERTIES
UNION HAS FILED A LAWSUIT AND
OTHERS ARE PLANNING TO DO THE
SAME THING.
BACK TO KRISTIN FISHER, A TOUCHY
SUBJECT THERE TODAY.
>> RIGHT.
SO BEFORE THESE EXEMPTIONS WERE
STRICTLY LIMITED TO RELIGIOUS
BELIEFS.
NOW THEY'VE BEEN EXPANDED TO
INCLUDE MORAL OBJECTIONS AS
WELL.
THERE'S A LOT OF QUESTIONS ABOUT
WHAT CONSTITUTES A MORAL
OBJECTION, HOW WILL THAT BE
DETERMINED.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS THAT WILL
BE DETERMINED BY THE STATE.
THIS IS A PRETTY SIGNIFICANT
ROLL BACK OF THE CONTRACEPTION
MANDATE BY THIS WHITE HOUSE AND
THE ACLU HAS NOW THREATENED TO
FILE A LAWSUIT.
JUST A MOMENT AGO, THE PRESS
SECRETARY WAS ASKED WHAT DOES
THE WHITE HOUSE THINK ABOUT
THIS?
COULD IT GO TO THE SUPREME
COURT?
HERE'S WHAT SHE SAID.
>> I WOULD PROBABLY NEVER USE
THE ACLU TO GET MY TALKING
POINTS.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THE FREEDOM
TO PRACTICE ONE'S FAITH IS A
FUNDAMENTAL RIGHT IN THIS
COUNTRY.
ALL OF US DO.
THAT'S ALL THAT TODAY WAS ABOUT.
OUR FEDERAL GOVERNMENT SHOULD
PROTECT THAT RIGHT.
AS LONG AS DONALD TRUMP IS
PRESIDENT, HE WILL.
>> THE FLIP SIDE IS COMING FROM
DEMOCRATS.
NANCY PELOSI CALLED THIS NEW
RULE DESPICABLE BECAUSE WHAT
THIS MEANS IS NOW THAT
POTENTIALLY HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF WOMEN ACROSS THIS
COUNTRY WILL NO LONGER HAVE
ACCESS TO FREE BIRTH CONTROL IF
THIS RULE GOES FORWARD, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU, KRISTIN.
LET'S TURN TO CHRIS WALLACE NOW,
THE ANCHOR OF "FOX NEWS SUNDAY"
LIVE WITH US IN D.C.
WITH A SMILE THE PRESIDENT SAYS,
YOU CAN TAKE THIS MEETING TO BE
THE CALM BEFORE THE STORM.
WHAT ARE WE SUPPOSED TO THINK?
>> WELL -- LOOK, WE DON'T KNOW
IS THE ANSWER.
THE PRESIDENT REFUSES TO ANSWER.
YOU SAW SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS,
HIS CHIEF SPOKESPERSON REFUSED
TO ANSWER.
MY GUESS IS THE PRESIDENT IS
SITTING THERE WITH A TOP BRASS
OF THE MOST POWERFUL MILITARY ON
EARTH EVER AND SAYING IT'S THE
CALM BEFORE THE STORM.
HE'S NOT SAYING WE'RE ABOUT TO
STRIKE NORTH KOREA, WE'RE ABOUT
TO STRIKE IRAN.
HE'S NOT GOING TO TIP HIS HAND
ON IMMINENT MILITARY ACTION.
HE'S SAYING, WE HAVE THE MOST
POWERFUL MILITARY AND DON'T MESS
WITH US.
WE CAN DO WHATEVER WE WANT.
DO I THINK HE'S LAYING OUT A
SPECIFIC -- SOMETHING THAT WILL
HAPPEN IN THE NEXT DAYS, WEEKS,
HOURS, MONTHS?
NO.
I THINK HE'S SAYING WE HAVE THAT
CAPABILITY.
THERE WAS A VERY GOOD QUESTION
ASKED IN THE BR