I'M DANA PERINO.
THANKS FOR JOINING "THE DAILY
BRIEFING."
SHEPARD SMITH IS NEXT.
>> Shepard: HE RECORDED THE
CARNAGE.
REPORTS THAT THE GUNMAN VIDEOED
HIMSELF AS HE MURDERED PEOPLE.
IT'S NOON IN LAS VEGAS WHERE
VICTIMS RELATIVES TRY TO PROCESS
THEIR LOSS AND THEIR FEELINGS
FOR THE KILLER.
>> YOU HAVE PROBLEMS WITH
SOMEONE, DON'T TAKE IT OUT ON
EVERYBODY.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS.
>> AHEAD, WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT THE
VICTIMS ALONG WITH THE BRAVE
BYSTANDERS THAT RISKED AND IN
SOME CASES GAVE THEIR LIVES TO
HELP SAVE OTHERS.
FROM AN IRAQ WAR VETERANS TO
CIVILIAN PARAMEDICS THAT FOUND
THEMSELVES UNDER FIRE, WE'LL
MEET THE HEROS OF LAS VEGAS.
WE'RE ALSO WATCHING THE RECOVERY
EFFORT IN PUERTO RICO WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS MEETING WITH
LEADERS AND FIRST RESPONDERS.
WE EXPECT TO HEAR FROM THE
PRESIDENT IN THIS HOUR.
LET'S GET TO IT.
>> Shepard: FIRST FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK, THERE'S VIDEO OF THE
MASSACRE SHOT FROM THE SNIPER'S
ROOST IN HIS 32nd FLOOR SUITE AT
MANDALAY BAY.
THAT'S THE REPORT NOW FROM THE
DAILY MAIL NEWSPAPER BASED IN
THE UNITED KINGDOM.
THE PAPER IS REPORTING THAT
ALONG WITH 23 GUNS THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK BROUGHT INTO THE ROOM,
HE ALSO BROUGHT MULTIPLE CAMERAS
WITH HIM.
THE PAPER INDICATES HE SET UP
ONE BY A WINDOW WHICH HE BROKE
TO RECORD THE KILLING SPREE AND
ANOTHER IN THE HALL OUTSIDE THE
HOTEL ROOM DOOR SO HE WOULD KNOW
WHEN THE COPS APPROACHED.
AUTHORITIES HAVE NOT CONFIRMED
THAT REPORT.
WE ARE GETTING A LOOK INTO THE
HOTEL ROOM ITSELF FROM WHICH THE
GUNMAN CARRIED OUT THE DEADLIEST
SHOOTING IN MODERN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
THE "NEW YORK POST" OBTAINED
THIS VIDEO FROM THE CRIME SCENE
IN TEXAS -- FROM THE CRIME SCENE
IN LAS VEGAS, I SHOULD SAY.
FOX NEWS CHANNEL AND THE PAPER
SHARE COMMON OWNERSHIP.
THE VIDEO SHOWS AN ASSAULT RIFLE
RESTING ON A BIPOD ON THE FLOOR.
YOU CAN SEE WHAT APPEARED TO BE
A USED ROOM SERVICE TRAY.
YOU CAN SEE THE BREACHED DOOR
ITSELF THERE COVERED WITH THE
YELLOW POLICE TAPE.
THE SWAT TEAM BROKE DOWN THE
DOOR WITH EXPLOSIVES TO GET TO
THE GUNMAN ALREADY TO FIND OUT
HE ALREADY KILLED HIMSELF.
INVESTIGATORS LOOKING INTO THE
SUSPECTS SAY THEY'RE STRUGGLING
TO FIGURE OUT WHY HE CARRIED OUT
THIS MASSACRE.
FEDERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIALS TELL FOX NEWS, STEPHEN
PADDOCK SENT ABOUT $100,000
OVERSEAS.
THE MONEY MAY HAVE GONE TO HIS
GIRLFRIEND AND THEY'RE STILL
LOOKING INTO IT AND HAVE NOT
CONFIRMED THAT.
WE HAVE NEW IMAGES OF THE GUNS
THE SHOOTER USED DURING THE
MASSACRE.
FROM BOSTON 25 NEWS, WE OBTAINED
THESE PHOTOS.
AT THE END OF EACH GUN APPEARED
TO BE A BUMP STOCK WHICH
MODIFIES WEAPONS TO MAKE THEM
FULLY AUTOMATIC.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE SHOOTER
BROUGHT TEN SUITCASES FILLED
WITH GUNS INTO THE HOTEL ROOM.
POLICE OFFICERS SAY 23 FIREARMS
WERE FOUND THERE.
WE'RE LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
PEOPLE THAT RISKED THEIR LIVES
TO SAVE OTHERS.
FIRE OFFICIALS SAY OFF DUTY
FIREFIGHTERS WERE SHOT WHILE
TAKING ACTION.
>> AFTER ALL HELL BROKE LOOSE,
12 OF THE MEMBERS WERE SHOT AS
THEY WENT TO WORK HELPING OTHER
MEMBERS IN THE AUDIENCE.
TWO OF THESE MEMBERS WERE SHOT
WHILE PERFORMING CPR.
THIS IS A TRUE FEAT OF HEROISM
ON THEIR PART.
>> Shepard: MORE AHEAD ON THE
ACTS OF HEROISM.
INVESTIGATOR SAY THE GUNMAN
SMASHED OUT TWO WINDOWS TO FIRE
GUNS ON BIPODS AT CROWDS A
QUARTER MILE AWAY.
INJURING MORE THAN 500 AND
KILLING 59.
DURING THE MASSACRE,
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE SHOOTER
SHOT AT SECURITY GUARDS THROUGH
HIS HOTEL DOOR HITTING ONE IN
THE LEG.
THE GUARD WE'RE TOLD SURVIVED.
STEPHEN PADDOCK LIVED IN A
RETIREMENT COMMUNITY IN
MESQUITE, NEVADA.
HE WAS A 64-YEAR-OLD FORMER
ACCOUNTANT.
PEOPLE THAT KNEW HIM SAID HE WAS
A MILLIONAIRE, HAD A HIGH STAKES
VIDEO POKER HABIT.
INVESTIGATORS SAY POD DOCK HAD
NO CRIMINAL RECORD AS FAR AS
THEY KNOW.
HE WAS THE SON OF A BANK ROBBER
THAT DECADES AGO WAS ON THE
FBI'S MOST WANTED LIST.
FAMILY MEMBERS SAY THEY ALSO
CANNOT EXPLAIN WHAT WOULD
MOTIVATE PADDOCK TO CARRY OUT
THE MASSACRE.
ACCORDING TO HIS BROTHER,
STEPHEN PADDOCK WAS A
MULTIMILLIONAIRE.
HE MADE MUCH OF THE MONEY FROM
REAL ESTATE AND LIVED A
COMFORTABLE LIFE.
THE BROTHER SAYS THE GUNMAN
DIDN'T CARE ABOUT RELIGION OR
POLITICS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY PADDOCK WAS
THE ONLY SHOOTER.
JASON ALDEAN WAS PERFORMING AT
THE END OF THE THREE-DAY
FESTIVAL WHEN THE GUN FIRE
BEGAN.
HE POSTED A STATEMENT SAYING HE
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND WHY THIS
HAPPENED.
HE SAID I'M SORRY FOR THE HURT
AND PAIN EVERYONE IS FEELING
RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S WORDS I CAN SAY TO TAKE
THAT PAIN AWAY.
JASON ALDEAN ADDED, TIME TO COME
TOGETHER AND STOP THE HATE.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON ALL OF THE
DEVELOPMENTS IN LAS VEGAS,
INCLUDING VIDEO IN JUST A
MOMENT.
BUT FIRST, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
SPEAKING.
THIS IS HAPPENING IN PUERTO
RICO.
YOU'LL REMEMBER, THAT HE'S
HELPING HAND OUT SUPPLIES AT A
CHURCH THERE ABOUT TEN MILES
NORTH OF -- SOUTH OF SAN JUAN.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
>> I SEE AN INCREDIBLE JOB DONE
BY FEMA, THE COAST GUARD, THE
ARMY, THE NAVY, THE AIR FORCE,
THE MARINES.
THE JOB OF THE FIRST RESPONDERS
HAS BEEN SOMETHING LIKE I HAVE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
WHAT FEMA HAS DONE, WHAT THE
PEOPLE THAT GOT HERE BEFORE THE
HURRICANE HAVE DONE -- AND THE
GOVERNOR IS WITH US.
YOUR MAYOR IS WITH US ALSO, THE
GOVERNOR.
WHAT HAS HAPPENED IN TERMS OF
RECOVERY IN TERMS OF SAVING
LIVES, 16 LIVES.
THAT'S A LOT.
BUT YOU COMPARE THAT TO THE
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE THAT DIED IN
OTHER HURRICANES AND FRANKLY
WE'RE NOT NEARLY AS SEVERE.
I JUST HAVE SUCH RESPECT FOR
FEMA AND ALL OF THE PEOPLE THAT
GOT HERE EARLY.
GOVERNOR, YOU MAY WANT TO SAY
SOMETHING.
>> WE'RE GRATEFUL FOR THE
PRESIDENT, GRATEFUL FOR THE
EFFORTS THAT THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT HAS EMBARKED.
THIS IS A TEAM EFFORT.
WE HAVE ALL THE WAY FROM MAYORS
TO FEMA, THE DODs, GENERAL
BUCHANAN IS HERE AS WELL.
WE COULDN'T HAVE DONE THIS IF WE
DIDN'T HAVE THOSE SUPPORT.
OF COURSE, WE RECOGNIZE AND THE
PRESIDENT RECOGNIZES WE STILL
NEED TO DO MORE.
WE KNOW WE'LL DO IT TOGETHER,
THIS IS A COMMITMENT BY THE
PRESIDENT, THE FIRST LADY BEING
HERE SHOWS A COMMITMENT TO BEING
HERE FOR THE LONG HAUL, HELPING
US GET THE EMERGENCY HELP,
HELPING US GET STABILITY AND
BUILDING PUERTO RICO STRONGER
THAN BEFORE.
>> FIRST OF ALL, THANK YOU.
ONE OF THE THINGS YOU MAY HEARD
ON THE MAINLAND THAT IS NOT
HAPPENING HERE.
PEOPLE WERE ON THE ISLAND BEFORE
THE HURRICANE, BEFORE, DURING
AND AFTER MARIA.
SO WE'VE BEEN HIT BY A HURRICANE
CAT 5 IN LESS THAN TEN DAYS, ONE
AFTER THE OTHER.
SO IT'S NOT BY THE NAVY AND THE
COAST GUARD.
THEY ARE RESCUING MORE THAN 800
PEOPLE AND STILL ONGOING IN
RESCUE MISSIONS.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN HISTORY,
THE PUERTO RICAN HAS WORKED WITH
THE GOVERNOR, TO DEAL WITH THIS
ISSUE.
WE NEVER HAVE BEFORE.
WE'RE USED TO HAVING A HURRICANE
BUT NEVER LIKE THIS ONE.
THIS IS A MAJOR ONE.
DEVASTATION.
THANKS FOR ALL OF THE HELP AND
ALL THE RESOURCES.
ALL FEDERAL AGENCIES ARE ON THE
ISLAND BECAUSE OF YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE POWER GRID WAS DEVASTATED
BEFORE THE HURRICANES EVEN HIT.
THEN THE HURRICANES HIT.
THEY WIPED THEM OUT.
WE'RE GETTING A LOT OF
GENERATORS THAT HAVE BEEN
BROUGHT TO THE ISLAND.
MOST OF THE HOSPITALS ARE OPEN.
AT LEAST PARTIALLY OPEN.
MOST OF THEM NOW ARE OPEN.
AGAIN, THE JOB DONE HERE IS
NOTHING SHORT OF A MIRACLE.
IT'S BEEN INCREDIBLE.
I APPRECIATE VIRTUALLY -- THIS
IS THE MAYOR FROM THIS VERY
IMPORTANT AREA.
MR. MAYOR, I APPRECIATES YOUR
EFFORTS.
>> THANK YOU.
ON BEHALF OF MY PEOPLE, ON
BEHALF OF THE 3.5 MILLION U.S.
CITIZENS.
IS A TEAM.
YOUR PEOPLE ARE DOING THE RIGHT
STUFF FOR US.
WE AS THE MAYOR -- THIS IS A
TEAM.
THAT IS MY EXPERIENCE AND THE
HELPING OF THOUSANDS AND
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
EVERYBODY.
>> WHAT DID YOU MEAN EARLIER
THAT THEY COULD DO MORE?
>> Shepard: NOW THE PRESIDENT
WILL WALK IN THE BUILDING AND
BEGIN THIS EFFORT OF
DISTRIBUTING SUPPLIES TO PEOPLE
WHO WERE THERE.
SO LET'S LISTEN TO THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: THERE YOU HAVE IT.
LOTS OF PHOTOGRAPHS WITH THE
PRESIDENT.
SOME WELL-WISHES, SOME CHEERS
AND APPLAUSE AND SOME SUPPLIES
TO BE HANDED OUT THERE.
OF COURSE, THE REAL PROBLEM IN
PUERTO RICO HAS BEEN WITH
DISTRIBUTION.
SO MANY OF THE DRIVERS OF THE
TRUCKS THAT WOULD NORMALLY TAKE
THE PRODUCTS, THAT ARE NECESSARY
FOR SURVIVAL AROUND THE ISLAND,
THOSE DRIVERS HAVE LOST IN MANY
CASES THEIR HOMES OR THEIR
ABILITY TO GET WHEREVER THEY
NEED TO GO TO DRIVE THE
VEHICLES.
SO THEY'RE HAVING A LOT OF
PROBLEMS WITH DISTRIBUTION.
HURTING A LOT OF PEOPLE IN SMALL
TOWNS AND OUTSIDE OF SAN JUAN.
TO HEAR IT FROM THE WHITE HOUSE,
THEY'RE WORKING AS HARD AS THEY
CAN TO GET THE DISTRIBUTION
CHANNELS IN LINE SO THAT NO ONE
ELSE LOSES THEIR LIVES IN THE
HORROR THAT HAS BEEN PUERTO
RICO.
IN JUST A MOMENT, WE'LL RETURN
TO TRACE GALLAGHER WHO IS IN
LAS VEGAS.
AGAIN, THE HEADLINE FROM THIS
HOUR, WE NOW HAVE REPORTS FROM
THE DAILY MAIL THE UNITED
KINGDOM THAT THE GUNMAN BROUGHT
ALONG WITH ALL THE WEAPONS TO
CREATE HIS CARNAGE, CAMERAS TO
RECORD IT SET UP AT THE WINDOW
WHERE HE WAS SHOOTING AT LEAST
ONE OF THEM AND IN A HALL SO HE
WOULD KNOW WHEN POLICE WERE
COMING.
NEW DETAILS ON THE SUSPECT AND
THE VICTIMS STRAIGHTAWAY ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
Patrick woke up
with a sore back.
But he's got work to do.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Check this Sunday's paper
for extra savings on
products from Aleve.
>> Shepard: WE KNOW FROM THE
REPORTING OF THE DAILYMAIL.COM
FROM THE UNITED KINGDOM THAT THE
GUNMAN HAD CAMERAS REPORTING HIS
CARNAGE.
IN ADDITION, WE LEARNED MORE
ABOUT THE WEAPONS THAT HE HAD IN
THE ROOM.
23 IN THE ROOM TOTAL.
MORE THAN 40 IN HIS POSSESSION
AT HIS HOMES AND THERE.
INSIDE THE ROOM, 4  DDM-4
RIFLES.
SOME HAD BEEN AUGMENTED, AFTER
MARKET, SO THEY COULD BECOME
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS AND MANY MORE.
TRACE GALLAGHER IS LIVE IN
VEGAS.
WHAT ARE INVESTIGATORS DOING AT
THE SCENE TODAY.
>> SHEP, THERE'S A COUPLE OF
CRIME SCENES AS YOU KNOW.
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE GOING BACK TO
THE CRIME SCENE IN MESQUITE.
THAT'S WHERE THEY FOUND 17
WEAPONS AND EXPLOSIVES.
THEY PULLED HARD DRIVES AS WELL.
WE'LL HAVE MORE IN A NEWS
CONFERENCE.
AT THE HOTEL, THEY WERE STILL ON
SCENE PROCESSING THE WEAPONS AND
THE AMMUNITION.
THAT WILL TAKE THEM A COUPLE
MORE DAYS.
THEY WITH BACK HERE EARLY THIS
MORNING.
THE MANDALAY BAY IS FULLY OPEN
EXCEPT FOR THE 32nd FLOOR, WHICH
IS COMPLETELY SHUT DOWN.
THIS VIDEO WHERE THE CONCERT
TOOK PLACE, STILL SHUT DOWN TO
THE MEDIA AND THERE'S STILL
INVESTIGATORS CRAWLING ALL OVER
THIS PLACE TRYING NOT TO DISTURB
THE EVIDENCE BY WEARING BOOTIES.
YOU CAN TELL THE CARS TELL THE
STORY HERE.
STILL HUNDREDS OF CARS AROUND
THIS AREA.
WE HAD SOME PEOPLE COME OUT LAST
NIGHT ASKING US IF THEY COULD
GET THEIR CAR, ASKING POLICE.
THEY'RE BEING TOLD NO.
WE'RE BEING TOLD THAT EVERY CAR
HAS TO MATCH UP TO A CERTAIN
PERSON.
AS WE ALL KNOW, SOME OF THESE
CARS WILL NOT BE PICKED UP BY
THEIR OWNERS.
THE FBI IS ON SCENE.
THEY'RE MAPPING CARS OVER HERE.
THERE'S A SPECIFIC PURPOSE.
SOME OF THESE CARS TRIED TO GET
OUT WHEN THE SHOOTING STARTED
AND RAN INTO A DEAD END.
THE GREEN JEEP HAS BLOOD-STAINED
HAND PRINTS ON THE HOOD.
IF YOU LEAVE THE CAR, LOOK
AROUND THE GROUND AND THERE'S
BLOOD PRINTS ALL THE WAY OUT
HERE.
THIS DOESN'T GIVE US MOTIVE BUT
GIVES US AN IDEA HOW THE
INVESTIGATORS ARE TRYING TO MAP
THIS INVESTIGATION, WHICH COULD
GO ON FOR WEEKS AND WEEKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: TRACELA G OGHALNER
EN
E.SC
CH
O OEAFNEHE T VICTIMS IN
LAS VEGAS HAS HIS OR OWN STORY.
ALL OF THEM HAVE PEOPLE THAT
CARE ABOUT THEM, WHO MISS THEM,
WHO MOURN THEM.
WE'LL REMEMBER THE ONES ABOUT
WHICH WE HAVE KNOWLEDGE AND TELL
YOU ABOUT THEIR LIVES NEXT.
FIRST, TWO YEARS AGO, THE
REPLICA EIFFEL TOWER AT THE
PARIS CASINO IN LAS VEGAS WENT
DARK IN MEMORY OF ALL THAT WENT
DIED IN A TERROR ATTACK IN THE
FRENCH CAPITOL.
LAST NIGHT, THE ORIGINAL
RETURNED THE RESPECT.
DARKENING THOSE THAT WERE KILLED
IN LAS VEGAS AND A WEEKEND
TERROR ATTACK IN MARSEILLE.
THE NEWS CONTINUES NEXT.
al stooe
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night,
so he got home safe.
Yeah, my dad says our
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
If you have Medicare
Parts A and B
guess what?
You could apply for a
Medicare supplement insurance
plan whenever you want.
No enrollment window.
No waiting to apply.
That means now may be a
great time to shop for an
AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Medicare doesn't
cover everything.
And like all standardized
Medicare supplement
insurance plans,
these help cover some
of what Medicare
doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide.
It could help you find the
AARP Medicare Supplement plan
that works for you.
These types of plans have
no networks,
so you get to choose any
doctor who accepts
Medicare patients.
Rates are competitive,
and they're the only plans
of their kind endorsed by AARP.
Remember -
these plans let you apply
all year round.
So call today.
Because now's the perfect time
to learn more.
Go long.
>> Shepard: MUCH OF THE FOCUS IN
LAS VEGAS HAS BEEN ON THE
SHOOTER FOLLOWING THE MASSACRE.
BUT STORIES AFTER HEROISM
CONTINUE TO EMERGE.
FOR INSTANCE, 30-YEAR-OLD COPY
MACHINE REPAIR MAN JONATHAN
SMITH.
ACCORDING TO "THE WASHINGTON
POST," THE FATHER OF THREE WAS
SEPARATED FROM HIS FAMILY BUT
STAYED BEHIND TO DIRECT DOZENS
OF PEOPLE TO SAFETY.
A BULLET STRUCK HIM IN THE NECK
LEAVING HIM WITH A CRACKED RIB
AND BRUISED LINK.
THEN THERE'S 29-YEAR-OLD MARINE
VETERAN TAYLOR WINSTON WHO SAID
HE STOLE A TRUCK TO DRIVE PEOPLE
TO THE HOSPITAL.
HE TRANSPORTED BETWEEN 20 AND 30
PEOPLE AND LATER RETURNED THE
KEYS TO THE TRUCK'S OWNER AND
THEN THERE'S TRAVIS PHIPPEN AN
EMT.
HE STAYED BEHIND TO REVIVE HIS
FATHER THAT WAS SHOT.
ONE OF THE GUNMAN'S BULLETS HIT
TRAVIS WHO IS EXPECTED TO
SURVIVE.
HIS FATHER DID NOT MAKE IT OUT
ALIVE.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE WENT TO
HOSPITALS AFTER THE SHOOTING AND
SOME DOCTORS HAVE SAID IT WAS
VERY TOUGH TO KEEP UP AS THE
PATIENTS KEPT COMING.
OUR CHIEF CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN
HUNT IS LIVE AT UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL CENTER IN LAS VEGAS.
JONATHAN, HOW MANY PATIENTS ARE
STILL LISTED AS CRITICAL?
>> WELL, THERE'S TWO HOSPITALS
WITH CRITICAL PATIENTS NOW.
OVER AT SUNRISE MEDICAL, THEY
HAVE 33 IN CRITICAL CONDITION.
HERE AT UNIVERSITY MEDICAL
CENTER, 20 REMAIN AT THIS POINT
IN THE ICU.
I SPOKE TO ONE OF THE SURGEONS
WHO HAS BEEN WORKING DAY AND
NIGHT HERE.
HE SAID MANY OF THE GUNSHOT
WOUNDS WERE SO HORRIFIC, A LOT
OF THE STAFF WILL LIKELY NEED
PSYCHOLOGICAL HELP.
LISTEN HERE.
>> THERE WAS A LOT OF ANXIETY
AND LOSS OF FOCUS.
THAT CAN BE EASILY CORRECTED.
THE UNCONSCIOUS FORMS OF STRESS
ARE THINGS THAT AFFECT PEOPLE IN
THE SECOND AND THIRD DAY.
WE HAVE DEBRIEFING TEAMS
OFFERING SERVICE TO THE STAFF.
>> A REMINDER, SHEP, AS WELL AS
SO MANY PHYSICAL SCARS, THERE
WILL BE MANY MENTAL SCARS THAT
WILL TAKE A LONG TIME TO HEAL.
>> TELL US HOW THE MURDERER
MODIFIED THE WEAPONS TO SHOOT
MORE BULLETS QUICKLY.
>> YEAH,  WE TALKED TO AN ATF
SERVICE THAT SAID SOME OF THE
WEAPONS WERE MODIFIED AS WHAT IS
CALLED A SLIDE-FIRE MECHANISM.
THE INFORMATION APPARENTLY AND
THE COMPONENTS TO DO THAT EASILY
AVAILABLE ON THE INTERNET.
THIS VIDEO IS FROM ONE SUCH
SITE.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT MR. PADDOCK
USED THIS PARTICULAR SITE, OF
COURSE, BUT IT'S AN EXAMPLE OF
WHAT IS OUT THERE.
WHAT IT DOES, ACCORDING TO OUR
SOURCE, IS CHANGED THE SHOULDER
REST AND EFFECTIVELY MAKE THE
TRIGGER MIMIC FULLY AUTOMATIC
OPERATION.
OUR SOURCE SAYS THAT IT
BASICALLY TURNS A SEMIAUTOMATIC
RIFLE INTO A MACHINE GUN AND
REMEMBER, PADDOCK WAS ARMED WITH
MORE THAN ONE MACHINE GUN.
THAT'S THE KIND OF FIREPOWER
THAT RAINED DOWN ON THOSE
INNOCENT CONCERT GOERS.
>> THANKS, JONATHAN.
FIRST A LOOK AT MORE OF THE
VICTIMS.
MEN AND WOMEN MURDERED AT A WARM
WEEKEND NIGHT IN LAS VEGAS.