accident-free.
And I don't share it
with Mom. Right, Mom?
Right.
Safe Driving Bonus Checks,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH A FOX
REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
IN SPAIN, LAWMAKERS IN THE
NORTHEASTERNNGO BREAKAWAY
FROM THE COUNTRY NEXT WEEK.
THOUSANDS FILL THE STREETS IN
BARCELONA TO PRO TEST A RECENT
POLICE CRACKDOWN THAT INJURED
HUNDREDS.
TWO WEEKS AFTER A MASSIVE
EARTHQUAKE IN MEXICO, SEARCH
TEAMS HAVE RECOVERED THE LAST
KNOWN BODY.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM THE MAYOR
OF MEXICO CITY AS RESEARCHERS
DUG THROUGH A COLLAPSED OFFICE
BUILDING.
OFFICIALS SAY 369 PEOPLE HAVE
DIED AFTER THE 7.1 MAGNITUDE
QUAKE.
AND E. COLI AND BACTERIA HAVE
BEEN FOUND AT A SWIMMING VENUE
FOR THE SUMMER OLYMPICS IN
TOKYO.
ORGANIZERS SAY WATER TESTING
SHOWED E. COLI LEVELS 20 TIMES
HIGHER THAN THE LIMITS.
ORGANIZERS HAVE PROMISED TO
IMPROVE THE WATER QUALITY.
THE NEWSES CONTINUES WITH
SHEPARD SMITH AFTER THIS.
>> Shepard: ACTUALLY, A LITTLE
NKIBREWNG SHERE
.
MONENEDTIHE TREENS PASTID
MEETING WITH FIRST RESPONDERS IN
LAS VEGAS.
WE'RE WAITING FOR HIM TO WALK IN
THE ROOM.
HE'S DONE SO.
NOTICE WE'RE USING AN INTERNET
CONNECTION HERE, THE WHITE HOUSE
POOL IS, BECAUSE OF WHERE IT IS.
IT'S A LITTLE GLITCHY.
IT TENDS TO CLEAR UP.
WE WANT YOU TO HEAR WHAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS TO SAY.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> THIS IS WHERE WE DO ALL THE
OPERATIONAL DECISIONS IN THE
AREA.
ALL INVESTIGATIVE LEADS,
EVERYTHING THAT YOU CAN IMAGINE
FUNNELS THROUGH HERE.
THIS IS WHERE -- ACTUALLY,
JOINING FORCES.
ALL OF THE DEPARTMENT OF PUBLIC
SAFETY REPRESENTATION HERE ALONG
WITH EMERGENCY MANAGERS AND
HOSPITAL SYSTEMS, THE FIRST
RESPONDER MEDICAL SYSTEMS AND
EVERYTHING THAT YOU CAN IMAGINE.
SO WE CAN SPEAK WITH ONE VOICE.
THAT'S THE IMPORTANT PIECE.
SO A LOT OF THESE FOLKS ARE NOT
SUPPOSED TO BE IN HERE BUT
YOU'RE HERE.
SO THESE ARE ALL THE PEOPLE THAT
ARE INSTRUMENTAL IN THE SUCCESS
OF OUR CRITICAL JOB.
THEY'RE ALL PART OF THE SUCCESS
FOR THE CONTINUANCE OF THE
INVESTIGATION.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR YOU TO SEE
WHAT YOUR LEADERSHIP IS
PROVIDING YOU.
>> I CAN TELL YOU ON BEHALF OF
OUR COUNTRY, OUR GREAT, GREAT
COUNTRY, WE WANT TO THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE BEEN A REAL
INSPIRATION.
THIS IS A ROUGH TIME, BUT IF YOU
DIDN'T GET UP THERE SO QUICKLY,
COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE A LOT
WORSE.
WE JUST WANT TO THANK YOU.
THE WHOLE WORLD IS WATCHING.
THEY'VE SEEN PROFESSIONALISM
LIKE YOU RARELY SEE.
I WANT TO THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Shepard: THIS IS A POOL
CAMERA.
THE WHITE HOUSE POOL WHICH
FOLLOWS THE PRESIDENT EVERYWHERE
HE GOES.
EACH OF THE NETWORKS AND THE
WHITE HOUSE POOL TAKES A DAY AND
TODAY THE POOL IS ONE OF THE SIX
OR SEVEN NETWORKS, SIX NETWORKS
THAT WERE PART OF THE WHITE
HOUSE POOL.
THEY'RE JUST FOLLOWING.
OH, LET'S LISTEN AS LONG AS HE'S
SAYING HELLO.
WE'LL GET THE WHITE HOUSE POOL
OUT OF THE ROOM ON THE
INSTRUCTIONS OF THE PRESS
SECRETARY.
JOHN ROBERTS FAMILIAR WITH THIS.
IN A COUPLE MOMENTS, HE'S GOING
TO A BIT MORE FORMAL SETTINGS
WHERE HE WILL MEET WITH POLICE
CHIEFS AND OTHERS.
>> YES, HE WILL BE MAKING BRIEF
REMARKS.
IT'S A FIVE NETWORK POOL.
IT'S UNDERSTAND, CNN, ABC AND
CBS AND US.
WE WERE HOPING HE WOULD COME
BACK IN TO TALK WITH US, GIVE US
THOUGHTS ABOUT TODAY AND MAYBE
TALK ABOUT OTHER NEWS OF THE DAY
AND THE ISSUES SWIRLING AROUND
THIS INCREASINGLY LOUD VOICES ON
CAPITOL HILL.
BUT HE HAD A LOT OF COMPANY WITH
HIM ON BOARD AIR FORCE ONE.
KEVIN McCARTHY WAS WITH HIM,
SENATOR HELLER AND HIS WIFE,
MELANIA WAS THERE WITH HIM.
SO THE PRESIDENT STAYED IN THE
FORWARD CABIN.
YOU CAN SEE THE BREAK-UP.
IT'S A UNIT THAT OPERATES ON
CELL SERVICE.
HOOKS IN TO A DIFFERENT OF CELL
NODES.
IF YOU'RE OUTSIDE, YOU GET
PRETTY GOOD RECEPTION.
SOMETIMES INSIDE, YOU LOSE
CONNECTIVITY AND THE PICTURE
GOES FUZZY LIKE THAT.
IT'S A WAY TO BRING YOU
IMMEDIATE PICTURES FROM
SOMETHING THAT NORMALLY WE
WOULDN'T HAVE ACCESS TOO.
LATER ON WHEN WE GET THE
FEEDBACK OVER THE SATELLITE,
YOU'LL SEE THE PICTURES IN THE
ENTIRETY AND CLARITY.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO MAKE
SPECIAL MENTION, SHEP, I'M TOLD
BY SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS WHO
SAW IT ON THE WAY HERE BEFORE WE
LANDED, WANTS TO MAKE SPECIAL
MENTION OF THE CIVILIANS WHO AT
RISK TO THEIR OWN LIVES AND SOME
OF THEM DID DIE DOING THIS,
PROTECTED OTHER PEOPLE,
PROTECTED LOVED ONES, TRIED TO
GET PEOPLE OUT OF THE AREA, DID
WHATEVER THEY COULD TO GET
PEOPLE TO THE HOSPITALS.
THESE ARE CITIZEN HEROS, SHEP
THAT THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO
HONOR.
WE'LL SEE THEM IN A COUPLE
MINUTES.
HE'S TOURING THE COMMAND CENTER
THERE WITH THE SHERIFF WHO HAS
DONE AMAZING WORK IN THE WAKE OF
THIS HORRIBLE TRAGEDY.
YOU CAN IMAGINE, YOU CAN
PROBABLY COUNT ON ONE HAND THE
NUMBER OF HOURS OF SLEEP HE'S
HAD.
THE PRESIDENT TAKING THE TOUR OF
THE COMMAND CENTER, MEETING WITH
THE FIRST RESPONDERS AND WE'LL
HEAR FROM HIM SHORTLY WHERE HE
WILL PAY TRIBUTE TO THE BRAVE
MEN AND WOMEN OF LAW ENFORCEMENT
THAT PUT THEIR LIVES ON THE LINE
AND THE CIVILIANS THAT DID THE
SAME THING SUNDAY NIGHT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: JOHN, THANKS SO
MUCH.
THE ROOM BEGINNING TO FILL WHERE
THE PRESIDENT WILL GREET THOSE
FOLKS.
THEY'VE BEEN FILLING IN THE DOOR
ON THE LEFT TO OUR LEFT SIDE OF
THAT -- THE BLUE WALL BACK
THERE, THE BLUE CURTAIN.
YOU'LL SEE MORE COMING IN NOW.
IT'S OUR BELIEF THE PRESIDENT IS
ON HIS WAY RIGHT NOW.
THE OTHER STORY OF THE DAY HAS
BEEN THE REPORTS ON SECRETARY
TILLERSON.
IT WAS BACK IN THE SUMMER THAT
CNN REPORTED AND NBC REPORTED
OVERNIGHT AND INTO THIS MORNING,
I THINK THEY DEBUTED IT ON
MORNING JOE, THAT REX TILLERSON
SAID I'M DONE, I'M GOING TO
TEXAS.
BUT THE PRESIDENT INTERVENED IN
SOME WAY AND IT NEVER HAPPENED.
NOW SECRETARY TILLERSON HAS SAID
NONE OF THAT HAPPENED, IT'S FAKE
NEWS.
NBC NEWS STANDS BY ITS
REPORTING.
WITH THAT, WE RETURNED TO A.B.
STODDARD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF
THIS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY TIMES I
TRIED TO QUIT AROUND HERE.
EVERYBODY HAS BAD DAYS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF
THIS.
SECRETARY TILLERSON SAYS IT'S
FAKE NEWS.
NBC NEWS STANDS BY IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHO TO MAKE OF IT.
>> THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
REPORTING BETWEEN THE TENSION OF
THE WEST WING AND THE WHITE
HOUSE.
REX TILLERSON WAS THE MOST
POWERFUL MEN IN THE WORLD, HEAD
OF EXXON MOBIL.
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO HAVE REPORTERS
FOLLOWING HIM AROUND ASKING HIM
QUESTIONS IN HIS OLD LIFE ABOUT
GLOBAL CONFRONTATIONS, HAVING TO
DO WITH NATIONAL SECURITY.
HE'S NOT TOTALLY AT EASE IN ALL
THE ASPECTS OF THE JOB BUT HE
MADE COMMENTS TODAY THAT WERE
VERY COMPELLING ABOUT HIS
COMMITMENT TO THE PRESIDENT AND
THE PRESIDENT'S AGENDA AND THAT
AS A TEAM THEY'LL STICK
TOGETHER.
THEY'VE HAD SUCCESS.
HE COMPLIMENTED NIKKI HALEY THAT
SAID WOULD REPLACE HIM IF HE
LEFT.
THERE'S A LOT OF TALK ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT HE HAS BEEN
PERFORMING A JOB THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP APPROVES OF.
THAT HE'S BEEN SLOW TO HIRE --
>> Shepard: THAT WAS THE POINT.
>> HE'S NOT DOING THINGS THE WAY
THAT THE WHITE HOUSE WANTS HIM
TO BE DOING THEM.
BUT ALL THIS GOSSIP ABOUT WHAT
HE'S CALLED THE PRESIDENT AND
ALL OF THAT STUFF OBVIOUSLY GETS
TO THE TOP OF THE HEADLINES.
THIS IS AN EXTRAORDINARY
SITUATION.
ALSO BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT SENT
OUT A TWEET UNDERMINING HIM
SAYING HIS WASTING HIS TIME IN
CHINA TALKING ABOUT HOW WE HAVE
PASSIVE NEGOTIATION OR DIALOGUE
WITH THE NORTH KOREANS.
HE'S WORKING ON A DIPLOMATIC
SOLUTION TO A GRAVE CRISIS.
MANY PEOPLE SAID ON SUNDAY LIKE
RICHARD HAAS, REPUBLICAN FOREIGN
POLICY EXPERT WITH EXPERIENCE,
THAT REX TILLERSON SHOULD RESIGN
AFTER THE WAY THE PRESIDENT
SPOKE ABOUT HIM.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY FILLED WITH
TENSION AND THEY BOTH SOUNDED
LIKE THEY WANT TO WORK.
THE VERY UPBEAT IS HONORED BY
TILLERSON'S COMMENTS, BUT
THERE'S MORE BEHIND THE SCENES
THAN WE UNDERSTOOD.
>> Shepard: THERE'S A LOT THERE.
WE HEAR FROM THE STATE
DEPARTMENT OFFICIALS THAT
THERE'S GREAT CONCERN AND GREAT
FRUSTRATIONS THAT THE POSITIONS
HAVE NOT BEEN FILLED.
ON THE MATTER OF THE PRESIDENT'S
TWEET REGARDING SECRETARY
TILLERSON IN NORTH KOREA, THE
PRESIDENT SAID DON'T WASTE YOUR
TIME, SECRETARY TILLERSON.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED WHAT NEEDS
TO BE DONE.
IN OTHER WORDS, STOP YOUR
DIPLOMACY.
IT'S HIS JOB TO HEAD UP THE
A LOT OF CONSERVATIVES THAT ARE
VERY UPSET ABOUT WHAT IT WAS
THAT THE PRESIDENT TWEETED
BECAUSE IF HE MEANT IT, IT'S
HARD TO SAY THAT HE MEANT
ANYTHING OTHER THAN WE'RE GOING
DO WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
SOUNDS LIKE HE'S TALKING ABOUT
SOMETHING AGGRESSIVE.
>> ALSO JUST WHAT IT SHOWS TO
THE CHINESE WHEN REX TILLERSON
AS OUR SECRETARY OF STATE IS
OVER IN CHINA DOING THIS VERY
DIFFICULT WORK.
THIS IS VERY SENSITIVE WORK.
WHAT IT SHOWS WITH THE PRESIDENT
UNDERMINING HIM AND THROWING HIM
UNDER THE BUS AND UNDERMINING
THE IMPORTANCE OF DIPLOMACY
SENDS A WORRISOME SIGNAL ABOUT
HOW HE'S TREATING REX TILLERSON
AND HOW HE'S HANDLING THE
PROCESS IN TERMS OF WHAT HE'S
ASKING THE CHINESE TO DO TO TRY
TO MITIGATE THE THREAT OF NORTH
KOREA.
WE VERY MUCH OBVIOUSLY DEPEND ON
THE CHINESE IN THIS SITUATION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO HIS CREDIT
HAS GOTTEN THE CHINESE
GOVERNMENT TO STOP ALL CENTRAL
BANK ACTIVITY WITH THE NORTH
KOREANS.
THAT'S A HUGE STEP.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT COULD HAVE
GREAT -- COULD BE CONSEQUENTIAL
IF THEY ACTUALLY ENFORCE IT.
BUT IT'S A REAL QUESTION ABOUT
NOT ONLY TRUMP'S LEADERSHIP WHEN
HE DOES SOMETHING LIKE THAT
TWEET, BUT HOW LONG PEOPLE THAT
WORK UNDERNEATH HIM AND REPORT
TO HIM CAN ACTUALLY CONTINUE TO
DO THEIR JOBS IF THEY'RE TREATED
THAT WAY.
THAT'S A VERY CRITICAL JOB.
BEING SECRETARY OF STATE AND
TRYING TO HANDLE THE NORTH KOREA
CRISIS IS AT THE TOP OF THE
LIST.
>> Shepard: THERE'S A LOT ON THE
PLATE TODAY.
NOW THE PRESIDENT MAKING THE
ROUNDS OUT IN LAS VEGAS AND
SAYING WE'RE GOING TO DISCUSS
GUN CONTROL AT A LATER DAY.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
SUGGESTED OVER TIME PRESIDENT
TRUMP THAT USED TO BE MUCH MORE
LIBERAL IN MANHATTAN WAS --
MIGHT HAVE BEEN MORE FOR GUN
CONTROL AT A TIME BEFORE HIS
PRESIDENCY.
I KNOW BECAUSE I READ THE MAIL
AND STUFF THAT THERE'S A LOT OF
CONSERVATIVES CONCERNED THAT HE
MIGHT BECOME MORE PRO GUN
CONTROL IN THE DAYS AHEAD.
>> THE SUPPORTERS THAT PUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN OFFICE ARE
LITTLE CONCERNED THAT HE'S NOT
GOTTEN OUT OF THE TRADE
AGREEMENTS EXCEPT FOR THE TRANS
PACIFIC PARTNERSHIP.
HE'S PUT MORE TROOPS IN
AFGHANISTAN.
AND THAT HE WAS WILLING TO TALK
ABOUT DOING AN AGREEMENT ON
IMMIGRATION WITH THE DEMOCRATIC
LEADERS IN CONGRESS.
SO THERE'S A LOT OF CONCERN
ABOUT HIS UNPREDICTABILITY AND
WHETHER OR NOT HE IS MORE TO A
SET OF IDEALOGICAL PRINCIPLES
THAT HE WILL STICK TO AS
PRESIDENT.
HE'S ON THE RECORD IN THE PAST
BEING SUPPORTING GUN CONTROL.
HE'S A WILD CARD, SHEP.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY WILL
HAPPEN WITH HIM.
IF HE CREATES A BRIDGE,
SOMETHING COULD HAPPEN.
>> Shepard: WE'LL SEE.
HE SAYS HE WILL DISCUSS IT IN
THE DAYS AHEAD.
AS THAT HAPPENS, WE'LL FOLLOW
THE DEVELOPMENTS AS THEY COME.
IN ONCE AGAIN, FOX TELEVISION
STATIONS ACROSS THE NATION WILL
JOIN US RIGHT NOW.
GOOD AFTERNOON FROM FOX NEWS IN
NEW YORK.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THE PRESIDENT THIS AFTERNOON IS
IN LAS VEGAS WHERE HE'S ABOUT TO
MEET WITH FIRST RESPONDERS.
THESE ARE POLICE CHIEFS, FIRE
OFFICIALS AND OTHERS THAT WERE
INSTRUMENTAL IN ENDING THE
MASSACRE THAT HAPPENED OUTSIDE
THE MANDALAY BAY AND LUXOR
HOTELS ON THE STRIP DURING THE
COUNTRY MUSIC FESTIVAL.
59 KILLED.
A LOT OF QUESTIONS ABOUT DEATH
TOLL.
THE GUNMAN DIED, ACCORDING TO
AUTHORITIES, KILLED HIMSELF.
THERE'S 59 OTHERS THAT HAVE DIED
AS ANOTHER DIED IN THE HOSPITAL.
THAT BRINGS THE DEATH TOLL TO
59.
MORE THAN 540 INJURED.
THE PRESIDENT SPREADING THE LOVE
OF THE PEOPLE AND THANKS FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE AND FROM THE
AMERICAN FEEL IN LAS VEGAS.
ABOUT A MINUTE AGO, WE GOT A
TWO-MINUTE WARNING ON THIS.
OUR VIEWERS ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL
HAVE BEEN LISTENING DELONG AS WE
DISCUSS THE OTHER NEWS ITEMS OF
THE DAY.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN CLEAR.
WE'VE SEEN HIM AT THREE
DIFFERENT APPEARANCES IN
LAS VEGAS SINCE HE ARRIVED A FEW
SHORT HOURS AGO.
HE AND THE FIRST LADY ARE THERE.
THE ORDER OF THE DAY HAS BEEN TO
THANK PEOPLE TO ALLOW THEM TO
TELL THEIR STORIES OF WHAT
HAPPENED DURING THE MASSACRE.
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT HOW ORDINARY
PEOPLE STEP FORWARD AND BECOME
EXTRAORDINARY INDIVIDUALS OR WE
LEARNED OF THEIR EXTRAORDINARY
FORTITUDE AS THEY HELPED PEOPLE
OUT, STORIES OF PEOPLE PUTTING
FOLKS IN THE BACK OF THEIR
TRUCKS TO TAKE THEM TO
HOSPITALS.
PEOPLE PLUGGING WOUNDS, STOPPING
BLOOD FROM FLOWING OUT OF
PEOPLE'S BODIES.
THERE'S NO TELLING SPECIFICALLY
HOW MANY PEOPLE WERE SAVED AS A
RESULT OF THE ACTIONS OF PEOPLE
THAT WERE NOT DOCTORS.
THEY WERE JUST PEOPLE THAT
STEPPED IN TO TRY TO HELP AT A
MOMENT'S NOTICE.
JOHN ROBERTS IS THERE.
HE'S THE CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT.
JOHN, A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT NEED
REST IN THAT CITY, ESPECIALLY
THE ONES WE'VE BEEN LISTENING TO
HAVE BEEN MIGHTY GLAD TO SEE THE
PRESIDENT.
>> IT'S NOT JUST THE PHYSICAL
FATIGUE, EITHER.
THE MENTAL FATIGUE AS WELL.
LIVING EVERY DAY WITH WHAT
HAPPENED SUNDAY NIGHT AND IT
SPREADS ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THE MAJORITY OF PEOPLE WOULD
HAVE BEEN VISITORS FROM OUT OF
TOWN HERE FOR THE WEEKEND AND
JUST WANTED TO ENJOY SOME
COUNTRY MUSIC AND JASON ALDEAN
PACKING IN A CROWD OF 22,000
PEOPLE.
YOU CAN IMAGINE WHAT WAS GOING
ON IN THE CONCERT WHEN FROM THE
32nd FLOOR WINDOWS BEHIND ME,
THIS GUY PADDOCK TOOK THE
SEMIAUTOMATIC WEAPONS THAT WERE
CONVERTED TO FEAR NEW HAMPSHIRE
AUTOMATIC RATE OF FIRE AND START
RAINING HELLFIRE DOWN UPON
PEOPLE THERE JUST LISTENING TO
MUSIC.
SO MANY OF THEM RAN FOR THE EXIT
AS YOU WOULD EXPECT AS MANY
PEOPLE WOULD.
MANY OF THEM FELL TO THE GROUND
MORE TALLY WOUNDED OR SERIALLY
WOUNDED.
AND MANY DECIDED THEY WOULD
STAND AND HELP PEOPLE.
YOU CAN IMAGINE IN A STATE OF
FEAR AND SHOCK THAT THEY WOULD
DO THAT IS EXTRAORDINARY.
THAT'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT WILL
PAY TRIBUTE TOO.
>> Shepard: WE'RE WATCHING THE
CROWD MAKE ITS WAY IN THE ROOM.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN TOURING
THE COMMAND FACILITY THERE.
THIS IS A LAS VEGAS POLICE
DEPARTMENT COMMAND FACILITY.
IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING FROM THE
INFORMATION FROM LAS VEGAS
POLICE, AND THEY CALL THEM METRO
THERE, THAT WHAT THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT, THIS IS THE PLACE WHERE
THE CALLS WERE INCOMING.
IMAGINE HOW MANY PEOPLE GOT ON
THE PHONE CALLING THE POLICE
DEPARTMENT.
AND THEN THE POLICE DEPARTMENT
ITSELF TRYING TO ORGANIZE ALL OF
THE FIRST RESPONDERS COMING.
AT ONE POINT WE HEARD ON POLICE
RADIOS THEM TELLING PEOPLE TO
GET OFF OF NORTH LAS VEGAS
BOULEVARD BECAUSE THEY REALIZED
WHERE THE SHOTS WERE COMING FROM
IN THE NORTH TOWER OF MANDALAY
BAY.
BUT THE POLICE AT THE TIME SAID,
YOU KNOW, DON'T USE THAT HIGHWAY
BECAUSE YOU'RE IN SIGHT OF HIM.
THEY WERE VERY CONCERNED THAT
AUTHORITIES AND OTHERS ARRIVING
TO HELP IN THIS SITUATION WOULD
BECOME VICTIMS.
WE KNOW A NUMBER OF LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICERS THAT WERE
OFF DUTY AND AT THAT CONCERT
WERE INJURED IN ONE WAY OR
ANOTHER.
EIGHT I BELIEVE FROM THE STATE
OF CALIFORNIA FROM DIFFERENT
JURISDICTIONS.
DIFFERENT POLICE DEPARTMENTS
WITH DIFFERENT PEOPLE INJURED.
THE AUTHORITIES TOLD US THIS
MORNING THAT THEY'VE BEEN ABLE
TO IDENTIFY ALL BUT THREE OF THE
VICTIMS.
SADLY THEY REPORTED TO US SOME
OF THE VICTIMS WITH REALLY --
WERE LEFT IN A POSITION TO
IDENTIFY THEM.
AUTHORITIES ARE WORKING ON
IDENTIFYING THREE OF THEM WHO
DIED ON THAT FATEFUL NIGHT.
IN ADDITION, THE HOSPITAL
WORKERS WERE CONGRATULATED BY
THE PRESIDENT AND THANKED BY THE
PRESIDENT ON BEHALF OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
THEY DISCUSS HOW THE HALLWAYS,
THE TRAUMA CENTER AND THE OTHER
HOSPITALS IN THE AREA WERE JUST
LITERALLY OVERFLOWING WITH
PEOPLE.
MEDICAL -- SOME PEOPLE GETTING
OUT OF THEIR HOSPITAL BEDS TO
MAKE ROOM FOR OTHERS THAT WERE
MORE GRAVELY WOUNDED.
THE SAME IN AMBULANCES AS THEY
WERE LOADING PEOPLE IN
AMBULANCES TO TAKE THEM TO
HOSPITALS FROM THE SHOOTING
SCENE.
WE GOT WORD OF I DON'T KNOW HOW
MANY DOZENS OF PEOPLE THAT
TRANSPORTED VICTIMS TO THE
HOSPITALS IN VANS, TRUCKS.
SOME PEOPLE INJURED THEMSELVES
HELPING TO STOP THE BLEEDING OF
OTHER PEOPLE.
THE STORIES ARE ENDLESS OF MAN
AND WOMAN HELPING MAN AND WOMAN.
THERE WERE TEENAGERS INVOLVED
THERE AS WELL.
A MATT RUSH TO TRY TO GET OUT.
DIFFERENT PEOPLE TELLING STORIES
OF IF I DIDN'T KNOW TO CROUCH
DOWN AND WAIT AND WAIT FOR
INSTRUCTIONS OR BE RUNNING FOR
THE EXITS WHERE THE HUGE CROWDS.
THINK OF WHEN YOU EXIT A CONCERT
VENUE HOW LONG YOU HAVE TO STAND
AND WAIT FOR PEOPLE TO GET UP
THE AISLES IN CASES LIKE THAT
WHERE THERE'S AN ACTIVE SHOOTER
SHOOTING DOWN FROM THE 32nd
FLOOR.
WELL, THEY WERE IN MANY CASES
JUST DEFENSELESS AND OUT IN THE
WIDE OPEN.
CLAUDIA COWAN IS IN LAS VEGAS
WITH THE STORY WITH SOME OF
THESE VICTIMS.
CLAUDIA?
>> WELL, WITH SHEPARD, EVERY
STORY OF A VICTIM IS A LIFE CUT
SHORT.
THERE WAS A MEMORIAL LAST NIGHT
IN MARIN COUNTY, CALIFORNIA FOR
50-YEAR-OLD STACY ECHABAR.
VINCENT PUT HIS WIFE IN A PLACE
THAT HE THOUGHT WOULD BE SAFE
FOR HER WHILE HE HELPED OTHER
PEOPLE TO SCRAMBLE FOR SAFETY.
ONLY TO LEARN LATER THAT SHE HAD
DIED.
I CAN TELL YOU A LAS VEGAS
POLICE OFFICER THAT WAS OFF DUTY
OUT ENJOYING THE MUSIC SUNDAY
NIGHT, HE PASSED AWAY AS WELL
AND A VIGIL SUNDAY NIGHT.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: THANKS.
THE GOVERNOR IS INTRODUCING THE
PRESIDENT.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
>> THE FIRST RESPONDERS AND HOW
THEY REACTED TO THIS SITUATION
PROVIDED SO MANY LOVE AND CARE
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT WERE HARMED
BY THIS HORRIBLE INCIDENT.
THE MEDICAL COMMUNITY, THOSE
THAT CAME TO THE AID OF THESE
PEOPLE.
THE EMPLOYEES AT MGM RESORTS AND
HOW THEY RESPONDED AS WELL.
AND EVERYONE ELSE, PERFECT
STRANGERS AND HOW THEY RESPONDED
TO THIS AND GAVE LOVE AND
ASSISTANCE TO THEIR FELLOW MAN.
I ALSO WANT TO THANK THE PEOPLE
FROM ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND
ACROSS THE WORLD FOR THEIR
OUTPOURING OF SUPPORT AND
GENEROSITY THAT HAS COME HERE.
IT'S UNPRECEDENTED IN OUR
HISTORY.
MAKES US FEEL LIKE WE'RE NOT
ALONE AND GIVES US STRENGTH.
BRIEFLY I ATTENDED A CANDLELIGHT
VIGIL LAST NIGHT AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA.
IT WAS AN IMPROMPTU EVENT.
OVER 1,500 PEOPLE SHOWED UP ON
SHORT NOTICE.
WE ALL HELD CANDLES, WE ALL
HUGGED ONE ANOTHER.
WE HELD HANDS.
WE HELD THOSE FLAMES OUT IN
FRONT OF US TO SHOW TRIBUTE TO
THE VICTIMS AND THEIR FAMILIES
OF THIS HORRIBLE EVENT.
AND TO -- AT THAT MOMENT,
DESPITE HOW DARK AND COLD IT WAS
I SAW AND WE ALL SAW THE
GREATEST DARKNESS CAN'T PUT OUT
THE SMALLEST LIGHT.
WE COLLECTIVELY FELT FOR THE
FIRST TIME THE FIRST PANES OF
HOPE.
WE SAW DESPITE THE SADNESS AND
GRIEF AROUND US THAT WE'RE
RESILIENT AND THAT WE'RE
COMMITTED TO FIGHT AND RECOVER
AND BEGIN THE LONG PROCESS OF
HEALING.
WE HAVE A LONG HISTORY OF
PULLING TOGETHER.
YES, WE'RE HURT, WE'RE HURT
BADLY, BUT WE'RE NOT BROKEN.
AS I SAID, WE'VE SEEN GENEROSITY
ON A SCALE THAT IS UNPRECEDENTED
IN NEVADA HISTORY.
WE KNOW THAT WE WILL NEVER EVER
FORGET THIS HORRIFIC EVENT.
WE WILL MARCH FORWARD AS A
FAMILY, GIVING EACH OTHER
COMFORT, SUPPORT AND LOVE.
FUTURE WILL COME ONE DAY AT A
TIME.
WE ALL HAVE A CHOICE HOW WE'RE
GOING TO LIVE EACH DAY.
WE MUST BE GLAD, WE MUST BE
GOOD, WE MUST BE BRAVE.
WE MUST HAVE FAITH.
WE WILL EMERGE AS A STRONGER,
KINDER, BETTER STATE AND NATION.
GOD BLESS THE VICTIMS AND THEIR
FAMILIES.
MAY THEY GIVE THEM PEACE, GOD
BLESS OUR STATE AND THE NATION,
THE GREATEST NATION ON EARTH.
WITH THAT, I'M VERY PRIVILEGED
AND HONORED TO INTRODUCE THE
FIRST LADY AND THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
I PERSONALLY WANT TO THANK THEM
ON BEHALF OF ALL OF THE PEOPLE
OF NEVADA FOR TAKING THE TIME TO
COME OUT HERE AND PROVIDE US
THEIR SUPPORT AND THEIR COMFORT
AND EVERYTHING ELSE THAT THEY'LL
BRING TO US.
WITH THAT, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE THE
PRESIDENT OF OUR GREAT NATION,
DONALD TRUMP.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
GOVERNOR.
WE APPRECIATE THAT.
I WILL TELL YOU, THE PEOPLE OF
NEVADA AND THE EXTRAORDINARY
CITY HAVE SHOWN THE WORLD THEIR
INCREDIBLE CHARACTER, COURAGE
AND RESOLVE.
NEVADA IS REALLY A SPECIAL
PLACE.
I'M HONORED TO BE HERE TODAY AT
THE LAS VEGAS METROPOLITAN
POLICE DEPARTMENT AND THE
COMPANY OF HEROS.
THANK YOU TO OUR POLICE, OUR
FIREFIGHTERS AND TO OUR FIRST
RESPONDERS AND OF COURSE TO
SHERIFF LOMBARDO.
INCREDIBLE JOB YOU'VE DONE.
MAYOR GOODMAN.
HELLO, MAYOR.
SENATOR HELLER.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SENATOR CORTEZ, MAJORITY LEADER.
WHERE IS KEVIN.
KEVIN McCARTHY.
ADAM LAXAULT.
ALL OF THE GREAT CONGRESSMAN
WITH US TODAY FROM BOTH PARTIES.
WE JUST ARE VERY HONORED THAT
YOU COULD BE WITH US.
ON BEHALF OF THE GRATEFUL
NATION, MELANIA AND I THANK EACH
AND EVERY ONE OF YOU IN LAW
ENFORCEMENT IN THE DEPTHS OF
HORROR, WE WILL ALWAYS FIND HOPE
IN THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO RISK
THEIR LIVES FOR OURS.
THE MASS MURDER TOOK PLACE
SUNDAY NIGHT FILLS AMERICA'S
HEART WITH GRIEF.
AMERICA IS TRULY A NATION IN
MOURNING.
I VISITED THE HOSPITAL EARLIER
TODAY WHERE MANY VICTIMS ARE
STILL RECOVERS FROM THEIR
WOUNDS.
WE ASK GOD TO EASE THEIR
SUFFERING.
WE PRAY FOR THE RECOVERY OF THE
INJURED AND THOSE INJURED
OFFICERS THAT SO BRAVELY THROUGH
THEMSELVES INTO DANGER WHEN DUTY
CALLED.
AND WE GRIEVE THE LOSS OF THE
LAW ENFORCEMENT PERSONNEL WHO
WERE KILLED IN THIS VICIOUS
ATTACK.
MANY FAMILIES TONIGHT WILL GO TO
BED IN A WORLD THAT IS SUDDENLY
EMPTY, THE PEOPLE THEY SO DEARLY
LOVE WERE TORN AWAY FROM THEM
FOREVER.
OUR SOULS ARE STRIKEN WITH GRIEF
FOR EVERY AMERICAN WHO LOST A
HUSBAND OR A WIFE, A MOTHER OR A
FATHER, A SON OR A DAUGHTER.
WE KNOW THAT YOUR SORRY FEELS
ENDLESS.
WE STAND TOGETHER TO HELP YOU
CARRY YOUR PAIN.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
WE WILL NEVER LEAVE YOUR SIDE.
HERE AT THE POLICE DEPARTMENT,
WE REMEMBER ONE OF OUR OWN WHO
DIED THIS WEEK, CHARLES
HARTFIELD.
HE WAS A VERY, VERY SPECIAL
PERSON.
OFFICER HARTFIELD WAS A PROUD
VETERAN, A DEVOTED HUSBAND, A
LOVING FATHER.
HIS DEATH IS A TRAGIC LOSS FOR
THIS POLICE FORCE, FOR THIS CITY
AND FOR OUR GREAT NATION.
WE STRUGGLE FOR THE WORDS TO
EXPLAIN TO OUR CHILDREN HOW SUCH
EVIL CAN EXIST, HOW THERE CAN BE
SUCH CRUELTY AND SUCH SUFFERING.
WE CANNOT BE DEFINED BY THE EVIL
THAT THREATENINGS US OR THE
VIOLENCE THAT INCITES SUCH
TERROR.
WE'RE DEFINED BY THE LOVE, OUR
CARING AND OUR COURAGE.
IN THE DARKEST MOMENTS, WHAT
SHINES MOST BRIGHTLY IS THE
GOODNESS THAT THRIVES IN THE
HEARTS OF OUR PEOPLE.
THAT GOODNESS IS OUR LIGHT HOUSE
AND OUR SOLACE.
IS KNOWLEDGE.
THAT THE SOULS OF THOSE THAT
PASSED ARE NOW AT PEACE IN
HEAVEN.
HERE ON EARTH, WE'RE BLESSED TO
BE SURROUNDED BY HEROS.
AS ONE EYE WITNESS RECOUNTED
THIS WEEK, WHILE EVERYONE ELSE
WAS CROUCHING, POLICE OFFICERS
WERE STANDING UP AS TARGETS JUST
TRYING TO DISTRICT PEOPLE AND
TELL THEM WHERE TO GO.
THE OFFICERS WERE STANDING UP IN
THE LINE OF FIRE TO HELP THOSE
IN DANGER AND TO FIND OUT WHERE
THOSE HORRIBLE SHOTS WERE COMING
FROM.
WORDS CANNOT DESCRIBE THE
BRAVERY THAT THE WHOLE WORLD
WITNESSED ON SUNDAY NIGHT.
AMERICANS DENIED DEATH AND
HATRED WITH LOVE AND WITH
COURAGE.
WHEN THE WORD AND WORST OF