TODAY FOR THE FIRST "THE DAILY
BRIEFING."
HERE'S SHEP.
>> Shepard: PANIC AND CHAOS WHEN
THE SHOOTING BEGAN.
THOUSANDS DESPERATE FOR SAFETY
AS THE VEGAS KILLERS SPENT
MINUTES RAINING BULLETS ON A
MUSIC CONCERT.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN WE HEARD POPS
WHEN JASON ALDEAN CAME ON TO
PERFORM.
PEOPLE STARTED DROPPING BY THE
STAGE AREA AND BY US.
>> THE SHOTS KEPT COMING.
WE WERE GOING DOWN.
WHEN WE GOT DOWN, THERE WAS A
MAN THAT WAS SHOT RIGHT THERE.
THEY WERE TRYING TO TAKE HIM
OUT.
HE WAS BLOODY AND UNCONSCIOUS.
>> NOW 58 PEOPLE CONFIRMED DEAD.
515 HURT.
THE KILLER'S OWN BROTHER SAYS
HIS FAMILY HAS NO ANSWERS.
>> WE'RE SHOCKED, HORRIFIED,
COMPLETELY DUMBFOUNDED.
>> Shepard: AS ARE SO MANY
OTHERS.
BUT LAST NIGHT, AS THE BULLETS
FELL AND THE BODIES DROPPED,
HEROS ROSE TO CARRY THE WOUNDED,
TO COMFORT THE SURVIVORS, TO
OFFER THEIR BLOOD TO VICTIMS
THEY MAY NEVER MEET.
MOMENTS THAT REMIND OUR NATION,
WE STAND STRONGER THAN A
MURDEROUS MADMAN.
IN THE HORROR, THERE'S REASONS
FOR HOPE.
LET'S GET TO IT.
THE WHITE HOUSE REMEMBERING THE
VICTIMS OF THE DEADLIEST MASS
SHOOTING IN MODERN U.S. HISTORY.
A GUNMAN TURNING A MUSIC
FESTIVAL IN LAS VEGAS AS WHAT
WITNESSES DESCRIBE AS A HORROR
SHOW.
POLICE CONFIRM 58 PEOPLE DEAD,
MORE THAN 515 INJURED.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND FIRST LADY
MELANIA TRUMP LEADING A MOMENT
OF SILENCE OUTSIDE THE WHITE
HOUSE A SHORT TIME AGO.
[BELL RINGING].
ONE WOMAN THAT SAID SHE
WITNESSED THE SHOOTING SAID
THERE WAS BLOOD EVERYWHERE.
MORE THAN
22,000 PEOPLE WERE AT
THE COUNTRY MUSIC FESTIVAL LAST
NIGHT.
JASON ALDEAN ON STAGE WHEN THE
SHOOTING STARTED.
♪♪
[GUN SHOTS]
>> Shepard: YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
HEAR A STEADY STREAM OF GUN FIRE
CAUSING PANIC AND CONFUSION.
PEOPLE SCREAMING AND CRYING AS
THEY RUN FOR THEIR LIVES.
ONE PERSON SAID IT SOUNDED LIKE
A THOUSAND SHOTS AND THE
SHOOTING KEPT GOING NONSTOP.
[GUN SHOTS].
ANOTHER PERSON SAID THE CONCERT
VENUE FELT LIKE A KILL BOX
BECAUSE IT WAS SO HARD FOR
PEOPLE TO GET OUT.
OTHER WITNESSES SAY THEY SAW
PEOPLE PLUGGING BULLET HOLES
WITH THEIR FINGERS.
PEOPLE SAID THEY WEREN'T SURE
WHICH WAY TO RUN.
HERE'S A LOOK AT WHERE IT
HAPPENED ON THE VEGAS STRIP.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE GUNMAN WAS
ON THE 32nd FLOOR OF THE
MANDALAY BAY.
THE DISTANCE, A LITTLE MORE THAN
1/4 MILE TO THE STAGE.
PEOPLE SAID THEY DIDN'T KNOW
WHERE THE BULLETS WERE COMING
FROM AT FIRST.
THE GUNMAN HAD TWO ROOMS.
YOU CAN SEE THE WINDOW OPEN ON
THE LEFT, THE WINDOW OPEN ON THE
RIGHT.
THAT'S WHAT A COUNTY OFFICIAL
TOLD AN INDEPENDENT NEVADA
NEWSPAPER.
THE SUSPECT USED SOMETHING LIKE
A HAMMER TO OPEN OUT THE WINDOWS
AND THEN OPENED FIRE ON THE
CONCERT GROUNDS.
POLICE HAVE IDENTIFIED THE
GUNMAN AS THIS MAN, STEPHEN
PADDOCK.
THEY SAY HE LIVED IN MESQUITE,
NEVADA, ABOUT 80 MILES NORTH OF
LAS VEGAS.
HE HAD BEEN STAYING AT THE
MANDALAY BAY A FEW DAYS.
POLICE SAY SWAT TEAMS STORMED
HIS ROOM USING EXPLOSIVES.
>> SWAT HAS EXPLOSIVE BREACH.
EVERYBODY IN THE HALL NEEDS TO
MOVE BACK.
ALL UNITS MOVE BACK.
>> Shepard: AND THERE WAS AN
EXPLOSIVE BREACH.
THE OTHERS DID MOVE BACK.
POLICE SAY THEY FOUND THE GUNMAN
HAD KILLED HIMSELF.
THEY SAY HE HAD AT LEAST TEN
GUNS WITH HIM INCLUDING RIFLES.
THE "WALL STREET JOURNAL"
NEWSPAPER SAYS IT'S 18 TO 20
WEAPONS.
SOURCES TELL FOX NEWS THE NUMBER
IS HIGHER AND THE WEAPONS
INCLUDED FULLY AUTOMATIC RIFLES
WITH HIGH CAPACITY MAGAZINES.
THE GUNMAN'S BROTHER THAT LIVES
IN CENTRAL FLORIDA SAID HE'S
JUST AS SHOCKED AND CONFUSED AS
EVERYONE ELSE.
>> THERE'S NOT ANYTHING THAT I
CAN SAY.
I MEAN, HOW DO YOU -- MY BROTHER
DID THIS.
THIS IS LIKE IT WAS DONE -- LIKE
HE SHOT US.
WHERE THE HELL DID HE GET
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS?
HE'S NOT -- HE HAS NO MILITARY
BACKGROUND OR ANYTHING LIKE
THAT.
LIKE I SAID, HE'S A GUY THAT
LIVED IN A HOUSE IN MESQUITE AND
DROVE DOWN AND GAMBLED IN
LAS VEGAS.
HE CALLED HIS MOM UP AND SENT
HER A WALKER AND HE'S GIRLFRIEND
SENT HER COOKIES.
YOU KNOW.
I MEAN, THERE'S NOTHING -- YOU
KNOW.
LIKE I SAID, THERE'S NO
POLITICAL, THERE'S NO RELIGIOUS,
THERE'S NO ANY OF THAT STUFF.
>> Shepard: NOTHING FROM THE
BACKGROUND THAT WE KNOW ABOUT
YET.
THE BROTHER SAID THE SHOOTER WAS
NOT NORMAL, A HIGH STAKES
GAMBLER, PARTICULARLY VIDEO
POKER.
HE SAID HEARING HIS BROTHER WAS
A SHOOTER WAS LIKE AS IF AS
ASTEROID FELL OUT OF THE SKY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP CALLING THE
SHOOTING AN ACT OF PURE EVIL AND
ORDERING FLAGS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY TO HALF STAFF OUT OF
RESPECT FOR THE VICTIMS AND
THEIR FAMILIES.
JOHN ROBERTS LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS HE'S GOING TO
LAS VEGAS THIS WEEK.
>> HE WILL BE.
HE WILL BE GOING WEDNESDAY,
SHEP.
BUT CLEARLY THE PRESIDENT WILL
BE KEPT ABREAST OF A MAJOR
UNFOLDING FEDERAL INVESTIGATION
AS TO HOW PADDOCK GOT THE
WEAPONS, WHERE HE GOT THEM, WHY
HE WAS IN POSSESSION OF SO MANY
WEAPONS.
MANY GUN COLLECTORS HAVE FAR
MORE THAN THAT AND WHAT DROVE
HIM TO COMMIT THAT HEINOUS
MURDER LAST NIGHT IN
LAS VEGAS.
SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS WAS
VISIBLY EMOTIONAL THIS AFTERNOON
AND SAID IT WAS TOO EARLY TO
DECLARE THIS AN ACT OF TERROR.
WHEN THE PRESIDENT WENT ON
TELEVISION THIS MORNING, HIS
MAIN GOAL WAS TO TRY TO CONSOLE
THE PEOPLE WHO HAD BEEN INJURED,
CONSOLE THE SURVIVORS OF THOSE
THAT HAD BEEN KILLED AND CALM AN
ANXIOUS NATION.
LISTEN HERE.
>> IN MOMENTS OF TRAGEDY AND
HORROR, AMERICA COMES TOGETHER
AS ONE.
AND IT ALWAYS HAS.
WE CALL UPON THE BONDS THAT
UNITE US, OUR FAITH AND OUR
FAMILY AND OUR SHARED VALUES.
WE CALL UPON THE BONDS OF
CITIZENSHIP, THE TIES OF
COMMUNITY AND THE COMFORT OF OUR
COMMON HUMANITY.
OUR UNITY CANNOT BE SHATTERED BY
EVIL.
>> THE FIRST TIME THAT SOMETHING
LIKE THIS HAS HAPPENED ON
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S WATCH.
HE'S HAD MORE THAN HIS FAIR
SHARE OF DISASTERS.
BY THE WAY, SHEP, WE SHOULD
POINT OUT, IT TOOK THE SECOND
QUESTION FOR THE ISSUE OF GUN
CONTROL TO COME UP.
AS I SAID IN THE BEGINNING, A
MAJOR FEDERAL INVESTIGATION
GOING ON WITH ALCOHOL, TOBACCO
AND FIREARMS TO FIND OUT HOW
THIS MAN GOT AHOLD OF THE
WEAPONS THAT HE DID AND WHY HE
WAS IN THE POSSESSION OF
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS.
SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS DEFLECTED
ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT GUN CONTROL
SAYING THERE'S A TIME TO HAVE
POLICY DEBATES.
TODAY IS NOT THE DAY TO DO THAT.
TODAY IS THE DAY TO REMEMBER THE
VICTIMS OF THE SHOOTER AND TO
PRAY FOR THOSE THAT WERE SO
GRIEVE USUALLY WOUNDED.
NOW, THE PRESIDENT PLANS ON
LEAVING EARLY WEDNESDAY MORNING
FOR LAS VEGAS AFTER HE GETS BACK
FROM HIS TRIP TO PUERTO RICO AND
PERHAPS THE VIRGIN ISLANDS
TOMORROW.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO SPEND
TIME IN VEGAS.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THAT HE WANTS
TO SPENT MORE THAN A DAY IN
VEGAS.
BUT TODAY SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS
SAID THE ITINERARY FOR THE
MOMENT LOOKS LIKE HE WILL BE
THERE FOR WEDNESDAY AND NOTHING
BEYOND THAT, SHEP.
>> Shepard: MUCH MORE ON VEGAS
IN JUST A MOMENT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HEADED TO PUERTO
RICO TOMORROW AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA DEVASTATED THE TERRITORY
TWO WEEKS AGO.
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS ARE
WITHOUT POWER AND MANY NEED
BASIC SUPPLIES LIKE FOOD AND
WATER.
THE PRESIDENT WENT AFTER THE
MAYOR OF SAN JUAN ON TWITTER
OVER THE WEEKEND ACCUSING HER OF
POOR LEADERSHIP.
THAT WAS AFTER THE MAJOR SAID
THE ISLAND NEEDED MORE HELP FROM
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
BACK TO JOHN ROBERTS OF THE
WHITE HOUSE NOW.
PUERTO RICO TOMORROW.
>> YES.
HE'S GOING EARLY TOMORROW
MORNING TO SPEND AS MUCH TIME ON
THE GROUND AS HE CAN THERE.
THE PRESIDENT WAS CRITICAL OF
CARMEN CRUZ, THE MAYOR OF
SAN JUAN IN A SERIES OF TWEETS
OVER THE WEEKEND.
THE LATEST SAID WE'VE DONE A
REMARKABLE JOB IN THE SITUATION
IN PUERTO RICO.
PEOPLE ARE STARTING TO RECOGNIZE
THE AMAZING WORK DONE BY FEMA
AND MILITARY.
ALL BUILDINGS INSPECTED TO
SAFETY.
THANKS TO THE GOVERNOR OF PUERTO
RICO AND ALL OF THOSE WORKING SO
CLOSELY WITH THE FIRST
RESPONDERS.
FANTASTIC JOB.
YOU MENTIONED THAT CARMEN CRUZ
SAID THAT THE GOVERNMENT NEEDS
TO DO MORE.
FRIDAY MORNING SHE WAS CRITICAL
OF ELAINE DUKE, THE ACTING DHS
SECRETARY.
SHE SAID THERE WAS A GOOD NEWS
STORY TO THE FACT THAT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT WAS BEGINNING
TO GET SUPPLIES IN THE HARDEST
HIT AREAS.
IT'S NOT A GOOD NEWS STORY.
IT'S A PEOPLE DYING STORY.
I ASKED SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS
BEYOND THAT THOUGH, BECAUSE THIS
CLEARLY GOES DEEPER, WHAT ELSE
THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN TO HAVE
THE PRESIDENT RESPOND TO HER IN
A CRITICAL FASHION.
LET'S LISTEN TO THAT EXCHANGE.
>> THE PRESIDENT WAS VERY
SHARPLY CRITICAL OF MAYOR CRUZ.
OTHER THAN HER COMMENTS ON
FRIDAY MORNING WHICH SHE
CRITICIZED ELAINE DUKE FOR
SAYING THIS WAS A GOOD NEWS
STORY FOR DHS GETTING SUPPLIES
TO AREAS THAT WAS NEEDED, WHAT
WAS SHE DOING THAT PROMPTED
CRITICISM?
>> OUR FOCUS IS TO BRING THE
MAYOR IN THE COORDINATION
EFFORTS.
THIS ADMINISTRATION AS WELL AS
OTHER MEMBERS ON THE GROUND HAVE
REACHED OUT TO HER.
WE HOPE SHE WILL JOIN WITH US.
>> SO THERE'S CLEARLY A DEEPER
STORY THERE.
IT SORT OF REVOLVES AROUND THE
IDEA THAT SHE THOUGHT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT SHOULD BE
GOING TO HER.
FEMA HAS RESPONDED BY PUTTING A
LIAISON RIGHT WITH HER LITERALLY
AT HER SHOULDERS, SHEP.
WE'LL SEE TOMORROW WHEN THE
PRESIDENT GOES THERE IF IT IS
CONTENTIOUS.
>> Shepard: AND THE PRESIDENT
ALSO TWEETED ABOUT NORTH KOREA.
>> HE DID.
THAT WAS IN RESPONSE TO REX
TILLERSON SAYING THERE WERE
DIRECT ONE-ON-ONE COMMUNICATIONS
GOING ON BETWEEN THE UNITED
STATES AND NORTH KOREA.
THE PRESIDENT SEEMED TO SLAP THE
SECRETARY STATE BACK SAYING REX
TILLERSON DON'T WASTE YOUR TIME
WITH THAT.
SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS WAS ASKED
ABOUT THAT AT THE BRIEFING THIS
AFTERNOON.
HERE'S HOW SHE RESPONDED.
>> THERE'S A DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
TALKING AND PUTTING DIPLOMATIC
PRESSURE.
WE STILL STRONGLY SUPPORT
PUTTING DIPLOMATIC PRESSURE ON
NORTH KOREA, WHICH WE'RE
CONTINUING TO DO.
NOW IS NOT THE TIME TO HAVE
CONVERSATIONS WITH NORTH KOREA.
WE'VE ENCOURAGED ALL OF OUR
ALLIES AND PARTNERS TO DO MORE.
WE'RE GOING TO KEEP ALL OPTIONS
ON THE TABLE.
>> THAT'S THE VIEWPOINT FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THEY DON'T BELIEVE THAT KIM
JONG-UN HAS BACKED UP ENOUGH TO
WARRANT DIRECT TALKS WITH NORTH
KOREA.
THEY WANT TO SEE HIM COME TO
THEM TO SAY OKAY, I'M WILLING TO
DEAL, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JOHN.
COMPLETE COVERAGE THIS HOUR OF
THE SHOOTING IN LAS VEGAS.
AHEAD WE'LL GO LIVE TO THE
LAS VEGAS STRIP WITH NEW DETAILS
ON THE GUNMAN, HIS BACKGROUND
AND THE VICTIMS OF THIS HORRIBLE
AMERICAN TRAGEDY.
♪♪
If you have moderate to severe
Ulcerative Colitis or Crohn's,
and your symptoms have left you
with the same view,
it may be time for a different
perspective.
If other treatments haven't
worked well enough,
ask your doctor about ENTYVIO,
the only biologic developed
and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO works by focusing right
in the GI-tract
to help control damaging
inflammation
and is clinically proven to
begin helping many patients
achieve both symptom relief as
well as remission.
Infusion and serious allergic
reactions
can happen during or after
treatment.
ENTYVIO may increase risk of
infection,
which can be serious.
While not reported with ENTYVIO,
PML, a rare,
serious brain infection caused
by a virus may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you have
an infection,
experience frequent infections,
or have flu-like symptoms,
or sores.
Liver problems can occur
with ENTYVIO.
If your UC or Crohn's medication
isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO.
ENTYVIO. Relief and remission
within reach.
It's OK
that everybody
ignores me
when I drive.
It's fine, 'cause I get
a Safe Driving Bonus Check
every six months
I'm accident-free.
And I don't share it
with Mom. Right, Mom?
Right.
Safe Driving Bonus Checks,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS FIREWORKS.
THEN IT JUST DIDN'T STOP.
AND I'M LIKE DEBBY, THAT'S NOT
FIREWORKS.
PEOPLE STARTED RUNNING.
WE ASKED WHAT WAS GOING ON.
THEY SAID THERE WAS A SHOOTER.
WE REALIZED IT SOUNDED LIKE
MACHINE GUNS.
>> Shepard: A SURVIVOR OF THE
DEADLIEST MASS SHOOTING OUR
NATION HAS SEEN.
THE SHOOTER LIVED IN A
RETIREMENT COMMUNITY ON A
CULDESAC WITH A WIPE DESCRIBED
AS HIS GIRLFRIEND.
POLICE SAY SHE'S BEEN LOCATED
OUT OF THE COUNTRY AND IS NOT
HIS ACCOMPLICE.
BEFORE LIVING IN MESQUITE,
NEVADA, HE LIVED FOR EIGHT YEARS
IN MESQUITE, TEXAS.
AUTHORITIES IN BOTH TOWNS SAID
THEY NEVER HAD ANY CONTACT WITH
HIM.
THERE WAS LAWSUIT AGAINST
ANOTHER CASINO IN LAS VEGAS.
IT WAS LATER DISMISSED WITH
PREJUDICE.
SOMETHING ABOUT SAFETY
VIOLATIONS.
AND THERE WAS A TRAFFIC TICKET
IN 2010.
NOTHING ELSE THAT WE CAN FIND.
THOUGH HIS FATHER WAS ONCE A
BANK ROBBER AND ON THE FBI'S
MOST WANTED LIST DECADES AGO.
AS FOR THE VICTIMS, AUTHORITIES
SAY LAW ENFORCEMENT MEMBERS FROM
ACROSS CALIFORNIA AMONG THOSE
WOUNDED.
THE LAPD SAID TODAY THAT AN
OFF-DUTY OFFICER WAS SHOT IN THE
LEG AND EXPECTED TO RECOVER.
L.A. COUNTY SHERIFF OFFICIALS
SAY TWO OFF DUTY DEPARTMENT
EMPLOYEES WERE HIT BY GUN FIRE.
ONE CRITICAL.
THE OTHER STABLE.
ORANGE COUNTY CALIFORNIA
AUTHORITIES SAY ONE OFF DUTY
SHERIFF DEPUTIES, TWO WIVES
SUSTAINED WOUNDS.
BAKERSFIELD POLICE SAID ONE OFF
DUTY OFFICER WAS WOUNDED AND
EXPECTED TO SURVIVE.
POLICE IN ONTARIO, CALIFORNIA
SAID A 24-YEAR-OLD OFFICER THAT
WAS WOUNDED IS STABLE.
THE OFFICER'S WIFE HAD MINOR
INJURIES.
THAT BUT A HANDFUL OF THE MORE
THAN 515 VICTIMS LAST NIGHT.
TRACE GALLAGHER IS LIVE IN
LAS VEGAS FOR US THIS AFTERNOON.
TRACE?
>> SHEP, IT'S VITAL TO GIVE YOU
A PERSPECTIVE ON HOW VAST THIS
CRIME SCENE WAS AND HOW IT WENT
DOWN.
I WANT TO GO BACK TO THE WINDOWS
ON THE 32nd FLOOR.
IT'S TWO ROOMS THAT THE SHOOTER
BUILT FLAT FORMS ON TOP SO HE
CAN GET A BETTER ANGLE SHOOTING
DOWN.
IT'S DECEIVING.
THE WINDOW ON THE RIGHT IS ABOUT
A 45 DEGREE DIFFERENCE, WHICH IS
WAY INVESTIGATORS SAY HE WAS SO
EFFECTIVELY ABLE TO SHOOT DOWN
AT VARIOUS PARTS AT THE CROWD.
YOU LOOK DOWN AT THE STAGE
ACROSS THE STREET.
THE 22,000 WERE IN FRONT OF THAT
STAGE AND BETWEEN THE WINDOW AND
THE STAGE, WE'RE ABOUT 300 YARDS
BEHIND.
IF YOU LOOK OVER HERE, ALL THE
WAY ACROSS WHEN THE STAMPEDE
STARTED, SHEP, YOU HAVE A
LIBRARY OF SHOES AND HANDBAGS
AND BOTTLES AND NOW LOOK AT
THIS.
THIS GAIT WAS IN CONCRETE.
THE CROWD PUSHED THEIR WAY
THROUGH THIS.
AS YOU WIND YOUR WAY OVER HERE,
THEY PUSHED THEIR WAY ACROSS THE
STREET TO THIS BUILDING HERE.
YOU CAN HEAR THE GUYS PULLING
THE WINDOW OUT.
SOME OF THE VICTIMS WENT IN
THERE AND BROKE THIS WINDOW
BECAUSE THEY WANTED TO USE THAT
AS SHELTER.
THERE'S A LINE OF BLOOD DOWN
THERE.
THIS RIGHT HERE IS THE BACK
SIDE.
YOU CAN SEE THE TAIL SECTION OF
AN AREA PLANE.
THIS IS THE BACK SIDE OF
McCARRAN AIRPORT, THIS IS WHERE
IT ENDED.
THIS WAS ANOTHER FENCE THAT WAS
PUSHED DOWN AND PEOPLE WERE
MAKING THEIR WAY ON TO THE
GROUNDS OF McCARRAN AIRPORT.
LISTEN TO A FEW MORE OF THE
WITNESSES.
>> IT WAS PRETTY MUCH LIKE A WAR
SCENE INSIDE.
I'VE SEEN A LOT OF STUFF WITH
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT.
IT WAS HARD TO SEE.
THE BODIES WERE CARRIED
PROBABLY 1/2 MILE FROM THE
INCIDENT.
I PROBABLY PRONOUNCED 15 TO 20
PEOPLE INSIDE.
IT'S A VERY SAD DAY.
>> WE RAN.
EVERYBODY IS HIDING EVERYWHERE.
THEY'RE HIDING UNDER THE
BLEACHERS AND THE STANCHIONS AND
EVERYWHERE THEY COULD.
EVERYBODY IS TELLING TO US RUN,
RUN AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
>> RUN AS FAST AS YOU CAN.
WE SHOULD ALSO NOTE THAT INSIDE
THE MANDALAY BAY HOTEL BECAUSE
OF THE GUN FIRE, THE SMOKE, THE
ALARMS WENT OFF.
THAT IS ONE OF THE WAYS THAT
POLICE HONED IN ON THE AREA SO
QUICKLY.
>> Shepard: TRACE WHAT DO WE
KNOW ABOUT THE GUNNMAN HIMSELF?
>> YOU HEARD SOUND FROM STEPHEN
PADDOCK'S FAMILY.
THEY SAID THEY NEVER EXPECTED
THIS AND THEY THINK HE MIGHT
HAVE SNAPPED.
THIS IS NOT THE CASE OF A MAN
THAT SNAPPED.
THIS WAS METICULOUSLY AND
METHODICALLY PLANNED.
THE MANDALAY BAY, AS YOU KNOW,
NOBODY HAS BETTER SECURITY THAN
CASINOS IN VEGAS.
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO.
THEY'LL GO THROUGH THE LAST FOUR
DAYS OF VIDEO AND TRY TO PUT
TOGETHER A TIMELINE OF EXACTLY
HOW STEPHEN PADDOCK GOT THOSE
GUNS, 10, 11, MAYBE MORE INSIDE
THE HOTEL.
HOW HE HID THEM TO GET THEM
INSIDE.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE DOING THAT.
THEN YOU GO BACK TO HIS HOUSE IN
MESQUITE, TEXAS.
NOTHING OUT OF THE ORDINARY.
HE OWNED SOME GUNS.
HE WAS A HUNTER, A PRIVATE
PILOT.
THEY SAY THERE'S NO CONNECTION
AT ALL TO TERRORISM, SHEP.
>> Shepard: TRACE, TELL US MORE
ABOUT THE WOMAN LIVING WITH HIM
DESCRIBED AS A GIRLFRIEND.
>> YEAH, VERY QUICKLY.
WE DON'T REALLY KNOW IF THAT
LIVED TOGETHER AS BOYFRIEND OR
GIRLFRIEND OR AS ROOMMATES.
THE REASON HER NAME CAME UP IS
BECAUSE HER DEBIT CARD WAS
INSIDE THE HOTEL ROOM AT THE
MANDALAY BAY.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW IT GOT THERE.
RIGHT NOW SHE'S OUT OF THE
COUNTRY.
HE'S NOT CONSIDERED AS BEING
PART OF THE SHOOTING.
BUT THEY STILL WANT TO TALK TO
HER BECAUSE SHE MAY HAVE VITAL
INFORMATION ON HOW THIS
HAPPENED, SHEP.
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER IN
LAS VEGAS.
THANK YOU.
SOME FAMILIES ARE STILL WAITING
FOR WORD ON THEIR LOVED ONES
THAT WERE AT THE CONCERT.
WE'LL HEAD TO NEVADA'S ONLY
LEVEL ONE TRAUMA CENTER FOR A
LIVE UPDATE.
THAT'S STILL TO COME ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
Is that whole thing
still dragging on?
No, I took some pics
with the app and...
filed a claim, but...
You know how they send you
money to cover repairs and...
They took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid
right away, but...
at the very end of
it all, my agent...
Wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy.
But if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience
for any reason,
they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim Satisfaction
Guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
[VO] QuickBooks introduces
Rodney.
only from Allstate.
He has a new business teaching
lessons.
Rodney wanted to know how his
business was doing...
...so he got QuickBooks.
It organizes all his accounts,
so he can see his bottom line.
Ahhh...that's a profit.
Know where you stand instantly.
Visit QuickBooks-dot-com.
You do all this research
on a perfect car,
then smash it into a tree.
Your insurance company
raises your rates.
Maybe you should've done
more research on them.
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't
raise your rates due to
your first accident.
Switch and you could save $782
on home and auto insurance.
Call
for a free quote today.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>> Shepard: WE'RE LEARNING ABOUT
TWO OF THE VICTIMS IN LAS VEGAS.
FIRST, SONNY MELTON FROM BIG
SANDY, TENNESSEE, WHICH IS WEST
OF NASHVILLE.
RIGHT AROUND JACKSON, TENNESSEE.
FAMILY MEMBERS TOLD OUR STATION
WZTV HE WAS AT THE CONCERT AND
DIED PROTECTING HIS WIFE.
SONNY MELTON WAS A REGISTERED
NURSE THAT WORKED AT A HOSPITAL
IN JACKSON.
ACCORDING TO HIS FACEBOOK
PROFILE.
HIS WIFE SAID IN A STATEMENT, HE
SAVED MY LIFE AND LOST HIS.
LAS VEGAS POLICE ALSO CONFIRM
ONE OF THEIR OFFICERS DIED
DURING THE SHOOTING.
THEY SAY THE OFFICER WAS OFF
DUTY AT THE TIME.
NO NAME YET RELEASED.
ONE WITNESS TO THE MASSACRE IN
LAS VEGAS TELLS US THAT HE IS
STILL IN ABSOLUTE SHOCK, AS HE
PUTS IT.
HE SAYS HE AND HIS FIANCE WERE
TRAPPED IN A V.I.P. TENT WHERE
BULLETS WERE HITTING PEOPLE AND
FIRST RESPONDERS THROWING THEIR
BODIES ON PEOPLE TRYING TO
PROTECT THEM.
RUSSELL BLECK IS ON THE PHONE.
RUSSELL, WHAT DID YOU SEE AND
EXPERIENCE?
>> HEY, SHEP.
WE WERE IN THE V.I.P. TENT TO
THE RIGHT OF THE STAGE WHEN
EVERYTHING HAPPENED.
I HAVE VIDEO OF THE SHOOTING,
THE END OF THE CONCERT.
WE HEARD TWO -- LIKE THREE ROUND
BURSTS AND SOUNDED LIKE A FIRE
CRAMP OR AMP CRACKING.
I SAID THAT SOUNDED LIKE AN
AR-15.
AFTER THAT, WE JUST -- BULLETS
STARTED RAINING DOWN
RELENTLESSLY AND WOULDN'T STOP.
>> WAS THERE ANY ONE IN YOUR
IMMEDIATE AREA BECOME A VICTIM?
>> A LADY IN FRONT OF ME.
I SAW HER DROP TO THE SIDE.
EVERYBODY DROPPED DOWN LIKE A
FROG.
I DON'T KNOW --
>> Shepard: YOU'RE WATCHING
PEOPLE AROUND YOU DROP AS YOU --
LIKE A WHAT?
>> YEAH, JUST DROPPING LIKE --
LIKE YOU'RE GETTING IN A FROG
STANCE, LIKE CROUCHING AND HIDE.
I SAW ONE LADY TURN SIDEWAYS AND
SPIN AND FELL AND WE TOOK OFF
RUNNING.
TOOK COVER EVERY TIME THE
SHOOTER WOULD RELOAD.
THERE WAS A GAP THERE WHERE WE
COULD GET TO COVER.
AND THEN THE BULLETED STARTING
RAINING OUT AGAIN AND WE WOULD
JUMP BACK AND HIDE.
AS WE HIT, WE COULD HEAR THE
SOUNDS OF THE BULLETS COMING
THROUGH THE TENT.
I'M CRAWLING, GETTING HIT WITH
JUST BULLETS RICOCHETTING OFF
THE GROUND.
YOU CAN FEEL THE DIRT KICK UP AT
YOUR FACE.
THE AMOUNT OF CARNAGE
IS CRAZY.
>> ONE SECOND YOU'RE LISTENING
TO JASON ALDEAN AND THE NEXT
SECOND THIS IS HAPPENING.
HOW WERE YOU PROCESSING IT?
>> THERE WAS NO PROCESSING.
IT WAS CRAZY.
THE SHOOTER WAS SO FAR AWAY.
SO THE SOUND DIDN'T LIKE LIKE A
NATURAL GUNSHOT AT FIRST.
BUT THEN YOU SAW PEOPLE FALL TO
THE GROUND LIKE HEAPS, JUST LEFT
AND RIGHT.
THEN YOU CAN SEE WHERE THE
SHOOTER WAS SPRAYING.
YOU COULD SEE BULLETS COME
TOWARDS WHERE YOU ARE AND THEN
THEY MIGHT SKIP AWAY FROM YOU.
NO METHOD BEHIND IT.
YOU KEPT HEARING THE SHOTS OVER
AND OVER AGAIN.
>> Shepard: YOU WERE THERE WITH
YOUR FIANCE.
WHAT WERE THE TWO OF YOU DOING
AND SAYING TO EACH OTHER?
>> WELL, FIRST, WE GOT
SEPARATED.
WHEN THE FIRST HAPPENED, I WAS
GETTING A DRINK.
I HAD JUST LEFT THE CORNER OF
THE BAR AT THE END OF THE V.I.P.
TENT.
SHE WAS TOWARDS THE BACK.
LUCKILY MY BEST FRIEND WAS
THERE.
AS SOON AS THE SHOTS STARTED
HAPPENING, REALIZED WASN'T A
TECHNICAL MALFUNCTION.
BECAUSE THE MUSIC WAS PLAYING
CITY.
EVEN JASON ALDEAN HAD NO IDEA
WHAT HAPPENED.
LUCKILY I MANAGED TO FIND THEM
ABOUT FIVE MINUTES AFTER
EVERYTHING STARTED.
THEY WERE HIDING BEHIND THE BAR.
EVERYBODY WAS RUNNING TO THE
MAIN EXIT.
JUST TURN AROUND AND COME BACK
TOWARDS US.
SLOWLY MADE OUR WAY ACROSS THE
BIG FIELD.
YOU CAN SEE BODIES AND PEOPLE
SCREAMING AND YELLING FOR HELP.
WHEELCHAIRS GETTING KNOCKED
OVER.
YOU COULDN'T STOP TO HELP
ANYBODY.
THE BULLETS WERE -- WE'RE
TALKING HUNDREDS OF ROUNDS OVER
AND OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
RAPID SUCCESSION.
WOULD NOT STOP.
>> Shepard: WHERE DID YOU
EVENTUALLY FEEL SAFE?
>> MY HOUSE.
I LIVE TEN MINUTES FROM THE
STRIP.
IT TOOK US ABOUT 15 MINUTES FROM
THE TIME IT STARTED TO SLOWLY
MAKE OUR WAY.
ALL WHILE UNDER FIRE.
IT WAS A BATTLE ZONE.
NOTHING THAT YOU