KIM JUDGE UN HAS CALLED
PRESIDENT TRUMP MENTALLY
DERANGED.
THE PRESIDENT REACHING BACK,
CALLING HIM A MADMAN.
NOW THE NORTH COULD REANSWER
THREATENING THE BIGGEST EVER
HYDROGEN BOMB TEST IN THE
PACIFIC OCEAN.
JEFF HORIGIAN A MILITARY
COMMANDER WHO RUNS THE AIR FAR
AGAINST THE ISLAMIC STATE.
RUNS MISSES IN AN F-22 RAPTOR.
COMMANDS TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
TROOPS.
DIRECTED MOSUL, THE FIGHT FOR
RAKKA AND OVERSAW THE TOMORROW
HAWK MISSILE STRIKE AGAINST
SYRIA.
WHEN THINGS GET TENSE WITH
RUSSIAN FORCES, THE GENERAL USES
THIS PHONE TO KEEP PROBLEMS FROM
SPREADING.
WITH RUSSIA RECENTLY BOMBING
U.S. FORCES IN SYRIA OR NEAR
THEM, AND THREATENING NEW
RETALIATION, I'LL ASK THE
GENERAL WHAT HE EXPECTS NEXT.
HE'LL JOIN US LIVE.
AND THE REPUBLICAN SENATOR JOHN
McCAIN DEALING A HUGE SETBACK TO
THE PRESIDENT'S EFFORT TO CHANGE
OBAMACARE.
McCAIN, NO ON GRAHAM-CASSIDY.
HIS REASONS AHEAD.
LET'S GET TO IT.
>> Announcer: SHEPARD SMITH
REPORTING LIVE FROM THE FOX
NEWSDESK.
>> Shepard: FROM THE FOX
NEWSDESK, THE LATEST G.O.P.
HEALTHCARE PLAN IS NOW ONE VOTE
AWAY FROM COLLAPSE.
AFTER THE REPUBLICAN SENATOR
JOHN McCAIN ANNOUNCED HE CANNOT
SUPPORT THE BILL.
THE EDITION SO SIGS DESPITE THE
FACT ONE OF ITS CO-SPONSORS IS
HIS CLOSEST FRIEND IN THE
SENATE, LINDSAY GRAHAM.
SENATOR McCAIN BROKE THE NEWS
HOURS AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP
WARNED HIS FELLOW REPUBLICANS TO
VOTE YES.
THE PRESIDENT TWEETING, RAND
PAUL OR WHOEVER VOTES AGAINST
THE HEALTHCARE BILL WILL FOREVER
FUTURE POLITICAL CAMPAIGN BE
KNOWN AS THE REPUBLICAN WHO
SAVED OBAMACARE.
KENTUCKY SENATOR RAND PAUL WAS
THE FIRST REPUBLICAN TO COME OUT
AGAINST THE BILL.
HIS REASONING, IT DOESN'T GO FAR
ENOUGH TO REPEAL THE AFFORDABLE
CARE ACT.
NOW WE'RE WAITING TO HEAR FROM
THE OTHER TWO REPUBLICANS WHO
HELPED KILL THE LAST XW O.P.
HEALTHCARE HILL.
CHIEF CONGRESSIONAL REPORTER
MIKE OMANUAL.
>> WITH SENATOR JOHN McCAIN BEAK
A NO ON THE GRAHAM-CASSIDY PLAN
THERE'S INTENSE PRESSURE TO LOCK
DOWN ALL OTHER REPUBLICAN
SENATORS.
MAINE SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS SAID
HE'S LEANING AGAINST SUPPORTING
THIS GRAHAM-CASSIDY LEGISLATION.
COLLINS IS ONE OF THE NO VOTES
ON HEALTHCARE REFORM IN JULY.
THERE WAS PRESIDENT TO SUPPORT
WITH IT HER GOVERNOR AND
VICE PRESIDENT PENCE URGING HER
TO GET ONBOARD.
>> WE'RE ENCOURAGING SENATOR
CAIN, BUT ESPECIALLY ENCOURAGING
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS.
TO JOIN US IN THIS EFFORT.
TO GIVE THE PEOPLE OF MAINE, THE
GOVERNMENT OF MAINE THE
FLEXIBILITY TO IMPROVE THE LIVES
AND THE HEALTH OF PEOPLE OF
MAINE.
>> IF COLLINS OR ALASKA'S LISA
MURKOWSKI SAY THEY'RE AGAINST
GRAY WHOM-CASSIDY LEADERSHIP DUS
VENLT VOTES TO PASS IT.
MURKOWSKI WAS NO ON THE SKINNY
REPEAL BILL IN JULY, SO-CALLED.
PRESIDENT REPUBLICAN SOURCES
HOPE THIS TEAM WOULD BE
DIFFERENT IF FOR NO OTHER REASON
THAN JOHN McCAIN'S BEST FRIEND
IN THE WORLD IS LINDSAY GRAHAM,
AUTHOR OF THE BILL.
>> Shepard: WHAT ARE YOU HEARING
FROM DEMOCRATS?
>> THEY'RE VOI VOWING TO
CONTINUE THE FIGHT, PRAISING
SENATOR McCAIN FOR STANDING UP
AND STOPPING THIS BILL.
BOTTOM LINE, A NUMBER OF
DEMOCRATS SAY THEY PISH THE
BIPARTISAN TALKS TO TRY TO FIX
OBAMACARE WERE CONTINUING.
>> I FELT LIKE WE WERE MAKING
STEADY PROS TOWARD A BIPARTISAN
COMPROMISE TO ADDRESS THE
CHALLENGES AND PROBLEMS WITH
OBAMACARE REPEAL.
THERE'S AN AN ABRUPT HALT BY THE
REPUBLICAN LEADERSHIP, WE WILL
HAVE A VOTE THIS COMING WEEK ON
THIS BILL.
I HAVE CONCERNS HOW IT WILL
AFFECT DELAWARE AND THE COUNTRY
AND I PLAN TO VOTE AGAINST IT.
>> MITCH McCONNELL INTENDS TO
BRING UP GRAHAM-CASSIDY NEXT
WEEK BUT THAT WAS BEFORE HE HAD
TWO HARD NO VOTES AGAINST THE
BILL.
>> MIKE EMMANUEL, THANKS.
>> Shepard: CHRIS WALLACE,
MODERATOR OF "FOX NEWS SUNDAY."
JOHN McCAIN GAVE HIS REASONS.
LAST TIME AROUND, HE MADE A
PRETTY CLEAR STATEMENT WHEN HE
WAS THAT DRAMATIC VOTE FOR NO.
WE HAVE A FULL SCREEN OF THAT
I'D LIKE TO SHOW THE VIEWING
AUDIENCE.
HERE IT IS.
THIS IS WHAT HE SAID LAST TIME.
THE CONGRESS MUST NOW RETURN TO
REGULAR ORDER.
HOLD HEARINGS.
RECEIVE INPUT FROM MEMBERS OF
BOTH PARTIES.
AND HEED THE RECOMMENDATIONS OF
OUR NATION'S GOVERNORS SO THAT
WE CAN PRODUCE A BILL THAT
FINALLY PROVIDES AMERICANS WITH
ACCESS TO QUALITY AND AFFORDABLE
HEALTHCARE.
THAT PART OF IT HADN'T CHANGED,
THOUGH THIS IS TECHNICALLY
REGULAR ORDER IT WASN'T.
COMMITTEES HAD MET ON IT, AND
THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE
HADN'T MARKED IT UP.
>> EXACTLY RIGHT.
THE COMMITTEES HAVE NOT MET ON
IT.
THEY'LL HOLD ONE OR TWO HEARINGS
THIS NEXT WEEK.
SIMPLY, I THINK, TRYING TO
SATISFY JOHN McCAIN,nd SOME
OTHERS WHO SAID THIS IS A HECK
OF A WAY TO COMPLETELY REFORM
THE HEALTH SYSTEM, ONE-SIXTH OF
THE ECONOMY.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET A CBL
SCORE, CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
OFFICE.
THE IMPACT ON PREMIUMS OR THE
IMPACT IT WOULD HAVE ON MILLIONS
OF PEOPLE POTENTIALLY LOSING
THEIR COVERAGE.
JOHN McCAIN DECIDED TO PULL THE
PLUG EARLY.
MAYBE HE DIDN'T WANT TO BE THE
ONE, THE FINAL VOTE AS HE WAS
LAST TIME, WHEN HE LITERALLY PUT
HIS THUMB DOWN.
BUT HE MADE IT CLEAR HE'S A NO
VOTE.
RAND PAUL HAS MADE IT CLEAR HE'S
A NO VOTE.
THIS REMINDS ME OF THE LINE
ABOUT THE KNIGHT AND THE PRINCE,
IN THE PRINCESS BRIDE, IT'S
MOSTLY DEAD, THIS IS MOSTLY DEAD
RIGHT NOW.
I SUPPOSE SUSAN COLLINS COULD
CHANGE BUT SHE'S BEEN AGAINST
ALL OF THESE REPEAL AND REPLACE
PLANS.
I'D BE SHOCKED IF SHE WERE TO
CHANGE.
LISA MURKOWSKI HAS BEEN AGAINST
ALMOST ALL OF THEM.
I'D BE A LITTLE LESS SHOCKED IF
SHE CHANGED.
SHELLEY MOORE OF WEST VIRGINIA,
ROB PORTMAN OF OHIO, GRASSLEY
AND EARNS THE FROM IOWA.
THERE'S A LOT OF OPPOSITION.
IT'S ON- SUPPORT, WOULD BE AN
OVERSTATEMENT.
ON LIFE SUPPORT.
>> Shepard: LISA MURKOWSKI OF
ALASKA, THERE'S A LARGE GIFT
BASKET WAITING IN THE WINGS,
IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING FOR THE
PEOPLE OF ALASKA IF SHE CHANGES
HER MIND.
>> YES, THERE'S A PROVISION FOR
SPARSELY POPULATED STATES,
ALASKA CERTAINLY QUALIFIES AS A
SPARSELY POPULATED STATE, THAT
THEY WOULD NOT FALL UNDER ALL OF
THE PROVISIONS AND IT WOULD MAKE
SURE THAT THEY GOT MORE FUNDING
RATHER THAN LESS FUNDING WHICH
THEY WOULD OTHERWISE IF THEY
WERE TREATED LIKE EVERY OTHER
STATE.
THIS IS, IT'S INTERESTING TO
SEE, SHEP, WE ALL REMEMBER
OBAMACARE, ALL OF THE COMPLAINTS
THAT REPUBLICANS HAD AT THE TIME
ABOUT THE MESSY WAY THAT WAS
PASSED.
WE HAVE A PASS IT IN ORDER TO
FIND OUT WHAT'S IN IT.
THINGS ARE JAMMED DOWN.
THERE WAS THE CORNHUSKER
KICKBACK, ALL OF THE SPECIAL
DEALS TO BUY THE VOTES OF
SENATORS.
YOU'RE SEEING ALL OF THAT IF NOT
MORE ON THE PART OF REPUBLICANS
THIS TIME.
IT'S PERFECT HYPOCRISY, WHAT YOU
SEE ON CAPITOL HILL.
>> Shepard: I WANTED TO SPEAK
SPECIAL ABOUT SUSAN COLLINS OF
MAINE.
FOR HER, SHE SAID REPEATEDLY, I
THINK, CHRIS, THIS IS ABOUT
MEDICAID.
HER CONCERNS ABOUT IT.
>> WELL, THAT'S RIGHT.
IN FACT ACCORDING TO THE
FORMULA, MAINE WOULD DO BETTER,
THERE ARE SOME STATES, ABOUT 31
STATES THAT ARE LOSERS IN THIS
BILL.
THERE ARE SOME THAT ARE WINNERS.
MAINE WOULD BE A WINNER.
BUT SHE'S VERY CONCERNED ABOUT
THE MEDICAID.
IT TURNS IT FROM A BASICALLY
OPEN-ENDED ENTITLEMENT INTO A
BLOCK GRANT AND EVENTUALLY A
FORMULA WITH DIMINISHING
FINANCING PER CAPITA, PER
PERSON.
IN THE LONG RUN, CERTAINLY AFTER
2026, PEOPLE ON MEDICAID GET
LESS FUNDING THAN IN THE PAST.
SUSAN COLLINS IS MAD ABOUT THAT.
YOU SAW THE GOVERNOR, THE
INDEPENDENT GOFF OF MAINE
JOIN -- GOVERNOR OF MAINE TO
JOIN WITH THE VICE PRESIDENT TO
URGE HER TO DO IT.
SHE'S REPORTING A LOT OF FOLKS
IN MAINE LIKE HER STAND AGAINST
PASSING THIS BILL.
>> Shepard: IT SEEMS THAT LAST
TIME THE REPUBLICANS CAME UP
WITH A PLAN, IT ONLY HAD 17%
APPROVAL ACROSS THE NATION.
THIS TIME THE CONCERN SEEMS TO
BE IF NOT PRIMARILY, LARGELY,
ABOUT A CAP ON LIFETIME BENEFITS
FOR PEOPLE WITH PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS.
AND THEY'RE DISCUSSING THIS IN
THE JIMMY KIMMEL WAY, IF YOU
HAVE A CHILD WHO NEEDS MULTIPLE
IN HIS CASE HEART SURGERIES AND
YOU HAVE A MILLION DOLLAR CAP
AND YOUR CHILD DICE AS A RESULT
OF THE FACT YOU DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY THAT SEEMS TO BE A
CONCERN FOR A LOT OF VOTERS.
>> LOOK, THE PROBLEM IS THAT
WHAT THIS DOES IS BASICALLY
KEEPS ALL OF THE TAXES FROM
OBAMACARE AND DOES AWAY WITH THE
MANDATES, DOES AWAY WITH THE
MEDICAL DEVICE TAX.
IT TAKES THE OTHER BIG TAXES AND
SIMPLY GIVES IT BACK TO THE
STATE AND SAYS FEDERALISM, YOU
DO IT.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT EVERY STATE
WOULD HAVE A DIFFERENT PLAN AND
THEY WOULD HAVE TO GET WAIVERS
FROM THE DEPARTMENT, FROM
WASHINGTON, FROM THE DEPARTMENT
OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES OF
APPROPRIATE AND AFFORDABLE
COVERAGE.
NOBODY KNOWS WHAT THAT MEANS.
NOW, THERE'S A LIKELIHOOD THAT
SOME STATES, LIBERAL STATES,
BLUE STATES, WOULD HAVE VERY
LENIENT BENEFITS AND WOULD, FOR
INSTANCE, PEOPLE WITH
PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS ARE WELL
COVERED.
OTHER STATES WE AREN'T SURE.
WHO KNOWS WHAT A WAIVER FOR
APPROPRIATE AND AFFORDABLE
COVERAGE MEANS.
THERE IS A CONCERN.
WE DON'T KNOW, IN FACT, BUT
THERE IS A CONCERN THAT SOME SAY
WITH PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS MAY
SAY ON PAPER THEY CAN GET
COVERAGE BUT IN TERMS OF THE
FINANCING, COST OF THE PREMIUMS
OR DEDUCTIBLES, THEY CAN'T.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOT DEAD BUT
IT'S EXTREMELY COLD AND
EXTREMELY WHITE.
>> IT'S MOSTLY DEAD.
>> Shepard: THE LEADERS OF NORTH
KOREA AND UNITED STATES ARE
PERSON
ALLY INSULTING EACH OTHER
AND BRINGING THE NUCLEAR
STANDOFF TO A NEW LEVEL.
THE DICTATOR KIM JUDGE UN HAS
CALLED PRESIDENT TRUMP MENTALLY
DERANGED N A PERSONAL STATEMENT,
IT COMES AFTER PRESIDENT PLUMP
THREATENED TTAO DELLTOY STY
RO
A KORTHAIFRE WT  TITHAIS T
KE
DS TAD EFTOUNTHEN ITE
ED
.SST
THAT WAS DURING HIS SPEECH TO
THE UNITED NATIONS GENERAL
ASSEMBLY.
ACCORDING TO NORTH KOREAN STATE
TELEVISION, KIM JUNG UN SAID
WHATEVER TRUMP MIGHT HAVE
EXPECTED HE WILL FACE RESULTS
BEYOND HIS EXPECTATION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETED THIS
MORNING, KIM JUN-UN OF NORTH
KOREA, OBVIOUS LAY MADMAN,
DOESN'T MIND STARVING AND
KILLING HIS PEOPLE, WILL BE
TESTED LIKE NEVER BEFORE.
NOW, NORTH KOREA'S FOREIGN MIN
CITY SAID THEY MIGHT CONSIDER
TESTING A HYDROGEN BOMB IN THE
PACIFIC OCEAN.
HERE'S HOW THE SECRETARY OF
STATE, REX TILLERSON, RESPONDED
TO THAT.
>> ALL OF OUR MILITARY OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE AS THE
PRESIDENT SAID.
THERE WILL BE ASSEMBLED AND
THERE IS ASSEMBLED A NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNCIL THAT MEETS ON
EACH OF THESE ISSUES TO ADVISE
THE PRESIDENT.
IT WILL BE HIS DECISION
ULTIMATELY.
>> Shepard: SECRETARY TILLERSON
SAID THE U.S. WILL CONTINUE
EFFORTS IN THE DIPLOMATIC ARENA
A BACK TO CHRIS WALLACE.
GOING AT IT LIKE CHILDREN IN A
PLAYGROUND, DOES THIS LEAD TO
WAR?
YESTERDAY THE STOCK MARKET
SEEMED TO SUGGEST SO, 10 DEFENSE
STOCKS HIT THE ALL-TIME HIGH.
>> WE'RE A WAYS AWAY FROM THAT.
GENERAL McMASTER, H.R. McMASTER,
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR, SAID
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF ROAD.
THERE IS MORE ROAD.
YOU CAN SEE THAT YESTERDAY WHEN
THE PRESIDENT ANNOUNCED THAT HE
SIGNED AN EXECUTIVE ORDER GIVING
THE TREASURY SECRETARY THE
POWERS TO CUT OFF ANY TRADE, ANY
DEALINGS WITH ANY COMPANY, ANY
BANK, THAT HAS TRADE OR DEALINGS
WITH NORTH KOREA.
PRESIDENT ALSO ANNOUNCED THAT
CHINESE, THE CHINESE CENTRAL
BANK, IN ACCOUNT THEIR FEDERAL
RESERVE, IS ORDERING ALL OF
THEIR BANKS TO CUT OFF ANY
FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS WITH
PYONGYANG, WITH THE KIM REGIME.
WE'LL WAIT TO SEE HOW IT WORKS,
WHETHER SQUEEZING NORTH KOREA IN
THAT FINANCIAL AND TRADE SENSE
SHAKES ANY SENSE INTO THE KIM
REGIME AND GETS THEM TO STAND
DOWN.
THE QUESTION, SHEP, IS WHETHER
KIM HAS MADE IN EFFECT AN
EXISTENTIAL CHOICE, BELIEVES
THAT HAVING A LONG-RANGE
BALLISTIC MISSILE WITH A NUCLEAR
WAR HEAD ON IT IS NOT THE PATH
TO DISASTER BUT THE PATH TO
SURVIVAL FOR HIS REGIME.
YOU KNOW, HE LOOKS AROUND THE
WORLD, SEES SADDAM HUSSEIN, NO
WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION,
ENDED UP DEAD.
SAME WITHCA DAFIE AND MAY
HAVE -- KHADAFFI.
THE THING THAT ENSURES HIS
SURVIVAL HE BELIEVES IS TO HAVE
A NUCLEAR WEAPON.
>> Shepard: WONDER WHAT KIND OF
REACTION HE'D GET TO AN H-BOMB
TEST IN THE PACIFIC.
>> WE HAVE HAD H-BOMB TESTS
BEFORE, A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO,
WE THINK, IT WAS UNDERGROUND.
THIS WOULD OBVIOUSLY BE MORE
STUNNING BECAUSE IT WOULD BE
OVER GROUND.
IT WOULD BE OVER THE WATER.
WE WOULD SEE THE MUSHROOM CLOUD
THAT WOULD BRING HOME WHAT THE
THREAT IS.
DO I THINK WE'LL GO TO WAR OVER
A NUCLEAR TEST, PROBABLY NOT.
PARTICULARLY NOT WITH ALL OF
THESE SANCTIONS JUST GETTING
STARTED.
>> Shepard: CHRIS WALLACE, FROM
WASHINGTON, LOOKING FORWARD TO
YOUR PROGRAM ON FOX NEWS SUNDAY.
HE'LL TALK WITH MICROSOFT
CO-FOUNDER BILL GATES ABOUT THE
GATES FOUNDATION, THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST PRIVATE CHARITY AMONG
OTHER THINGS, ON FOX NEWS SUNDAY
ON YOUR LOCAL FOX STATION.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS GETTING SET
TO TAKE ANOTHER TRY AT A TRAVEL
BAN.
THE FIRST BAN CAUSED A BIT OF
CHAOS.
SO WHAT IS DIFFERENT THIS TIME?
JUST RELEASED DETAILS COMING UP
FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK ON THIS
FRIDAY AFTERNOON.
Dynamic performance,
Track tuned handling,
and aggressive styling.
The bold Lexus IS.
Lease the 2017 IS Turbo for
$299 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing at
your Lexus dealer.
WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE TO
THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE,
DOES PSORIASIS EVER GET IN
THE WAY OF A TOUCHING MOMENT?
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE TO SEVERE
PSORIASIS, YOU CAN EMBRACE
THE CHANCE OF COMPLETELY
CLEAR SKIN WITH TALTZ.
TALTZ IS PROVEN TO GIVE YOU A
CHANCE AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
WITH TALTZ, UP TO
90% OF PATIENTS
HAD A SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT
OF THEIR PSORIASIS PLAQUES.
IN FACT, 4 OUT OF 10 EVEN
ACHIEVED COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DO NOT USE IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING YOU
SHOULD BE CHECKED
FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE YOUR
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU ARE BEING TREATED
FOR AN INFECTION
OR HAVE SYMPTOMS.
OR IF YOU HAVE RECEIVED
A VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ.
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
JUST ASK YOUR
DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
you get time for more life.
This family wanted to
keep the game going.
SON: Hey mom, one more game?
TECH: With Safelite, you get a
text when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
MOM: Sure.
Bring it!
TECH: I'm Micah with Safelite.
MOM: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care!
FAMILY: Bye!
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
S.
>> Shepard: THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION PREPAING A NEW
ORDER TO REPLACE THE
CONTROVERSIAL TRAVEL BAND.
DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND SECURITY
HAS TAILORED RESTRICTIONS TO
EACH COUNTRY.
BASED ON WHAT THEY CALL MULTIPLE
FACTORS INCLUDING THE THREAT
EACH COUNTRY POSES AND WHETHER
IT COOPERATES WITH U.S.
REGULATIONS.
THE NEW RULES WOULD REPLACE
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S EARLIER
EXECUTIVE ORDER THAT BANNED
TRAVELERS FROM SIX MUSLIM
MAJORITY COUNTRIES.
BUT WE'RE STILL WAITING TO HEAR
WHICH COUNTRIES THE NEW TRAVEL
RULES WILL AFFECT.
KEVIN CORK, LIVE IN SOMERSET,
NEW JERSEY NOT FAR FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S GOLF CLUB WHERE HE'S
SPENDING THE WEEKEND.
KEVIN?
>> RIGHT ON THE MONEY, SHEPARD.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE PREVIOUS SIX
COUNTRY, WE DON'T KNOW HOW MANY
COUNTRIES WILL BE INVOLVED IN
THE NEW TRAVEL RESTRICTIONS.
WE DO HAVE IT ON GOOD AUTHORITY
BASED ON WHAT WE'VE BEEN
LEARNING FROM ADMINISTRATION
SOURCES AND BASE ON WHAT WE
LEARNED FROM A RECENTLY
CONCLUDED CALL THE NUMBER OF
COUNTRIES INVOLVED WILL LIKELY
EXPAND TO INCLUDE MORE THAN THE
ORIGINAL SIX COUNTRIES THAT WE
TALKED ABOUT.
LET ME SHARE PART OF AN
ADMINISTRATION STATEMENT THEY'VE
BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS IDEA OF
SECURING THE HOMELAND AND MOST
IMPORTANTLY PROTECTING THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION WILL ENSURE
WE ONLY ADMIT THOSE PROPERLY
VOTED AND WILL NOT POSE A THREAT
TO NATIONAL SECURITY OR PUBLIC
SAFETY.
SO IN EXPANDING THE NUMBER OF
COUNTRIES ON THE LIST THE
ADMINISTRATION PROPOSES AS YOU
SAID, TO CREATE MORE
RESTRICTIONS BUT ON A
CASE-BY-CASE BASIS.
THIS IS ALSO RELEVANT FOR ONE
MAJOR IMPORTANT REASON, THAT IS
BY EXPANDING IT AND MAKING IT
COUNTRY-TO-COUNTRY, SHEPARD,
WHAT THEY'RE EFFECTIVELY TRYING
TO DO IS BLUNT PERHAPS SOME OF
THE LEGAL PUSHBACK THAT THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS PREVIOUSLY
GOTTEN.
YOU MAY RECALL THE STATE
DEPARTMENT SAID THERE WERE LIKE
17 COUNTRIES NOT UP TO U.S.
STANDARDS AND FAILED TO FALL
INTO COMPLIANCE B HALF HAVE.
WE'LL SEE WHAT THAT NUMBER LOOKS
LIKE.
I WANT TO SHARE A TWEET THAT THE
PRESIDENT SENT OUT AFTER AN
ATTACK ON LONDON.
I THINK IT'S INSTRUCTIVE, WILL
GIVE YOU A SENSE OF WHAT HE'S
BEEN THINKING.
THIS IS BACK IN SEPTEMBER 15.
A TRAVEL BAN INTO THE U.S.
SHOULD BE FOR LARGER, TOUGHER,
AND MORE SPECIFIC.
INDEED THAT APPEARS TO BE THE
CASE.
>> Shepard: KEVIN CORK, LIVE FOR
US, THANK YOU.
THERE'S BREAKING NEWS FROM
PUERTO RICO, WORD OF A DAM THAT
HAS FAILED AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA.
PEOPLE ARE RACING TO ESCAPE.
WE'LL TAKE YOU THERE.
MEXICO CITY FACES OF AGONY,
VIDEO SHOWS RELATIVES OF SOME OF
THOSE STILL MISSING DAYS AFTER
THE EARTHQUAKE LEVELED
BUILDINGS.
WAITING FOR WORD.
COMING UP.
Endless Shrimp is back
at Red Lobster.
And we went all out
to bring you even more
incredible shrimp
and new flavors.
Like new
Nashville Hot Shrimp,
drizzled with
sweet amber honey,
and new grilled
Mediterranean Shrimp
finished with a savory blend
of green onions,
tomatoes, and herbs.
Feeling hungry yet?
Good, 'cause there's plenty
more where these came from.
Like Garlic Shrimp Scampi,
and other classics you love.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
But hurry, Endless Shrimp
won't be here long.
If you have Medicare
Parts A and B
guess what?
You could apply for a
Medicare supplement insurance
plan whenever you want.
No enrollment window.
No waiting to apply.
That means now may be a
great time to shop for an
AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Medicare doesn't
cover everything.
And like all standardized
Medicare supplement
insurance plans,
these help cover some
of what Medicare
doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide.
It could help you find the
AARP Medicare Supplement plan
that works for you.
These types of plans have
no networks,
so you get to choose any
doctor who accepts
Medicare patients.
Rates are competitive,
and they're the only plans
of their kind endorsed by AARP.
Remember -
these plans let you apply
all year round.
So call today.
Because now's the perfect time
to learn more.
Go long.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS IN
PUERTO RICO, HURRICANE MARIA
CAUSED MAJOR DESTRUCTION AFTER
MAKING LANDFALL AS A CATEGORY 4
STORM EARLIER THIS WEEK.
THIS IS THE BREAKING NEWS, NOW.
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE JUST
ANNOUNCED A DAM IN THE WESTERN
PART OF THE ISLAND ABOUT AN HOUR
AND A HALF DRIVE WEST OF THE
CAPITAL IS FAILING.
A DAM IS FAILING AND TWO TOWNS
ARE HURRIEDLY EVACUATED, THEY
HAVE SENT IN BUSS TO GET PEOPLE
OUT MACHLT REA WAS THE MOST
POWERFUL STORM TO HIT PUERTO
RICO IN 80 YEARS.
STEVE IS LIVE IN SAN JUAN, ABOUT
AN HOUR AND A HALF DRIVE EAST OF
THE DAM.
WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD, STEVE?
>> SHEPARD, PEOPLE ARE JUST
AFRAID OF WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
SO MUCH UNCERTAINTY AROUND ABOUT
WHAT IS HAPPENING IN THE OUTER
REGIONS.
IT WAS EXPECTED, ANTICIPATED,
AND FEARED THAT THIS AGING
INFRASTRUCTURE OF THE BANKRUPT
ISLAND WOULD BE TESTED BY
HURRICANE MARIA.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
DETAILS COMING IN BIT BY BIT.
THIS DAM IN NORTHWESTERN PART OF
THE ISLAND IS FAILING RIGHT NOW.
THEY'RE USING SCHOOL BUSES TO
EVACUATE PEOPLE AS QUICKLY AS
POSSIBLE FROM TWO TOWNS.
ALREADY FLASH FLOODING IN THE
RIVER AROUND THERE.
THIS HIGHLIGHTS A COUPLE OF
THINGS.
NOT ONLY THE INFRASTRUCTURE ISCA
LAPSING AND DEALT A DEATH FLOW
BUT THE PROBLEM WITH
INFORMATION.
CELL PHONE COVERAGE DOWN.
ROADS BLOCKED.
IN THESE OUTER REGIONS OF THE
ISLAND WHERE TRAGEDIES ARE
HAPPENING IN THE WAKE OF THE
STORM, VERY DIFFICULT.
INFORMATION COMING IN JUST IN
BITS AND PIECES.
THREE DEAD HERE, EIGHT DEAD
THERE AS THE CASUALLY FIGURE
CONTINUES TO RISE.
WE'LL MONITOR THE DAM COLLAPSE.
>> Shepard: SEARCH TEAMS PULLING
SURVIVORS FROM UNEARTHED CRUSHED
BUILDINGS THREE DAYS AFTER AN
EARTHQUAKES DECIMATED AREAS
AROUND MEXICO CITY.
MUCH OF THAT AREA WAS DESTROYED.
CITY GOVERNMENT REPORTING 60
RESCUES SINCE THAT QUAKE HIT ON
TUESDAY.
NEARLY 300 CONFIRMED DEAD.
THE MEXICAN NAVY OFFICIAL SAYS
THAT RUMORS OF A CHILD ALIVE
UNDERNEATH A COLLAPSED SCHOOL
WERE ALL WRONG.
BUT HE SAID THERE ARE STILL
COULD BE SOMEBODY UNDERNEATH
THERE, AS LONG AS THERE'S A
CHANCE HE SAID THE TEAMS WILL
KEEP DIGGING.
SIMILAR SCENES PLAYING OUT IN
AND AROUND MEXICO CITY, RESCUERS
REFUSING TO GIVE UP, RELATIVES
HOLDING OUT HOPE THAT MISSING
LOVED ONES WILL COME HOME.
OUR CHIEF CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN
HUNT IS IN MEXICO CITY AT A
TEXTILE FACTORY, CREWS SEARCHING
FOR SURVIVORS.
>> THIS HAS BEEN THE SCENE OF AN
INTENSE SEARCH AND RESCUE
OPERATION.
OVERNIGHT, ONE MAN WAS PULLED
ALIVE FROM WHAT WAS A FOUR-STORY
TEXTILE FACTORY.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT RIGHT NOW.
AS YOU CAN ALSO SEE RIGHT NOW,
THE HUNDREDS OF RESCUE WORKERS
AND VOLUNTEERS HERE HAVE PAUSED
FOR THE MOMENT.
THAT APPEARS TO TELL ITS OWN
STORY.
WE ARE AWAITING A VISIT BY THE
MAYOR OF MEXICO CITY.
AND THE VERY FACT THAT THEY HAVE
JUST, IN THE LAST FEW MINUTES,
PAUSED ALL THEIR WORK MAY
INDICATE THAT THIS IS ABOUT TO
MOVE FROM A SEARCH AND RESCUE
OPERATION TO A RECOVERY
OPERATION ONLY.
ALL DAY THEY'VE BEEN TELLING US
POSSIBLY EIGHT WOMEN WORKERS
WERE STILL MISSING IN THIS
FACTORY, SHEPARD.
IT APPEARS THAT WE ARE MOVING
TOWARDS THE POINT WHEN THEY MAY
WELL ANNOUNCE THAT THEY HAVE
DECIDED THERE ARE NO MORE
SURVIVORS.
THEY'VE GONE DOWN TO THE
BASEMENT HERE, THEY HAVE HAD THE
RESCUE DOGS SNIFFING THERE.
BUT EVERYBODY WILL TELL
WEDNESDAY YOU GET TO THE 72-HOUR
MARK HERE, IT'S VERY, VERY
UNLIKELY THAT THEY WILL FIND
MORE SURVIVORS.
AND THE FAMILIES ARE BRACING
THEMSELVES FOR THE MOVEMENT THAT
THE GOVERNMENT DECLARES THIS IS
NO LONG AREA RESCUE OPERATION,
BUT A RECOVERY OPERATION.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: JONATHAN, THANK YOU.
AMERICAN AND RUSSIAN GENERALS
MEETING FACE-TO-FACE AS THEY
FIGHT A PROXY WAR IN SIRIA.
THE PENTAGON ACCUSES MOSCOW OF
DROPPING BOMBS DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
TO U.S. SPECIAL OPERATIONS
GROUPS.
RUSSIANS SAYING THEY WILL
RETALIATE IF ANYBODY FIRES ON
THEIR SOURCES.
WE'LL SPEAK WITH THE GENERAL HO
HAS A HOTLINE TO RUSSIA,
COMMANDER OF AIR WAR AGAINST THE
ISLAMIC STATE, A FIRE PILOT
HIMSELF STILL FLYING COMBAT
MISSES OF THE GENERAL JOINS US
LIFE ON THE FOX NEWSDESK NEXT.
y,
Huh!
We gotta go.
Come on.
♪
“Grandma! Grandpa!”
Thanks mom.
Here we are. Look, right up
to here.
Principal. We can help
you plan for that.
Patrick woke up
with a sore back.
But he's got work to do.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
I wanted to know who I am
and where I came from.
I did my AncestryDNA
and I couldn't wait
to get my pie chart.