>> Shepard: DO YOU REMEMBER
SAYING ANYTHING TO EACH OTHER IN
THAT DRIVE?
>> WE HAVE TO -- IN THE DRIVE
ITSELF?
NO.
MY FIANCE JUST LOST IT.
I WAS JUST TRYING TO GET US OUT
OF THERE.
>> Shepard: HAVE YOU SLEPT?
>> I GOT AN HOUR SLEEP BEFORE I
WORK UP TO ANOTHER NIGHTMARE.
>> Shepard: I WONDER IF YOU GOT
PLANS FOR HOW TO DEAL WITH THISR
YOU'VE SEEN A LOT.
>> IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS THAT
YOU'RE NOT PREPARED FOR.
I MEAN, YOU ALWAYS WONDER WHAT
YOU'RE GOING TO DO IN THAT
SCENARIO AND STUFF.
WHEN YOUR THRUST INTO IT,
THERE'S NOTHING YOU CAN DO.
THERE'S TEN FOOT WALLS
EVERYWHERE.
THAT'S THE SCARIEST PART.
I HAD NIGHTMARES ABOUT NOT BEING
ABLE TO GET OUT OF WHERE I
NEEDED TO GET OUT.
THERE WERE WALLS BLOCKING US IN.
WE HAD NO WHERE TO GO.
>> Shepard: BIG CROWDS IN
LAS VEGAS FOR EVERYTHING.
MAY BE TOO SOON TO JUDGE SUCH A
THING.
BIG CROWDS STILL OKAY WITH YOU?
OPEN SPACES?
YOU WONDER WHEN PEOPLE WILL
START THINKING DIFFERENTLY.
>> THAT'S ONE THING WE TALKED
ABOUT A LITTLE WHILE BACK.
A LITTLE BIT THIS MORNING WHEN
WE GOT BACK AND SAFE AROUND
FAMILY.
I'VE GROWN UP AROUND FESTIVALS.
I DON'T KNOW.
I DON'T KNOW IF I'LL BE ABLE TO
BE AROUND PEOPLE FOR A LITTLE
WHILE.
WE HEARD THE OVEN DOOR SHUT AND
YOU FLINCH.
IT'S WEIRD HOW OUR BODIES ARE
NATURALLY REACTING TO THIS.
>> Shepard: RUSSELL BLECK ON THE
LINE WITH US.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU AND YOURS.
APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
A LIVE LOOK AT THE PLACE WHERE
IT HAPPENED.
VERY QUIET IN LAS VEGAS THIS
AFTERNOON.
HALF PASSED THE HOUR.
WAITING TO HEAR MUCH MORE ON THE
LAS VEGAS SHOOTING.
COMING UP, A LIVE REPORT FROM A
MEDICAL CENTER.
SO MANY OF YOU APPEAR TO BE
DABBLING IN CONSPIRACY THEORIES
ON THIS.
THE FBI SAID THERE WAS ONE
SHOOTER AND HE'S DEAD.
has gotten to know our business
so well,
that is feels like he's a part
of our team.
With one phone call, he sets me
up with tailored products and
services.
And when my advisor is focused
on my tech,
I can focus on my small
business.
A Dell Advisor can help you
choose the right PC's,
with powerful Intel® Core™
processors.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
NEARLY TWO WEEKS AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA SLAMMED PUERTO RICO,
GOVERNMENT RESCUE TEAMS ARE
FINALLY REACHING SOME OF THE
AREAS CUT OFF BY THE STORMS.
THESE PHOTOS ARE IN THE
MOUNTAINS IN CENTRAL PUERTO RICO
WHERE THERE'S BEEN MASSIVE
MUDSLIDES.
THE "WASHINGTON POST" REPORT
FOLKS HAD NO WAY TO LIVE AND
ALMOST RUN OUT OF DRINKING
WATER.
THE GOVERNOR OF PUERTO RICO SAYS
THE SURGE OF SUPPLIES INCLUDING
FOOD AND GAS CAME IN OVER THE
WEEKEND.
MORE THAN HALF OF THE ISLAND
STILL DOESN'T HAVE RUNNING WATER
AND MOST DON'T HAVE POWER.
THE GOVERNOR SAYS FOLKS ARE
STARTING TO GET CELL PHONE
SERVICE AGAIN.
FEMA'S ADMINISTRATOR TOLD FOX
NEWS THIS IS THE MOST
LOGISTICALLY CHALLENGE EVENT THE
UNITED STATES HAS EVER SEEN.
THE GOVERNOR OF FLORIDA IS
DECLARING A STATE OF EMERGENCY.
HE SAYS FLORIDA IS PREPARING TO
SUPPORT FAMILIES ESCAPINGH WIT
ER
ICTOPUITO RH WRY EVE AAVABLILE
RESOURCE FROM THE STATE.
THE NEWS CONTINUES WITH SHEPARD
SMITH AFTER THIS.
“Grandma! Grandpa!”
♪
Thanks mom.
Here we are. Look, right up
to here.
Principal. We can help
you plan for that.
>> Shepard: HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE
ARE IN HOSPITALS ACROSS THE
LAS VEGAS AREA.
JONATHAN HUNT IS AT UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL CENTER.
A LEVEL 1 TRAUMA FACILITY ABOUT
FIVE MILES FROM THE SHOOTING
SCENE.
JONATHAN?
>> SHEP, THERE ARE OR WERE ABOUT
104 INJURED CONCERT GOERS
BROUGHT HERE.
IT CAME CLOSE TO OVERWHELMING
THE SYSTEM HERE AT LAS VEGAS'
ONLY LEVEL ONE TRAUMA CENTER.
IN THE END, THEY WERE ABLE TO
COPE AS BEST THEY COULD.
TRAGICALLY, FOUR OF THOSE
BROUGHT HERE DIED.
12 REMAIN IN CRITICAL CONDITION.
YOU CAN JUST IMAGINE THE CHAOS
AS THE AMBULANCES LINED UP AT
THE SCENE OF THE SHOOTING AND
THEN AT THE EMERGENCY ROOM HERE.
WE'RE HEARING SOME EXTRAORDINARY
TALES, SHEP, OF PEOPLE,
PASSERSBY STOPPING IN THEIR
PICKUP TRUCKS AND LOADING THE
VICTIMS IN THE TRUCKS AND
BRINGING THEM HERE.
HOSPITAL OFFICIALS SAY THEY WERE
AMAZED BY THE SPIRIT OF THE
PEOPLE WHO PITCHED IN IN ANY WAY
THEY COULD IN SUCH AN
EXTRAORDINARY CIRCUMSTANCE.
THEY SAY, SHEP, THAT THEY HAVE
SAVED LIVES HERE OVER THE PAST
HOURS SINCE THAT SHOOTING
HAPPENED AND RIGHT NOW WITH 12
CRITICAL, THE DOCTORS AND NURSES
AT THIS TRAUMA FACILITY CONTINUE
TO DO THEIR UTMOST TO SAVE MORE
LIVES.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THEY'RE STILL ASKING
FOR BLOOD DONATIONS AS WELL.
>> YEAH, BLOOD.
THEY REALLY NEED BLOOD
DONATIONS.
WE'VE SEEN AN EXTRAORDINARY
SPIRIT IN THE PEOPLE OF
LAS VEGAS.
A COUPLE BLOCKS FROM HERE DOWN
TO MY LEFT, THEY SET OF TWO
MOBILE BLOOD DONATION UNITS AND
THEY HAVE BEFORE OVERWHELMED
WITH THE NUMBER OF PEOPLE
COMING.
THE LINE HAS STRETCHED AROUND
THE BLOCK ALL DAY.
OFFICIALS ARE SAYING DON'T
CHANGE YOUR MIND ABOUT COMING IF
YOU'RE PLANNING TO JUST BECAUSE
YOU SEE THE LINE.
THEY NEED BLOOD.
THEY'RE BOOKED NOW THROUGH
MONDAY AND THEY NEED MORE PEOPLE
TO SIGN UP AND DONATE BLOOD.
IT'S AN EXTRAORDINARY SPIRIT,
SHEP.
YOU'LL HAVE TO SAY JUST
RETURNING FROM MEXICO CITY AND
THE EARTHQUAKE THERE, IT'S THE
SAME SPIRIT OF VOLUNTEER
CIVILIANS THAT YOU SEE HERE A
FEW MINUTES AGO BEHIND ME.
TWO GUYS RIDING IN THEIR
OPEN-TOP JEEPS.
THEY HAVE THEM LOADED WITH
WATERS, WITH GATORADES, PROTEIN
BARS AND BRINGING THEM TO A FOOD
DROP OFF CENTER.
EVERYBODY JUST WANTS TO DO
WHATEVER THEY CAN TO HELP, SHEP.
>> Shepard: JONATHAN HUNT ON THE
SCENE.
THANK YOU.
COMING UP, WE'LL HEAR FROM A
SURVIVOR ON STAGE WHEN THE
SHOOTING BEGAN.
(AVO)
When you have type 2 diabetes,
you manage your A1C,
but you also have a higher risk
of heart attack or stroke.
Non-insulin Victoza®
lowers A1C,
and now reduces
cardiovascular risk.
Victoza® lowers my
A1C and blood sugar
better than
the leading
branded pill.
(AVO)
And for people with
type 2 diabetes
treating cardiovascular disease,
Victoza® is NOW approved
to lower the risk of major
cardiovascular events
such as heart attack,
stroke, or death.
And while it isn't
for weight loss,
Victoza® may
help you lose some weight.
(AVO)
Victoza® is not for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not take Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza® and get
medical help right away
if you get symptoms of a serious
allergic reaction such as rash,
swelling, difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Gallbladder problems have
happened in some people.
Tell your doctor right away
if you get symptoms.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting,
decreased appetite,
indigestion, and constipation.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may cause kidney problems.
Ask your doctor
about Victoza®.
Prudential asked these couples:
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>> EVERYONE SAID HIT THE FLOOR.
SO EVERYBODY WAS LAYING ON TOP
OF EACH OTHER TRYING TO GET
AWAY.
THE SHOTS JUST KEPT COMING.
SO WE WERE GOING DOWN.
WHEN WE GOT DOWN, THERE WAS A
MAN THAT WAS SHOT RIGHT THERE.
THEY WERE TRYING TO TAKE HIM
OUT.
I WAS UNCONSCIOUS.
>> Shepard: ANOTHER WITNESS TO
THE SHOOTING IN LAS VEGAS.
ONE WOMAN THAT SURVIVED THE
ORDEAL IS THANKING FIRST
RESPONDERS AND STRANGERS THAT
HELPED HER OUT.
HER AND OTHERS WITH AN EMOTIONAL
POST ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
HER NAME IS TIFFANY MICHELLE.
SHE'S IN THE FRONT THERE AND
MIDDLE.
SHE SAID THANK YOU TO THE BRAVE
MEN AND WOMEN THAT STAYED BEHIND
WHEN EVERYBODY WAS RUNNING
TERRIFIED FOR THEIR LIVES.
THANK YOU TO THE MAN THAT PULLED
ME OVER THE FENCE WHEN MY BOOT
WAS STUCK.
THANK YOU TO THE GIRLS THAT
GRABBED ME AND RAN WITH ME WHEN
THEY SAW I HAD BEEN SEPARATED
FROM MY HUSBAND AND FRIENDS.
THANK YOU TO THE FRIENDS THAT
CAME AND GOT ME FROM MY PLACE OF
REFUGE EVEN WHEN THE SHOOTER WAS
STILL ACTIVE.
ABOVE ALL, THANK YOU FOR MY
BRAVE HUSBAND WHO USED HIS OWN
BODY TO SHIELD ME AND OTHERS
FROM BULLETS.
HE AND OTHERS AND MILITARY AND
POLICE OFFICERS AND ANYBODY ELSE
THAT HELPED OUT AND HELPED SAFE
A LIFE ARE THE TRUE HEROS.
TIFFANY MICHELLE IS ON THE PHONE
WITH US.
A LOT OF PEOPLE GAVE YOU A HAND,
HUH?
>> YES, THEY DID.
SO MANY PEOPLE OUT THERE THAT
YOU WOULDN'T THINK THAT THEY
WOULD BE THINKING OF HELPING
OTHERS IN A TIME LIKE THAT.
IT WASN'T ANY -- AN EVERY MAN
FOR HIMSELF SITUATION.
EVERYBODY GRABBED SOMEBODY
AROUND THEM AND TRIED TO DO
EVERYTHING THEY COULD TO GET THE
OTHERS OUT.
>> Shepard: TIFFANY, WHERE WERE
YOU WHEN IT STARTED AND WHAT DID
YOU HEAR AND SEE?
>> WE WERE ABOUT 20 MINUTES INTO
JASON ALDEAN'S SET.
WE WERE STANDING NEAR CENTER
STAGE ON THE RIGHT SIDE OF THE
STAGE.
WE WERE PROBABLY ABOUT 60, 75
FEET AWAY FROM THE STAGE.
HE HAD JUST STARTED ONE OF HIS
SONGS WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN WE
STARTED HEARING WHAT I THOUGHT
WERE FIRECRACKERS.
I WENT ON FOR A WHILE.
WE STARTED LOOKING AT EACH
OTHER.
THAT'S STRANGE.
WHERE ARE THE FIREWORKS?
I DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
WE SAW JASON ALDEAN'S BAND RUN
OFF THE STAGE.
EVERYBODY STARTED GETTING ON THE
GROUND.
AT THIS POINT, I THOUGHT IT WAS
FIRECRACKERS.
SO I HUNCHED DOWN.
I SAID DON'T WORRY.
IT'S OKAY.
IT'S JUST FIREWORKS.
EVERYBODY WAS FREAKING OUT.
IT WASN'T UNTIL I TURNED AROUND
AND OUR GROUP OF SEVEN PEOPLE WE
SAW, ONE OF THE GIRLS BEHIND US
HAD GOTTEN SHOT IN THE RIGHT
SIDE OF HER CHEST.
SHE HAD A WHITE T-SHIRT.
YOU COULD SEE THE BLOOD OOZE
OUT.
EVEN AT THAT POINT, I THOUGHT,
OKAY, SO IT WAS GUN SHOTS.
I THOUGHT MAYBE IT HAD BEEN A
DRIVE-BY SHOOTING AND A STRAY
BULLET HAD GONE INTO THE CROWD.
I DIDN'T REGISTER AT THAT POINT
THAT WE WERE UNDER ATTACK.
>> Shepard: YOU MENTIONED YOUR
BOOT GOT STUCK.
TELL ME ABOUT THAT.
>> AFTER THE SECOND ROUND OF
SHOTS, MY HUSBAND SAID WE NEED
TO GET OUT OF HERE.
THERE WERE SOME GIRLS ON THE
GROUND AT MY FEET.
THERE WERE PEOPLE ALL IN THE
WAY.
WE WERE JUST TRYING TO GET THE
CROWD UP AND MOVING.
WHEN WE GET TO THIS CENTER
DIVIDE GOING DOWN THE CENTER
STAGE, IT WAS LIKE A FENCE A
METAL FENCE.
ONE MAN HOPPED OVER IN FRONT OF
ME.
HE TURNED AROUND TO HELP ME.
MY BOOT GOT STUCK ON SOMETHING
ON THE GROUND.
I DON'T KNOW IF IT WAS
UNDERNEATH PART OF THE FENCE AND
I HAD TO RUN THE REST OF THE WAY
WITHOUT IT.
>> Shepard: YOU GOT SOME HELP
THERE THOUGH.
>> I DID, YEAH.
HE WAS VERY HELPFUL.
I DON'T KNOW IF I WOULD HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO GET IT UNSTOCK
WITHOUT HIM.
I'M SO THANKFUL THAT SOMEBODY
WAS THERE.
>> Shepard: YOU SAID THAT SORT
OF THING KEPT HAPPENING OVER AND
OVER AGAIN.
>> YEAH.
EVERYBODY WAS -- AS WE KEPT
RUNNING, PEOPLE WERE TRYING TO
KEEP OTHER PEOPLE CALM.
WE MADE IT TO ONE OF THE TENTS
WHERE THEY HAD BEEN SERVING
FOOD.
THERE WERE PEOPLE IN THERE.
WE DIDN'T KNOW IF THERE WAS AN
ACTIVE SHOOTER ON THE GROUND.
WE DIDN'T KNOW IF HE WAS
FOLLOWING US WITH A GUN.
WE THOUGHT WE SHOULD STOP AND
HIDE UNDER SOMETHING.
THERE WERE PEOPLE THERE TRYING
TO KEEP EVERYBODY QUIET.
THERE WAS ONE MAN THAT SAID, NO,
IT'S OKAY.
RUN OUT THE BACK.
THAT'S WHEN EVERYBODY DECIDED TO
RUN OUT OF THE BACK OF THE TENT
AND KEEP GOING.
I GOT SEPARATED FROM THE GROUP
OF SEVEN THAT I WAS WITH,
INCLUDING MY HUSBAND.
I WAS RUNNING DOWN THE STREET
AND A GROUP OF GIRLS SAW ME BY
MYSELF AND ASKED ME, HEY, WHO
ARE YOU WITH?
ARE YOU MISSING ANYBODY?
I SAID YEAH, I CAN'T FIND MY
HUSBAND.
THEY GRABBED ME AND TOOK ME WITH
THEM.
WE RAN TO THE CLOSEST MOTEL WE
COULD FIND.
THEY HID WITH ME BETWEEN A ROW
OF CARS.
>> Shepard: HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE
TO THINK ABOUT THIS YET?
THE LAST CALLER, YOU'VE BEEN
THROUGH SO MUCH, YOU KNOW?
>> REALLY HARD TO PROCESS
EVERYTHING.
JUST GOING BACK, GETTING BACK TO
OUR PLACE AND WATCHING THE NEWS
AND SEEING THE NUMBERS, JUST
KEEP INCREASING, THE NUMBERS OF
DEAD AND THE NUMBERS OF INJURED.
IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE THAT MYSELF
AND ALL OF MY FRIENDS, MY
HUSBAND, MANAGED TO GET OUT
WITHOUT ANY KIND OF INJURIES TO
US PHYSICALLY BESIDES A COUPLE
OF BRUISES AND SCRAPES.
IT'S UNFATHOMABLE.
I'M JUST SO GRATEFUL, SO
THANKFUL THAT WE MADE IT OUT
OKAY.
>> Shepard: IN THE DAYS AHEAD,
WILL YOUR PATTERNS CHANGE?
WILL YOU CHANGE ANYTHING?
OR ARE YOU JUST GOING TO BE
CALM, CARRY ON?
>> YOU KNOW, I LOVE COUNTRY
MUSIC.
I LOVE GOING OUT WITH FRIENDS.
I LOVE GOING TO CONCERTS.
FOR ME, VEGAS, I DON'T KNOW IF
IT'S GOING TO CHANGE FOR ME.
YOU CAN'T LIVE YOUR LIFE IN
FEAR.
YOU CAN'T LIVE THINKING I CAN'T
GO OUT IN PUBLIC OR BIG CROWDS
ANYMORE.
YOU HAVE TO TRY TO MAKE SENSE OF
WHAT HAPPENED, TRY TO JUST MOVE
ON WITH YOUR LIFE.
BE THANKFUL THAT YOU WERE GIVEN
A SECOND CHANCE AND MAKE THE
MOST OF YOUR LIFE WITH THAT
SECOND CHANCE.
WE'RE STILL GOING TO GET OUT
THERE, STILL GOING TO LIVE OUR
LIVES AND HAVE FUN AND BE EXTRA
CAUTIOUS RIGHT NOW.
WHEN WE GO TO A BIG EVENT, WE'LL
HAVE A PLAN, LOOK AROUND, BE
OBSERVANT.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT THROUGH
OKAY.
>> Shepard: TIFFANY MICHELLE,
REALLY NICE TO TALK TO YOU.
GLAD YOU'RE DOING WELL AND BEST
TO YOUR FIANCE AND ALL OF YOUR
FRIENDS AND LOVED ONES.
>> THANK YOU, SHEP.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
IMAGINE HOW MANY PEOPLE HAVE
LIFE-CHANGING EXPERIENCES.
I MEAN, THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS
OF PEOPLE, RIGHT?
AND THEN SO MANY MORE WHO KNEW
THEM CLOSELY OR WERE INTIMATELY
INVOLVED WITH THEM IN SOME WAY
THAT LOVED A MEMBER OF THEIR
FAMILY.
SO MANY PEOPLE AFFECTED BY THE
TENS AND THOUSANDS EVENTUALLY.
THERE WERE REPORTS YOU SHOULD
KNOW OF AN ACTIVE SHOOTER AT USC
IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA.
NOT TRUE.
WE CAN KNOCK THAT DOWN FOR YOU.
THERE'S DISTURBING REPORTS ABOUT
TOM PETTY.
WE'RE NOT OBLIVIOUS TO THE FACT
THAT TMZ HAS REPORTED THAT HE'S
HAD A HEART ATTACK AND MAY HAVE
BEEN ON LIFE SUPPORT.
WE CAN'T CONFIRM THAT.
WE DON'T KNOW DETAILS OF THAT.
WE'RE WAITING TO HEAR SPECIFICS
OF THAT IT'S NOT AS IF WE NOYO
DON'T HAVE PHONES, TOO.
WE'RE GETTING THESE THINGS.
PART OF OUR JOB IS TO KNOCK DOWN
THINGS THAT ARE NOT TRUE.
A, NO ACTIVE SHOOTER AT USC.
ON TOM PETTY, WHEN WE KNOW MORE,
WE'LL LET YOU KNOW MORE.
THE NEWS CONTINUES AFTER THIS.
I didn't know where I
was from ethnically.
So we sent that sample
off to Ancestry.
My Ancestry DNA results
are that I am 26% Nigerian.
I am just trying to
learn as much as I can
about my culture.
I put the Gele on my
head and I looked
into the mirror and I
was trying not to cry.
Because it's a hat,
but it's like the most
important hat I've
ever owned.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
WHERE YOU LIVE. IN THE PLACE YOU
CALL HOME. THERE'S ROOM TO GROW.
FRESH AIR. FREEDOM. THERE WAS
JUST ONE THING MISSING, FAST
INTERNET. REALLY FAST INTERNET.
IT'S HERE. INTRODUCING HUGHESNET
GEN5. THE NEXT GENERATION OF
SATELLITE INTERNET. WITH FASTER
SPEEDS, MORE DATA, AND BUILT IN
WIFI. NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
WHAT YOU LOVE ONLINE. STAY IN
TOUCH, LEARN, SHARE, WATCH
VIDEOS, CHAT WITH FRIENDS, AND
GET THINGS DONE. ENJOY HIGH
SPEED INTERNET AT HOME, WHEREVER
YOU LIVE. THERE'S NEVER BEEN A
BETTER TIME TO GET AMERICA'S
NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR SATELLITE
INTERNET. THE NEW HUGHESNET GEN5
IS HERE, AND IT'S FASTER THAN
EVER. STANDARD INSTALLATION IS
FREE, SO DON'T WAIT. CALL NOW OR
TEXT (PROMO CODE) TO THIRTY-FIVE
THOUSAND, TODAY.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING COVERAGE
OF THE MASSACRE IN LAS VEGAS.
STORMY WARREN IS WITH US FROM
SIRIUS XM.
HE WAS ON THE STAGE WHEN THE
SHOOTING HAPPENED.
NICE TO TALK TO YOU.
>> GREAT TO TALK TO YOU, SHEP.
>> Shepard: YOU WERE ON STAGE.
JASON ALDEAN WAS STILL PLAYING.
WHAT IS YOUR MEMORY OF IT?
>> MEMORY IS OF PYROTECHNICS
MISFIRING WITH THE RAT A TAT
SOUND.
WE KNEW SOMETHING WAS WRONG WHEN
THE BULLETS WERE BOUNCING OFF
THE DECK OF THE STAGE.
JASON ALDEAN'S CREW
PROFESSIONALLY CLEARED HIM AND
HIS BAND AND HIS CREW OFF THE
STAGE.
THE CROWD OBVIOUSLY REALIZED
WHAT WAS GOING ON WHEN THE SOUND
CUT OFF.
THEY CUT THE SOUND TO THE P.A.
SYSTEM.
SO EVERYBODY KNEW THAT SOMETHING
WAS WRONG.
WE JUMPED OFF STAGE, RIGHT
BEHIND A CONCRETE BARRIER.
TWO OF US HID BEHIND THAT AS THE
BULLETS WERE RICOCHETTING OFF
THE DECK OF THE STAGE AND GOING
THROUGH THE STAGE.
SOME AT OUR FEET, SOME AROUND
US.
IT JUST SEEMED TO GO ON FOREVER.
EVERY TIME IT PAUSED, WE THOUGHT
IT WOULD BE DONE AND THEN
STARTED AGAIN.
>> Shepard: WHERE DID YOU END
UP?
>> I'M STILL TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT WHERE I'M GOING TO END UP.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE THINGS.
CONSTANT EVOLUTION.
WE FINALLY LEFT THE VENUE.
FOUND SAFE HAVEN IN CHRIS YOUNG,
A COUNTRY SINGER.
HE TOOK US IN AND TOOK ALL OF
THE MISFITS THAT HE COULD FIND
IN HIS SUITE.
THERE WERE HOURS OF HELPING
PEOPLE.
JUST TRYING TO FIND ANYBODY THAT
NEEDED HELP.
IF IT WAS JUST WITH COMFORT,
WITH TOWELS.
THE MEDICS WERE EVERYWHERE.
THEY WERE SO SPREAD THIN.
EVERYBODY CHIPPED IN.
IT WAS A GREAT EXERCISE IN
HUMANITY LAST NIGHT.
I HEAR A LOT OF RUMORS, PANIC.
YES, WE WERE ALL PANICKED.
EVERYBODY WANTED TO HELP.
IT WAS AN INCREDIBLE EXERCISE
LAST NIGHT DESPITE THE CHAOS.
>> Shepard: STORMY WARREN FROM
SIRIUS XM.
WE'RE SHORT ON TIME.
I HAVE TO HIT A BREAK.
THANKS SO MUCH.
>> YOU BET.
>> ALL OF THE BEST TO YOU AND
YOURS.
>> SO MUCH TO GO ON THIS.
NEIL CAVUTO WILL PICK THINGS UP
AT THE TOP OF THE HOUR.
THE MARKETS WILL BE CLOSING ON
WALL STREET IN ABOUT 3 MINUTES
AND 15 SECONDS.
UP AN UPDATE ACROSS THE BOARD ON
WALL STREET.
A SAD DAY ACROSS AMERICA.
THE PRESIDENT ORDERING FLAGS
FLOWN AT HALF STAFF.
NEIL CAVUTO PICKS UP OUR
COVERAGE IN THREE MINUTES.
[VO] QuickBooks introduces
Jeanette
and her new mobile wedding
business.
At first, getting paid was
tough...
until she got QuickBooks.
Now she sends invoices, sees
when they've been viewed
and-ta-dah-paid twice as fast
for free.
Visit QuickBooks-dot-com.
Liberty Mutual saved us almost
eight hundred dollars when we
switched our auto and
home insurance.
With Liberty, we could afford