ATLANTIC HURRICANE THIS SEASON
500 MILES SOUTH OF BERMUDA.
NOT EXPECTED TO MAKE LAND.
I'M SANDRA SMITH.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
HERE'S SHEP.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST, 3:00 IN WASHINGTON
WHERE ONE OF PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CABINET SECRETARIES IS IN
TROUBLE FOR CHARTERING PLANES
INSTEAD OF FLYING COMMERCIAL.
AND IS TOM PRICE GOING TO BE OUT
OF A JOB?
THE PRESIDENT'S RESPONSE AHEAD.
WE'LL TAKE YOU TO INDIANAPOLIS
WHERE MR. TRUMP IS SET TO REVEAL
HIS TAX PLAN THIS HOUR.
THE PROPOSAL, LOWER TAXES FOR
BUSINESS, FEWER INCOME TAX
BRACKETS FOR INDIVIDUALS AND A
STANDARD DEDUCTION NEARLY
DOUBLE.
AHEAD, WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT WHO
PAYS WHAT.
PLUS, SET BACKS FOR THE
PRESIDENT AND REPUBLICAN LEADERS
AT THEIR CANDIDATE FAILS IN THE
ALABAMA PRIMARY.
IT HAPPENED ON THE SAME DAY
THEIR HEALTHCARE PLAN COLLAPSED.
NOW WILL THE GOP NEED TO START
WORKING WITH DEMOCRATS?
COULD THAT HAPPEN?
TODAY A CROSS-ROADS FOR
CONGRESS.
AND IN PUERTO RICO, HEAVY
EQUIPMENT COMING IN TO MORE THAN
THREE MILLION AMERICANS THAT
CALL THE ISLAND HOME.
WE'LL GO LIVE WITH GERALDO
RIVERA ABOUT THE RESCUE EFFORTS
AND WHAT THEY NEED THE MOST.
LET'S GET TO IT.
GOOD WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON FROM
THE FOX NEWS DECK.
ONE DAY AFTER COMING UP EMPTY ON
HEALTHCARE, AND IN ALABAMA'S
SENATE RACE, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
TAKING A SWING AT ANOTHER BIG
TICKET ITEM FROM HIS REPUBLICAN
WISH LIST.
TAXES.
A LIVE LOOK IN INDIANAPOLIS.
THE PRESIDENT ABOUT TO UNVEIL
HIS TAX PLAN WHICH THE WHITE
HOUSE AND REPUBLICAN LEADERS ARE
PUSHING.
WE'LL TAKE YOU THERE AS THE
PRESIDENT STARTS TO SPEAK.
WE WOULD REPORT TO YOU HOW YOUR
HOUSE HOLD WOULD BE AFFECTED IF
WE COULD.
THE PROBLEM IS, THERE'S CRUCIAL
DETAILS WE DON'T KNOW AND
PROBABLY WON'T KNOW FOR MONTHS
BECAUSE CONGRESS HAS TO GET
THEIR HANDS ON IT.
DETAILS WHICH COULD HAVE A BIG
IMPACT ON YOUR MONEY.
UNDER THE PROPOSAL, THE NUMBER
OF PERSONAL INCOME TAX BRACKETS
DROPS FROM SEVEN TO THREE.
WE DON'T+++
INDIVIDUALS AND $24,000 FOR
FAMILIES.
IT INCREASES THE AMOUNT OF
INCOME THAT IS TAX-FREE.
THE WHITE HOUSE AND REPUBLICAN
LEADERS ARE ALSO CALLING FOR AN
INCREASED CHILD TAX CREDIT.
IN ADDITION, THEY SAY THEY WANT
TO OPEN IT UP TO FAMILIES WITH
HIGHER INCOMES.
A NEW TAX CREDIT TO HELP PAY FOR
THE CARE OF ELDERLY AND SICK
DEPENDENTS.
NO MORE ESTATE OR DEATH TAX AT
ALL, WHICH IS A WIN FOR
WEALTHIER INDIVIDUALS THAT
INHERIT BUSINESSES AND REAL
ESTATE.
THE PLAN WOULD BE A BIG WIN FOR
BUSINESS OWNERS.
IT CUTS THE CORPORATE TAX RATE
FROM 35% DOWN TO 20%.
AND FOR SMALL BUSINESS OWNERS
FROM NEARLY 40% TO 25%.
BEFORE HE HEADED TO INDIANA, THE
PRESIDENT SAID THE PLAN FOCUSES
ON THE MIDDLE CLASS AND NOT THE
RICH.
>> MY PLAN IS FOR THE WORKING
PEOPLE.
I DON'T BENEFIT.
IN FACT, VERY STRONGLY AS YOU
SEE, THERE'S NO -- I THINK
THERE'S VERY LITTLE BENEFIT FOR
PEOPLE OF WEALTH.
>> THE TOP DEMOCRAT IN THE
SENATE SAYS THAT IS NOT TRUE.
>> UNDER THIS PLAN THE
WEALTHIEST AMERICANS AND
WEALTHIEST CORPORATIONS MAKE OUT
LIKE BANDITS WHILE MIDDLE CLASS
AMERICANS ARE LEFT HOLDING THE
BACK.
>> SENATOR SCHUMER SAID THE PLAN
DIFFERS FROM EVERYTHING THE
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN PROMISING.
THE CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JOHN ROBERTS LIVE
ON THE NORTH LAWN.
HI, JOHN.
>> SHEP, GOOD AFTERNOON.
THIS IS THE BIG ONE FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
THE CENTERPIECE OF HIS ELECTION
CAMPAIGN.
THIS IS WHAT HE PROMISED THE
NATION.
SO HE WANTS TO GET THIS
DELIVERED.
OBAMACARE WAS JUST A STEPPING
STONE ALONG THE WAY.
BECAUSE THIS IS THE SIGNATURE
PLAN FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP.
WE SHOULD POINT OUT THAT 12% IN
THE LOWEST TAX RATE, THAT IS A
2% INCREASE FROM WHERE IT
CURRENTLY IS.
IT'S NOW 10%.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAID IN VARIOUS
BRIEFINGS, BY THE TIME YOU
FACTOR IN DEDUCTIONS, THE CHILD
CARE, THE STANDARD DEDUCTION AND
MORE OF PEOPLE'S MONEY WILL BE
TAXED AT 0% THAN BEFORE MEANS
THEY'LL STILL GET A TAX CUT.
GARY COHN WAS ASKED WHAT THE
AVERAGE CUT WOULD BE FOR A
MIDDLE INCOME FAMILY OF FOUR.
HE SAID HE THOUGHT, DON'T TOLD
ME TO IT, BUT ABOUT $1,000.
ONE OF THE OTHER THINGS THE
PRESIDENT WAS PUSHING FOR HERE
ALMOST MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE,
A CUT IN THE CORPORATE TAX RATE.
HE TALKED THROUGH THE ELECTION
CAMPAIGN ABOUT 15%.
SAID 15, MAYBE 20.
AT SOME POINTS.
I ASKED HIM ABOUT THAT TODAY,
WHETHER 20% WAS A RED LINE OR
COULD IT GO UP FROM THERE.
HERE'S WHAT HE TOLD ME.
>> IS A 20% RATE A RED LINE?
>> VERY MUCH A RED LINE.
>> WHAT ABOUT 15%?
>> I WANTED TO START AT 15 TO
GET 20.
IT JUST -- THE NUMBERS WERE --
15 WAS SO LOW WE DIDN'T TAKE IN
THE REVENUE.
I WANTED 15, SO WE GOT 20.
20 IS MY NUMBER.
I'M NOT NEGOTIATING THAT NUMBER.
I'M NOT GOING TO NEGOTIATE.
>> INTERESTING WHAT THE
PRESIDENT SAID THERE.
HE WANTED 15 BUT THEY COULDN'T
RAISE THE REVENUE WITH 15 SO HE
AGREED ON 20.
WE'LL SEE HOW HARD HE IS WILLING
TO PUSH ON THE RED LINE.
THE PRESIDENT SAID IN THE PAST,
I DON'T SET RED LINES BUT IN
THIS CASE HE HAS.
IN TERMS OF THE WEALTHY AND
WHETHER OR NOT THERE WOULD BE A
FOURTH TAX RATE, GARY COHN WAS
TALKING ABOUT THAT TODAY SAYING
THIS WOULD BE FOR THE VERY TOP
INCOME EARNERS, FEWER THAN 1%.
STEVE BANNON WAS TALKING ABOUT
PEOPLE MAKING MORE THAN $5
MILLION A YEAR.
HE WANTED THE RATE TO START WITH
A FOUR.
COHEN SAID IT MIGHT BE SOMEWHERE
AROUND 36, 37%, SHEP.
WITH ALL OF THE ELIMINATION OF
DEDUCTIONS, THAT MEANS EVEN
THOUGH THE TAX RATE WOULD BE
LOWER FROM 39 1/2, THE VERY TOP
EARNERS WOULD PAY MORE THAN
THEY'RE PAYING NOW.
>> Shepard: JOHN, BEFORE THE
PRESIDENT TOOK OFF ON HIS
SPEECH, PRESIDENT SAID HE WASN'T
HAPPY WITH HIS SECRETARY OF
HOMELAND.
BUT FIRST THE BACK STORY.
POLITCO BROKE THIS STORY LAST
WEEK.
IT REPORTED THAT TOM PRICE
CHARTERED JETS FOR OFFICIAL
BUSINESS AT LEAST TWO DOZEN
TIMES SINCE MAY.
SINCE THEN, THE DEPARTMENT'S
INSPECTOR GENERAL AND THE HOUSE
OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE HAVE
LAUNCHED INVESTIGATIONS.
SATURDAY, SECRETARY PRICE TOLD
FOX NEWS THAT HE WELCOMED THE
REVIEW AND WON'T FLY PRIVATE
UNTIL IT'S OVER.
THE SECRETARY SAID THAT HE
REALIZES "THE OPTICS IN SOME OF
THIS DON'T LOOK GOOD."
WHAT WILL HAPPEN HERE?
>> IF I WAS TOM PRICE, I'D BE
WORRIED.
THE PRESIDENT SAID HE DIDN'T
LIKE IT.
HE TALKED TO TOM PRICE ABOUT IT
AND SAID HE DIDN'T LIKE IT.
HE'S BEEN ANGRY BEFORE.
HE WAS ANGRY AT JEFF SESSIONS
AND MADE UP FOR IT.
LISTEN TO HOW THE PRESIDENT
PHRASED IT WHEN HE TALKED ABOUT
PRICE'S USE OF PRIVATE PLANES.
LOOK AT IT.
>> I'M NOT HAPPY WITH IT.
I'LL TELL YOU, I'M NOT HAPPY
WITH IT.
>> WILL YOU FIRE HIM, SIR?
HE CAVALIERLY SAID WE'LL SEE.
SHEP, HE HAD THAT LOOK ABOUT
HIM.
I DON'T KNOW IF TOM PRICE WANTS
TO LOOK AT MOVING BACK TO
ATLANTA OR NOT.
I WOULD SAY THE WRITING IS ON
THE WALL.
>> JOHN, HOURS AFTER REPUBLICAN
LEADERS FAILED TO GET SOMETHING
DONE ON HEALTHCARE YESTERDAY,
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S CHOICE FOR
ALABAMA'S SENATE SEAT LOST.
WE HAVE A PHOTO HERE ON THE LEFT
IN THIS PHOTO, ROY MOORE, THE
CONSERVATIVE FORMER CHIEF
JUSTICE OF ALABAMA'S SUPREME
COURT.
YESTERDAY HE DEFEATED LUTHER
STRANGE IN A REPUBLICAN
REASON-OFF.
MORE HAS CALLS ISLAM A FALSE
RELIGION.
HE SAID THE ATTACKS OF 9-11 WERE
PUNISHMENT FROM MOVING AWAY FROM
GOD.
IN 2003, HE SAY GAY SEX IS A
CRIME AGAINST NATURE.
TWO YEARS AGO, HE INSTRUCTED
JUDGES IN ALABAMA TO DEFY A
SUPREME COURT RULING AND INSTEAD
ENFORCED THEIR MINISTERIAL DUTY
BY REFUSING TO ISSUE SAME SEX
MARRIAGE LICENSES.
ROY MOORE IS EXPECTED TO DEFEAT
THE DEMOCRAT AND WIN THE SET
THAT JEFF SESSIONS LEFT EMPTY.
LAST NIGHT'S RESULTS COMES DAYS
AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP WENT DOWN
TO ALABAMA TO STUMP FOR LUTHER
STRANGE.
A PRO MITCH McCONNELL SUPER PACT
DUMPED MILLIONS IN ALABAMA TO
TRY TO KEEP MOORE FROM WINNING.
IN ANOTHER BLOW TO THE
REPUBLICAN ESTABLISHMENT, ONE OF
SENATOR McCONNELL'S ALLIES BON
CORKER ANNOUNCED HE WILL NOT RUN
FOR RE-ELECTION NEXT YEAR.
AGAIN TO JOHN ROBERTS.
BUSY DAYS.
>> YEAH, ALWAYS IS, SHEP.
THE PRESIDENT CAMPAIGNED
AGGRESSIVELY ON BEHALF OF LUTHER
STRANGE.
STEVE BANNON WAS CAMPAIGNING FOR
ROY MOORE.
THE REASON HE WAS, HE THOUGHT
ROY MOORE WOULD BE A BETTER ALLY
OF THE PRESIDENT THAN STRANGE.
EVEN THOUGH HE WAS CAMPAIGNING
AGAINST THE PRESIDENT, HE WAS
CAMPAIGNING ON HIS BEHALF.
THE PRESIDENT TELEPHONED ROY
MOORE TO CONGRATULATE HIM AND
SAID HE LOOKS FORWARD TO WORKING
WITH HIM.
INTERESTING TO SEE THAT CORKER
WON'T RUN FOR RE-ELECTION NEXT
YEAR.
CORKER SAID THE PRESIDENT HAS
NOT DEMONSTRATED THE STABILITY
OR CONFIDENCE TO BE PRESIDENT.
STEVE BANNON WAS PLANNING TO
MOUND A PRIMARY CHALLENGE
AGAINST CORKER.
SO SENATOR CORKER DECIDED HE'S
GOING TO PLAY GOLF OUTSIDE OF
CHATTANOOGA AT THE HONORS CLUB
AFTER 2018 AS OPPOSED TO RUNNING
FOR RE-ELECTION.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JOHN.
AFTER HIS LATEST HEALTH CARE
LOSS, THE PRESIDENT SAID HE'S
WILLING TO NEGOTIATE MORE WITH
DEMOCRATS TO COME UP WITH A
BETTER BILL AND PERHAPS A SIGN
OF THINGS TO COME.
TODAY PRESIDENT TRUMP TRAVELED
WITH A DEMOCRAT TO HIS TAX PLAN
EVENT IN INDIANAPOLIS.
INDIANA SENATOR JOE DONNELLY
JOINING THE PRESIDENT ON AIR
FORCE ONE.
OUR CHIEF CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MIKE EMANUEL IS ON
CAPITOL HILL.
WHAT ARE DEMOCRATS SAYING ABOUT
THIS TAX PLAN?
>> DEMOCRATS SAY THEY WOULD LIKE
TO GET THE TAX CODE IMPROVED,
FIXED.
THEY DON'T LIKE THE IDEAS
THEY'RE HEARING IN THE
BLUEPRINT.
FOR EXAMPLE, LOWERING THE TOP
RATE FROM 39.6% TO 35% FOR UPPER
INCOME AMERICANS.
>> WHEN DONALD TRUMP WAS TALKING
ABOUT THIS PLAN OVER THE LAST
FEW DAYS, HE TALKED ABOUT
FOCUSING ON THE MIDDLE CLASS AND
NOT HELPING THE WEALTHY.
THE PLAN IS A MAJOR
DISAPPOINTMENT BECAUSE IT SO
DEVIATES FROM EVERYTHING THE
PRESIDENT SAID.
>> WHAT HAS BEEN RELEASED TODAY
MAKES A TOTAL MOCKERY OUT OF THE
PRESIDENT'S PLEDGE THAT HE
WANTED TAX RELIEF TO BE FOR THE
WORKING CLASS AND IT WOULDN'T BE
FOR THE WEALTHY.
>> TOP DEMOCRATS NOTE THE
PRESIDENT SAID THE RICH WOULD
NOT BENEFIT FROM TAX REFORM.
AND THEY ARE ACCUSING REPUBLICAN
LEADERS HERE ON CAPITOL HILL OF
BREAKING THAT PROMISE.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: ARE THERE ANY SIGNS,
MIKE, THE TWO SIDES ARE WILLING
TO WORK TOGETHER ON THIS?
>> BOTH SIDES SAY THEY WANT TO
GET IT DONE NO SURPRISE THEY
COME AT IT FROM DIFFERENT
PERSPECTIVES.
BOTTOM LINE, TOP REPUBLICANS ARE
SAYING THEY WOULD LIKE DEMOCRATS
AS A PART OF THE DEBATE, A PART
OF THE CONVERSATION.
NOTING THIS IS A CRITICAL
PRIORITY FOR THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
>> INSTEAD OF A SOURCE OF PRIDE,
OUR TAX CODE HAS BECOME A
CONSTANT SOURCE OF FRUSTRATION.
IT'S TOO BIG.
IT'S TOO COMPLICATED.
IT'S TOO EXPENSIVE.
TODAY WE ARE TAKING THE NEXT
STEP TO LIBERATE AMERICANS FROM
OUR BROKEN TAX CODE.
>> I THINK WE CAN, BUT WE'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO HAVE SOME
DEMOCRAT HELP.
I THINK WE HAVE TO SET ASIDE THE
DIFFERENCES AND WORK TOGETHER.
>> WORKING TOGETHER, OF COURSE,
HAS BEEN A CHALLENGE HERE ON
CAPITOL HILL IN RECENT TIMES.
PERHAPS THERE WILL BE SOME
COMMON GROUND THEY CAN FIND ON
FIXING THE TAX CODE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, MIKE.
WE'LL GO LIVE TO INDIANAPOLIS AS
THE PRESIDENT LAYS OUT HIS TAX
PLAN.
IS IT TIME FOR REPUBLICANS TO
COME UP WITH A NEW STRATEGY TO
GET THE PRESIDENT'S AGENDA
PASSED?
WHAT MIGHT IT BE?
THAT'S COMING UP FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK ON THIS WEDNESDAY
AFTERNOON.
GREAT TO HAVE YOU IN.
I'll have the langoustine
lobster ravioli.
For you, sir?
The original call
was for langoustine ravioli.
A langoustine
is a tiny kind of lobster.
A slight shellfish allergy
rules that out,
plus my wife ordered
the langoustine.
I will have chicken tenders
and tater tots.
If you're a ref, you way
over-explain things.
It's what you do.
If you want to save fifteen
percent or more on car insurance
you switch to GEICO.
Sir, we don't have tater tots.
It's what you do.
I will have nachos!
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
SUPPOSED TO HAVE A SPEECH ABOUT
HIS NEW TAX PLAN.
THE PRESIDENT IS ESSENTIALLY ON
TIME AND SHOULD WE WILL CARRY IT
LIVE ANY MOMENT NOW.
THIS COMES A DAY AFTER THE
REPUBLICANS SUFFERED ANOTHER
HEALTHCARE LOSS.
SOME SAY REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS NEED TO WORK TOGETHER
TO ACCOMPLISH SOMETHING.
WILL THAT HAPPEN?
HERE'S JOHN BUSSEY.
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS ON
HEALTHCARE, THAT'S A NONSTARTER.
WHAT ABOUT ON TAXES?
>> IT'S A NONSTARTER WITH THIS
PARTICULAR HEALTHCARE BILL.
TRUMP HAS TO BE LOOKING AT THIS
AND SAYING, IT'S NOT A GREAT
WEEK.
THE HEALTHCARE BILL DIDN'T GET A
VOTE.
HIS CANDIDATE LOST IN ALABAMA.
THE CANDIDATE IN ALABAMA RAN
AGAINST THE ESTABLISHMENT, WHICH
WAS DONALD TRUMP'S ZONE.
SO HE'S LOOKING AT THIS AND JUST
ABOUT TO LAY OUT HIS TAX PLAN.
WE HAVE THE DETAILS.
>> Shepard: NOT MANY.
>> WE HAVE THE OVERALL SCOPE BUT
NOT THE DETAILS.
HE'S PROBABLY THINKING TO
HIMSELF, IF WE'RE GOING TO WORK
WITH THE DEMOCRATS, NOW IS THE
TIME TO BE DOING IT.
>> Shepard: I WAS TALKING THIS
MORNING AND THE SUGGESTION WAS
SAID YOU SHOULD LAY IT OUT.
IF YOU MAKE THIS, THIS IS HOW IT
WILL CHANGE FROM WHERE YOU WERE
BEFORE.
THOSE DETAILS DON'T EXIST.
WE DON'T KNOW WHERE THE SECOND
TAX BRACKET IS.
WE DON'T KNOW.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
VIEWERS WILL PROBABLY NOT FIND
OUT IN THIS PRESS CONFERENCE.
WE KNOW THE OVERALL SCOPE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE WHAT WAS
CAMPAIGNED ON.
SIMPLIFYING THE TAX CODE, REDUCE
THE NUMBER OF BRACKETS TO 3 OR 4
FROM 7.
REDUCE TAXES FOR COMPANIES, FOR
INDIVIDUALS, FOR INDIVIDUALS WHO
OWN BUSINESSES.
ALL THAT SOUNDS GOOD.
BUT THE SORT OF THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE EQUATION HASN'T BEEN
ADDED UP YET.
>> Shepard: HOW YOU PAY FOR IT.
>> HOW YOU PAY FOR IT.
HOW YOU FUND THE GOVERNMENT,
REDUCE THE DEBT WITH CUTTING
TAXES THIS MUCH IF THIS GOES
THROUGH.
YOU KNOW, CORPORATE TAX CUT FROM
35% TO 20, 1 TO 15.
MAYBE IT UNDER UP AT 25.
STILL A SUBSTANTIAL CUT IN
REVENUE.
THE ARGUMENT IS BEING MADE, IT
WILL TAKE CARE OF ITSELF.
WHY?
CUTTING COMPANY TAXES AND YOURS
AND MY TAXES IF THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENS RESULTS IN ECONOMIC
GROWTH BECAUSE THAT MONEY GETS
INVESTED IN THE ECONOMY.
THAT IS A BIG ROLL OF THE DICE.
>> Shepard: WE'VE HEARD THAT
BEFORE.
HAS IT WORKED IN THE PAST?
>> WE HAVE HEARD IT BEFORE.
THE REGAN ERA PROVED IT TO BE
TRUE.
IT STIMULATES TAXES.
>> Shepard: HIGH TAXES UNDER
REAGAN.
>> THAT, TOO.
AN UNEVEN ECONOMIC GROWTH BASED
ON A LOT OF FACTORS.
NOT JUST WHETHER COMPANIES HAVE
MORE TO INVEST AND YOU AND I DO.
>> Shepard: THERE'S MIXED
REPORTING ON ROY MOORE IF HE
DEFEATS THE DEMOCRAT WHICH HE IS
EXPECTED TO DO, IF HE WILL BE
WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP OR AGAINST
HIM.
>> SO YOU'D THINK STRIKE.
BECAUSE PRESIDENT TRUMP
CAMPAIGNED FOR HIS OPPONENT.
LUTHER STRANGE IN THE ELECTION.
SO DID McCONNELL.
MOORE RAN AS AN ANTI
ESTABLISHMENT CANDIDATE, WHICH
SEEMS TO BE DONALD TRUMP'S
TERRITORY.
HE RAN AGAINST McCONNELL, HE RAN
AGAINST THE ADMINISTRATION.
HE SAID I'M YOUR GUY.
AT THIS STAGE OF THE GAME, ONE
KIND OF ARGUMENT CAN BE MADE
THAT STEVE BANNON IS RIGHT.
WHICH IS AT THE END -- STEVE
BANNON THAT SUPPORTED MOORE AND
SAYS WE'RE GOING TO DO MORE OF
THIS.
WE'RE GOING TO FIGHT AGAINST THE
ESTABLISHMENT REPUBLICAN
HIERARCHY BY ELECTING NEW
REPUBLICANS.
HE MAY BE RIGHT.
MOORE COMES IN AS SORT OF AN
ANTI ESTABLISHMENT,
ANTI-WASHINGTON CANDIDATE WHICH
ALIGNS HIMSELF PERHAPS WITH
TRUMP'S AGENDA MORE CLEARLY.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
SAID I'LL WORK WITH HIM.
HE SAID IT ON HIS STUMP IN
ALABAMA.
IF ROY MOORE WINS, WE'LL WORK
TOGETHER.
>> BY THEN WILL HE HAVE TO BE
WORKING MORE CLOSELY WITH THE
DEMOCRATIC CAUCUS.
>> Shepard: WHAT DOES THIS SAY
MORE ABOUT THE ESTABLISHMENT AND
MITCH McCONNELL AND THE MACHINE
THAT THAT IS.
>> BAD WEEK FOR DONALD TRUMP.
WORSE LAST FEW DAYSOR F
L.NNEL
IT WAS THE LATEST ITERLATION OF
THE HEALTHCARE BILL NOT GETTING
PASSED.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JOHN.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: HURRICANE MARIA LEFT
PARTS OF PUERTO RICO IN RUINS.
THERE'S NEW VIDEO OF THE
DEVASTATION IN POOREST
NEIGHBORHOODS.
MORE THAN HALF OF THE PEOPLE
THERE ARE HOMELESS.
THEY'RE AMERICANS THAT LOST SO
MUCH TO THIS STORM.
WE'LL TAKE YOU LIVE TO PUERTO
RICO.
WE'LL MEET UP WITH GERALDO THAT
IS ON HOW THE MILITARY IS
STEPPING IN TO HELP.
WE'RE WAITING FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S BIG -- MUCH ANTICIPATED
TAX SPEECH THAT IS COMING FROM
INDIANAPOLIS.
WE'RE EXPECTING THAT MOMENTS
FROM NOW.
WE'LL HAVE LIVE COVERAGE ON
AMERICA'S CHOICE FOR NEWS AND
INFORMATION ON CABLE.
THIS IS FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
Approaching Medicare
eligibility?
Don't put off checking out your
Medicare options until 65.
Now is a good time to get the
ball rolling.
Medicare only covers about
eighty percent of
Part B medical costs.
The rest is up to you.
That's where AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plans
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company come in.
Like all standardized Medicare
supplement insurance plans,
they could help save you in
out-of-pocket medical costs.
Taking informed steps really
makes a difference later.
That's what it means to
GO LONG™.
Call now and request this free
Decision Guide
and explore the range of AARP
Medicare Supplement Plans.
All plans like these let you
choose any doctor or hospital
that accepts Medicare patients.
These are the only Medicare
supplement insurance plans
endorsed by AARP.
Call now and request your free
Decision Guide...
and start gathering the
information you need
to help you GO LONG™.
>> Shepard: YOU ARE LOOKING LIVE
IN INDIANAPOLIS, INDIANA.
WE WAIT FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP TO
LAY OUT HIS PROPOSED TAX PLAN.
THAT EVENT SCHEDULED TO START IN
A FEW MINUTES.
WE'RE LED TO BELIEVE IT WAS
BEGIN PRESENTLY.
WE'LL HAVE IT LIVE WHEN THE
PRESIDENT STARTS TO SPEAK.
SOME IN PUERTO RICO SAY THEY
HAVE NOT HAD A SINGLE GOVERNMENT
WORKER SINCE HURRICANE MARIA
DEVASTATED THE IDEA COME TO
THEIR AREA.
SOME PEOPLE SAY THEY'RE WAITING
AND WAITING FOR CLEAN WATER AND
FOOD.
THIS IS CATANYO.
A TOWN OUTSIDE SAN JUAN.
MORE THAN HALF OF THE PEOPLE ARE
HOMELESS.
ONE WOMAN TOLD GARRETT TENNEY
RED CROSS WORKERS CAME BY A
COUPLE DAYS AGO AND PROMISED
FOOD AND WATER BUT SO FAR NOBODY
HAS RETURNED.
FEMA OFFICIALS SAY IT'S VERY
DIFFICULT TO GET AID TO SOME
AREAS BECAUSE OF THE EXTENT OF
THE DAMAGE.
THE UNITED STATES MILITARY IS
SENDING THOUSANDS OF ADDITIONAL
SERVICE MEMBERS TO HELP.
FOX NEWS' GERALDO RIVERA IS LIVE
IN SAN JUAN.
GERALDO?
>> PART OF THE PROBLEM IS, I
DON'T THINK UNTIL MAYBE THIS
MORNING THE PRESIDENT, THE
CABINET AND THE ENTIRE AMERICAN
GOVERNMENT UNDERSTOOD THE
MAGNITUDE OF THIS DISASTER.
THEY HAVE BEEN SENDING IN AID.
IT'S BEEN TRICKLING IN.
WE SAW THE PORT LAST NIGHT, THE
PORT OF SAN JUAN, OPERATING WHAT
SEEMED TO BE MINIMAL CAPACITY.
EVEN THE AIRPORT, WHICH IS JUST
BEHIND THE CAMERA DOES NOT SEEM
ANYTHING LIKE THE ACTIVITY YOU'D
EXPECT IN THE BERLIN AIRLIFT.
THEY DON'T UNDERSTAND THAT THIS
IS PUERTO RICO'S KATRINA.
THIS IS A GENERALIZED DISASTER.
WE FOUND MY FATHER'S YOUNGEST
SIBLING.
ONE OF THE LAST SURVIVING OF MY
FATHER'S BIG FLOCK.
HE'S ONE OF 17 SIBLINGS.
WE FOUND HER IN A DARKENED HOUSE
LAST NIGHT WITH A TREE THROUGH
THE ROOF AND ANOTHER TREE
BLOCKING THE STREETS.
I HAVE NOT SEEN NUMBERS OF
FEDERAL OFFICIALS OUT WILL DOING
WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE FOR THIS
ISLAND IN CRISIS, THIS ISLAND IN
DIRE STRAITS.
YOU MENTIONED THE UNITED STATES
MILITARY.
THE FLEET HAS ARRIVED OFF THE
EASTERN SIDE.
WE TOOK A HELICOPTER OUT TO THE
AIRCRAFT CARRIER YET.
THEY'RE MUSTERING HELP FOR THE
PEOPLE ASHORE WHERE THEY CAN
LOCATE AREAS OR SPECIFIC
LOCATIONS WHERE THEIR EXPERTISE
IS NEEDED.
WE SAW ONE OF THE LOCATIONS IN A
CITY ON THE EASTERN END OF
PUERTO RICO.
THE RIDER MEMORIAL HOSPITAL,
WHICH HAD BEEN DECIMATED BY THE
HURRICANE.
HURRICANE MARIA SWEPT THROUGH
THIS AND RENDERED THE HOSPITAL
INOPERABLE.
THE MARINES AND THE NAVY CBs DID
LAND TODAY.
THE EMERGENCY GENERATOR, THEY
WORKED AT IT, WORKED AT IT AND
TRIED TO START IT.
THEY TRIED TO START IT.
FINALLY THAT EMERGENCY GENERATOR
KICKED IN, PROVIDING MUCH-NEEDED
POWER TO THE HOSPITAL IN NEED.
THE ADMINISTRATORS OF THE
HOSPITAL WERE BEYOND GRATEFUL,
SHEP.
>> I CAN'T EVEN EXPRESS THE JOY.
I'M SPEECHLESS, EXCEPT I WANT TO
MAKE SURE THAT EVERYBODY IS
LISTENING TO US KNOWS HOW
GRATEFUL, HOW THANKFUL WE ARE
FOR EVERYTHING, EVERY PERSON,
EVERY RESOURCE, EVERYBODY THAT
WE KNOW ARE WORKING AROUND THE
CLOCK TO HELP US.
HELP WE NEED.
WE ARE GETTING UP.
WE HAVEN'T CLOSED OUR DOORS.
WE ARE JUST SO GRATEFUL.
THANK YOU, THANK YOU, THANK YOU,
AMERICA.
>> THAT GRATITUDE IS
HEART-RENDERING AND TOUCHING.
BUT THE SCALE OF THE ASSISTANCE
THEY'RE RECEIVING DOESN'T MATCH
THE SCALE OF THIS DISASTER,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: I KEEP WONDERING
ABOUT THE POORER COMMUNITIES
THAT WE HAVEN'T SEEN REPORTS.
AS FAR AS WE CAN TELL, WE DON'T
KNOW WHETHER THEY'RE GETTING THE
FOOD AND THE WATER AND THINGS
THAT THEY NEED.
DO YOU KNOW?
>> THEY ARE NOT.
THEY ARE NOT.
YOU KNOW, WHAT COMES IN ON A
C-130, THESE CASES OF WATER OR
THESE MREs, THE MEALS READY TO
EAT DOESN'T BEGIN TO MATCH WHAT
THIS POPULATION NEEDS.
THE SYSTEMS HAVE BEEN CRUSHED.
THERE IS NO INFRASTRUCTURE.
THERE'S NO ELECTRICITY.
THE FRUSTRATION OF TRYING TO GET
A CELL PHONE TO WORK ON THIS
ISLAND.
YOU KNOW, PEOPLE GET SO USED TO
THE INTERNET.
THERE IS NO INTERNET HERE EXCEPT
MAYBE IN THIS HOTEL OR THAT
HOTEL.
THE NEED IS SO PROFOUND.
THE NEED IS REALLY SO
WIDESPREAD.
I THINK THE PRESIDENT'S VISIT IS
HOPEFUL.
WE NEED THAT PORT OPEN.
THERE'S SOMETHING CALLED THE
JONES ACT.
THE JONES ACT PREVENTS SHIPS
THAT BEAR A FOREIGN FLAG FROM
TRANSPORTING GOODS OF THE
MAINLAND TO THE UNITED STATES TO
PUERTO RICO, WHICH IS CONSIDERED
PART OF THE MAINLAND OF THE
UNITED STATES.
THEY HAVE TO BE ON U.S.-FLAGGED
MERCHANT VESSELS.
THE JONES ACT MUST BE SUSPECTED.
EVERY VESSEL AVAILABLE MUST BE
USED TO BRING FUEL OIL.
THERE'S A SIX-HOUR WAIT AT GAS
STATIONS STILL.
THE PEOPLE ARE RUNNING
GENERATORS SO THEY HAVE TO STAY
ONLINE.
THEY RUN OUT OF GAS IN THEIR
CARS WAITING TO GET GAS TO FUEL
THEIR GENERATORS.
I THINK IN TERMS OF THE PUBLIC
HEALTH AND WELL-BEING OF THE
FOLKS.
THE HOSPITALS ARE DOING
HERCULEAN WORK TO MAKE THEM
WELL.
WHAT WE NEED ARE PEOPLE TO PUT
UP TELEPHONE POLES, CELL PHONE
TOWERS, TO GET THE ELECTRIC GRID
WORKING.
70% WAS ALREADY OUT FROM
HURRICANE KATRINA.
WE NEED GENERATORS.