ge.
I wanted to be clear.
I wanted it to last.
So I kept on fighting.
I found something that worked.
And keeps on working.
Now?
They SEE ME.
SEE ME.
See if COSENTYX could make a
difference for you-
COSENTYX is proven to help
people with moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis...
...find clear skin that
can last.
Don't use if you're allergic
to COSENTYX.
Before starting COSENTYX,
you should be checked
for tuberculosis.
An increased risk of infections
and lowered ability
to fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor if you have
an infection or symptoms.
Or if you have received a
vaccine or plan to.
If you have inflammatory
bowel disease,
tell your doctor if symptoms
develop or worsen.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
Never give up.
SEE ME.
Clear skin can last.
Don't hold back...
...ask your dermatologist
if COSENTYX can help you
find clear skin that lasts.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
THE U.S. BOOTING MORE THAN HALF
OF CUBA'S DIPLOMATS FROM
WASHINGTON.
THIS COMES AFTER A MYSTERIOUS
SONIC ATTACK AGAINST AT LEAST 22
AMERICANS IN HAVANA.
THE SYMPTOMS ARE BRAIN DAMAGE
AND HEARING LOSS.
THE CUBAN GOVERNMENT HAS DENIED
ANY INVOLVEMENT.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT IS ALSO
PULLING MOST OF ITS STAFF OUT OF
CUBA AND WARNING AMERICANS
AGAINST TRAVELING THERE.
NEARLY TWO WEEKS AFTER A MASSIVE
EARTHQUAKE ROCKED MEXICO, SEARCH
TEAMS ARE STILL PULLING OUT
BODIES.
THE QUICK KILLED MORE THAN 300
AND DAMAGED THOUSANDS OF HOMES.
MUSIC FANS REMEMBERING TOM PETTY
LEAVING CANDLES AND FLOWERS ON
HIS HOLLYWOOD STAR.
AG MER SAID H WEENO ITNT
CCARRIAT ANDES A DIED AT THE
HOSPITAL.
HE WAS 66.
THE NEWS CONTINUES WITH SHEP
AFTER THIS.
eed in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP
VISITING PUERTO RICO AFTER TWO
WEEKS AFTER HURRICANE MARIA TORE
THROUGH THE U.S. TERRITORY.
THE PRESIDENT AND THE FIRST LADY
ALSO MEETING THIS HOUR WITH THE
GOVERNOR OF THE U.S. VIRGIN
ISLANDS WHICH ARE STILL
RECOVERING FROM HURRICANES IRMA
AND MARIA.
WE'LL HAVE THAT FOR YOU WHEN WE
GET IT.
TODAY PRESIDENT TRUMP MET WITH
STORM VICTIMS IN PUERTO RICO.
OFFICIALS SAY ABOUT 95% OF THAT
ISLAND STILL HAS NO ELECTRICITY.
THAT INCLUDES SOME HOSPITALS.
LOTS OF PEOPLE ARE STILL
DESPERATE NEED OF THE BASICS.
FOOD, FRESHWATER, FUEL AND
MONEY.
THE PRESIDENT'S VISIT COMES AS
CRITICS SAY THAT THE FEDS HAVE
BEEN SLOW TO RESPOND.
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR HAS
DEFENDED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S EFFORTS.
THE MAJOR OF SAN JUAN SAID LAST
WEEK THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN
KILLING US WITH INEFFICIENCY.
THAT'S A QUOTE.
SHE ALSO SAID THAT PUERTO RICO
WAS HEADING TOWARDS GENOCIDE
BECAUSE OF THE CRISIS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP OVER THE WEEKEND
PUSHED BACK SAYING THE MAJOR AND
OTHERS HAVE SHOWN POOR
LEADERSHIP.
THE PRESIDENT ALSO TWEETED THAT
THERE'S BEEN TREMENDOUS
PROGRESS.
DESPITE THAT, AS HE PUT IT,
POLITICALLY MOTIVATED INGRATES
WE'RE SAYING.
THAT'S WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP TOLD
JOHN ROBERTS BEFORE LEAVING THE
WHITE HOUSE THIS MORNING.
>> I THINK SHE'S COME BACK A
LONG WAY.
NOW ACKNOWLEDGING WHAT A GREAT
JOB WE'VE DONE.
PEOPLE ARE LOOKING AT THAT.
TEXAS AND FLORIDA, WE GOT AN A
PLUS.
I TELL YOU WHAT, WE'VE DONE JUST
AS GOOD IN PUERTO RICO.
IT'S A MUCH TOUGHER SITUATION.
BUT NOW THE ROADS ARE CLEARED,
COMMUNICATIONS ARE STARTING TO
COME BACK.
WE NEED THEIR TRUCK DRIVERS.
THEIR DRIVERS HAVE TO START
DRIVING TRUCKS.
WE HAVE TO DO THAT.
ON A LOCAL LEVEL, WE NEED MORE
HELP.
THE FIRST RESPONDERS, MILITARY,
FEMA HAVE DONE AN INCREDIBLE JOB
IN PUERTO RICO.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SHOOK HANDS WITH THE SAN JUAN
MAYOR JUST BEFORE A BRIEFING ON
THE RELIEF EFFORTS.
YOU CAN MAKE OUT A LITTLE BIT OF
THAT OR WHAT SHE SAID TO THE
PRESIDENT.
HERE, LOOK.
>> Shepard: DURING THE BRIEFING
WHEN THEY THANKED FEDERAL AND
LOCAL OFFICIALS FOR THEIR
EFFORTS, HE DID NOT MENTION THE
MAYOR.
THE PRESIDENT MENTIONED THE
TRUCKERS.
ACCORDING TO OUR REPORTERS ON
THE GROUND, MANY OF THOSE THAT
WOULD MOVE THE SUPPLIES HAVE
LOST THEIR HOMES AND VEHICLES IN
THE STORM.
SOME OF THE TRUCKERS CAN'T BE
REACHED BECAUSE THERE'S NO
COMMUNICATION WORKING IN SO MANY
AREAS STILL.
REPORTS THAT A UNION TRUCKER'S
STRIKE ADDED TO THE PROBLEMS ARE
NOT TRUE.
THEY ARE IN FACT FAKE NEWS
SPREAD LARGELY BY A WEBSITE
CALLED CONSERVATIVE TREE HOUSE
AND THEN OVER TWITTER AND
FACEBOOK.
AGAIN, THERE'S NO TRUCKER'S
STRIKE.
THAT'S FAKE NEWS.
THE TRUCKERS IN PUERTO RICO ARE
VICTIMS, TOO.
THE CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HAS AN UPDATE.
HI, JOHN.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON, SHEP.
THERE'S SO MANY VICTIMS IN
PUERTO RICO AND THE PRESIDENT
GOT TO MEET A FEW OF THEM.
THE PRESIDENT WITH HIGH PRAISE
FOR THE FEDERAL RESPONSE AND THE
MILITARY.
THE PRESIDENT THANKING VERY MUCH
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR WHO
ALIGNS WITH DEMOCRATS FOR
LEAVING POLITICS OUT OF THIS
THING.
THE DISCUSSION ABOUT STORM
RELIEF.
LISTEN TO WHAT THE PRESIDENT
SAID JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
>> HE WAS TREMENDOUSLY
SUPPORTIVE.
HE KNEW THE LEVEL OF PROBLEM
THAT YOU HAD AT THE BEGINNING
BEFORE AND THE LEVEL OF WHAT
HAPPENED WITH RESPECT TO THE
TREMENDOUS STORMS THAT HAVE HIT
YOUR BEAUTIFUL ISLAND.
TO THE GOVERNOR, I WANT TO TELL
YOU THAT RIGHT FROM THE
BEGINNING, THIS GOVERNOR DID NOT
PLAY POLITICS.
HE DIDN'T PLAY IT AT ALL.
HE WAS SAYING IT LIKE IT WAS.
HE WAS GIVING US THE HIGHEST
GRADES.
ON BEHALF OF OUR COUNTRY, I WANT
TO THANK YOU.
>> THE PRESIDENT SPENDING SOME
TIME WITH RESIDENTS IN A
SAN JUAN NEIGHBORHOOD AND WENT
TO A LOCAL CHURCH, WHICH IS A
DISTRIBUTION POINT FOR RELIEF
SUPPLIES AND HANDING OUT RICE
AND PAPER TOWELS.
THE PRESIDENT HAS TWEETED ABOUT
THE ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF MONEY
IT'S GOING TO TAKE TO REBUILD
PUERTO RICO AND JOKED THIS
MORNING THE DISASTER HAS
STRETCHED THE FEDERAL BUDGET A
LITTLE BIT THIN.
LISTEN HERE.
>> I HATE TO TELL YOU, PUERTO
RICO, BUT YOU'RE THROWING OUR
BUDGET A LITTLE OUT OF WHACK.
WE SPENT A LOT OF MONEY IN
PUERTO RICO.
THAT'S FINE.
WE SAVED A LOT OF LIVES.
>> ON CAPITOL HILL, SENATOR
CHUCK SCHUMER OF NEW YORK SAID
HE DIDN'T APPRECIATE THE JOKE
SAYING IT LOOKS LIKE THE
PRESIDENT WAS BLAMING PUERTO
RICO.
A LOT OF FOLKS WOULD LIKE TO
BLOW THE LINES FOR DISASTER
RELIEF AND THE ENORMOUS DEBT IN
PUERTO RICO.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO MAKE SURE
THE FOCUS IS ON DISASTER RELIEF
AND ANY DISCUSSION ABOUT PUERTO
RICO'S DEBT WILL HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL LATER, UNTIL AFTER THEY
HAVE RECOVERED FROM THE STORM.
>> Shepard: JOHN, THE PRESIDENT
WHILE IN PUERTO RICO TALKED
ABOUT THE HORRIBLE MURDER
RAMPAGE IN LAS VEGAS.
>> YEAH.
HE GETS BACK FROM PUERTO RICO
LATE TONIGHT, TOMORROW MORNING
AND WILL HEAD OUT TO LAS VEGAS.
THE PRESIDENT SAYING A WHILE AGO
IN TERMS OF THE TRIP TO
LAS VEGAS, HE LOOKS FORWARD TO
PAYING HIS PERSONAL RESPECTS AND
CONDOLENCES TO EVERYONE.
SUCH A TRAGEDY, SO UNNECESSARY.
I LOOK FORWARD TO GOING
TOMORROW.
THE FIRST LADY WILL BE COMING
WITH ME AND PAYING OUR RESPECTS.
THE PRESIDENT SAID HIS ANXIOUS
TO GET A FULL UNDERSTANDING WHY
THE GUNMAN DID THIS AND A HIGH
PRAISE FOR POLICE THAT RAN
TOWARDS DANGER AND TRACKED DOWN
WHERE HE WAS FIRING FROM.
LISTEN HERE.
>> WE HAVE A TRAGEDY.
WHAT HAPPENED IN LAS VEGAS IS IN
MANY WAYS A MIRACLE.
THE POLICE DEPARTMENT HAS DONE
SUCH AN INCREDIBLE JOB.
WE'LL BE TALKING ABOUT GUN LAWS.
HIS A SICK MAN, DEMENTED MAN.
WE'RE LOOKING INTO HIM VERY
SERIOUSLY.
BUT WE'RE DEALING WITH A VERY,
VERY SICK INDIVIDUAL.
>> A LOT OF THORNY POLITICAL
ISSUES LIE AHEAD.
DEMOCRATS ARE TALKING ABOUT GUN
CONTROL.
A BILL IN CONGRESS THAT APPEARS
TO HAVE BEEN SHELVED FOR NOW
THAT MAKES SILENCERS ILLEGAL.
I ASKED THE PRESIDENT ABOUT HIS
POSITION.
HE SAID WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT
LATER.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU, JOHN.
IN PUERTO RICO, SOME BUSINESSES
ARE STARTING TO REOPEN.
AS WE HEARD, MANY AREAS OF THE
ISLAND ARE STILL DEVASTATED AND
IN NEED OF SO MUCH HELP.
SOME FAMOUS PUERTO RICANS ARE
CHIPPING IN.
GERALDO RIVERA REPORTS FROM
SAN JUAN.
>> SHEP, PUERTO RICO IS SLOWLY
GETTING BACK ON ITS FEET.
A LONG ROAD TO RECOVERY.
95% OF THE PEOPLE ARE STILL
WITHOUT ELECTRICAL POWER.
EVEN HERE ON TOURIST STRIP.
HALF THE PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
RUNNING WATER AND A THIRD OF
THEM HAVE ANY KIND OF CELL
SERVICE OR INTERNET.
THAT'S PART OF THE PROBLEM, NO
COMMUNICATIONS.
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT IS
UNDERREPORTED IS HOW THE PUERTO
RICAN FAMILY, THE EXTENDED
FAMILY, NEIGHBORS, RELATIVES AND
SO FORTH ARE COMING TOGETHER TO
HELP PEOPLE.
J-LO DONATING A BUNCH OF MONEY.
RICKY MARTIN CAME YESTERDAY.
LOOK AT THIS CREW FROM QUEENS,
NEW YORK.
NATIONAL GUARDSMEN AND OTHER
VOLUNTEERS BRINGING AID AND
ASSISTANCE TO THEIR PUERTO RICAN
FAMILY.
>> WE CAME.
THESE ARE DONATIONS THAT CAME
FROM NEW YORK CITY.
WE'RE GOING OUT TODAY TO TAKE
CARE OF THEM.
>> SHEP, MANY HERE IN PUERTO
RICO ARE WORRIED THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES WOULD BE
DIVERTED BY THE AWFUL TRAGEDY IN
LAS VEGAS.
THE FOLKS ARE DELIGHTED THAT HE
IS MAKING THE VISIT HERE TO
PUERTO RICO AND WILL GO ON TO
NEVADA ON WEDNESDAY.
THERE HAVE BEEN REPORTS OF
LOOTING HERE IN PUERTO RICO.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT
ACCORDING TO THE OFFICIALS, THE
CRIME RATE IS ABOUT THE SAME AS
IT WAS.
THOSE REPORTS ARE EXAGGERATED.
WHAT SHOULD BE EMPHASIZED IS HOW
THE PUERTO RICAN PEOPLE ARE
COMING TOGETHER TO HELP EACH
OTHER.
REPORTING FROM SAN JUAN, SHEP,
BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: THANKS, GERALDO.
BETWEEN THE CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO AND THE MASSACRE IN
LAS VEGAS, THE PRESIDENT IS PUT
TO A TEST.
MORE ON HIS ROLE AS CONSOLER IN
CHIEF NEXT.
>> MORE ON THE PRESIDENT'S TRIP
TO PUERTO RICO AFTER OFFICIALS
THERE CRITICIZED THE FEDERAL
RESPONSE TO HURRICANE MARIA.
AT LEAST THE LOCAL MAYOR DID AND
SOME OTHERS.
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR HAS
PRAISED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S RESPONSE TO
THAT DEADLY STORM.
LET'S BRING IN ALEX FROM
POLITICO.
SAN JUAN IS COMING ALONG WELL.
SOME OTHERS ARE NOT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS A REALLY TROUBLING
SITUATION, WHAT YOU SAW TODAY IS
THE PRESIDENT TRAVELED THERE AND
TRIED TO BEST SPIN FORWARD ON
WHAT HIS ADMINISTRATION'S
EFFORTS HAVE BEEN SO FAR.
EVEN AS HE'S GOTTEN TO THIS
FIGHT WITH LOCAL OFFICIALS
THERE.
A LOT OF THIS SEEMED TO BE ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT TRYING TO DEFEND
HIMSELF AND HIS WHITE HOUSE AND
HOW THEY HAVE DONE SO FAR IN
MANAGING THIS CRISIS.
>> Shepard: IT WAS A BIT OF A
PRESS AVAILABILITY AND PHOTO
OPPORTUNITY THERE UNLIKE ANY
I'VE SEEN WITH PREVIOUS
PRESIDENTS AT DISASTERS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU GOT THE SENSE THAT THE
PRESIDENT WAS TRYING TO PUT ON A
SHOW HERE AND TRYING TO
ADVERTISE HIMSELF AND WHAT HE'S
DONE AND DEFEND HIMSELF AND HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
YOU KNOW, HERE'S THE THING ABOUT
THIS TRIP AND WHAT YOU'LL ALSO
SEE WITH THIS TRIP THAT WILL
COME TOMORROW WITH LAS VEGAS.
THIS SQUEAK SPOTLIGHTS A ROLE
THAT TRUMP HADN'T NECESSARILY
EXPECTED TO PLAY WHEN HE FIRST
RAN FOR PRESIDENT, WHICH IS THAT
OF CONSOLER IN CHIEF.
THAT OF A LEADER THAT IS COMING
TO THE COMFORT --
>> Shepard: I DON'T KNOW WHY HE
WOULDN'T EXPECT TO DO THAT.
EVERY PRESIDENT FOREVER HAS HAD
TO DO THAT.
LOOK HOW GREAT RONALD REAGAN WAS
AT IT ON THE HEELS OF THE
CHALLENGER DISASTER.
EACH PRESIDENT SINCE THEN HAS
HAD A SHINING MOMENT IN TIMES OF
NEED, I WOULD SAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AT ONE TIME OR THE OTHER.
YOU'RE SEEING A PRESIDENT THAT
CAMPAIGNED ON THE IDEA THAT HE
WAS GOING TO BE A STRONG MAN
LIKE FIGURE, A FIGURE OF
STRENGTH.
HE'S DOING SOMETHING THAT HE
DIDN'T REALLY CAMPAIGN ON.
>> Shepard: ALEX, HAVE TO CUT IT
SHORT.
THERE'S NEW INFORMATION COMING
IN TO FOX NEWS ABOUT THE
INVESTIGATION INTO THE LAS VEGAS
MASSACRE, INCLUDING WORD THAT
THE FEDS HAVE TALKED WITH AN
IMMEDIATE RELATIVE OF THE
GUNMAN'S GIRLFRIEND.
WE HAVE BRAND NEW DETAILS.
OUR CHIEF INTELLIGENCE
CORRESPONDENT CATHERINE HERRIDGE
JUST PULLED THEM TOGETHER.
LIVE TO HER NEXT.
KEEPING ME FROM THE
THINGS I LOVE TO DO.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-214-2424.
I just saved thousands
on my loan at LendingTree.com.
In less than a minute, I found
out how much home I can afford.
I like how you shop for loans
the same way you
shop for flights online.
I didn't realize at LendingTree
you can save money
on almost any sort of loan.
I consolidated my credit card
debt with a personal loan.
I found a new credit card
with 0% interest for 15 months.
You just shop, compare,
and save. And it's all free.
Go to LendingTree right now
and start saving.
If you have Medicare
Parts A and B
guess what?
You could apply for a
Medicare supplement insurance
plan whenever you want.
No enrollment window.
No waiting to apply.
That means now may be a
great time to shop for an
AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Medicare doesn't
cover everything.
And like all standardized
Medicare supplement
insurance plans,
these help cover some
of what Medicare
doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide.
It could help you find the
AARP Medicare Supplement plan
that works for you.
These types of plans have
no networks,
so you get to choose any
doctor who accepts
Medicare patients.
Rates are competitive,
and they're the only plans
of their kind endorsed by AARP.
Remember -
these plans let you apply
all year round.
So call today.
Because now's the perfect time
to learn more.
Go long.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS NOW.
WE HAVE AN UPDATE ON THE
INVESTIGATION OF THE MASSACRE IN
LAS VEGAS.
A U.S. GOVERNMENT SOURCE SAYS
THE FEDS HAVE INTERVIEWED A
RELATIVE OF THE SHOOTER'S
GIRLFRIEND AND WE HAVE JUST
LEARNED THAT IN THE 70s AND 80s,
THE SHOOTER WORKED AS A LETTER
CARRIER AND AN IRS AGENT
SEPARATELY FOR A TOTAL OF A
DECADE.
SO WHAT ABOUHITS T INTERVIEW
WITH THE GIRLFRIEND'S FAMILY?
CATHERINE HERRIDGE HAS THAT LIVE
IN WASHINGTON.
KATHERINE?
>> I'VE BEEN WORKING ON THIS
INFORMATION THROUGHOUT THE DAY
WITH THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
PRODUCER, JAKE GIBSON.
WE CONFIRMED THROUGH A U.S.
GOVERNMENT SOURCE THAT FALEDER
IN
S ATSTHAORVE INTEREWED A
IMMEDIATE RELATIVELY MARILOU
DANLEY.
THIS RELATIVE SAID TO THE FBI
THAT THEY FOUND PADDOCK UNSTABLE
AND HE MADE THEM UNCOMFORTABLE.
FBI OFFICIALS DECLINED TO
COMMENT ON THIS INTERVIEW ONE
WAY OR THE OTHER TO FOX NEWS
EARLIER TODAY.
AND THE FBI RAN PADDOCK THROUGH
THE CRIMINAL SYSTEM.
WE'RE TOLD IT WILL TAKE A DAY OR
TWO TO PROCESS HIS RECORD.
THE FBI INDICATED IN CONNECTION
TO TERROR WAS MADE BEFORE THE
FULL ANALYSIS OF HIS ELECTRONICS
WAS COMPLETE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE, WHAT DO
WE KNOW ABOUT THE MONEY THAT
THIS MURDERER SENT OVERSEAS
PRIOR TO THE MASSACRE?
>> INVESTIGATORS HAVE DISCOVERED
THAT PADDOCK SENT TENS OF
THOUSANDS OVERSEAS AND MAY HAVE
BEEN TO THE GIRLFRIEND, MARILOU
DANLEY.
THEY'RE STILL INVESTIGATING.
THEY THINK IT WAS TO THE
PHILIPPINES BUT THERE'S
CONFUSION OVER HER LOCATION AND
WHETHER SHE'S IN JAPAN.
HE SEND A LOT OF MONEY OVERSEAS
BEFORE THE SHOOTING AND
INVESTIGATORS ARE TRYING TO
DETERMINE IF IT WENT TO THIS
GIRLFRIEND OR SOMEONE ASSOCIATED
WITH HER, SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE A LOT OF
GAPS IN THE STORY OF THIS MAN.
AUTHORITIES SAY IT'S SO RARE TO
HAVE A SHOOTING WITHOUT A
MOTIVE.
SOMETHING THEY HAVE NOT FOUND.
>> EVERYONE I SPEAK TO ABOUT
THIS CASE, SHEP, TALKS ABOUT IT
AS BEING AN ANOMALY.
YOU KNOW FROM YOUR EXPERIENCE
COVERING THESE EVENTS, THAT
USUALLY WITHIN 24 HOURS YOU HAVE
A GOOD SENSE OF THE SHOOTER AND
A LIKELY MOTIVATION.
THEY HAVE SOME KIND OF PRESENCE
ON SOCIAL MEDIA OR THEY HAVE
BEEN ON BLOGS WRITING ABOUT
THEIR POINT OF VIEW.
THIS GUY IS REALLY A GHOST WHEN
IT COMES TO SOCIAL MEDIA AND NO
ONE HAS COME FORWARD IN A VERY
PUBLIC WAY TO TALK ABOUT WHAT
HIS MOTIVATION MAY HAVE BEEN ON
THE IDEOLOGY.
BUT WHAT IS CLEAR FROM THE SCOPE
OF THE INVESTIGATION, THE
LOCATIONS, THE FIREPOWER, THE
AMMUNITION, ALL OF THESE THINGS
WE'VE BEEN DISCUSSING THE LAST
24 HOURS IS THAT IT TOOK
SIGNIFICANT PREMEDDATION, RIGHT?
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT YOU CAN
THROW TOGETHER ON SHORT NOTICE.
>> Shepard: NOT THIS CLEARLY.
>> YEAH.
>> Shepard: NICE TO TALK WITH
YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU BET.
>> Shepard: WE'LL BE BACK WITH A
LOOK AT TWO OF THE MOST FAMOUS
COURT VERDICTS IN AMERICAN
HISTORY AND BOTH OF THEM
HAPPENED ON THIS DAY.
(AVO)
When you have type 2 diabetes,
you manage your A1C,
but you also have a higher risk
of heart attack or stroke.
Non-insulin Victoza®
lowers A1C,
and now reduces
cardiovascular risk.
Victoza® lowers my
A1C and blood sugar
better than
the leading
branded pill.
(AVO)
And for people with
type 2 diabetes
treating cardiovascular disease,
Victoza® is NOW approved
to lower the risk of major
cardiovascular events
such as heart attack,
stroke, or death.
And while it isn't
for weight loss,
Victoza® may
help you lose some weight.
(AVO)
Victoza® is not for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not take Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza® and get
medical help right away
if you get symptoms of a serious
allergic reaction such as rash,
swelling, difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Gallbladder problems have
happened in some people.
Tell your doctor right away
if you get symptoms.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting,
decreased appetite,
indigestion, and constipation.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may cause kidney problems.
Ask your doctor
about Victoza®.
>> Shepard: ON THIS DAY IN
HISTORY, THE COURT HANDED DOWN
TWO DIFFERENT VERDICTS TO O.J.
SIMPSON.
IN 1995, HE WAS CLEARED OF
MURDERS NICOLE SIMPSON AND RON
GOLDMAN.
O.J. LED POLICE ON A LOW SPEED
CHASE ACROSS L.A.
PROSECUTORS SAID THEY HAD A
MOUNTAIN OF EVIDENCE, A TRAIL OF
BLOCK FROM ROCKINGHAM TO BUNDY.
BUT JOHNNY COCHRAN SAID IF THE
GLOVE DOESN'T FIT, YOU MUST
ACQUIT AND THE JURY DID THIS DAY
22 YEARS AGO TODAY.
AND ON THIS DATE, A.J. WAS
CONVICTED ON CHARGES RELATED TO
AN ARMED ROBBERY IN LAS VEGAS.
INVESTIGATOR SAY HE STOLE SPORTS
MEMORABILIA.
O.J. SAID HE WAS JUST TRYING TO
GET HIS STUFF BACK.
THE JUDGE SENTENCED HIM TO 33
YEARS IN PRISON.
JUST TWO DAYS AGO HE WENT FREE
O.J. SIMPSON