ake Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza® and get
medical help right away
if you get symptoms of a serious
allergic reaction such as rash,
swelling, difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Gallbladder problems have
happened in some people.
Tell your doctor right away
if you get symptoms.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting,
decreased appetite,
indigestion, and constipation.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may cause kidney problems.
Ask your doctor
about Victoza®.
>> Shepard: HEADLINES FROM THE
FOX NEWS DECK.
AN USHER SAVED COUNTLESS LIVES
WHEN A GUNMAN OPENED FIRED AT A
CHURCH.
THAT IS THE WORD FROM POLICE AND
NATURAL.
INVESTIGATORS SAY EMANUEL SAMSON
KILLED ONE WOMAN AND SHOT SIX
PEOPLE THE CHURCH, INCLUDING A
PASSER, AND ACCIDENTALLY SHOT
HIMSELF WHEN THE CHURCHES USHER,
A MAN NAMED CALEB ENGLE, IT
CONFRONTED HIM.
THERE IS THE USHER.
IN A STATEMENT, THE REAL HEROES
ARE POLICE AND OTHER
FIRST RESPONDERS SAID CALEB
ENGLE.
JOHN McCAIN, 3-14% CHANCE OF
SURVIVAL WITH HIS BATTLE AGAINST
BRAIN CANCER.
>> A VERY POOR PROGNOSIS.
I UNDERSTAND, AND WE WILL DO
WHAT WE CAN.
GET THE BEST DOCTORS WE CAN FIND
IT AT THE SAME TIME, CELEBRATE
WITH GRATITUDE OF LIFE WELL
LIVED.
>> Shepard: SENATOR MCCAIN
TOLD "60 MINUTES" COMING HE
FEELS MORE FIND AND ENGAGE
BECAUSE OF HIS CANCER DIAGNOSIS.
THERE'S BREAKING NEWS, AN
ANNOUNCEMENT ON JOBS, THE
PRESENT WILL SIGN A MEMORANDUM
DIRECTING THE DEPARTMENT OF
EDUCATION TO SPEND $200 MILLION
OF ITS $59 BILLION BUDGET IN
SUPPORT OF THE STEM FIELDS.
STEM IS SCIENCE, TECH,
ENGINEERING, AND MATH.
AND COMPUTING-CODING CLASSES.
TECH GIANTS RESIGNED THEIR POST
ON
ON TWO COUNCILS ADVISING
PRESIDENT TRUMP ON BUSINESS.
MORE RECENTLY, APPLE, FACEBOOK,
GOOGLE AND MICROSOFT CRITICIZED
HIM FOR ENDING THE DREAMER'S
IMMIGRATION PROGRAM.
THE PRESIDENT ALSO ASKED ABOUT
NORTH KOREA, THIS IS A PLAYBACK
PARALLELISM
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> DO THEY LOOK LIKE NICE
PEOPLE?
HE DOES.
THANK YOU ALL.
IT IS A GREAT PLEASURE TO BE
HERE WITH SECRETARY DeVOS AND
IVANKA.
I WANT TO GIVE MY APPRECIATION
TO REPRESENTATIVES, LAMAR SMITH,
SUSAN BROOKS, AND VIRGINIA FOXX.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
FOR BEING WITH US AND AMY
WALTERS.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
THANK USED, SUSAN.
I WANT
TO TALK ABOUT LEADERSHIP.
THAT IS A MOST OF HORTON.
WE NEED LEADERSHIP IN THIS
COUNTRY.
THE WOMEN AND GIRLS, AND EVERY
CHILD IN AMERICA.
TWO REPRESENTED BY ALL THE
INCREDIBLE STUDENTS HERE TODAY.
THESE ARE GOOD STUDENTS.
ARE YOU ALL GOOD STUDENTS?
EVERYBODY HAS TERRIFIC MARKS,
RIGHT?
YOU ARE DOING FANTASTIC.
THAT IS WHY YOU ARE HERE.
I SAID BEFORE THE PRESS CAME IN,
WHAT IS THE NAME OF THIS OFFICE?
>> GLOBAL OFFICE.
>> EVERYONE DO THAT.
THE WORKPLACE IS CHANGING, AND
WE NEED TO CREATE NEW PATHWAYS
FOR ALL OF OUR CITIZENS TO
GET THE BEST JOBS.
YOU'LL GET GREAT JOBS.
I ASKED OF
ANKE TO LEAD
UP THE WHITE HOUSE EFFORTS
DEVELOPMENT AND INITIATIVE
TODAY.
IT IS A CRITICAL PART OF THAT
ENDEAVOR.
AND YOU SAID, DO NO IVANKA?
SHE IS HERE.
WHEREAS BEFORE?
THIS BEFORE.
MY ADMINISTRATION WILL DO
EVERYTHING POSSIBLE TO PROVIDE
OUR CHILDREN, ESPECIALLY KIDS IN
UNDERSERVED AREAS WITH ACCESS TO
HIGH-QUALITY EDUCATION AND
SCIENCE, TECHNOLOGY, ENGINEERING
AND MATH.
ARE YOU GOOD MATH STUDENT?
ARE YOU?
WHAT IS YOUR STRENGTH IN SCHOOL?
SCIENCE?
WAS YOUR STRENGTH?
WHAT IS YOUR STRENGTH?
WOW, AND PARTICULARLY COMPUTER
SCIENCE K-12.
IT IS A WHOLE NEW WORLD.
LEARNING HOW TO USE THOSE
COMPUTERS.
AND THIRDLY MORE THAN HALF OF
HIGH SCHOOLS DO NOT OFFER
COMPUTER PROGRAMMING IN NEARLY
40% DO NOT OFFER PHYSICS.
DO YOU HAVE COMPUTER PROGRAMMING
IN YOUR SCHOOLS?
DO HAVE THEM IN YOUR SCHOOLS?
YOU'RE ALL GOOD WITH A COMPUTER?
>> YES.
>> IT IS IMPORTANT NOWADAYS.
GREATER ACCESS TO STEM AND
COMPUTER SCIENCE PROGRAMS WILL
ENSURE THAT OUR CHILDREN CAN
DEVELOP THE SKILLS THEY NEED TO
COMPETE AND WIN IN THE WORKFORCE
OF TOMORROW.
WHO LIKES TO WIN?
>> I DO!
>> WHO LIKES TO LOSE?
[LAUGHS]
THE WISE GUY BACK THERE.
EDUCATION MEANS BETTER WORKERS
FOR FAMILIES.
YOU GET REALLY GREAT JOBS OUT OF
SCHOOL.
WE ARE DOING VERY WELL WITH THE
EMPLOYMENT DRAWS.
REALLY GOOD JOBS.
WE WANT OUR AMAZING YOUNG
AMERICANS TO FILL THESE JOBS,
EARN A GREAT LIVING, LIFT UP
THEIR COMMUNITIES, AND ACHIEVE
THEIR AMERICAN DREAMS.
THE DIRECTIVES I AM SHARING
TODAY WITH SECRETARY DeVOS AT
THE HELM TO MAKE A STEM
EDUCATION, INCLUDING COMPUTER
SCIENCE, A PRIORITY FOR THE
DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION.
IS THAT RIGHT, BETSY?
IT WILL BE A BIG, BIG THING THAT
YOU ARE DOING.
IT IS WORKING OUT WELL?
YOU ARE MOVING INCREDIBLY.
THE DEPARTMENT WILL EXPLORE WAYS
TO ADD OR INCREASE COMPUTER
SCIENCE TO EXISTING K-12 AND
K-12 AND POSTSECONDARY EDUCATION
PROGRAMS, THERE ARE ALSO
ESTABLISHED AS A GOAL DEVOTING
AT LEAST 200 -- LISTEN TO THIS,
$200 MILLION EACH YEAR IN GRANTS
TOWARDS FUNDING THIS PRIORITY.
$200 MILLION.
DOES THAT SOUND LIKE BIG BOX?
IT'S PEANUTS, PEANUTS, RIGHT?
YOU WILL SAY, GIVE US MORE.
YOU WILL GET MORE -- BUT
$200 MILLION EACH YEAR IN
GRANTS, AND AS TOWARDS FUNDING.
VERY, VERY IMPORTANT PRIORITY.
WITH TODAY'S ACTION, WE WILL
HELP THE AMERICAN CHILDREN GIVE
THEM A PATHWAY TO SUCCESS IN THE
WORKFORCE OF TOMORROW.
THANK YOU, AND GOD BLESS YOU
ALL.
I REALLY APPRECIATE BEING AT THE
WHITE HOUSE, AND I KNOW YOU WILL
TAKE A LITTLE TOUR IN A WHILE.
WE START RIGHT HERE IN THE
OVAL OFFICE.
IT IS AN HONOR TO HAVE YOU ALL,
AND SOMEDAY, YOU WILL GREAT
STUDENTS, AND THE LEADERS OF THE
WORLD.
THE UNITED STATES AND THE WORLD,
RIGHT?
WOULD ANY OF OUR
REPRESENTATIVES, MAYBE I WILL
START WITH BETSY, WOULD YOU LIKE
TO SAY SOMETHING?
BETSY DeVOS, EVERYBODY.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, THANK YOU FOR
YOUR SUPPORT ON THE INITIATIVE,
AND ESPECIALLY TO THE STUDENTS
WHO ARE HERE TODAY.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR COMMITMENT TO
YOUR OWN FUTURE.
WITH THIS INITIATIVE, WE HOPE
AND TRUST THAT YOU WILL HAVE
MORE OPPORTUNITIES TO PURSUE THE
THINGS THAT ARE MOST IMPORTANT
TO YOU, AND AFFORD YOU A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY FOR YOUR FUTURE AND
COLLECTIVELY FOR OUR FUTURE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH,
MR. PRESIDENT, AND FOR ALL THE
STUDENTS, GOOD LUCK.
ALL THE BEST IN YOUR STUDIES.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AND THE SECRETARY HAS BEEN
WORKING REALLY HARD TO GET THIS
DONE.
THIS IS ONE OF MANY THINGS THAT
SHE HAS BEEN WORKING REALLY HARD
FOR IT ALEX, WHAT YOU A FEW
THINGS CAN MAKE ALEX ACOSTA.
>> IS THE FATHER OF TWO YOUNG
GIRLS, I KNOW FIRSTHAND HOW
IMPORTANT IT IS TO START EARLY,
AND WHAT IS SO EXCITING ABOUT
THIS INITIATIVE FROM MY
PERSPECTIVE IS THAT ALL THE
YOUNG KIDS THAT ARE GOING TO BE
EXPOSED TO COMPUTER SCIENCE AND
CODING IN STEM, BECAUSE IF YOU
START EARLY, IT IS
TRANSFORMATIVE, ESPECIALLY FOR
YOUNG GIRLS.
I SEE IT AT HOME.
IT IS SO IMPORTANT.
I'M EXCITED TO SEE ALL OF YOU
HERE.
IT IS WONDERFUL THAT YOU ARE
HERE, A MR. PRESIDENT, THANK YOU
FOR DOING THIS.
>> THANK YOU, ALEX.
GOOD JOB.
BRADLEY?
>> I'M FROM ALABAMA.
WE STARTED THE ALABAMA MATH
SCIENCE INITIATIVE ALMOST 20
YEARS AGO, AND WE THOUGHT IT WAS
A THING OF THE FUTURE.
NOW THI OF THE
PRESENT, AND YOU SIGNED THIS
TODAY MEANS A LOT FOR YOUNG
PEOPLE AND EDUCATORS ALL OVER
AMERICA.
THANK YOU FOR DOING SO.
>> ALABAMA'S GREAT STATE GREAT
STATE.
LOVE ALABAMA.
>> HELLO, KIDS.
I'M FROM INDIANA.
I WAS IN A FOURTH GRADE CLASS IN
CARMEL, INDIANA.
TODD METAL ELEMENTARY, AND AIR
USING COMPUTERS ALL DAY LONG
DOING A VIRTUAL FIELD TRIPS,
LEARNING INSTANTLY AND THE
TEACHER KNOWS WHERE THE PROBLEMS
ARE RIGHT AWAY.
AS YOU KNOW, THE JOBS OF THE
FUTURE, WE'LL EVEN KNOW WHAT
THEY ALL ARE.
BECAUSE OF TECHNOLOGY AND,
BECAUSE OF THIS FUNDING,
COMPUTER SCIENCE AND CLASS,
YOU'LL BE READY.
THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
>> President Trump: THESE ARE
ALL VERY POWERFUL PEOPLE WHO
JUST SO YOU KNOW, OKAY?
LAMAR SMITH.
>> I AM THE CHAIRMAN OF THE
SCIENCE COMMITTEE IN THE HOUSE.
I JUST WANT TO THANK THE
PRESIDENT FOR GIVING PRIORITY TO
STEM EDUCATION AND TO COMPUTER
SCIENCE IN PARTICULAR.
THE LAST CONGRESS, I INTRODUCED
A BILL THAT BECAME LAW TO EXPAND
THE DEFINITION OF STEM TO
INCLUDE COMPUTER SCIENCE.
I'M ESPECIALLY GRATEFUL TO THE
PRESIDENT FOR EMPHASIZING THAT.
MR. PRESIDENT, THANK YOU.
>> President Trump: VIRGINIA?
>> AS CHAIRWOMAN OF THE
EDUCATIONAL WORKFORCE COMMITTEE,
MR. PRESIDENT --
'S >> President Trump: I'LL
TAKE SPEAKER TOO.
>> WE ARE SO PROUD OF YOU FOR
YOU DOING THIS.
WE KNOW WE HAVE 5.6 MILLION JOBS
AVAILABLE RIGHT NOW TO OUR
WORKFORCE, AND MANY OF THEM ARE
UNFILLED, BECAUSE EMPLOYEES DO
NOT HAVE THE SKILLS THEY NEED.
IT IS WONDERFUL TO SEE US
ENCOURAGING THESE YOUNG PEOPLE
TO BEGIN EARLY, TO BE INVOLVED
IN THE SUBJECT MATTERS, AND WE
NEED TO SPREAD THIS IDEA
THROUGHOUT OUR CULTURE FOR
PEOPLE OF ALL AGES, BUT WE
PARTICULARLY AS OTHERS HAVE
SAID, WANT TO GIVE THE YOUNG
PEOPLE ENGAGED, INVOLVED, AND
EXCITED ABOUT ALL OF THESE
SUBJECTS.
>> President Trump: THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>> I AM AMY WALTERS FROM
CALIFORNIA, I WANT TO THANK YOU
VERY MUCH FOR SIGNING THIS
LEGISLATION TODAY.
I AM A MOM OF FOUR KIDS AND STEM
IS VERY EXCITING.
WHEN I WAS IN HIGH SCHOOL COMIC
COMPUTERS WERE JUST GETTING INTO
SCHOOL.
WE HAVE COME A LONG WAY, AND IT
IS VERY EXCITING TO SEE SO MANY
YOUNG KIDS HERE THAT ARE
INTERESTED IN A STEM.
YOU VERY MUCH.
>> President Trump: THANK YOU
VERY MUCH, AND YOU'VE DONE A
GREAT JOB PRETTY WELL DONE A
GREAT JOB.
SOMETHING VERY SPECIAL PRAYER
AND MY DAUGHTER, SHOULD BE HERE
FROM IVANKA?
>> FIRST OF ALL, THANK YOU ALL
FOR BEING HERE.
YOU ARE THE FUTURE OF INNOVATORS
AND ENTREPRENEURS AND ENGINEERS,
AND PROGRAMMERS, IN THIS
CENTURY.
IT IS SO EXCITING TO SEE THE
ENTHUSIASM.
TODAY, RIBS
TO REPRESENT A LEAP FORWARD WITH
THE SKILLS IN THE CLASSROOM WITH
THE SKILLS THAT ARE IN DEMAND IN
THE MODERN ECONOMY.
WE ARE VERY EXCITED ABOUT
TODAY'S ANNOUNCEMENT AND PUTTING
AMERICANS TO WORK IN MAKING SURE
THAT ALL AMERICANS GET GOOD
PAYING JOBS.
THANK YOU ALL FOR BEING HERE,
AND I LOOK FORWARD TO WATCHING
YOU ALL GO ON TO ACCOMPLISH MANY
AMAZING EXTRA ORDINARY THINGS.
>> President Trump: THANK YOU,
IVANKA.
EDUCATION IS SO IMPORTANT.
AT EVERY LEVEL, WHETHER IT IS
THIS OR YOU ARE STUDYING.
ALWAYS REMEMBER THIS -- DO WHAT
YOU LOVE, STUDY WHAT YOU LOVE.
YOUR PARENTS MAY WANT YOU TO DO
SOMETHING, YOU SHOULD ALWAYS
LISTEN TO YOUR PARENTS, BUT TRY
TO FOCUS ON THE THINGS THAT YOU
LOVE, WHETHER IT IS STUDIES OR
WHEN YOU GET OUT OF SCHOOL, DO
WHAT YOU LOVE, AND YOU WILL BE
SUCCESSFUL.
WORK HARD.
ALL OF THOSE THINGS, BUT YOU
HAVE TO FOLLOW YOUR HEART TO A
CERTAIN EXTENT, AND MAYBE EVEN
TO A LARGER EXTENT.
WHEN YOU GET OUT THERE, DESH IS
VERY INTERESTING AND I SAY THIS
A LOT, DO WHAT YOU LOVE, IF YOU
LOVE IT IT IS NOT WORK.
IT IS A PLEASURE.
YOU'LL BE TREMENDOUSLY ASK
SUCCESSFUL
DURING A SPECIAL PLACE, AND VERY
FEW GET TO COME AND SEE THIS,
BUT I WANTED YOU TO SEE IT
TODAY.
IT IS A VERY, VERY SPECIAL AREA
OF THE WORLD.
IT ALL HAPPENS HERE.
IT IS MY HONOR TO HAVE YOU.
GO OUT AND WORK REALLY HARD AND
DO REALLY WELL.
I WILL SEE YOU SOON.
WE WILL SEE YOU SOON.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> President Trump: WE WILL
SIGN.
THE QUESTION IS, WHO GETS THE
PEN?
>> ME!
>> President Trump: WE WILL
GET YOU ANOTHER ONE.
GIVE ME SOME ADDITIONAL PENS,
AND WHAT WE WILL DO IS GIVE THEM
OUT TO THE STUDENTS.
YOU WILL BE THE ONE SIGNING THIS
IN THE FUTURE.
>> WOW.
>> President Trump: IF YOU CAN
GIVE ME SOME ADDITIONAL PENS.
THANK YOU.
SEND THEM THE GOOD ONES.
NOT THE BAD ONES.
WE WILL GIVE THIS A VERY SPECIAL
WOMAN WHO HAS WORKED SO HARD,
ARE YOU READY FOR A?
[APPLAUSE]
MAYBE WE WILL PUT HER IN CHARGE
OF HEALTH CARE?
IT WILL GET DONE, RIGHT?
IF YOU DO HEALTH CARE, IT WILL
GET DONE.
OKAY, EVERYBODY.
THIS IS VERY IMPORTANT.
THANK YOU ALL VERY IMPORTANT   .
>> Shepard: THE PRESIDENT
SPEAKING AT THE WHITE HOUSE WITH
SOME MIGHTY GOOD LITTLE KIDS
ABOUT STEM PROGRAM.
THERE PLAINTIFF SPENT
$200 MILLION FOR CODE AND
COMPUTER SCIENCE.
PUERTO RICO
IS HOME TO MILLIONS OF AMERICANS
AND CAN RIGHT NOW, THEY ARE
DEVASTATED.
THEY'RE RUNNING OUT OF FOOD.
THERE'S NOT ENOUGH GAS TO GO
AROUND.
PEOPLE THERE ARE GROWING MORE
DESPERATE BY THE HOUR.
WE WILL GO LIVE AND TALK TO
GERALDO RIVERA, WHO IS THERE,
BECAUSE HE HEADED TO THE ISLAND
TO HELP HIS FAMILY.
THAT IS NEXT.
RISK
MUSICAL
WHERE YOU LIVE. IN THE PLACE YOU
CALL HOME. THERE'S ROOM TO GROW.
FRESH AIR. FREEDOM. THERE WAS
JUST ONE THING MISSING, FAST
INTERNET. REALLY FAST INTERNET.
IT'S HERE. INTRODUCING HUGHESNET
GEN5. THE NEXT GENERATION OF
SATELLITE INTERNET. WITH FASTER
SPEEDS, MORE DATA, AND BUILT IN
WIFI. NOW YOU CAN DO MORE OF
WHAT YOU LOVE ONLINE. STAY IN
TOUCH, LEARN, SHARE, WATCH
VIDEOS, CHAT WITH FRIENDS, AND
GET THINGS DONE. ENJOY HIGH
SPEED INTERNET AT HOME, WHEREVER
YOU LIVE. THERE'S NEVER BEEN A
BETTER TIME TO GET AMERICA'S
NUMBER ONE CHOICE FOR SATELLITE
INTERNET. THE NEW HUGHESNET GEN5
IS HERE, AND IT'S FASTER THAN
EVER. STANDARD INSTALLATION IS
FREE, SO DON'T WAIT. CALL NOW OR
TEXT (PROMO CODE) TO THIRTY-FIVE
THOUSAND, TODAY.
>> Shepard: OFFICIALS AND
NORTH CAROLINA ARE TELLING
PEOPLE TO LEAVE SOME AREAS OF
THE OUTER BANKS AS HURRICANE
MARIA MOVES TOWARD THE AREA.
OFFICIALS HAD MANDATORY
EVACUATION SEVERAL ISLAND
STARTING TODAY.
HERE'S THE LATEST TRACK FOR YOU,
FORECASTERS SAY THEY DO NOT
EXPECT THAT CATEGORY 1 HURRICANE
TO MAKE LANDFALL IN THE
UNITED STATES AT ALL.
IT WILL NOT MAKE LANDFALL THEY
TELL US, BUT THEY SAY IT WILL
CAUSE MAJOR PROBLEMS FOR PEOPLE
UP AND DOWN THE EAST COAST.
TELLING PEOPLE TO PREPARE FOR
STRONG WINDS, STORM SURGE, AND
SOME FLOODING.
THIS COMES DAYS AFTER THE STORM
SLAMMED PUERTO RICO, LEAVING
BEHIND DESTRUCTION AND I CANNOT
POWER IT TO EVERYBODY THERE.
OF COURSE, THERE'S SO MUCH
STRONGER.
ONE LOCAL OFFICIALS SAY,
HURRICANE MARIA SAID BACK TO
UNITED STATES TERRITORY BY
DECADES, AND IT IS A DIFFERENT
ISLAND THAT IT WAS WEEK AGO.
IMAGES TO SHOW YOU IN A
SLIDESHOW THIS AFTERNOON,
CERTAINLY DIFFERENT ISLAND AND
IT WAS A WEEK AGO.
PEOPLE STANDING OUTSIDE AND AT
SAN JUAN TO LINE UP TO BUY GAS.
REPORTS PEOPLE WAITED HOURS IN
SOME AREAS TO GET A LITTLE BIT.
HERE ARE KIDS FEELING JUGS WITH
FRESH WATER IN A DISTRIBUTION
POINT A LITTLE BIT FARTHER EAST
OF THERE.
EMERGENCY WORKERS DELIVERED MORE
THAN 1 MILLION AND A HALF
GALLONS OF WATER TO THE ISLAND.
THIS IS SAN JUAN.
A WI-FI HOT SPOT.
PEOPLE GETTING SERVICE.
CELL PHONES ARE TOUGH.
WATER FLOWS FROM THE DAM ON THE
NORTHWEST SIDE OF THE ISLAND,
WHERE OFFICIALS TOLD THOUSANDS
OF PEOPLE TO EVACUATE.
CONCERNS OF THE DAM WOULD BREAK
AND CAUSE MORE FLOODING.
MEMBERS OF THE NATIONAL GUARD
OFFERING TO HELP THIS WOMAN
EVACUATE AFTER THE GOVERNMENT
OPENED THE GATES OF A DAM NEAR
HER HOME.
GERALDO RIVERA IS IN
PUERTO RICO.
HE IS PUERTO REAGAN HIMSELF AND
HIS LIVE WITH US THIS AFTERNOON.
GERALDO, TELL US HOW IT IS FIRST
AND?
>> SHEP, LET ME WELCOME YOU TO
PUERTO RICO ISLAND OF DESPAIR.
THE ISLAND GOT RACKED BY
HURRICANE IRMA TWO WEEKS AGO.
THAT HURRICANE ACT OF 17% OF THE
POWER GRID.
THEN CAME THE MUCH MORE SAVAGE,
POWERFUL HURRICANE MARIA, AND
THAT HAS ABSOLUTELY DECIMATED
THIS ISLAND.
IT HAS SCORCHED THE AGRICULTURAL
FIELD OF PUERTO RICO.
80% OF THE CROPS HAD BEEN
DESTROYED.
THERE IS NO ELECTRIC POWER SHEP,
THE POLLS ARE DOWN EVERYWHERE.
THE LARGE CONDUCTIVE POLLS, THE
TELEPHONE POLES, THERE'S VERY
LITTLE COMMUNICATION.
SO SERVICE, EXTREMELY SPOTTY.
THERE IS NO SYMPTOM OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING ON AN ISLAND WITH NO
WATER AND NO FUEL THEN THE LINES
AT THE SERVICE STATIONS.
NOT ONLY EITHER SCORES OF
PEOPLE, YOU LOOK AT THIS LINE IT
GOES ALL THE WAY I'LL COME
AROUND THAT CORNER, AND THIS IS
THE SCENE AT EVERY SINGLE GAS
STATION IN PUERTO RICO.
WITHOUT GAS, THEY CAN'T RUN THE
GENERATORS THAT THE FEW HAVE TWO
POWER THE WATER PUMPS THAT ALLOW
THEM NOT ONLY TO GET WATER TO
BATHE AND DRINK, BUT ALSO TO RUN
THE TOILET.
THIS SITUATION IS AS DIRE AS YOU
CAN POSSIBLY IMAGINE.
3.4 MILLION AMERICAN CITIZEN IN
THE MOST DESPERATE SITUATION,
AND IT IS ONLY GOING TO GET
WORSE.
THE MILLION AND A HALF GALLON
ALREADY DELIVERED, A DROP IN THE
BUCKET, IT IS NEEDED.
>> Shepard: IN YOUR OPINION,
GERALDO, WITH INTEREST AND A LOT
OF LOVE THERE, ARE THEY GOING TO
NEED AN AIRLIFT OR BOLT LEFT
OUT OF THERE AND TO, OR CAN THEY
GET THIS BACK UP AND RUNNING TO
GET THIS FROM BEING A NECESSITY?
>> SHEP, THERE HAS BEEN AN
EXODUS FROM PUERTO RICO SINCE
THE FINANCIAL CRISIS.
THIS U.S. COMMONWEALTH IS
BANKRUPT.
MORE THAN A MILLION HAVE LEFT
THE ISLAND.
I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT THE PEOPLE
FORCED TO LIVE UNDER THE
PRIMITIVE CONDITIONS, THE YOUNG
ONES WILL LEAVE.
WHAT HAPPENS, THE OLD AND FEEBLE
THEY STAY BEHIND, THEN YOU
CANNOT LEAVE.
SCHOOLS ARE CLOSER, BY THE WAY.
BUSINESSES INCREDIBLY DISRUPTED.
OF THE 3.4 MILLION, YOU'LL SEE A
TREMENDOUS EXODUS TO FLORIDA,
NEW YORK STATE, AND LESS THIS
POWER GRID IS RESTORED.
IT WAS IN TERRIBLE SHAPE BEFORE.
IT WAS PLAGUED BY CORRUPTION, BY
INCOMPETENCE, BY SCANDALOUS
DEALINGS WITH PEOPLE PURCHASING
FUEL OIL, PURCHASED THE LOW
WAS GREAT, IT SOLD FOR THE
HIGHEST.
NOW THE GRID IS DESTROYED.
TO BRING AN AIRCRAFT CARRIER IN
AND THEY ARE NOBLE PEOPLE, AND
ARE HELPING, BUT WITH THIS
ISLAND NEEDS IS AN ENTIRE NEW
POWER GRID.
3.4 MILLION PEOPLE, MORE THAN A
MANY STATES IN THE UNION.
I THINK WHAT YOU WILL SEE HERE
IS A.
OF SEVERE DISRUPTION.
THEY ARE SAYING THAT 4-6 MONTHS
BEFORE THEY GET THE POWER GRID
UP AND RUNNING SO PEOPLE WOULD
GENERATORS, THIS WILL BECOME A
SYMBOL OF WHAT THEY BECOME
TODAY.
WIND POWER, THE TURBINES HAVE
BEEN SHREDDED BY THE SUCCESS OF
THE HURRICANES.
THE TOURISM HERE ALSO SHREDDED.
THIS IS AN ISLAND IN CRISIS.
IT IS BECAUSE -- EIGHT HUGE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS.
IT IS NOT LIKE THEY ARE ALL
JOINING OR BILLIONS OR COLLAPSE,
BUT IT IS NEVERTHELESS A
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS.
PEOPLE ARE IN DIRE STRAITS.
THIS WILL BE A MARSHALL PLAN
SCALE REBUILDING OF THE
ELECTRICAL GRID BEFORE YOU CAN
HAVE THE END OF CIVILIZATION AS
WE KNOW IT IN PUERTO RICO.
ARMED GUARDS ON THE GASOLINE.
ONLY LESS THAN A WEEK INTO THIS
CRISIS.
IMAGINE A MONTH FROM NOW OR TWO
MONTHS FROM NOW.
KNOWING NO ONE HAD A HOT SHOWER,
NO ONE CAN FLUSH THE TOILET BUT
FOR THE COSTLY INCLUSION OF A
GALLON OF GAS IN THE COMMODE.
IMAGINE WHAT IS GOING TO BE
LIKE, SHEP.
THERE IS NO OVERSTATING THE
CRISIS HERE, THE PRESIDENT
SHOULD COME.
THE PRESIDENT SHOULD SEE FOR
HIMSELF.
SEND MARCO RUBIO AND HEAD OF
FEMA, THEY ARE HERE TODAY.
THE GOVERNOR OF NEW YORK STATE
CAME IN WITH THE PLANE.
ALL THOSE GESTURES ARE VERY
IMPORTANT, BUT YOU NEED IT
SYSTEMIC REFORM, WAY TO BAIL
THESE PEOPLE OUT.
IT IS NOT JUST MY FAMILY.
MY FAMILY, GOD KNOWS I LOVE
THEM.
I LIVED IN THE VERY HOUSE WHEN I
WAS A TEENAGER.
THEY ARE HIGH-FUNCTIONING, THEIR
CHILDREN HAVE BECOME DOCTORS.
I HAVE NO DOUBT THAT THEY WILL
HAVE TO GIVE UP EVERYTHING THE
WATER AND POWER IS NOT RESTORED.
MAYBE THE BRONX IN NEW YORK OR
SOMEWHERE ELSE WHERE THEY CAN
LIVE WITH A DECENT LIFE WITHOUT
WHAT IS DEFINITELY, DEFINITELY,
A HUMANITARIAN CRISIS OF MONTA
MONUMENTAL PROPORTIONS.
SPILLED BEST OF LUCK TO YOUR
FAMILY AND THE PEOPLE OF
PUERTO RICO
THANK YOU, MY FRIEND.
>> Shepard: WALL STREET WILL
BE SHUTTING DOWN FOR THE DAY AND
JUST ABOUT 3 MINUTES AND 15
SECONDS.
IT HAS BEEN A DOWN DAY.
THE TACK
GOT WALLOPED TODAY, BUT THERE IS
SOME BRIGHT SPOT.
NO CAVUTO CAN ALWAYS FIND HIM.
YOU'LL START LOOKING FOR THEM
WHEN "YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL
CAVUTO BEGINS RIGHT AFTER THIS