THEORY.
ONE OF THE EFFECTIVE TOOLS A
PRESIDENT CAN USE AS THE MOST
POWERFULMAN ON EARTH IS TO LAY
DO ANYTHING.
YOU BETTER BE CONCERNED.
THERE'S AN INTERESTING STORY
THAT CAME OUT LASTEEK TH HIS
TRADE REPRESENTATIVE WAS GOING
TO SOUTH KOREA TO NEGOTIATE A
NEW SOUTH KOREAN TRADE DEAL.
THE PRESIDENT SAID TO HIM, WE'RE
GOING TO ONLY GIVE THIS 30 DAYS.
WHEN THE TRADE REPRESENTATIVE
SAID, ALL RIGHT, I'LL TELL THEM
30 DAYS.
HE SAID NO, NO.
I MIGHT DROP OUT AT ANY POINT
AND PULL THE PLUG ON THIS AT ANY
MOMENT.
THE POINT BEING THAT SOUTH KOREA
SHOULD NOT BE AT ALL CONFIDENT
IN THAT THEY HAVE AN IDEA WHAT
THIS PRESIDENT WILL DO.
MY GUESS IS THAT IS BASICALLY
WHAT THE PRESIDENT WAS SAYING
HERE.
>> Shepard: IF YOU'RE IN
NEW ORLEANS OR IN GULFPORT AND
YOU SAY THIS IS THE CALM BEFORE
THE STORM THAT MEANS THERE'S A
TROPICAL STORM OR HURRICANE
HEADED AND HELL COMING.
WHEN YOU SAY IT WITH YOUR
MILITARY LEADERS BEHIND YOU,
THIS MEETING OF THE LEADERS IS
THE CALM BEFORE THE STORM,
YOU'RE SUGGESTING THAT SOME SORT
OF CONFLICT IS BREWING.
ARE YOU NOT?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT ELSE IT COULD
MEAN.
HERE'S THE MILITARY LEADERS,
CALM BEFORE THE STORM IS COMING.
IT'S NOT EXACTLY A CALMING,
COMFORTING THING.
>> IT ISN'T.
BUT I DON'T THINK HE WANTS IRAN
OR NORTH KOREA OR THE LEADERS OF
THOSE REGIMES TO BE CALM AND
COMFORTABLE.
IT'S LIKE WHEN HE SAID TO NORTH
KOREA, YOU KNOW, IF THEY PUSH US
TOO FAR, WE'LL RAIN DOWN FIRE
AND FURY ON THEM.
HE'S NOT SAYING I'M ABOUT TO DO
IT.
HE'S NOT SAYING NEXT TUESDAY AT
3:00 P.M., WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
THIS PARTICULAR TACTIC.
HE'S SAYING I HAVE THAT
CAPABILITY AND PREPARED TO USE
IT IF NECESSARY.
>> Shepard: THERE'S A NEW POLL
OUT FROM ASSOCIATED PRESS.
24% OF AMERICANS SAY THE UNITED
STATES IS HEADING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
67% DISAPPROVE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S PERFORMANCE.
NORMALLY WHEN THINGS LIKE THIS
HAPPEN, HE WILL TRY TO TAKE SOME
ACTION TO CHANGE THE POLLS.
I WONDER HOW CONCERNED THEY ARE
IF AT ALL?
>> LOOK, HE'S BEEN LOW IN THE
POLLS FOR QUITE A PERIOD OF TIME
NOW.
HE BASICALLY HAS SUPPORT OF 34
TO 40, OCCASIONALLY PICKS UP
INTO THE 40%.
HE'S UNDER WATER IN ALMOST ALL
OF THE POLLS.
HE'S NOT RUNNING FOR RE-ELECTION
FOR MORE THAN THREE YEARS.
I THINK HE FEELS IN REASONABLY
STRONG SHAPE.
HE DOESN'T ACT LIKE A FELLOW
THAT KNOW WHAT'S HE WANTS TO DO
HE'S GOTTEN HIGH MARKS ON SOME
THINGS.
VERY HIGH MARKS ON THE REACTION
TO IRMA AND HARVEY AND TEXAS AND
FLORIDA.
NOT NEARLY AS HIGH MARKS ON HIS
REACTION TO MARIA IN PUERTO
RICO.
THIS IS A PRESIDENT WHO WILL
BUMP ALONG.
NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
THERE'S TIMES WHEN PEOPLE ARE
VERY SUPPORTIVE AND THINK HE
DOES THE RIGHT THINGS AND TIMES
WHEN HE UPSETS PEOPLE.
>> Shepard: AND ALSO IN THE
NEWS, THIS CONTRACEPTION CHANGE.
HOW IS THAT FLYING THERE
POLITICALLY AND OTHERWISE?
>> LOOK, IT'S THE USUAL
SUSPECTS.
IF YOU'RE A STRONG SUPPORTER OF
BIRTH CONTROL, YOU'RE OUTRAGED
BY THIS.
THE PRESIDENT IS DRAMATICALLY
INCREASING THE EXCEPTIONS.
LET'S GO BACK.
OBAMACARE AS PART OF OFFERING
EMPLOYERS, OFFERING HEALTHCARE
SERVICES TO THEIR EMPLOYEES,
THEY HAVE TO OFFER AS A FREE
BENEFIT BIRTH CONTROL.
NOW WE HAVE THE FIGHT IN THE
SUPREME COURT WHEN OBAMA WAS
PRESIDENT.
THE HOBBY LOBBY, GROUPS THAT
WERE EXEMPTED.
NOW THE PRESIDENT WITH HIS HHS
REGULATION IS DRAMATICALLY
INCREASING THE EXCEPTIONS AND IS
GOING TO MAKE IT EASIER FOR
GROUPS, NONPROFITS, TO PROPER IF
ITS, RELIGIOUS ORGANIZATIONS,
NONRELIGIOUS ORGANIZATIONS IF
THEY HAVE A RELIGIOUS OR A MORAL
OBJECTION, THEY CAN SAY THAT
THEY ARE NOT OBLIGATED TO
PROVIDE BIRTH CONTROL TO THEIR
EMPLOYEES.
THE ACLU IS ALREADY FILING A
SUIT ON THIS.
THIS WILL UNDOUBTEDLY END UP IN
THE COURTS.
>> Shepard: IT IS A BIT
CONFUSING AS BIRTH CONTROL
PREVENTS ABORTIONS FROM EVER
HAPPENING.
IF YOU ALLOW THEM TO HAVE BIRTH
CONTROL, FAMILY PLANNING COMES
ALONG MORE EASILY AND WITHOUT
THE CONTROVERSY THAT COMES ALONG
WITH ABORTIONS.
IT JUST SEEMS TO BE WORKING
AGAINST ITSELF IN A WAY.
>> WELL, YES, BUT THAT'S THE
TENANT OF THE CATHOLIC CHURCH.
THEY DON'T WANT TO DO ANYTHING
TO INTERFERE WITH LIFE.
ABORTION INTERFERES WITH LIFE.
THEY THINK THAT BIRTH CONTROL,
ARTIFICIAL BIRTH CONTROL
INTERFERES WITH LIFE.
THERE ARE PLENTY OF RELIGIONS
THAT HOLD TO THOSE TENANTS EVEN
THOUGH YOUR POINT ABOUT THE LACK
OF BIRTH CONTROL POSSIBLY
LEADING TO UNWANTED PREGNANCIES
IS ALSO TRUE.
>> Shepard: ALL RIGHT, CHRIS.
WHAT'S HAPPENING THIS WEEKEND?
>> I FEEL LIKE YOU PUT ME
THROUGH MY PACES TODAY.
LAS VEGAS IS A BIG STORY STILL.
A TERRIBLE STORY.
WE'RE STILL LEFT A WEEK LATER
WITH THE QUESTION WHY AND WHEN
WILL PEOPLE BE TALKING TO YOU?
STEVE WYNN, ONE OF THE KINGS OF
LAS VEGAS.
THE HEAD OF TWO OF THE BIGGEST
HOTELS AND CASINOS IN THAT TOWN.
INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH, WYNN
DECIDE ADD YEAR AGO THAT
LAS VEGAS WAS A SOFT TARGET.
WHEN YOU HEAR THE KINDS OF
THINGS -- WE'LL HAVE AN
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW SUNDAY --
THAT HE DID TO TRY TO HARDEN THE
WYNN HOTEL AND TO HARDEN THE
ENCORE HOTEL IN TERMS OF
BRINGING IN FORMER SEAL TEAMS
SIX MEMBERS, FORMER CIA
OFFICERS, HIDDEN DETECTORS,
HIDDEN PROFILERS IN THE CASINOS.
JUST TRYING TO PROTECT HIS
PROPERTIES.
BUT NOW THERE'S A NEW THREAT,
WHICH WE SAW FROM STEPHEN
PADDOCK, WHICH IS KNOCKING OUT
THE WINDOWS AND FIRING DOWN FROM
THE 32nd FLOOR.
ONE OF THE THINGS WE'LL TALK TO
STEVE WYNN ABOUT, HOW DO YOU
HANDLE AND PREVENT THAT WE'LL BE
TALKING TO ERIC PRATT, THE
EXECUTIVE DIRECTOR OF GUN OWNERS
OF AMERICA.
INTERESTINGLY ENOUGH WHILE THE
NRA IS SAYING MAYBE WE SHOULD
REGULATE AND RESTRICT THE BUMP
STOCKS, ERIC PRATT SAYS NO.
WE'LL TALK TO HIM.
>> Shepard: WE'LL WATCH THIS
SUNDAY, CHRIS, ON "FOX NEWS
SUNDAY."
LET'S GO TO MICHAEL CROWLEY FROM
POLITCO.
I'M HAVING A HARD TIME GETTING
AWAY FROM THE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM THING, MICHAEL.
HE SAID IT.
NOBODY ASKED HIM ANYTHING ABOUT
IT.
IT JUST CAME OUT OF HIS MOUTH.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE VIDEO, HE HAS
A BIG SMILE ON HIS FACE WHEN
HE'S TALKING ABOUT THIS.
ALMOST FEELS LIKE A TEASE DURING
A REALITY SHOW.
SERIOUSLY.
WELL, YOU'LL SEE.
CALM BEFORE THE STORM!
>> HE'S A REALITY SHOW STAR,
SHEP.
HE BRINGS SOME OF THAT TO THE
PRESIDENCY.
I DON'T SAY THAT LIGHTLY.
I THINK THE GUY REALLY DOES HAVE
A SENSE OF DRAMA LIKE, THIS IT'S
ENTIRELY POSSIBLE THAT HE'S SORT
OF WORKING THE AUDIENCE.
IT'S POSSIBLE THIS.
A THROW-AWAY COMMENT THAT TOOK
ON A LIFE OF ITS OWN.
INITIALLY.
NOW HE'S RUNNING WITH IT.
HE'S ENJOYING IT.
NOBODY KNOWS WHAT HE'S TALKING
ABOUT.
THERE AREN'T OFFICIALS AROUND
HIM LEAKING THERE'S SOME SECRET
MEETING.
I WOULD SAY MY MAIN GUESS IS
THIS IS A CONTINUATION OF A MIND
GAME HE'S PLAYING WITH NORTH
KOREA.
HE'S TRYING TO GET INSIDE THE
HEAD OF KIM JONG-UN.
I DON'T KNOW FOR SURE THAT THIS
IS PART OF IT, BUT IT WOULD BE
CONSISTENT WITH THINGS LIKE
TRUMP CALLING HIM NICKNAMES LIKE
ROCKET MAN AND LITTLE ROCKET
MAN.
MAKING THE NORTH KOREANS THINK
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT TRUMP'S
NEXT MOVE IS.
HE COULD BE A LITTLE CRAZY.
THE GUY WAVING THE GUN AROUND.
YOU THINK I'M CRAZY?
THINK I'M GOING TO TAKE THE
CHANCE?
IT WOULD BE CONSISTENT WITH
THAT.
>> Shepard: YOU SAID I HOPE THE
CIA IS RIGHT IN HIS ASSESSMENT
OF KIM JONG-UN.
>> RIGHT.
THE CIA BELIEVES THAT KIM
JONG-UN IS FUNDAMENTALLY
RATIONALE.
THE KEY WAY TO TRANSLATE THAT
IS, HE'S NOT SUICIDAL.
HE'S NOT GOING TO GO DOWN -- HE
DOESN'T WANT TO GO DOWN IN
FLAMES.
HE LIKES HIS LIFE.
NORTH KOREA IS A MISERABLE PLAY
OVERALL.
HE LIVES COMFORTABLY.
THERE'S LIQUOR AND WOMEN AND
NICE TECHNOLOGY IF HE WANTS IT.
SO THAT'S GOOD NEWS IF WE'RE
WORRIED THAT HE MIGHT DO
SOMETHING TOTALLY IRRATIONAL AND
UNEXPECTED.
WHAT IS AMAZING AT THIS POINT,
IT'S THE AMERICAN PRESIDENT
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO DECIDE, IS
HE ACTING TOTALLY RATIONALLY.
MAYBE THAT TRUMP IS TRYING TO
PRESENT HIMSELF -- THERE'S A
THEORY, THE MAD MAN THEORY.
>> Shepard: EVERYBODY IS TALKING
ABOUT THAT TODAY.
CHRIS WALLACE MENTIONED IT.
I READ IT ON MY FEED.
WHAT PROMPTED THIS?
WHERE DID THIS COME FROM?
>> I THINK IT'S THE WAY TRUMP
APPROACHES THESE ISSUES, THIS
GOES BACK TO THE NIXON
ADMINISTRATION WHERE HE TRIED TO
CULTIVATE AN IMAGE THAT HE WAS
CAPABLE OF DOING ANYTHING, GOING
NUCLEAR, FOR INSTANCE AGAINST
THE CHINESE AND TRYING TO SCARE
YOUR OPPONENT BY MAKING THEM
THINK YOU'RE NOT A RATIONALE
ACTOR.
WHAT IS AMAZING, WE SPENT THIS
TIME TRYING TO DECIDE IF THE
NORTH KOREANS ARE NATIONAL.
NOW THEY'RE TRYING TO SEE IF
DONALD TRUMP IS RATIONALE.
DOES HE PLAY BY THE OTHER RULES
THAT AMERICAN PRESIDENTS HAVE?
THEY FELT LIKE AMERICAN
PRESIDENTS WOULD STAY WITHIN
CERTAIN BOUNDARIES AND NOT
INITIATE MILITARY ACTION.
OR IS HE REALLY GOING TO GO FOR
IT IN A WAY WE'VE NEVER SEN
BEFORE?
THEY DON'T KNOW RIGHT NOW.
TRUMP LIKES THAT.
>> Shepard: MICHAEL CROWLEY,
FOREIGN -- SENIOR FOREIGN
AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT FOR
POLITCO.
THANKS AS ALWAYS.
>> THANKS.
>> Shepard: AHEAD, THE
INVESTIGATION INTO THE LAS VEGAS
CONCERT KILLER.
NEW REPORTS ON WHAT THE GUNMAN
HAD IN HIS ROOM AND QUESTIONS
NOW.
LISTEN TO THE QUESTION THEY'RE
TRYING TO ANSWER NOW.
WAS SOMEONE ELSE IN HIS ROOM?
AS THE AGENT CHASE DOWN CLUES
AND SURVIVORS FACE CHANGED
LIVES, THIS WEEK A RETIRED
CARPENTER DRIVE TO CHICAGO TO
PLACE 58 WHITE CROSSES ON THE
STRIP.
ONE FOR EACH PERSON KILLED.
HERE ONE WOMAN SITS NEAR THE
CROSS FOR HER COUSIN,
20-YEAR-OLD BAILEY SCHWIETZER.
THE NEWS OF LAS VEGAS IS NEXT.
Prudential asked these couples:
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
(AVO)
When you have type 2 diabetes,
you manage your A1C,
but you also have a higher risk
of heart attack or stroke.
Non-insulin Victoza®
lowers A1C,
and now reduces
cardiovascular risk.
Victoza® lowers my
A1C and blood sugar
better than
the leading
branded pill.
(AVO)
And for people with
type 2 diabetes
treating cardiovascular disease,
Victoza® is NOW approved
to lower the risk of major
cardiovascular events
such as heart attack,
stroke, or death.
And while it isn't
for weight loss,
Victoza® may
help you lose some weight.
(AVO)
Victoza® is not for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not take Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza® and get
medical help right away
if you get symptoms of a serious
allergic reaction such as rash,
swelling, difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Gallbladder problems have
happened in some people.
Tell your doctor right away
if you get symptoms.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting,
decreased appetite,
indigestion, and constipation.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may cause kidney problems.
Ask your doctor
about Victoza®.
>> Shepard: BREAKING THIS HOUR.
INVESTIGATORS IN LAS VEGAS ARE
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHETHER
ANYBODY ELSE WAS IN THE
LAS VEGASLL ERKI'S HOTEL SWEET.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO NBC NEWS.
OFFICIALS TELL NBC THAT THEY
FOUND A PHONE CHARGER IN THE
ROOM THAT DOES NOT MATCH THE
GUNMAN'S CELL PHONE.
IN ADDITION, RECORDS SHOW
SOMEBODY ELSE DID ACCESS THAT
ROOM WHILE HIS CAR WAS GONE.
THERE COULD BE A FEW
EXPLANATIONS FOR THIS.
BUT THEY REALLY DON'T KNOW THE
CORRECT ONE YET.
THIS DEVELOPMENT AS
INVESTIGATORS ARE TRYING TO
DETERMINE WHY THE GUNMAN FIRED
ON A COUNTRY MUSIC FESTIVAL
KILLING 58 AND INJURING MORE
THAN 400.
DAN SPRINGER LIVE IN VEGAS THIS
AFTERNOON.
DAN?
>> SHEP, STILL NO CLEAR MOTIVE.
THERE'S A NEWS CONFERENCE IN
ABOUT 30 MINUTES.
THEY DIDN'T HAVE ONE YESTERDAY.
SO WE HOPE TO GET MORE DETAILS,
A PICTURE IS EMERGING OF STEPHEN
PADDOCK THAT PAYMENTS HIM AS A
LOSER, ALONER THAT WOULD GO TO
PROSTITUTES.
PROSTITUTES HAVE BEEN TALKING TO
HIM AND HE WAS CHEAP AND NEVER
SHOWED EMOTION WHILE HE WAS WITH
THEM.
IT APPEARS THE MYSTERY WOMAN
THAT HE WAS SEEN WITH GAMBLING
HOURS BEFORE THE SHOOTING WAS A
HOOKER.
HIS GIRLFRIEND SAID THAT HE
GAINED A LOT OF WEIGHT IN RECENT
WEEKS AND BECAME OBSESSED WITH
MARILOU DANLEY'S EX-HUSBAND.
BUT SHE TOLD POLICE SHE HAD NO
IDEA THAT HE WAS PLANNING MASS
MURDER.
THE CAR AT MANDALAY BAY HAD 50
POUNDS OF TANNERITE AND
AMMUNITION AND FERTILIZER.
AND THERE'S NOW REPORTS THAT
PADDOCK TRIED TO BUY TRACER
AMMUNITION AT A PHOENIX GUN
SHOW.
HE WAS UNABLE TO DO SO BECAUSE
THE GUN DEALER WAS SOLD OUT BUT
THE ASSOCIATED PRESS IS
RECORDING THAT HE HAD 1,000
TRACER ROUNDS BUT DIDN'T USE
THEM.
TRACERS COULD HAVE MADE THIS
SHOOTING MORE DEADLY, MORE
ACCURATE BECAUSE HE WOULD HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO SEE WHERE THE
ROUNDS WERE GOING.
THAT RAPID FIRE HAIL OF BULLETS
LASTED TEN MINUTES.
WE JUST INTERVIEWED AN OFF DUTY
EMT THAT WAS AT THE CONCERT WITH
HIS WIFE.
HE USED HIS BELT AS A TOURNIQUET
ON A MAN'S LEG AND CARRIED
SEVERAL TO A TENT INCLUDING A
WOMAN SHOT IN THE BACK.
THE EMT HAS BEEN ABLE TO SIDE
THE WOMAN WHO HE'S RESCUED AND
SAVED AT THE HOSPITAL.
HE FEELS LIKE HE'S FAMILY WITH
THEM JUST EMOTIONAL STORIES, ONE
AFTER THE OTHER.
>> Shepard: THANKS, DAN.
LIVE IN VEGAS.
THOUSANDS GATHERING TO HONOR A
FORMAL NATIONAL GUARD SERGEANT
AND LAS VEGAS POLICE OFFICER
KILLED IN SUNDAY NIGHT'S
MASSACRE.
FRIENDS AND FAMILY SAY
CHARLESTON HARTFIELD WAS ONE OF
THE GREATEST AMERICANS THEY EVER
KNEW WITH A HEART OF GOLD AND
THAT HE DIED TRYING TO SAVE
OTHERS.
IMAGES IN OUR SLIDE SHOW FOR YOU
THIS AFTERNOON.
HERE YOU CAN SEE THE FORMER
SERGEANT'S WIDOW AND THEIR TWO
CHILDREN AT THE FRONT OF THE
PROCESSION LAST NIGHT.
THE COUPLE APPARENTLY HIGH
SCHOOL SWEETHEARTS BACK IN THE
DAY.
ON THE NIGHT OF THE MASSACRE,
HARTFIELD WAS AT THE COUNTRY
MUSIC FESTIVAL WHEN THE BULLETS
HIT THE CROWD.
HARTFIELD IMMEDIATELY TOOK
ACTION TO SAVE LIVES BEFORE A
BULLET STRUCK AND KILLED HIM.
HERE YOU CAN SEE HIS FELLOW
OFFICERS HOLDING CANDLES.
HE ALSO COACHED HIS SON'S
FOOTBALL TEAM AND RECENTLY WROTE
A MEMOIR ABOUT SERVING ON THE
LAS VEGAS POLICE FORCE.
HIS FRIENDS SAID THE DECORATED
IRAQ WAR VETERAN WAS MOST PROUD
OF BEING A FATHER.
SERGEANT HARTFIELD, FATHER OF
TWO, SOLDIER, DEAD AT 34.
THE GULF COAST IS PREPARING FOR
ANOTHER HURRICANE.
RIGHT NOW IT'S A TROPICAL STORM.
TROPICAL STORM NATE HAS KILLED
21 PEOPLE IN CENTRAL AMERICA AND
HEADED OUR WAY.
FORECASTERS PREDICT IT WILL MAKE
LANDFALL.
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE THEY'RE SAYING
IT'S GOING TO BE A CAT 1
HURRICANE THIS WEEKEND SOMEWHERE
ALONG LOUISIANA, THE PANHANDLE,
IN THAT AREA.
WHILE IT'S NOT AS POWERFUL AS
STORMS THAT SLAMMED TEXAS AND
PUERTO RICO, NATE COULD BRING
DANGEROUS FLOODING, WINDS AND
STORM SURGE.
RICK REICHMUTH IS TRACKING THE
STORM.
HI, RICK.
>> RIGHT NOW THE STORM IS JUST
OFF THE COAST OF THE YUCATAN
PENINSULA.
LAST COUPLE IMAGES HERE FROM THE
SATELLITE LOOKING MORE
ORGANIZED.
THAT'S NOT A GOOD THING.
IT'S TRACKED FURTHER TO THE EAST
AND MAYBE MORE TIME OVER WATER.
WATER IS PLENTY WARM.
THE WORST THING GOING FOR THE
STORM AND THE BEST THING FOR US,
IT DOESN'T HAVE A LOT OF TIME
TILL IT MOVES TO THE COASTLINE.
MORE RAIN ACROSS CENTRAL AMERICA
ASSOCIATED WITH THIS.
THE RAINFALL TOTALS ARE GOING TO
BE IN THE GENERAL 2 TO 4 INCHES
RANGE JUST BECAUSE IT'S MOVING
SO FAST.
GET UP HERE IN THE SOUTHERN
APPALACHIANS, THAT'S WHERE WE'LL
EEK OUT FIVE TO SEVEN INCHES OF
RAIN AND CAUSE LOCALIZED
FLOODING.
IT'S MOVING QUICKLY RIGHT NOW.
21 MILES AN HOUR.
RIGHT NOW IT'S IN THE CARIBBEAN
BY ABOUT 36 HOURS FROM NOW.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A LANDFALL
SOMEWHERE IN THE CENTRAL GULF
COAST AREA AND MOVING ON VERY
QUICKLY.
MAYBE UP TO CATEGORY ONE
HURRICANE, A STORM TROPICAL
STORM.
EITHER WAY, THE IMPACTS WILL BE
THE SAME.
STORM SURGE AND HEAVY WIND.
>> RICK, THANKS.
>> YOU BET.
>> WE HEARD A LOT OF ABSOLUTELY
HEART WRENCHING NEWS THIS WEEK.
SO AHEAD, A STORY THAT SHOWS
HOPE AND LOVE ARE VERY MUCH
ALIVE AND WELL.
IT STARTS WITH A LITTLE GIRL
THAT SPENT YEARS WAITING TO BE
ADOPTED AND THE MOMENT SHE
FINALLY LEARNS IT'S HAPPENING.
YOU CAN SEE HER REACTION.
WE CAUGHT UP WITH HER FOR THIS
WEEK.
>> IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT FOR ME
TO HAVE A MOM AND A DAD.
BECAUSE NOW I HAVE SOMEONE THAT
ACTUALLY CARES ABOUT ME AND I
KNOW THEY WOULDN'T LEAVE ME.
>> Shepard: SHE HAS A MESSAGE
FOR ALL THE OTHER LITTLE
CHILDREN WAITING FOR ADOPTION.
THAT IS NEXT.
♪
If you could book a flight,
then add a hotel,
or car, or activity
in one place and save,
where would you go?
Expedia
Remember that accident I got in
with the pole, and I
had to make a claim
and all that?
Is that whole thing
still dragging on?
No, I took some pics
with the app and...
filed a claim, but...
You know how they send you
money to cover repairs and...
They took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid
right away, but...
at the very end of
it all, my agent...
Wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy.
But if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience
for any reason,
they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim Satisfaction
Guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> Shepard: AFTER WAITING MORE
THAN TWO YEARS A 11-YEAR-OLD
GIRL GOT THE BEST NEWS OF HER
LIFE.
SHE WAS FINALLY GETTING A FAMILY
OF HER OWN.
IT HAPPENED AT A SCHOOL OUTSIDE
SALT LAKE CITY.
SHE AND HER PARENTS SPOKE TO FOX
NEWS.
>> MY HEARTFELT LIKE IT WAS JUST
LIKE GOING TO EXPLODE LITERALLY
GOING TO EXPLODE.
>> A SCHOOL SECURITY CAMERA
CAUGHT THIS LIFE-CHANGING
MOMENT.
AN CSTATIC 11-YEAR-OLD.
TANNAH BUTTERFIELD LEARNING SHE
WAS GOING TO BE ADOPTED WITH HER
BROTHER AND SISTER.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS GOING
ON.
I SAID WHAT?
SHE'S LIKE SQUEEZING ANY CHEEKS
SAYING EVERYTHING WENT OKAY AT
COURT.
YOU'RE GETTING ADOPTED.
SHE WAS LIKE SUPER HAPPY.
SHE STARTED DRAGGING ME AROUND
THE ROOM KISSING MY FACE.
IT WAS AWESOME.
>> HER SCHOOL'S OFFICE MANAGER
IS A FRIEND OF THE FAMILY AND
SHE WAS THE BARER OF GOOD NEWS.
SHE POSTED THE VIDEO TO
INSTAGRAM WRITING THIS IS PURE
TESTAMENT.
IN A WORLD FULL OF STRIFE,
THERE'S STILL JOY IN EVERY DAY
MOMENTS.
>> TO TELL EVERYBODY THAT THEY
GET TO BE PART OF A FOREVER
FAMILY IS SOMETHING I HAVE NEVER
DONE BEFORE.
IT WAS A FEELING I NEVER HAD
BEFORE.
>> I WATCH IT OVER AND OVER AND
OVER.
IT WAS SO HAPPY.
THE BEST FEELING.
>> JEN AND JEFF FISHER HAVE TWO
BIOLOGICAL CONDITION.
NOW THEY ARE COUNTING THE DAYS
UNTIL THE THREE CHILDREN BECOME
PART OF THE FAMILY.
>> IT'S BEEN A LONG, LONG
JOURNEY.
IT TOOK A LONG TIME.
BUT IT WAS WORTH IT.
>> THEY'LL BE MINE INSTEAD OF
JUST PLANE SOMEBODY ELSE'S
FATHER.
NOW I GET TO PLAY THE ACTUAL
ROLE.
>> I WOULD TELL OTHER CHILDREN
WAITING TO GET ADOPTED THAT YOU
WILL GET ADOPTED AND YOU WILL
FIND GOOD PEOPLE AND YOU WILL
ALWAYS HAVE SOMEONE TO LOVE YOU.
>> Shepard: TANNAH'S ADOPTION IS
SET THE 15th.
THEY HOPE TO HAVE IT DONE
SOONER.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
4 hours.
My insurance company
definitely doesn't have that...
You can leave worry behind when
Liberty Stands With You™
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
But he has
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
Whatever you're doing
to stay healthy...
...there's something you
may be missing.
A key part of your wellness
that you may be...
...overlooking.
♪♪
It's your eyes.
That's why there's Ocuvite,
from Bausch + Lomb.
As you age your eyes can lose
vital nutrients.
Ocuvite helps replenish those
nutrients.
Ocuvite has Lutein, Zeaxanthin,
and Omega-3.
Nourish your eyes to help them
be their healthy best.
Ocuvite eye vitamins.
Be good to your eyes.
There's only one egg
that just tastes better.
Fresher.
More flavorful.
Delicious.
Only one egg
with better nutrition-
like more vitamins
D, E, and Omega 3s.
And 25% less saturated fat.
Only one egg good enough
for my family.
Because why have ordinary
when you can have the best.
Eggland's Best.
The only egg that
gives you so much more:
Better taste.
Better nutrition.
Better eggs.
I count on my Dell Small
Business Advisor,
for tech advice.
With one phone call,
I get products that suit my
needs,
and I get back to business.
Woman: For the holidays,
we get a gift for mom and dad.
And every year,
we split it equally.
Except for one of us.
I write them a poem instead.
And one for each of you too.
Woman:
Cool.
That actually yours...
That one. Yeah.
Regardless, we're
stuck with the bill.
To many, words are the
most valuable currency.
Last I checked,
stores don't take words.
Man:
Some do. Oh.
(Alert beeps)
Not everyone can
be the poetic voice
of a generation.
I know, right?
Such a burden.
Settle up with your friends
on October 17th
with the Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
>> Shepard: ON THIS DAY BACK IN
1979, POPE JOHN PAUL II WAS THE
FIRST POPE TO VISIT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
HE ARRIVED IN D.C. IN AN
OPEN-TOP LIMO.
HE MET JIMMY CARTER, THE FIRST
LADY AND THEIR DAUGHTER, AMY.
HE SHOOK HANDS WITH THE CROWD ON
THE SOUTH LAWN.
THE POPE VISITED SIX CITIES ON
THAT TRIP TO THE UNITED STATES.
THE CROWDS WERE SO BIG, "TIME"
MAGAZINE CALLED HIM -- I SHOULD
SAY JOHN PAUL SUPERSTAR.
THE POPE WOULD SURVIVE A
SHOOTING AND BECAME A SAINT
AFTER A PRESIDENT FIRST WELCOMED
THE PONTIFF TO THE WHITE HOUSE
38 YEARS AGO TODAY.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT,