NEW THINGS ON "THE DAILY BRIEFS"
TOMORROW.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> Shepard: IT'S 3:00 ON THE
EAST COAST.
NOON IN LAS VEGAS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS MEETING WITH
SOME OF THE HEROS OF THE
ATTACKS.
MEN AND WOMEN THAT STEPPED
FORWARD TO SAVE OTHERS.
AMONG THEM, POLICE OFFICERS.
NEWLY RELEASED VIDEO SHOWS WHAT
THEY WERE UP AGAINST.
KILLER'S GIRLFRIEND RETURNS TO
THE UNITED STATES.
DID SHE KNOW WHAT HE WAS
PLANNING?
HER SISTERS SAY NO WAY.
INVESTIGATORS ASK HER QUESTIONS.
WE'LL TAKE YOU TO VEGAS FOR A
LOOK AT THE CITY IN MOURNING AND
AN INVESTIGATION UNRELENTING.
LET'S GET TO IT.
FIRST FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK
THIS WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON,
PRESIDENT TRUMP ABOUT TO MEET
WITH HEROS OF THE LAS VEGAS
ATTACK INCLUDING THE FIRST
RESPONDERS AND ORDINARY PEOPLE
THAT RISKED THEIR LIVES TO SAVE
OTHERS.
WE'LL HAVE THAT LIVE WHEN IT
HAPPENS.
WE'RE EXPECTING IT IN 20
MINUTES.
THIS COMES AS WE GET A FIRST
HAND LOOK AT THE POLICE OFFICERS
THAT RISKED THEIR LIVES THAT
NIGHT.
LAS VEGAS POLICE RELEASED BODY
CAM FROM OFFICERS SHOWING THE
OFFICERS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
THE LOCATION OF THE SHOOTER AND
GET PEOPLE TO SAFETY AS BULLETS
RAIN DOWN FROM THAT HOTEL ROOM.
>> GET DOWN, GET DOWN!
GO THAT WAY.
GET OUT OF HERE.
THERE'S GUN SHOTS COMING FROM
OVER THERE.
GO THAT WAY.
>> GO THAT WAY, GO THAT WAY.
THEY'RE SHOOTING RIGHT AT US,
GUYS.
STAY DOWN.
>> WHERE IS IT AT?
>> IT'S AT THE MANDALAY BAY.
COMING OUT OF A WINDOW.
>> GO BACK, GO BACK.
GET BACK.
>> THERE'S MULTIPLE SHOTS COMING
UP THERE.
>> Shepard: BODY CAM FROM THE
RESPONDERS.
FBI AGENTS ARE INTERVIEWING THE
GUNMAN'S VIDEO RIGHT THIS MINUTE
THEY TELL US.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY'RE
CONFIDENT THEY WILL FIGURE OUT
WHY STEPHEN PADDOCK OPENED FIRE
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
DANLEY, THE GIRLFRIEND, ARRIVED
IN LOS ANGELES OVERNIGHT.
SHE WAS IN THE PHILIPPINES AT
THE TIME OF THE SHOOTING
ACCORDING TO AUTHORITIES.
THE SHERIFF SAYS SHE'S A PERSON
OF INTEREST, NOT A SUSPECT.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY WANT TO
FIND OUT WHETHER SHE KNEW WHAT
THE GUNMAN WAS PLANNING.
THE SHERIFF SAYS THE GUNMAN, THE
MURDERER, PLANNED THE MASSACRE
EXTENSIVELY.
STOCKPILING HE SAYS NEARLY TWO
DOZEN GUNS IN HIS HOTEL ROOM AT
MANDALAY BAY.
INVESTIGATORS SAY HE SET UP
CAMERAS ON A ROOM SERVICE CART
OUTSIDE THE DOOR SO HE COULD SEE
BOTH WAYS DOWN THE HALL AND
ANOTHER IN THE PEEP HOLE.
APPARENTLY TO WATCH FOR POLICE
OR SECURITY GUARDS.
THE SHERIFF SAYS THE GUNMAN
KILLED HIMSELF AS SWAT TEAMS
APPROACHED.
JOHN ROBERTS IS LIVE IN
LAS VEGAS ON THE TRIP WITH THE
PRESIDENT OUTSIDE MANDALAY BAY
THIS AFTERNOON.
JOHN?
>> SHEP, GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
THE PRESIDENT JUST WRAPPED UP A
MEETING WITH SOME VICTIMS.
SOME WITH GRIEVOUS INJURIES AND
FAMILY MEMBERS, MEMBERS OF THE
TRAUMA TEAM, THE SURGEONS, O.R.
NURSES AND ALL THOSE THAT HELPED
TO SAVE LIVES.
HE SAID HE WAS OVERWHELMED BY
WHAT HE SAW THERE.
THE PRESIDENT REALLY WANTED TO
COME HERE.
MONDAY WHEN ANNOUNCED THAT HE
WAS GOING TO COME, SITTING DOWN
AND TALKING WITH THE THAI PRIME
MINISTER, NOBODY FROM HIS STAFF
NEW THE PRESIDENT PLANNED TO
COME WEDNESDAY.
HE SAID I'M GOING TO BE HERE
WEDNESDAY AND HERE HE IS.
HE MAY BE COMING AGAIN AS WELL
DEPENDING HOW THINGS PROGRESS
WITH THE INVESTIGATION.
IF THERE'S A MEMORIAL SERVICE
THIS WEEKEND TO ATTEND, THE
WHITE HOUSE IS LOOKING TO ALL OF
THAT.
BACK TO THE UNIVERSITY MEDICAL
CENTER AND THE TOUR THE
PRESIDENT TOOK.
LET'S LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID
WHEN HE MET WITH THE DOCTORSES
AND MEETING THE PERSONNEL IN THE
HOSPITAL.
>> SOME OF THE MOST AMAZING
PEOPLE.
WE MET PATIENTS THAT WERE
ABSOLUTELY TERRIBLY WOUNDED AND
THE DOCTORS, THE NURSES, ALL OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE HOSPITAL HAVE
DONE A JOB THAT IS
UNDESCRIBABLE.
THEY WERE FULL THE NIGHT THAT IT
HAPPENED BEFORE IT HAPPENED.
AND THEY FOUND ROOM FOR MANY
PEOPLE.
HOW MANY PEOPLE CAME IN, DOCTOR?
>> WE HAD 100 COME IN AND WE
ADMITTED 50.
>> WHAT I SAW TODAY IS AN
INCREDIBLE TRIBUTE TO
PROFESSIONALISM.
WHAT THEY HAVE DONE IS
INCREDIBLE.
YOU NEVER WANT TO SEE IT AGAIN.
>> JUST REMARKABLE STORIES,
SHEP, OF HOW EVERYBODY IN THIS
AREA WHO WAS INVOLVED WITH THE
MEDICAL COMMUNITY PITCHED IN.
THEIR STORIES OF PEDIATRIC
SURGEONS OPERATING ON ADULTING,
OB-GYNS THAT TYPICALLY ARE NOT
IN THE TRAUMA CENTER MANNING THE
TABLES.
SO MANY PEOPLE COMING IN, SHEP,
THAT IT WAS JUST KIND OF FULL TO
OVERFLOWING.
EVERYBODY DID AN AMAZING JOB.
THE PRESIDENT WANTED TO PAY
TRIBUTE TO THAT.
FROM HERE, THE PRESIDENT WANTS
TO MEET THE HEROS OF THE EVENT
THAT WERE AT THE IT IS ON SUNDAY
NIGHT.
LAW ENFORCEMENT THAT RAN INTO
THE BULLETS TO PIN DOWN THE
SHOOTNER THE 32nd FLOOR OF THE
MANDALAY BAY BEHIND ME AND MANY
CIVILIANS, SOME OF WHO GAVE
THEIR LIVES TO PROTECT OTHER
PEOPLE AND STORIES OF PEOPLE
GRABBING PICKUPS OFF OF THE
STREETS, FILLING THE BEDS WITH
THE WOUNDED AND TAKING THEM TO
THE HOSPITAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THE PRESIDENT
WANTS TO THANK.
>> Shepard: AND JOHN, HE GOT A
QUESTION ABOUT GUN CONTROL AFTER
DOING THAT.
>> HE DID.
THE PRESIDENT HAS RECEIVED A
NUMBER OF QUESTIONS ABOUT GUN
CONTROL.
HE GOT A COUPLE FROM YESTERDAY.
THE PRESIDENT DEFERRING THE TALK
OF THE DISCUSSION OF GUN CONTROL
FOR THE MOMENT.
HE SAID THERE WILL BE TIME FOR
THAT.
NOT NOW.
I ASKED HIM ABOUT THE SILENCER
BILL THAT APPEARED TO BE
SHELVED.
HE SAID WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT
LATER.
A LOT OF TALK FOR THE NEED FOR
MORE GUN CONTROL.
DEMOCRATS ARE PUSHING THAT.
SOME MEMBERS OF CONGRESS ON THE
REPUBLICAN SIDE THAT ARE SAYING,
WE DON'T NEED MORE GUN CONTROL
MEASURES.
THEY'RE LOOKING AT THE SO-CALLED
BUMP OR SLIDE STOCKS THAT THE
SHOOTER HAD INSTALLED ON A FEW
RIFLES, MIGHT AS BE AS MANY AS
12, WHICH ALLOWS YOU TO FIRE A
SEMIAUTOMATIC RIFLE AT ALMOST
AUTOMATIC SPEED.
THESE WERE THINGS APPROVED IN
2010 BY THE ATF DURING THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION.
NOW YOU HAVE SENATOR JOHN CORNYN
SAYING MAYBE WE NEED TO LOOK AT
BANNING THESE.
NEWT GINGRICH WAS ON THE AIR,
MAYBE YOU LUMP THEM IN WITH THE
1934 LAW THAT BANS AUTOMATIC
WEAPONS BY CIVILIANS.
TOM COLE ON ANOTHER NETWORK
SAID, THIS.
>> NO QUESTION WE OUGHT TO LOOK
INTO THAT.
AUTOMATIC WEAPONSES -- WHEN I
SAW THE CLIPS AND HEARD THE
FIRE, I ASSUMED HE HAD AN
AUTOMATIC WEAPON.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT THERE WAS
TECHNOLOGY CAPABLE THAT CHEAPLY
OF TRANSFORMING A SEMIAUTOMATIC
INTO AN AUTOMATIC WEAPON.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY
QUESTION WE OUGHT TO LOOK AT
THAT.
>> EVEN REPUBLICANS ARE
DESCRIBING THIS AS A LOOP HOLE,
ONE THAT THEY CAN CLOSE QUICKLY.
DEMOCRATS, PEOPLE LIKE JOHN
LEWIS OUT THERE ON THE STEPS OF
THE CAPITOL SAYING HOW MANY MORE
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE KILLED
BEFORE WE GET MORE GUN CONTROL
MEASURES?
THERE'S DEFINITELY GOING TO BE A
CLASH IN CONGRESS OVER HOW FAR
TO GO IN THE WAKE OF THIS
INCIDENTS.
AGAIN, SHEP, THE PRESIDENT
SAYING LET'S MOURN THE DEAD,
TEND TO THE BOUNDED AND THEN
LET'S HAVE THE POLITICAL
DISCUSSION, SHEP.
>> Shepard: JOHN ROBERTS LIVE IN
MANDALAY BAY.
THANK YOU.
THE SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON IS NOT DENYING THAT HE
CALLED PRESIDENT TRUMP A
BLANKING MORON.
THE SECRETARY IS INSISTING THAT
HE NEVER THREATENED TO QUIT.
HE'S RESPONDING TO AN NBC NEWS
REPORT THAT MIKE PENCE HAD TO
CONVINCE SECRETARY TILLERSON NOT
TO STEP DOWN.
>> THE VICE PRESIDENT HAS NEVER
HAD TO PERSUADE ME TO REMAIN THE
SECRETARY OF STATE BECAUSE I
HAVE NEVER CONSIDERED LEAVING
THIS POST.
I'M NEW TO WASHINGTON.
I HAVE LEARNED THAT THERE'S SOME
THAT TRY TO SOW DISSENSION TO
ADVANCE THEIR OWN AGENDA BY
TEARING OTHERS APART AND AN
UNDERSTOOD TO UNDERMINE THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN AGENDA.
I DO NOT AND I WILL NOT OPERATE
THAT WAY.
>> WHEN A REPORTER ASKED
SPECIFICALLY WHETHER SECRETARY
TILLERSON CALLED THE PRESIDENT A
MORON, HE RESPONDED THAT HE
WASN'T GOING TO DEAL WITH PETTY
STUFF LIKE THAT.
RICH EDSON IS AT THE STATE
DEPARTMENT.
HEATHER NAUERT HAS COME FORWARD
TO DENY THAT CLAIM.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE DAILY PRESS BRIEFING JUST
WRAPPED UP.
HEATHER DENIED THAT THE
SECRETARY OF STATE CALLED THE
PRESIDENT A MORON.
>> THE SECRETARY DOES NOT USE
THAT TYPE OF LANGUAGE.
THE SECRETARY DID NOT USE THAT
TYPE OF LANGUAGE TO SPEAK ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
HE DOES NOT USE THAT LANGUAGE TO
SPEAKUT ABO AN.YONE
HHAE T TTTHARI CFIES IT.
>> HE NEVER SAID THAT?
>> HE DID NOT SAY THAT.
>> Shepard: SO THERE YOU HAVE
IT.
THE PRESIDENT NOW LIVE WITH
FIRST RESPONDERS.
WE DIDN'T EXPECT THIS.
LET'S LISTEN LIVE.
>> I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN YOU GUYS
ARE GOOD BUT YOU PROVED IT.
HE'S A SICK, DEMENTED MAN.
HAVE THEY FOUND OUT ANYTHING
ELSE?
>> STILL A LITTLE BIT SOON.
WE HAVE A COUPLE OF GOOD LEADS.
WE'RE WORKING OUR WAY THROUGH
THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO GET THE ANSWERS.
>> MIGHT BE SOMEBODY THERE.
THE WIRES ARE SCREWED UP.
MIGHT BE SOMETHING THERE.
I'M GOING TO SAY A FEW WORDS TO
YOUR GROUP.
I WANTED TO SAY HELLO AND
CONGRATULATE YOU.
I WAS A FAN BEFORE THIS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
EVERYONE IN THIS ROOM KNOWS
THAT.
A BIG FAN BEFORE THIS.
YOU CAN BE MORE OF A FAN, I'M
MORE OF A FAN NOW.
YOU SHOWED THE WORLD AROUND THE
WORLD WAS WATCHING AND YOU
SHOWED WHAT PROFESSIONALISM IS
ALL ABOUT.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT CAN TAKE
PLACE FOR HOURS AND HOURS AND
HOURS.
YOU CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU SHOULD BE VERY PROUD.
>> A MATTER OF IDENTIFICATION,
OFFICER HANCOCK AT THE END TO
YOUR RIGHT THERE, HE WAS THE
FIRST SWAT OFFICER TO ENGAGE THE
INDIVIDUAL.
OFFICER DRISCOLL THERE, THE K-9
OFFICER ASSISTED.
OFFICER MORRIS WAS ONE OF THE
TWO I DESCRIBED PARTNERED WITH
THE SECURITY GUARDS.
>> THEY DID A GOOD JOB.
YOU DID A GOOD JOB.
HIS OPTION WOULD HAVE BEEN TO DO
IT HIMSELF.
IF IT DOESN'T WORK, YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE HAD THE INFORMATION MAYBE,
RIGHT?
HE DID THE RIGHT THING?
>> HE DID.
WE RELIED ON THE INFORMATION.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
>> EVERYONE ELSE SEATED IN AND
BEHIND THE PRESS THERE WERE
INTEGRAL IN SAVING NUMEROUS
LIVES.
THE GENTLEMAN TO YOUR LEFT, THAT
FIREFIGHTER RIGHT THERE WAS OFF
DUTY WATCHING THE CONCERT AND
SAVED SEVERAL LIVES.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR YOU TO KNOW
THAT EVERY PERSON IN HERE WAS
INSTRUMENTAL IN LIFE SAVING
MEASURES.
THESE TWO YOUNG LADIES HERE ARE
DISPATCHERS.
PROBABLY THE MOST IMPORTANT
PEOPLE IN THE ROOM.
IF YOU EVER HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO LISTEN TO THE RADIO TRAFFIC,
THESE TWO YOUNG LADIES ARE
AMAZING.
THERE WAS A THIRD YOUNG LADY.
SHE DECIDED TO GO TO COLLEGE.
>> Shepard: PARDON THE
INTERVENTION WHILE OUR FOX
TELEVISION STATIONS JOIN US.
GOOD AFTERNOON FROM FOX NEWS IN
NEW YORK, A LIVE LOOK WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS MEETING SOME
OF THE FIRST RESPONDERS, THE
HEROS OF THE ATTACK OUTSIDE THE
MANDALAY BAY AT THE COUNTRY
MUSIC FESTIVAL SUNDAY NIGHT.
LET'S LISTEN LIVE.
AND AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT, THE
WHITE HOUSE POOL HAS WALKED OUT.
THE PRESIDENT SHARING
PLEASANTRIES AND THANKS WITH
FIRST RESPONDERS.
OUR AUDIENCE ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL
JUST A MOMENT AGO MET THE FIRST
POLICE OFFICERS CREDITED WITH
ENGAGING THE SUSPECT INSIDE THE
ROOM.
WE'VE HEARD THE 911 CALLS, THE
DIFFERENT POLICE RESPONDERS, THE
DISPATCH FROM POLICE
HEADQUARTERS.
IT'S BEEN A VERY GOOD DAY FOR
THANK YOUS TO THE FIRST
RESPONDERS AND EVERYDAY FOLKS
THAT HELPED OUTSIDE THE LUXOR
AND MANDALAY BAY ON THE
LAS VEGAS STRIP.
WE'RE WAITING FOR THE PRESIDENT
TO APPEAR AGAIN IN JUST A
MOMENT.
THAT WAS SORT OF AN UNSCHEDULED
PHOTO OP, MEET AND GREET WITH
SOME OF THE FIRST RESPONDER
THERE'S.
YOU CAN SEE A LIVE LOOK NOW IN
LAS VEGAS AT POLICE HEADQUARTERS
WHERE THE PRESIDENT WILL BE
MEETING WITH -- AND THE FIRST
LADY TO MEET WITH FIRST
RESPONDERS AND HEROS OF THE
ATTACK IN JUST A MOMENT.
JOHN ROBERTS FOLLOWING ALONG
WITH THE PRESIDENT OUT IN
LAS VEGAS TODAY.
THEY HAVE MADE A REAL EFFORT,
JOHN, TO PUT THESE HEROS OF THIS
TRAGEDY FRONT AND CENTER AND
THESE MEET AND GREETS.
FOR THOSE JOINING US ON FOX
TELEVISION STATIONS, HE GAVE AN
INVITATION TO THOSE IN THE
HOSPITAL ROOMS, THE O.R.s.
IF YOU'RE EVER IN WASHINGTON
D.C., COME SEE ME AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU.
A CONCERTED EFFORT ON THE PART
OF THIS WHITE HOUSE.
GREAT TO SEE.
>> ALL THROUGH THE CAMPAIGN AND
AS PRESIDENT, SHEP, PRESIDENT
TRUMP REALLY WAS A CHAMPION OF
LAW ENFORCEMENT.
SO MANY CAMPAIGNED EVENTS ACROSS
THE COUNTRY, HE WOULD ALWAYS
HOLD THEM UP FOR PRAISE.
HE'S DONE THAT AGAIN AS
PRESIDENT.
ANY TIME HE GETS IN THE SAME
ROOM WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT OR
MILITARY FOR THAT MATTER, HE
ALWAYS HAS THE HIGHEST PRAISE.
I KNOW THAT HE WAS VERY TAKEN,
NOT ONLY WITH THE SCOPE AND THE
DEPTH OF THIS TRAGEDY AND THE
HORRIBLE FACT THAT SO MANY
PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
WHEN THERE WERE BULLETS RAINING
DOWN FROM THE WINDOWS BEHIND ME,
50, 75 AT A TIME BECAUSE HE HAD
BIG MAGAZINES, THE OFFICERS TOOK
COVER BUT MOVED TOWARD THE
DANGER.
THEY WERE BLOWING THE DOOR OPEN
WITHIN MINUTES TO GET INSIDE AND
CLEARLY HAD CORNERED THIS GUY,
THE SHOOTER.
HE TOOK HIS OWN LIFE WHEN HE
KNEW THEY WERE COMING IN THROUGH
THE DOOR.
THE FACT THAT AS YOU POINTED
OUT, SO MANY CIVILIANS DOVE ON
THEIR LOVED ONES OR SACRIFICED
THEIR OWN LIVES OR STOLE PICKUP
TRUCKS TO PUT PEOPLE IN THE BEDS
BECAUSE THE AMBULANCES WERE SO
OVERWHELMED.
WHEN THEY GOT TO THE HOSPITALS,
THE DOCTORS AND NURSES ON STAFF
AND ALL OF THE MEDICAL STAFF
FROM ACROSS THE VALLEY HERE THAT
CAME IN TO THE TRAUMA CENTERS
AND THE HOSPITALS EVEN THOUGH
THEY WERE OFF DUTY.
JUST DIDN'T EVEN NEED TO PICK UP
THE PHONE.
RAN IN TO HELP WHEN THE SCOPE
BECAME CLEAR.
THE PRESIDENT WANTED TO TAKE
TIME TO RECOGNIZE ALL OF THOSE
PEOPLE.
HE SAYS THAT THEY HAVE DONE AN
INCREDIBLE SERVICE FOR THEIR
COMMUNITY.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT HE WANTS TO
HOLD UP AS AN EXAMPLE NOT ONLY
TO THE REST OF THE COUNTRY BUT
THE WORLD AS WELL TO SAY THIS IS
HOW WE RESPOND TO TRAGEDY IN
AMERICA AND HOPEFULLY TAKE STEPS
TO MAKE SURE SOMETHING LIKE THIS
NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN.
THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE GOING TO GET
INTO A REAL TUSSLE OF A DEBATE
IN CAPITOL HILL.
THERE'S GOING TO BE PEOPLE ON
ONE SAID THAT SAY WE NEED MORE
GUN CONTROL MEASURES, PEOPLE ON
THE OTHER SIDE THAT SAYS THERE'S
SOME THINGS THAT WE CAN DO ABOUT
THESE SO-CALLED PUMP STOCKS OR
SLIDE STOCKS THAT ALLOW
SEMIAUTOMATIC WEAPONS TO BE
FIRED AT A HIGH RATE OR OTHER
MEASURES TO BE TAKEN TO STOP
PEOPLE FROM CONVERTING THESE WE
POPS INTO A HIGH RATE OF FIRE.
WE DON'T NEED TO GO FURTHER THAN
THAT.
WE NEED TO ENFORCE EXISTING
LAWS.
EVERYTHING THAT THIS FELLOW
SEEMED TO DO SHORT OF WHAT HE
DID SUNDAY NIGHT WAS WITHIN THE
LETTER OF THE LAW.
IT'S A DILEMMA HOW THAT DEBATE
WILL GO FORWARD AS TO WHAT LAW
COULD BE CRAFTED TO STOP WHAT
HAPPENED SUNDAY NIGHT.
ALL OF THIS STUFF IS
RETROSPECTIVE AS OPPOSED TO
PROSPECTIVE.
YOU'RE ALWAYS REACTING TO THE
LAST INCIDENT.
IT'S DIFFICULT AND A HEATED
DEBATE GOING FORWARD, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JOHN.
LET'S GO TO A.B. STODDARD.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THIS DEBATE WILL
COME, THOSE ON THE GUN CONTROL
SIDE, ARE PUSHING FOR IT TODAY.
THEIR ARGUMENT IS THERE'S NO
TIME LIKE ON THE HEELS OF A
TRAGEDY TO KEEP ANOTHER TRAGEDY
FROM HAPPENING.
THAT'S THEIR POSITION.
>> THEY'RE MAKING AN ARGUMENT
THAT IS REASONABLE THAT THE TIME
TO TALK ABOUT THESE THINGS IS
WHEN THEY HAPPEN AND VICTIMS
FAMILIES ARE GRIEVING AND WANT
SOMETHING DONE ABOUT IT.
IF THIS IS A TERRORIST ATTACK,
WE TALK ABOUT WAYS TO KEEP THE
HOMELAND SAFE FROM TERRORISTS.
SO GUN CONTROL ADVOCATES TALK
ABOUT THE NEED TO CLOSE THE GUN
SHOW LOOP HOLE AND LOOK AT THE
ACCESSORIES LIKE THE BUMP STOP
MECHANISM TO MAKE A
SEMIAUTOMATIC TO AN AUTOMATIC
WEAPON.
I THINK IT'S INTERESTING IN THIS
INCREDIBLY POLARIZED TIME, SHEP,
WITH THIS DEBATE THAT NEVER GOES
ANYWHERE, THAT THERE'S SOME
REPUBLICANS WILLING TO LOOK
AT -- YOU PLAYED CLIPS FROM TOM
COLE, THE REPUBLICAN, REPORTS
THAT SENATOR JOHN CORNYN, THE
NUMBER 2 IN LEADERSHIP ON THE
SENATE SIDE IS INTERESTED.
I READ THAT CONGRESSMAN BILL
FLORES FROM TEXAS IS INTERESTED
IN IT.
SO THERE MIGHT BE SOME
INCREMENTAL PATH FORWARD TO SOME
KIND OF DISCUSSION ABOUT HAVING
TO DO THIS KIND OF WEAPONRY
WHERE 800 ROUNDS CAN GO OFF IN A
MINUTE AND KILL SO MANY
PEOPLING.
GENERALLY SPEAKING, I'LL BE
SURPRISED IF IT DOES BECAUSE
THEY BREAK DOWN SO QUICKLY IN
ALL OF THIS POLARIZING AND ALL
OF THE DIFFERENCES AND IF DEBATE
GOES NOWHERE BECAUSE OF THE
VOTES AND THE WAY THEY'RE SET UP
IN CONGRESS NOW.
>> Shepard: ALL RIGHT, A.B.
STODDARD LIVE FROM WASHINGTON.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
WE'RE WATCHING ANOTHER LIVE
EVENT AS WELL.
THE PRESIDENT ABOUT TO COME INTO
THIS ROOM WE'RE TOLD TO MEET
WITH ANOTHER SET OF FIRST
RESPONDERS.
THIS IS THE THIRD SET WE'VE SEEN
ON CAMERA.
FOLKS SITTING AROUND, WAITING TO
MEET THE PRESIDENT,
COMMANDER-IN-CHIEF AS HE MAKES
THE ROUNDS THERE IN LAS VEGAS.
WE'LL HAVE COVERAGE OF THAT ON
FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
THOSE OF YOU WATCHING ON FOX
TELEVISION STATIONS ACROSS THE
NATION, MUCH MORE ON THIS A
LITTLE LATER ON YOUR LOCAL NEWS.
IT CONTINUES NOW ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL ON SATELLITE AND CABLE.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
FOX NEWS, NEW YORK.
AS WE CONTINUE HERE ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL, WE'RE WAITING FOR THESE
FIRST RESPONDERS TO MEET WITH
THE PRESIDENT AND WE'LL HAVE
THAT LIVE FOR YOU IN JUST A
MOMENT.
TO MEET THE HEROS OF LAS VEGAS
THIS HELPED SAVE LIVES DURING
THE SHOOTING.
FIRST, THE LATEST FROM THE
INVESTIGATORS ON SCENE AND THE
PICTURES NOW THAT SHOW THE
INSIDE OF THE MURDER'S SWEET.
THAT'S COMING UP ON THE FOX NEWS
DECK THIS AFTERNOON.
I was always
"the girl with psoriasis."
People don't stare anymore.
I never joined in.
That wasn't fair to any of us.
I was covered.
I tried lots of things
over the years.
But I didn't give up.
I kept on fighting.
I found something that worked.
That still works.
Now?
SEE ME.
I found clear skin that lasts.
See if COSENTYX could make a
difference for you-
COSENTYX is proven to help
people with moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis...
...find clear skin that
can last.
Don't use if you're allergic
to COSENTYX.
Before starting COSENTYX,
you should be checked
for tuberculosis.
An increased risk of infections
and lowered ability
to fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection or symptoms.
Or if you have received a
vaccine or plan to.
If you have inflammatory
bowel disease,
tell your doctor if symptoms
develop or worsen.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
SEE ME
to know...
...clear skin can last.
Don't hold back...
...ask your dermatologist if
COSENTYX can help you
find clear skin that lasts.
[VO] QuickBooks introduces
Rodney.
He has a new business teaching
lessons.
Rodney wanted to know how his
business was doing...
...so he got QuickBooks.
It organizes all his accounts,
so he can see his bottom line.
Ahhh...that's a profit.
Know where you stand instantly.
Visit QuickBooks-dot-com.
If you have Medicare
Parts A and B
guess what?
You could apply for a
Medicare supplement insurance
plan whenever you want.
No enrollment window.
No waiting to apply.
That means now may be a
great time to shop for an
AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Medicare doesn't
cover everything.
And like all standardized
Medicare supplement
insurance plans,
these help cover some
of what Medicare
doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide.
It could help you find the
AARP Medicare Supplement plan
that works for you.
These types of plans have
no networks,
so you get to choose any
doctor who accepts
Medicare patients.
Rates are competitive,
and they're the only plans
of their kind endorsed by AARP.
Remember -
these plans let you apply
all year round.
So call today.
Because now's the perfect time
to learn more.
Go long.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
THE FIRST LADY MELANIA TRUMP IN
LAS VEGAS MEETING WITH THE HEROS
OF THE MASSACRE AND FIRST
RESPONDERS AND ORDINARY PEOPLE
THAT HELPED AFTER THE SHOOTING
STARTED.
EARLIER, THE PRESIDENT AND THE
FIRST LADY MET VICTIMS AND MED
CAT WORKERS AT A HOSPITAL IN
LAS VEGAS.
LET'S LISTEN.
WE'LL HAVE -- WELL, I THOUGHT WE
WOULD LISTEN TO SOUND FROM THAT
TIME.
APPARENTLY NOT.
WHEN THIS BEGINS, WE'LL TAKE YOU
THERE.
THE LAS VEGAS GUNMAN ENCOURAGED
HIS GIRLFRIEND, MARILOU DANLEY,
TO LEAVE THE COUNTRY FOR THE
MASSACRE.
THAT'S WHAT DANLEY'S SISTER TOLD
A TV SISTER IN AUSTRALIA.
HE SENT HER AWAY AT ONE POINT.
THEY SAY THE MURDERER BROUGHT
DANLEY A PLANE TICKET TO THE
PHILIPPINES SO SHE WOULDN'T GET
IN THE WAY OF HIS PLANS.
WE'RE NOT SURE HOW THEY KNOW
THAT.
THAT'S WHAT THEY TELL US.
IN THE INTERVIEW, THEIR FACES
ARE BLURRED TO PROTECT THEIR
IDENTITIES.
HERE, LOOK.
>> I KNOW THAT SHE DOESN'T KNOW
ANYTHING AS WELL LIKE US.
SHE WAS SENT AWAY.
SHE WAS SENT AWAY SO THAT SHE
WOULD NOT BE THERE.
>> Shepard: WE DON'T KNOW IF
THEY KNOW THAT OR IF SHE'S
SPECULATING ON THAT MATTER.
INVESTIGATORS QUESTIONING DANLEY
RIGHT NOW WE'RE TOLD THE FBI
HEADQUARTERS IN LOS ANGELES SAY
THEY HOPE SHE CAN GIVE THEM ANY
OU AUETBHAT WROV DE PADDOCK
TO COMMIT MASS MURDER.
TRACE GALLAGHER ON THE CASE IN
LAS VEGAS.
LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
SHOOTER'S ARSENAL TODAY, TRACE.
>> THEY RECOVERED SOME 47
WEAPONS FROM THREE LOCATIONS.
ONE FROM THE MANDALAY BAY BEHIND
ME AND HIS TWO HOMES, ONE IN
MESQUITE, NEVADA AND THE OTHER
ONE IN RENO, NEVADA.
THOSE GUNS WORTH BETWEEN
$100,000 AND $110,000.
THE SEMIAUTOMATICS ARE WORTH
BETWEEN $1,500 AND $3,000.
THESE PICTURES ARE FROM THE
DAILY MAIL.
THEY WERE PUT ON THE FLOOR OF
THE HOTEL SWEEP IN MANDALAY BAY.
WE SHOULD KNOW THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK HAS BEEN COLLECTING GUNS
FOR YEARS.
BUT IN THE PAST YEAR ALONE, HE
HAS AMASSED SOME 30-PLUS
WEAPONS, A GUN SHOP OWNER IN
MESQUITE WHERE HE HAD A HOME
SAID THAT ON SEPTEMBER 28th,
PADDOCK BOUGHT A WEAPON AND THAT
IS THE SAME DAY THAT HE CHECKED
IN TO THE MANDALAY BAY HOTEL.
LISTEN TO THE GUN SHOP OWNER.
>> I WAS ILL.
MADE ME ILL TO THINK THAT WE HAD
INTERACTED WITH HIM AND HE
COMMITTED A TRAGEDY.
>> HE WENT ON THE SAY THAT HE
DID NOT SELL STEPHEN PADDOCK ANY
AMMUNITION OR ANY OF THOSE BUMP
STOCKS WE'VE TALKED ABOUT ALL
DAY LONG.
THAT'S WHAT KIND OF MAKES THE
TRIGGER TURN INTO AUTOMATICALLY
ENGAGED WEAPON, SHEP.
HE ALSO POINTS OUT AND WE SHOULD
POINT THIS OUT, THE REASON THE
BUMP STOPS ARE LEGAL IN NEVADA
IS BECAUSE THEY DON'T PHYSICALLY
ALTER THE WEAPON.
IT'S TAKEN ON AND TAKEN OFF.
SO IT'S LEGAL NOW.
>> Shepard: WHAT ELSE ARE WE
LEARNING FROM INVESTIGATORS
ABOUT THE GIRLFRIEND?
>> WE KNOW THAT MARILOU DANLEY
IS IN HER THIRD HOUR OF
QUESTIONING IN LOS ANGELES.
SHE FLEW IN TO LOS ANGELES FROM
THE PHILIPPINES LAST NIGHT.
THEY CLEARLY WANT INFORMATION
ABOUT STEPHEN PADDOCK'S MENTAL
STATE, HIS RELIGIOUS BELIEFS,
HIS POLITICAL AFFILIATIONS AND
ANYTHING THAT COULD LEAD THEM TO
A POSSIBLE MOTIVE.
THE BIG TICKET ITEM FOR A LOT OF
INVESTIGATORS WHAT SHE KNEW
ABOUT THIS ARSENAL OF WEAPONS
AND HIS INTENT.
REMEMBER, THEY FOUND DOZENS AND
DOZENS OF WEAPONS INSIDE THE
HOMES THAT SHE LIVED IN WITH HIM
ALONG WITH EXPLOSIVES AND
SUITCASES OF AMMUNITION.
THEY WOULD LIKE TO FIND OUT WHAT
SHE KNEW ABOUT THAT.
HER FAMILY SAYS THAT THE REASON
HE SENT HER TO THE PHILIPPINES
IS BECAUSE HE WAS AFRAID THAT
SHE WOULD STOP HIM FROM COMMITS
THIS CRIME.
LISTEN TO THE FAMILY AGAIN.
>> NOBODY CAN PUT IT TOGETHER
EXCEPT MARILOU.
ONLY MARILOU CAN MAYBE HELP.
>> INVESTIGATORS ARE INTERESTED
IN THE $100,000 THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK SENT TO PHILIPPINES IN
RECENT WEEKS.
THE SPIC YOULATION IS THAT HE
SENT IT TO HER BECAUSE HE KNEW
AS SOON AS HE COMMITTED THE
CRIME THAT ALL OF HIS ASSETS
WOULD BE LOCKED DOWN POSSIBLY
FOREVER AND SHE WOULDN'T GET ANY
KIND OF MONEY OUT OF THAT AT
ALL.
WE SHOULD KNOW THIS FBI
INTERVIEW IN LOS ANGELES COULD
GO FOR SEVERAL MORE HOURS.
THERE'S A NEWS CONFERENCE COMING
UP.
WE HOPE TO GET MORE INFORMATION
ABOUT WHAT THEY'RE GLEANING FROM
THE INTERVIEW IN THE NEXT HOUR
OR SO.
>> Shepard: WE'LL CHECK IN FOR
YOU ON THAT.
TRACE, THANKS VERY MUCH.
COMING UP HERE, ANDREW
NAPOLITANO, THE JUDGE, ON WHERE
THE INVESTIGATION GOES FROM HERE
AND WHAT HAPPENS IN THE
SHOOTER'S GIRLFRIEND STOPS
COOPERATING WITH INVESTIGATORS?
THAT AND WE'RE WAITING FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO COME IN AND
MEET WITH FIRST RESPONDERS,
POLICE OFFICERS AND FIREFIGHTERS
THAT WILL MEET WITH HIM SHORTLY.
WE'LL BE THERE LIVE FOR THAT AS
THE NEWS ROLLS ON ON THIS
WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON.
RLY... OR T.
OR MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I'M NOT REALLY "THERE."
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-234-2424.