"FOX NEWS SUNDAY."
>>> WE ARE LIVE AT FOX REPORT.
AMERICAN WAR SHIPS SITTING NOT
FAR FROM SYRIA.
HERE IS WHAT WE KNOW.
THERE'S LITTLE DOUBT SYRIA IS
USING CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON ITS
OWN PEOPLE, FROM A SENIOR OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL.
IS IT TIME TO FIRE AWAY?
>> I CERTAINLY WOULD DO CRUISE
MISSILE STRIKES.
I THINK YOU CAN DO THAT WITHOUT
BOOTS ON THE GROUND, WITHOUT
HAVING AMERICANS IN HARM'S WAY.
>> IF THE MILITARY ADVISES, THIS
COULD DESTROY THE CHEMICAL
WEAPON STOCKPILE, I WOULD
SUPPORT THAT.
>> FOX REPORT, THE LATEST
RESPONSE HERE AND OVERSEAS TO
NEW TALKS OF MILITARY
INTERVENTION AGAINST THE ASSAD
REGIME.
ALSO BUGGING, THE UNITED
NATIONS?
A NEW REPORT SAYS AMERICA'S SPY
AGENCY, THE NSA, TARGETED U.N.
HEADQUARTERS.
IN MINUTES, WHAT THE LATEST
ALLEGATIONS AGAINST THE NSA
COULD MEAN FOR WASHINGTON AND
OUR ALLIES.
AND WHEN YOU RUN WITH THE BULLS,
YOU WANT TO DODGE THE HORNS.
BUT THERE'S ANOTHER DANGER
LURKING IN AMERICA'S NEWEST PAST
TIME, THE DRONES OVER THE SAND.
NO REALLY, YOU HAVE TO WATCH OUT
FOR THOSE, TOO, APPARENTLY.
I AM HARRIS FAULKNER.
THE POPE, LEADER OF ONE BILLION
CATHOLICS AROUND THE WORLD HAS
SPOKEN ABOUT SYRIA.
AS YOU KNOW, WORLD GOVERNMENTS,
INCLUDING OUR OWN, ARE PONDERING
WHAT TO DO ABOUT THE CIVIL WAR
IN SYRIA CREATING MILLIONS OF
REFUGEES, PUTTING PRESSURE ON
NEIGHBORING MUSLIM COUNTRIES AND
POTENTIALLY PUNCHING HOLES IN AN
ALREADY FRAGILE IMBALANCE THERE.
IT COULD BE THE OPENING FOR
TERRORISTS TO CAPITALIZE ON THE
CHAOS IN SYRIA.
ASIDE FROM THE WRANGLING BY THE
POLITICIANS AND DIPLOMATS,
TODAY, POPE FRANCIS CALLED FOR
ACTION, URGING THE INTERNATIONAL
COMMUNITY TO STEP UP EFFORTS TO
HELP SYRIA END THE WAR.
THE POPE ADDRESSED TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF WORSHIPPERS IN ST.
PETER'S SQUARE, SPEAKING ABOUT
THE TERRIBLE IMAGES SHOWING
INNOCENT CIVILIANS UNDER ATTACK.
HE RENEWED CALLS FOR THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT AND REBELS TO PUT
DOWN ARMS AND START TALKING.
POPE FRANCIS ALSO EXPRESSING
LOVE WITH PRAYERS AND SOLIDARITY
TO VICTIMS OF THE CONFLICT AND
THOSE SUFFERING, ESPECIALLY THE
CHILDREN.
NOW TO THE NEW REACTION IN
WASHINGTON.
JUST HOURS AGO, LAWMAKERS FROM
BOTH POLITICAL PARTIES CALLING
FOR A LIMITED MILITARY RESPONSE.
THE REPORTED CHEMICAL ATTACK IN
SYRIA'S CAPITAL CITY, KILLING
HUNDREDS.
THE U.N. ANNOUNCING SYRIA IS
CLAIMING IT WILL ALLOW A TEAM OF
INSPECTORS TO EXAMINE THE SITE.
THAT'S SET TO BEGIN TOMORROW.
A SENIOR OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIAL SAYING THERE'S VERY
LITTLE DOUBT PEOPLE WERE GASSED.
SENATOR BOB CORKER OF TENNESSEE,
RANKING MEMBER OF THE FOREIGN
RELATIONS COMMITTEE IS AMONG THE
LAWMAKERS GOING ON THE RECORD
TODAY.
>> I THINK WE WILL RESPOND IN A
SURGICAL WAY AND I HOPE THE
PRESIDENT AS SOON AS WE GET BACK
TO WASHINGTON WILL ASK FOR
AUTHORIZATION FROM CONGRESS TO
DO SOMETHING IN A VERY SURGICAL
AND PROPORTIONAL WAY, SOMETHING
THAT GETS THEIR ATTENTION, THAT
CAUSES THEM TO UNDERSTAND THAT
WE ARE NOT GOING TO PUT UP WITH
THIS KIND OF ACTIVITY.
WE HAVE TO VERIFY IT WAS
DIRECTED BY THE ASSAD REGIME.
THAT WILL ALLOW US TO BUILD AN
INTERNATIONAL COALITION AND THAT
IS NECESSARY TO TAKE FURTHER
STEPS IN SYRIA, ALSO WILL HELP
DIFFUSE SOME OF THE COUNTRIES
LIKE IRAN, RUSSIA, TRYING TO
PAWN THIS OFF ON THE REBELS.
>> AND THE SECOND LAWMAKER, OF
COURSE, YOU SAW THERE WAS
SENATOR JACK REED WHO TALKED
ABOUT DIFFUSING COUNTRIES LIKE
IRAN AND HE MENTIONED RUSSIA,
LONG TIME ALLY OF THE SYRIAN
PRESIDENT, BASHAR AL-ASSAD.
THE RUSSIAN FOREIGN MINISTRY
SAYS ANY BILATERAL ACTIONS THAT
BYPASSES UNITED NATIONS WOULD
HAVE A DEVASTATING IMPACT ON
SECURITY IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
ELIZABETH PRAN WITH MORE.
>> WE HEARD FROM THE
ADMINISTRATION OVER THE WEEKEND,
THE NAVY STATION DESTROYERS IN
THE EASTERN MEDITERRANEAN SEE,
BUT NO WORD ON PLANS FOR THE
SHIPS.
THE ADMINISTRATION SAYS A QUICK
INTERVENTION WOULD BE
PROBLEMATIC, WHILE SOME
LAWMAKERS THINK LEADERS SHOULD
BE ACTING OUT OF ABUNDANCE OF
CAUTION, OTHERS SAY THERE SHOULD
BE MORE ACTIVITY.
>> WE KNOW THERE ARE FOUR WAR
SHIPS, AGAIN, OFF THE COAST OF
SYRIA, MISSILES ARE AN OPTION TO
TRY TO TAKE OUT THE CHEMICAL
STOCK PILES.
>> JUST STANDING OFF, THROWING A
FEW MISSILES, DROPPING A FEW
BOMBS ON KEY TARGETS ARE WHAT WE
IN THE MILITARY CALL A FEEL GOOD
BOMBING.
IT GIVES THE PRESIDENT THE
ABILITY TO SAY HE'S DONE
SOMETHING, PERHAPS SOME IN
AMERICA FEEL BETTER, BUT IN
TERMS OF DEGRADING THE ABILITY
OF THE SYRIAN ARMY TO ATTACK ITS
OWN PEOPLE IN THIS CIVIL WAR, I
DON'T THINK MUCH IS GOING TO
COME OUT OF IT.
>> SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN KERRY
HAS ALSO BEEN IN CONTACT WITH
DOMESTIC AND FOREIGN COLLEAGUES
OVER THE WEEKEND.
HARRIS?
>> A COUPLE HOURS AGO, WE
LEARNED THE PRESIDENT SPOKE WITH
THE PRESIDENT OF FRANCE TODAY.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT WHAT THEY
SAID?
>> WE KNOW HE SPOKE WITH THE
FRENCH PRESIDENT TODAY.
ACCORDING TO THE ADMINISTRATION,
THEY DISCUSSED POSSIBLE FUTURE
RESPONSES BY THE INTERNATIONAL
COMMUNITY AND AGREED TO STAY IN
CONSTANT COMMUNICATION.
JUST YESTERDAY, THE PRESIDENT
SPENT MORE THAN 40 MINUTES
SPEAKING WITH THE BRITISH PRIME
MINISTER DAVID CAMERON.
THEY AGREE THE CRISIS IS
UPGRADED, WARRANTS SERIOUS
RESPONSE.
TWO LEADERS AGREE ALL OPTIONS TO
BE ON THE TABLE.
OF COURSE, HARRIS, ALL OF THE
MEN EXPRESS GREAT CONCERN ABOUT
THE ALLEGED USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
>> ELIZABETH PRANN, THANK YOU.
INSPECTORS ARE SET TO VISIT THE
SITE OF THE ALLEGED CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT AGREED TO
ALLOW THEM TO GO IN.
THEY WILL BEGIN FACT-FINDING IN
SYRIA IN A FEW HOURS.
IT IS ALREADY MONDAY THERE.
SENIOR U.S. OFFICIALS SAY IT MAY
BE TOO LATE TO FIND ANYTHING.
IF THE SYRIANS HAD NOTHING TO
HIDE, WOULD HAVE LET THEM IN
FIVE DAYS AGO.
BRITAIN'S FOREIGN SECRETARY SAYS
EVIDENCE OF THAT ATTACK MAY BE
GONE.
>>> COMING UP, INSIDE THE FOX
REPORT, YOU HEARD US SO FAR
REPORT TWO THREATS, ONE FROM
IRAN, ONE FROM RUSSIA.
IF OUR MILITARY WERE TO MAKE A
MOVE IN SYRIA OUTSIDE THE UNITED
NATIONS.
TO GET A BETTER IDEA WHAT THE
THREATS MEAN AND WHETHER THEY
WOULD ACTUALLY DETER US MAKING A
MOVE, WE BRING IN FORMER U.S.
AMBASSADOR TO UNITED NATIONS,
JOHN BOLTON.
I'LL ASK HIM ABOUT IT.
>>> AN INFERNO BURNING NEAR THE
NORTHERN BORDER OF YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK COVERS WELL OVER
200 SQUARE MILES.
THAT BREAKING DEVELOPMENT JUST
HOURS AGO.
IT IS NOW THE SIZE OF THE CITY
OF CHICAGO.
JUST OVERNIGHT IT GREW BY MORE
THAN SEVEN SQUARE MILES IN SIZE.
FIREFIGHTERS FACED WITH STRONG
WINDS IN THE FORECAST FOR
TONIGHT.
FOREST LAND, HOMES, LIVES, ALL
IN THE PATH OF THE SO-CALLED RIM
FIRE.
>> 15 MINUTES TO BE OUT OF OUR
HOUSE.
WE ONLY GOT OUR KIDS, OUR
ANIMALS, A LITTLE BIT OF
PICTURES AND OF PAPERWORK WE
REALLY NEEDED.
IT WAS HARD.
>> IT IS A LOT NOW.
JUST MOVED IN THREE MONTHS AGO.
WE'RE JUST GETTING ON OUR FEET,
GETTING STABLE.
>> ADDING TO THE SENSE OF ALARM,
CREWS ONLY ABLE TO CONTAIN THE
FIRE BY ABOUT 7%.
AS YOU MAY KNOW.
IT HAS BEEN A VERY ACTIVE
WILDFIRE SEASON WITH 50 BURNING
CURRENTLY ACROSS WESTERN STATES,
YOU SEE ON THE MAP.
REPORTS DENSE SMOKE FROM SOME
FIRES IS POURING INTO RENO,
NEVADA, CREATING MAJOR HEALTH
CONCERNS.
VISIBILITY SO BAD THERE THEY
CAN'T CARE FLIGHT AMBULANCES IN
THE AIR.
DOMINIC DID I NA TALLY HAS MORE.
>> Reporter: YOU'RE LOOKING AT A
MASSIVE VOLUME OF SMOKE.
IT BURST OUT IN THE PAST FEW
MOMENTS.
WE WERE SEEING THE ORANGE GLOW
OF THE FIRE ON THE EDGE OF THE
CITY.
THIS IS THE MOMENT THE FIRE
CRUCIAL HAVE BEEN ABSOLUTELY
DREADING THE PAST 48 HOURS.
THEY HAVE BEEN MAKING MAKE OR
BREAK EFFORTS TO PROTECT THIS
CITY FROM THE FIRE AS IT COMES
IN.
THE FIRE IS BURNING TWO
DIFFERENT COLORS, WHITE IS FUEL,
SO HOT.
THE GREEN FUEL IS PUTTING BLACK
WAVES INTO THE AIR.
AIR VURZ IS GOING OVER.
HAD A MASSIVE AIR TANKER, FOUR
PROP PLANE LOOKING TO SEE WHERE
IT SHOULD PUT RETARDANT.
ABOUT 16,000 HOMES HERE OR
SORRY, 1600 HOMES THAT NEED
PROTECTING.
2,000 FIRE CREW.
SOME MEMBERS OF THE CREW FROM
SUNNYVALE AND PALO ALTO ARE
LOOKING AT THAT COLUMN OF SMOKE,
EXTREMELY WORRIED.
A FEW COLLEAGUES MOMENTS BEFORE
WE CAME ON AIR LEFT IN THE FIRE
TRUCK, HEADED IN THEIR
DIRECTION.
YOU KNOW AN EXTRA 2,000
FIREFIGHTERS WERE BROUGHT IN
YESTERDAY TO PROTECT THIS TOWN.
ALMOST 8 FIREFIGHTERS PER HOME.
WITH EASTERLY WINDS COMING IN
AND PUSHING IN THIS DIRECTION,
THIS REALLY IS NOT WHAT THEY
WANTED TO SEE.
BUT THEY KNEW WINDS WOULD BE A
RISK, GOING ANYTHING FROM 10 TO
40 MILES PER HOUR GOING OVER THE
HILLSIDE.
THAT KIND OF WIND GUARANTEES HOW
MANY LINES THEY CREATE, THE FIRE
CAN JUMP THE LINES AND THAT WILL
BE DEVASTATING FOR THE TOWN.
BACK TO YOU.
>> THE FIRST IMAGE WAS FROM YOUR
OWN CAMERA.
I KNEW FROM MY NOTES YOU WOULD
BE LIVE NEAR IT.
YOU'RE FAIRLY CLOSE TO IT.
CAN YOU SMELL THE SMOKE?
>> OH, YES.
IT HAS BEEN THICK THROUGH THE
DAY.
YOU CAN FEEL IT ON THE BACK OF
OUR THROAT, COATING LIKE A
POWDER, IN OUR NOSTRILS.
IT IS QUITE DIFFICULT.
BLUE SKY ABOVE IT ONE SIDE AND
SMOKE KEEPS WASPING IN.
I HAVE TO SAY THIS DOES NOT LOOK
GOOD FOR THE TOWN.
THERE'S ALREADY ADVISORY,
EVACUATION.
LOOKS LIKE ANY TIME SOON A
MANDATORY EVACUATION.
WE WERE TIPPED OFF BY CAL FIRE
SAYING THAT PROBABLY WILL HAPPEN
TODAY.
LOOKING AT THE SIZE AND THE RACE
IT IS APPROACHING, I WOULDN'T BE
SURPRISED IF EVACUATION WAS PUT
IN IN MINUTES, CERTAINLY IN A
MATTER OF HOURS.
>> THAT WILL EFFECT EVERYBODY,
INCLUDING YOU.
REAL QUICKLY, BEFORE I LET YOU
GO, MASSIVE HISTORIC FIRE.
FROM WHAT I AM READING, THEY'RE
NOT TRYING TO PUT IT OUT
EXACTLY, THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO
DIVERT IT?
>> Reporter: IT IS TOO BIG.
UNCONTROLLABLE WINDS, VERY
DIFFICULT.
THEY'LL CREATE DIVISION LINES,
TRY TO DIRECT IT NORTH AND EAST,
AWAY FROM THE POPULATED AREAS.
ONCE THEY CAN DO THAT, THEY WILL
KNOW THE DIRECTION THE FIRE WILL
GO IN.
IT IS EASIER TO CONTAIN, EASIER
TO RING FENCE.
>> DOMINIC DI-NATALE SHOWING US
THE SMOKE, CAUSING THE CREW
TECHNICAL DIFFICULTIES.
WE LOST HIM AT THE END.
AS HE SAID, THEY'RE PROBABLY
GOING TO MOVE NOW.
YOU COULD SEE THE FLAMES, WELL,
NOT THE FLAMES BUT THE SMOKE.
WE WILL STAY ON THIS, GO BACK TO
HIM LATER IN THE HOUR, POSSIBLY
BY PHONE IF WE HAVE TO.
>>> RIGHT NOW, AN EMERGENCY IN
THE SKY IS PROMPTING A QUICK
REACTION FROM A COCKPIT.
WHAT FORCED A FLIGHT WITH NEARLY
200 PEOPLE ON BOARD TO GET BACK
ON THE GROUND AS FAST AS THEY
COULD.
>>> AND REMEMBERING A LIFE CUT
SHORT.
AN AUSTRALIAN STUDENT ATHLETE
LIVING OUT HIS DREAM IN AMERICA,
GUNNED DOWN BY THREE TEENAGERS
WHILE JOGGING.
POLICE SAY THEY DID IT BECAUSE
THEY WERE BORED.
NOW PAYING TRIBUTE HERE AND DOWN
UNDER.
STAY CLOSE.
[ Male Announcer ]
FREQUENT HEARTBURN?
THE CHOICE IS YOS.
CHALKY...
NOT CHALKY.
TEMPORARY...
24 HOUR.
LOTS OF TABLETS...
ONE PILL.
YOU DECIDE.
PREVENT ACID
WITH PREVACID 24HR.
HUMANS.
EVEN WHEN WE CROSS OUR t's
AND DOT OUR i's,
WE STILL RUN INTO PROBLEMS.
NAMELY, OTHER HUMANS.
WHICH IS WHY
AT LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE,
TO POLICIES COME
WITH NEW CAR REPLACEMENT
AND ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS
IF YOU QUALIFY.
SEE WHAT EE COMES STANDARD
AT LIBERTYMUTUAL.COM.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT'S YOUR POLICY?
it's a reality check.
I'd be sitting there
with my friends
who had their Verizon phones
and I'd be sitting there like
"mine's still loading!"
I couldn't get email.
I couldn't stream movies.
I couldn't upload
any of our music.
That's when I decided
to switch.
Now that I'm on Verizon,
everything moves fast.
With Verizon,
I have that reliability.
I'm completely happy
with Verizon.
Verizon's 4G LTE
is the most reliable
and in more places than
any other 4G network.
Period.
That's powerful.
Verizon.
Get the Nokia Lumia 928
for free.
IN THIS CORNER,
THE REIGNING LASAGNA DISH,
THE BIG CHEESE.
AND IN THIS CORNER,
THE BEST GENERATION
OF DAWN POWER,
PLATINUM!
[ BELL DINGS ]
HERE WE GO!
[ Female Announcer ]
DAWN PLATINUM POWER CLEAN'S
MICRO-SCRUBBING ENZYMES
GIVE YOU THE POWER OF AN
OVERNIGHT SOAK IN 3 MINUTES,
AND 3 TIMES MORE
EVERYDAY
GREASE CLEANING
INGREDIENTS.
FOR ALL YOUR DISHES.
SO IF YOU LIKE DAWN,
YOU'LL LOVE PLATINUM.
[ Sponge ] THE CHAMPION!
[ Female Announcer ]
DAWN PLATINUM DOES EVEN MORE...
[ Sponge ] SO IT'S NOT A CHORE.
[ Female Announcer ]
DAWN PLATINUM DOES EVEN MORE...
ALWAYS GO THE EXTRA MILE.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE,
I DID MY RESEARCH.
MY DOCTOR AND I
WENT WITH AXIRON,
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDITIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARG OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
E ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
>>> JUST IN.
DELTA REPORTS AN EMERGENCY
LANDING IN ALABAMA.
IT WAS ENROUTE FROM CANCUN TO
MEXICO.
THE PROBLEM SPARKED BY A BURNED
OUT FLUORESCENT LIGHT.
EVERYBODY IS OFF THE PLANE AND
SAFE WE ARE TOLD.
>>> A MEMORIAL SERVICE HELD
TODAY FOR A 22-YEAR-OLD
AUSTRALIAN MAN GUNNED DOWN
JOGGING IN OKLAHOMA.
FRIENDS, FAMILY, FORMER
TEAMMATES OF CHRISTOPHER LANE
GATHERED ON THE BASEBALL FIELD
IN MELBOURNE WHERE HE USED TO
PLAY.
A WREATH, FLOWERS, BASEBALL CAPS
PLACED ON THE DIAMOND.
A MINUTE OF SILENCE BEFORE RED
AND BLACK BALLOONS WERE RELEASED
IN HIS MEMORY.
>> TODAY IS PART OF THE GRIEVING
PROCESS.
IT IS IMPORTANT FOR OUR CLUBS TO
BE AROUND EACH OTHER TO MAKE
SURE THAT EVERYONE, INCLUDING
THE FAMILY, FEELS THE SUPPORT
AND MAKE SURE THAT THEY FEEL
LIKE THEY'RE NOT ALONE.
>> LANE WAS STUDYING IN THE
UNITED STATES ON A BASEBALL
SCHOLARSHIP.
THREE TEENAGERS ARE ACCUSED OF
HIS MURDER.
AUTHORITIES SAY ONE OF THEM SAID
THEY SHOT HIM BECAUSE THEY WERE
BORED.
NOW WE'RE LEARNING A LOT OF NEW
REACTION TO THAT MURDER.
PETER DOOCY IN WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: WHEN THEY CALLED
JAMES EDWARDS INTO THE STATION
TO BE CHARGED WITH MURDERING
AUSTRALIAN BASEBALL PLAYER CHRIS
LANE, EDWARDS DANCED AND DID
TWIRLS AND TREATED THE ENTIRE
PROCESS LIKE A JOKE.
THIS IS THE SAME SUSPECT WHO
TWEETED IN APRIL, QUOTE, 90% OF
WHITE PEOPLE ARE NASTY,
#HATETHEM.
BUT STEVENS COUNTY DISTRICT
ATTORNEY SAYS RIGHT NOW RACE IS
NOT SEEN AS A MOTIVE.
SO HE IS IS NOT INVESTIGATING A
HATE CRIME.
>> THERE'S NOTHING INSIDE THE
FILES AND THE AUDIO AND REPORTS
THAT WE'VE BEEN GIVEN THAT WOULD
LEAD US TO BELIEVE THAT
CHRISTOPHER LANE WAS KILLED
SIMPLY BECAUSE OF HIS
NATIONALITY OR BECAUSE OF HIS
RACE.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT OBAMA HAS
SO FAR BEEN QUIETER ABOUT CHRIS
LANE'S MURDER THAN TEENAGER
TRAYVON MARTIN'S DEATH.
OKLAHOMA'S GOVERNOR MARY FALLON
SAID IT WOULD BE NICE IF HE
SPOKE UP.
>> IT WOULD BE A NICE GESTURE TO
DO SO, ESPECIALLY SINCE
AUSTRALIA HAS EXPRESSED THEIR
SENTIMENT AS TO THE MURDER
ITSELF.
>> THE D.A. SAYS EXPECT TO SEE
THEM IN COURT IN OCTOBER.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> LAST NIGHT ON THE FOX
REPORT, REMEMBER WE TOLD YOU
SOME EMPLOYEES AT THE NSA USED
THE GOVERNMENT SPY GEAR TO LOOK
IN ON THEIR LOVE INTERESTS.
NOW A NEW REPORT SAYS THE AGENCY
ALLEGEDLY TARGETED THE UNITED
NATIONS.
>>> ALSO, TWO WOULD BE ROBBERS
BURST INTO A RESTAURANT AND RUN
RIGHT INTO A BIG SURPRISE, AN
EMPLOYEE, ON A MISSION.
♪
For a strong bag that
grips the can...
get Glad ForceFlex.
Small change,
big difference.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
NO, IT'S ONLY 15 CALORIES.
[ Male Announcer ]
WITH REDDI WIP,
FRUIT NEVER SOUNDED
MORE DELICIOUS.
MMM.
[ Male Announcer ]
WITH 15 CALORIES PER SERVING
AND REAL CREAM,
THE SOUND OF REDDI WIP
IS THE SOUND OF JOY.
AND THEN ANOTHER. AND ANOTHER.
AND IF YOU DO IT.
AND YOUR FRIENDS DO IT.
AND THEIR FRIENDS DO IT...
SOON WE'LL BE WALKING
OUR WAY TO AWARENESS, SUPPORT
AND AN END TO
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
AND THAT? THAT WOULD BE BIG.
GRAB YO FRIENDS AND FAMILY
AND START A TEAM TODAY.
REGISTER AT ALZ.ORG
>>> A NEW REPORT ABOUT THE
NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY SPYING,
ONE THAT COULD STRAIN RELATIONS
BETWEEN WASHINGTON AND OUR
ALLIES.
GERMANY'S WEEKLY MAGAZINE CLAIMS
THE NSA HAS BUGGED THE U.N.
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK CITY.
THE PUBLICATION CITES SECRET
DOCUMENTS OBTAINED BY EDWARD
SNOWDEN, FORMER NSA CONTRACTOR
LIVING AS A U.S. FUGITIVE INSIDE
RUSSIA.
THEY REPORT THE SECRET FILES
REVEAL HOW THE U.S. BUGGED SOME
80 EMBASSIES AND SPIED ON THE
EUROPEAN UNION AND U.N. NUCLEAR
WATCHDOG, INTERNATIONAL ATOMIC
ENERGY AGENCY.
THEY CLAIM THE SURVEILLANCE HAD
LITTLE OR NOTHING TO DO WITH
WARDING OFF TERROR.
>>> FORMER EGYPTIAN PRESIDENT
HOSNI MUBARAK WAS BACK IN A
CAIRO COURTROOM EARLIER TODAY,
HIS FIRST APPEARANCE BEFORE A
JUDGE SINCE BEING RELEASED FROM
PRISON LAST WEEK.
THE EX-LEADER, 85 YEARS OLD,
CURRENTLY LIVING IN A MILITARY
HOSPITAL.
MUBARAK IS FACING RETRIAL ON
CHARGES OF FAILING TO STOP THE
KILLINGS OF PROTESTERS DURING
THE 2011 UPRISING THAT LED TO
HIS DOWNFALL.
SINCE THEN, AS YOU KNOW, WE HAVE
BEEN REPORTING EGYPT HAS BEEN
PLAGUED BY GROWING ACTS OF
VIOLENCE WHERE MUSLIM
BROTHERHOOD SUPPORTERS ARE
TARGETING CHRISTIANS, HOLDING
THEM PARTIALLY RESPONSIBLE FOR
THE DEPARTURE OF THE MOST RECENT
PRESIDENT, MOHAMED MORSI.
BUT THOUSANDS OF MILES AWAY,
EGYPTIANS OF BOTH FAITHS FOUND A
PLACE TO PUT ASIDE RELIGIOUS
DIFFERENCES AND CO-EXIST IN
PEACE AND FRIENDSHIP.
BRIAN YENNIS JOINS US FROM THE
NEW YORK BUREAU.
>> HEADLINES READ OF CHAOS,
BLOODSHED, DEEP DIVISION.
6,000 MILES AWAY, THEY HOPE TO
INSPIRE HOPE AND DEMOCRACY.
>> WE LIVE TOGETHER IN PEACE, WE
DON'T PRETEND, WE DON'T DO IT,
IT COMES NATURALLY.
>> Reporter: COPTIC CHRISTIAN
HAS LIVED IN JERSEY CITY THE
LAST 27 YEARS.
>> YOU HAVE VERY FRIENDLY
RELATIONSHIP WITH OUR BROTHERS,
THE MUSLIMS, THEY COME INTO
OUR --
>> Reporter: ATTACKS ON MORE
THAN 40 COPTIC CHRISTIAN
CHURCHES AND DEATHS OF NEARLY A
THOUSAND EGYPTIANS STRAIN THE
COMMUNITY.
>> THERE HAS BEEN A LOT OF AGONY
AND PEOPLE VERY ALARMED WITH
THIS, WHO ARE PRAYING.
>> Reporter: PRAYING FOR PEOPLE
LIKE COPTIC CHRISTIANS, TWO OF
HIS COUSINS KILLED LAST WEEK.
HE IS ANGRY, BUT OLD AND NEW
TENSIONS THREATEN TO ERUPT, SOME
WELL AND OTHER OPENINGS
IMMIGRANTS REFUSE TO GIVE IN.
>> WHAT WE NEED IS THE REAL
JUSTICE TAKING PLACE, REAL
DEMOCRACY TAKING PLACE, THE REAL
FREEDOM TAKING PLACE.
>> THE MUSLIMS ARE -- THE MUSLIM
BROTHERHOOD, THEY COME AND TRY
TO DEFEND THE CHURCH.
>> Reporter: THIS MUSLIM LEADER
HOPES JERSEY CITY CAN INSPIRE
EGYPT TO KEEP RALLYING FOR
DEMOCRACY.
>> WE WANT TO GIVE EXAMPLE OF
HOW THE EGYPTIAN COMMUNITY LIVE
IN AMERICA AND HOW THEY
UNDERSTAND EACH OTHER.
>> A COMMUNITY STANDING STRONG
AS THE WORLD WATCHES EGYPT ON
THE BRINK.
HARRIS?
>> BRYAN, THANK YOU.
>>> CRUISE MISSILES LIKE THE
ONES I AM ABOUT TO SHOW YOU ARE
ONE OF THE WEAPONS IN OUR
ARSENAL.
ONE LAWMAKER SAYS THE U.S.
SHOULD BE PREPARED TO USE THEM
AGAINST THE ASSAD REGIME IN THE
WAKE OF CHEMICAL ATTACK AGAINST
HIS OWN PEOPLE.
BUT OUR NEXT GUEST SAYS THE
GOVERNMENT MAY HAVE IT WRONG
WHEN THEY SAY WHO SHOULD FEEL
THE BRUNT OF AMERICAN MILITARY
MIGHT.
>>> MANY PEOPLE THINK THEY'RE
COOL, SOME PEOPLE THINK THEY'RE
INVASIVE.
EITHER WAY, IT IS BEST IF A
SMALL DRONE STAYS IN THE AIR
WHEN HOVERING OVER A CROWD.
THIS ONE DIDN'T STAY IN THE AIR,
CAME DOWN VERY UNEXPECTEDLY.
♪
[ CRASHING ]
[ Male Announcer ] WHEN YOUR
FAVORITE FOOD STARTS A FIGHT,
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
AND GOES TO WORK IN SECONDS.
♪ TUM, TUM TUM TUM TUMS!
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
♪
(VO) Purina Cat Chow.
50 years of feeding great
relationship
FIRST WAIT TILL SUMMER.
THEN GET THE CARS READY.
NOW ADD THE DODGE PART.
♪
THE DODGE SUMMER
CLEARANCE EVENT.
RIGHT NOW GET 0% FINANCING FOR
TO 72 MONTHS
AND NO PAYMENTS FOR 90 DAYS ON
ALL DODGE VEHICLES.
Peace of mind is important when
So we provide IT services you
bucan rely on.
With CenturyLink as your trusted
IT partner,
you'll experience reliable
uptime for the network and
services you depend on.
Multi-layered security solutions
keep your information safe, and
secure.
And responsive dedicated support
meets your needs, and eases your
mind.
CenturyLink.
Your link to what's next.
PEOPLE WAIT FOR THIS PROMOTION
ALL YEAR LONG.
AND NOW THERE ARE ENDLESS WAYS
TO LOVE IT...
FROM CRISPY TO SPICY TO SAVORY.
[ Man ]
YOU CANNOT MAKE A BAD CHOICE.
[ Male Announcer ]
RED LOBSTER'S ENDLESS SHRIMP!
AS CH AS YOU LIKE,
Y WAY YOU LIKE!
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR SHRIMP.
AND YOU CAN EAT IT, TOO.
[ Male Announcer ] TRY OUR NEW
SOY WASABI GRILLED SHRIMP
OR CLASSIC GARLIC
SHMP SCAMPI.
ALL JUST $15.99
FOR A LIMITED TIME.
IT'S GONNA BE A HIT THIS YEAR.
[ Male Announcer ]
RED LOBSTER'S ENDLESS
SHRI IS NOW!
WE WOULD NEVERISS
ENDLESS SHRIMP.
[ Male Announcer ]
BUT IT WON'T LAST FOREVER.
SO COME
AND SEA FOOD DIFFERENTLY.
SEE, I KNEW TESTOSTERONE
COULD AFFECT SEX DRIVE,
BUT NOT ENERGY
OR EVEN MY MOOD.
THAT'S WHEN I TALKED
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD TESTS...
SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.
THAT'S IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.
[ Male Announcer ]
TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T
HAVE ANDROGEL
1.62% TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED
TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY
INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.
WOMEN AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WITH APPLICATION SITES.
DISCONTINUANDROGEL
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED SIGNS
OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,
WHICH MAY INCLUDE
CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE,
POSSIBLY DUE
TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER
OR WHO HAVE OR MIGHT HAVE
PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING,
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
WORSENING
OF AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,
POSSIBLE INCREASED RIS
OF PROSTATE CANCER,
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING
OF ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY,
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS,
PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP,
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICAL CONDITION
AND MEDICATIONS,
ESPECIALLY IULIN,
CORTICOSTEROIDS, OR MEDICINES
TO DECREASE BLOOD CLOTTING.
IN A CLINICAL STUDY, OVER 80%
OF TREATED MEN HAD THEIR
T LEVELS RESTORED TO NORMAL.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.
CHANGE YOUR NUMBER. TURN IT UP.
ANDROGEL 1.62%.
>>> A REMARKABLE STORY FROM
TEXAS ABOUT A REUNION INVOLVING
A VIETNAM WAR VETERAN AND
SOMETHING CLOSE TO HIS HEART.
IN 1968, U.S. MARINE LAN EE
MARTIN SON WAS SEVERELY INJURED
IN A MINE FIELD IN VIETNAM.
SIX FELLOW MARINES WERE KILLED.
DURING HIS LONG ROAD TO
RECOVERY, HIS DOG TAGS WERE
SOMEHOW LOST.
43 YEARS LATER AN AUSTRALIAN
SCHOOL TEACHER TREKKING THROUGH
THE VIETNAM BRUSH STUMBLED UPON
THE SAME DOG TAGS THAT MAN
COULDN'T FIND.
THANKS TO THE EFFORTS OF GOOD
SAMARITANS, HIS LONG LOST DOG
TAGS ARE BACK IN HIS POSSESSION.
>> I THOUGHT MAYBE I COULD FIND
HIM, POST IT BACK TO HIM IN THE
MAIL TO AMERICA.
I NEVER DREAMED THAT THIS WHOLE
THING WOULD END UP LIKE THIS.
>> IT WAS VERY OVERWHELMING.
I STILL DON'T KNOW WHY.
JUST A PIECE OF ALUMINUM, BUT I
HAD TO HAVE IT A LONG TIME.
>>> I AM HARRIS FAULKNER, THIS
IS THE FOX REPORT.
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR, TIME FOR THE
TOP NEWS.
A SENIOR U.S. OFFICIAL SAYS
THERE'S LITTLE DOUBT CHEMICAL
WEAPONS WERE USED BY THE SYRIAN
REGIME AGAINST ITS OWN PEOPLE.
HUNDREDS DIED IN LAST WEEK'S
ATTACK.
TODAY, THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT
CLAIMED THEY WILL ALLOW U.N.
INSPECTORS TO LOOK AT THE SITE
IT HAPPENED.
U.S. OFFICIALS SAY AT THIS POINT
IT IS PROBABLY TOO LATE.
ALL OF THIS HAPPENING AS
LAWMAKERS CALL FOR LIMITED
MILITARY RESPONSE, AND OTHER
WESTERN POWERS, INCLUDING
BRITAIN AND FRANCE EXPRESS GRAVE
CONCERN.
AMBASSADOR JOHN BOLTON, FORMER
AMBASSADOR TO THE U.N. AND FOX
NEWS CONTRIBUTOR.
DO YOU WAIT FOR THE INSPECTORS
TO TELL US WHAT THEY FOUND THERE
AT THE DEATH SITE OR IS THE
WHITE HOUSE STALLING FOR TIME TO
MAKE A DECISION?
>> I DON'T THINK THE U.N.
INSPECTORS WILL FIND MUCH OF
ANYTHING.
THE SYRIAN REGIME PROBABLY
CLEANED UP THE SITES, MADE THEM
MBIGUOUS THAT
NOBODY CAN TELL WHO USE THE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
THEY MAY HAVE HAD RUSSIAN
ASSISTANCE TO DO THAT.
I THINK THE SYRIANS THOUGHT THEY
WERE BUYING TIME AND MAY YET,
BUT THE RHETORIC FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE IS UNDOUBTEDLY STEPPED UP.
OF COURSE, WE HAVE BEEN DOWN
THAT ROAD BEFORE AS WELL.
I THINK THE REAL PROBLEM FOR THE
UNITED STATES IS THAT THE
ADMINISTRATION IS REACTING MORE
OUT OF POLITICAL CONCERN THAN
FROM STRATEGIC THINKING.
THE PRESIDENT LOOKED VERY
FOOLISH, VERY WEAK SIX MONTHS
AGO WHEN CHEMICAL WEAPONS WERE
FIRST REPORTED USED ON A LARGE
SCALE, CROSSING THE RED LINE
THAT THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF DREW
A YEAR AGO AND THE PRESIDENT DID
NOTHING.
NOW YOU HAVE AN EVEN MORE
EGREGIOUS USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS AND HE THINKS HE NEEDS
TO DO SOMETHING, BUT HE CLEARLY
DOESN'T KNOW WHAT OR FOR WHAT
PURPOSE.
>> THE PROBLEM IS THE RED LINE
IS THAT IT IS RED, FEW PEOPLE
WILL EVER FORGET IT.
TODAY, AMBASSADOR RAND ISSUED
THE FIRST OF TWO THREATS WE
HEARD, THE OTHER COMING FROM
RUSSIA, GET TO THAT IN A MOMENT.
IRAN SAID WE BETTER NOT TOUCH
SYRIA, PARAPHRASING IT.
SHOULD THAT BE DETERRENT FOR US?
>> NO, THE SYRIANS THINK
PRESIDENT OBAMA IS WEAK AND ARE
TRYING TO BULLY HIM.
IN THIS CONTEXT IT WILL HAVE THE
OPPOSITE EFFECT AND CONVINCE HIM
HE HAS TO DO SOMETHING, LOB A
COUPLE CRUISE MISSILES OR MORE
INTO SYRIA TO PROVE HE HAS,
QUOTE, UNQUOTE, DONE SOMETHING.
THE REAL ISSUE HERE IS WHAT TO
DO ABOUT IRAN.
LET'S FACE IT, THE ASSAD REGIME
AFTER TWO YEARS OF CONFLICT
WOULD NOT BE IN POWER IF IT WERE
NOT FOR RUSSIA AND IRAN, AND
PRIMARILY IRAN.
LOOKING AT SYRIA IS LOOKING AS
TRAGIC AS IT IS IS LOOKING IN A
STRATEGIC SENSE AT A SECONDARY
ISSUE.
THE REAL PROBLEM IS THE REGIME
IN IRAN.
THAT'S WHERE WE OUGHT TO DIRECT
OUR ATTENTION.
>> LET'S TALK ON THE SUBJECT
MATTER OF OTHER COUNTRIES
ISSUING THREATS TO AMERICA,
SHOULD IT GET INVOLVED OUTSIDE
THE BOUNDS OF THE UNITED
NATIONS.
NO ONE SAID WE WOULD DO THAT.
BUT RUSSIA TODAY ISSUING A
WARNING THAT THERE WOULD BE
GRAVE CONSEQUENCES IN THAT
REGION TO THE SECURITY IN THE
MIDDLE EAST, IF WE SHOULD
SUDDENLY USE OUR MILITARY WITH
REGARD TO SYRIA.
IN FACT, WE HAVE A LITTLE BIT
FROM A LAWMAKER, MIKE McCALL,
REPUBLICAN OUT OF TEXAS, WHO
TALKS ABOUT THAT TENUOUS
RELATIONSHIP NOW WITH RUSSIA.
LET'S WATCH THAT AND THEN WE'LL
TALK MORE.
>> THE RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE
WHITE HOUSE AND THE PUTIN
ADMINISTRATION IS SO BAD AND
LACKS SO MUCH CREDIBILITY THAT I
THINK IT IS VERY DIFFICULT.
WE HAVE A SHARED INTEREST.
I BELIEVE THE RUGS DON'T WANT
CHEMICAL WEAPONS USED, AS DOES
THE UNITED STATES, SO WE DO HAVE
AN OPPORTUNITY, I HOPE THE
PRESIDENT WILL TRY TO TAKE
ADVANTAGE OF.
>> AND THE COULD YOU TELL
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN THERE.
CURIOUS OF YOUR THOUGHTS.
>> I THINK THEY THINK OBAMA IS
WEAK AND CAN BULLY HIM, PUSHING
ON ONE OTHER BUTTON THAT THE
PRESIDENT HIGHLIGHTED LAST WEEK
WHEN HE WONDERED WHAT HIS
INTERNATIONAL AUTHORITY WAS TO
LAUNCH MILITARY ACTION.
AND THINKING SPECIFICALLY OF THE
U.N. SECURITY COUNCIL WHERE
RUSSIA HAS A VETO.
FRANKLY, I DON'T THINK THE
UNITED STATES SHOULD CARE ONE
WIT WHETHER WE HAVE A SECURITY
COUNCIL RESOLUTION OR NOT.
THIS IS THINKING IN A EUROPEAN
WAY, WHO HAS AUTHORIZED ME TO DO
THIS, AS OPPOSED TO THINKING IN
THE TRADITIONAL AMERICAN WAY,
WHO IS PROHIBITING ME FROM DOING
THIS.
WHILE I THINK WE OUGHT TO
DISREGARD IT, I THINK THE
RUSSIANS KNOW THE PRESIDENT'S
PSYCHOLOGY AND THAT'S WHAT
THEY'RE TRYING TO EFFECT.
>> CHAT ROOMS, THEY'RE SAYING
OUR NATION SHOULDN'T BE
INVOLVED, SOME OF THEM.
YOU ALSO SAID WE SHOULDN'T BE
INVOLVED THERE THE WAY WE ARE,
SYRIA IS A SECONDARY ISSUE.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
>> AS I SAID, THE ASSAD REGIME
WOULD NOT BE IN POWER BUT FOR
IRAN, AND WHILE PEOPLE SAY THIS
IS A PLACE WHERE WE CAN DEFEAT
IRAN, THIS IS EFFECTIVELY MUCH
LESS IMPORTANT THAN IRAN'S
NUCLEAR WEAPONS PROGRAM.
AND I'LL TELL YOU SOMETHING
RIGHT NOW.
IF THE PRESIDENT DOESN'T ACT
WITH MASSIVE FORCE IN SYRIA, IF
IT IS JUST A SLAP ON THE WRIST
TO THE ASSAD REGIME, WHICH MANY
ARE PREDICTING, I THINK THE
LESSON IRAN DRAWS FROM THAT WE
BETTER GET OUR NUCLEAR WEAPONS
CAPABILITY IMMEDIATELY BECAUSE
THEN WE WILL BE IMMUNE TO AN
AMERICAN SLAP ON THE WRIST.
ON THE OTHER HAND, IF THE
PRESIDENT DOES USE MASSIVE FORCE
TO CHANGE THE BALANCE OF FORCES
WITHIN SYRIA ITSELF, IT COULD
WELL RESULT IN THE OPPOSITION
TAKING POWER, WHICH I DON'T
THINK IS IN AMERICA'S INTEREST
EITHER.
THAT'S WHY I STRESS I DON'T
THINK THE PRESIDENT KNOWS HIS
OWN MIND.
I DON'T THINK HE KNOWS WHAT HIS
STRATEGY IS.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT ALL OF THE
AGONIZING IS ABOUT.
>> VERY INTERESTING.
YOU PAINT SUCH DIFFERENT
SCENARIOS THERE.
AND I'LL CHANGE TOPICS JUST
SLIGHTLY BECAUSE I WANT TO ASK
YOUR OPINION ABOUT THIS.
SAMANTHA POWER HAS TAKEN YOUR
OLD POST AS U.S. AMBASSADOR AT
THE U.N.
SHE WAS AWAY FOR PERSONAL
REASONS WE READ THIS WEEK,
MISSED THAT VERY IMPORTANT
EMERGENCY MEETING AT THE UNITED
NATIONS.
IT WAS ON SYRIA.
HOW UNUSUAL IS IT THAT THE
AMBASSADOR WOULD MISS A MEETING
LIKE THAT?
>> WELL, I THINK IT IS OKAY FOR
PEOPLE TO TAKE VACATIONS.
I THINK THAT'S FINE.
I DIDN'T TAKE A VACATION WHEN I
STARTED AT THE BEGINNING OF
AUGUST OF 2005, BUT MAYBE I'M A
WORKAHOLIC.
I THINK SHE WILL BE BACK IN TIME
FOR ANYTHING ELSE THAT HAPPENS,
GIVEN THAT PUBLICITY.
>> SO NO SIGNIFICANCE IN TERMS
OF HOW WE ARE MOVING FORWARD OR
ANYTHING LIKE THAT?
>> NOTHING OF SIGNIFICANCE ON
SYRIA IS GOING TO HAPPEN AT THE
UNITED NATIONS ANYWAY.
SHE PROBABLY COULD STAY IN
IRELAND ANOTHER COUPLE WEEKS
FROM THAT PERSPECTIVE.
>> THAT IS BLUNT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT SOMETHING
ENTIRELY DIFFERENT.
CHANGING TOPICS TO NEW
INFORMATION WE HAVE GOTTEN ABOUT
THE NSA SPYING, NOT JUST ON
MILLIONS OF AMERICAN CITIZENS AS
WE LEARNED ABOUT FROM EDWARD
SNOWDEN, THE U.S. CONTRACTOR NOW
A FUGITIVE INSIDE RUSSIA, BUT
THE UNITED NATIONS, THAT THEY
WERE BEING BUGGED.
UP TO 80 EMBASSIES AROUND THE
WORLD.
THAT'S GOT TO POSE SOME QUESTION
I WOULD IMAGINE THE MINDS OF OUR
ALLIES.
YOUR THOUGHTS ON IT?
>> THE DER SPIEGEL ARTICLE SAYS
ESPIONAGE AGAINST THE UNITED
NATIONS TOOK PLACE IN 2012,
WHICH I FIND DELICIOUSLY IRONIC
THAT THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION IS
SPYING ON THE UNITED NATIONS.
HERE IS WHAT I THINK.
ANY GATHERING OF FOREIGNERS IS A
LEGITIMATE TARGET FOR AMERICAN
ESPIONAGE, UNLESS WE HAVE
AGREEMENT THAT PRECLUDES US FROM
DOING IT.
AND ANY FOREIGN GOVERNMENT
ABSENT SUCH AN AGREEMENT THAT
DOESN'T THINK WE MAY BE SPYING
ON THEM DOESN'T LIVE IN THE REAL
WORLD.
THAT'S THE WAY IT IS, DOESN'T
BOTHER ME AT ALL.
I THINK THIS SHOWS A FUNDAMENTAL
POINT THAT SNOWDEN AND HIS MEDIA
FRIENDS ARE TRYING TO PROVE.
NOT TO AWAKEN AMERICANS ABOUT
POTENTIAL VIOLATIONS OF PRIVACY
BUT TO HURT THE UNITED STATES
INTERNATIONALLY.
WHILE MOST AMERICANS COULDN'T
CARE LESS IF WE'RE SPYING ON THE
U.N., IN MANY OTHER COUNTRIES,
THAT'S ALMOST SACK RIL AJ.
THAT'S THE POINT OF THIS COMING
OUT IN GERMANY.
>> AMBASSADOR BOLTON, WE
APPRECIATE YOUR CANDOR AND
EXPERIENCE.
THANK YOU AS ALWAYS FOR JOINING
US.
>> THANK YOU, HARRIS.
GLAD TO DO IT.
>>> ROBBERS HIT A RESTAURANT,
THEY RAN INTO SOMETHING, A QUICK
THINKING EMPLOYEE.
STOPPED THE BANDITS IN THEIR
TRACKS AND PROTECTED PEOPLE
INSIDE.
THE REST OF THE STORY COMING UP.
>>> AND REMEMBERING A GREAT
AMERICAN HERO THROUGH MUSIC.
ONE YEAR SINCE THE DAY OF HIS
PASSING.
NASA'S TOUCHING TRIBUTE TO NEIL
ARMSTRONG.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
YOU'VE REACHED THE AGE
WHERE YOU DON'T BACK DOWN
FROM A CHALLENGE.
THIS IS THE AGE OF KNOWING
HOW TO MAKE THINGS HAPPEN.
SO, WHY LET
ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION
GET IN YOUR WAY?
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT VIAGRA.
20 MILLION MEN ALREADY HAVE.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF YOUR HEART
IS HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE VIAGRA IF YOU TAKE
NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN;
IT MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE DROP
IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
HEADACHE, FLUSHING,
UPSET STOMACH,
AND ABNORMAL VISION.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION
LASTING MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
STOP TAKING VIAGRA
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU EXPERIENCE
A SUDDEN DECREASE OR LOSS
IN VISION OR HEARING.
THIS IS THE AGE
OF TAKING ACTION.
VIAGRA.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR.
I put in the hours
and built a strong reputation
in the industry.
I set goals and worked
hard to meet them.
I've made my success happen.
So when it comes
to my investments,
I'm supposed to just hand it
over to a broker and back away?
That's not gonna happen.
AVO: When you work with a
Schwab financial consultant,
you'll get the guidance you need
with the control you want.
Talk to us today.
EVERY DAY WE'RE WORKING TO
AND TO KEEP OUR COMMITMENTS.
AND WE'VE MADE A BIG
COMMITMENT TO AMERICA.
BP SUPPORTS NEARLY
250,000 JOBS HERE.
THROUGH ALL OF OUR
ENERGY OPERATIONS,
WE INVEST MORE IN THE U.S. THAN
ANY OTHER PLACE IN THE WORLD.
IN FACT, WE'VE INVESTED
OVER $55 BILLION HERE
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS -
MAKING BP AMERICA'S
LARGEST ENERGY INVESTOR.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS
NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
>>> A PLANE HITS A GOLF COURSE
AND A COUPLE OF PEOPLE PLAYING
ON THE 12th HOLE DROP THEIR
CLUBS, RUN TO HELP.
OUR TOP STORY ON THIS FOX TRIP
ACROSS AMERICA.
CALIFORNIA.
THAT AIRCRAFT BROKE INTO PIECES
WHEN IT WENT DOWN IN A WOODED
AREA ON THE BIG MALONEY GOLF
COURSE NEXT TO THE SACRAMENTO
EXECUTIVE AIRPORT.
>> SAW THE PLANE, ON THE 12th
HOLE, SAW THE PLANE BANKING
HARD, I WAS LIKE MAN, THAT'S
LOW.
THEN A COUPLE SECONDS LATER HIT
THE TREES AND BOOM.
>> THEY RAN TO IT, STOPPING FOR
JUST A MOMENT WHEN THEY SMELLED
THE FUEL.
>> THIS MAN IS A PILOT, SAID
DON'T RUSH IN, COULD BE SMOKE,
FLAMES.
WE NOTICED THERE WAS NO SMOKE,
NO FLAMES, SO WE RUSHED IN.
>> THE TWO MEN ON BOARD
SURVIVED, ONE WAS UNCONSCIOUS.
>> WE MADE A DECISION JUST TO
GET HIM IN CASE IT GOES UP, GET
HIM OUT OF HERE.
>> SACRAMENTO FIRE DEPARTMENT
TREATED THE CRASH SCENE AS A
LEVEL TWO HAZMAT SITUATION
BECAUSE OF ALL OF THE FUEL.
BOTH THE PILOT AND PASSENGER
WILL BE OKAY.
>>> OHIO.
A CHURCH'S CHICKEN EMPLOYEE IN
AKRON TOOK ON TWO WOULD BE
ROBBERS, HOSING THEM DOWN WITH
HOT WATER.
ONE CUSTOMER CALLED HIM A HERO.
>> HE COULD HAVE CAME IN HERE,
SHOT THE PLACE UP, HURT
SOMEBODY.
HE USED WHATEVER HE HAD TO GET
THE JOB DONE, YOU KNOW.
SO NOW THE HOSPITALS NEED TO
LOOK FOR SOMEONE WITH A BIG BURN
ON THEM.
>> THEY BELIEVE THEY ROBBED A
FAST FOOD RESTAURANT A WEEK AGO.
>> GOING TO NEED A LOT OF COCOA
BUTTER.
>>> PENNSYLVANIA, A FAMILY
THOUGHT A WEST PHILADELPHIA
WOMAN WAS DEAD AND BURIED, EVEN
HELD A FUNERAL FOR HER.
TURNS OUT SHE'S ALIVE.
>> YOU KNOW HOW YOU FEEL YOU
JUST ABOUT TO GET OVER IT, THAT
SHE'S DEAD, AND THEN TRAVIS
COMES HERE WITH THE NEWS THAT
SHE'S ALIVE.
>> THE WOMAN WHO IS 50 YEARS OLD
WAS MISSING FOR A MONTH.
THEN A BODY WAS FOUND.
AUTHORITIES SHOWED HER SON
TRAVIS A PICTURE AND HE
CONFIRMED TO OFFICIALS IT WAS
HER.
BUT OBVIOUSLY IT WASN'T.
NOW A POLICE INVESTIGATION INTO
WHO WAS ACTUALLY BURIED.
>>> FLORIDA.
A SOLDIER IN AFGHANISTAN FOR
NEARLY A YEAR, RETURNING HOME,
GIVING HIS FOUR CHILDREN A HUGE
SURPRISE.
THEY THREW OUT FIRST PITCH AT
THE FORT MYERS GAME.
KIDS DIDN'T KNOW IT, THAT'S DAD
BEHIND THE CATCHER'S MASK.
>> HEY!
>> PLEASE WELCOME HIM!
>> JUST REALLY KIND OF BRINGS
HOME EVERYTHING THAT I'VE BEEN
WANTING FOR THE LAST TEN MONTHS.
>> THAT'S FOX WATCH ACROSS
AMERICA.
>>> GOOD-BYE, A YEAR LATER FOR
ONE OF THE NATION'S TOP SPACE
PIONEERS.
♪
>> MUSIC VIDEO CURRENTLY POSTED
ON NASA'S WEBSITE AND ON YOUTUBE
IN MEMORY OF ASTRONAUT NEIL
ARMSTRONG.
THE FIRST PERSON TO STEP FOOT ON
THE MOON DIED EXACTLY ONE YEAR
AGO TODAY.
HE WAS 82.
THE VIDEO IS A MIX OF ICONIC
PICTURES FROM ARMSTRONG'S
HISTORIC MOON LANDING IN JULY OF
1969, AND THAT BEAUTIFUL MUSIC,
TITLE TRANQUILITY BASE BY SONG
WRITER, GRAMMY NOMINEE, ERIC
GRACE.
REFERS TO THE NAME ARMSTRONG
GAVE THE SITE WHERE THE LUNAR
MODULE TOUCHED DOWN ALL THOSE
YEARS AGO.
>>> A BREWING CONTROVERSY, WHERE
A SMALL TIME COFFEE SALESMAN
CLAIMS HE IS ABOUT TO LOSE HIS
BUSINESS TO THE BIG DOGS HAS
SOME WAR VETERANS STEAMED.
>>> AND URBAN
THE MOST FREE RESEARCH REPORTS,
CUSTOMIZABLE CHARTS,
POWERFUL SCREENING TOOLS,
AND GUARANTEED 1-SECOND TRADES.
AND AT THE CENTER OF IT ALL
IS A SURPRISINGLY LOW PRICE --
JUST $7.95.
IN FACT, FIDELITY GIVES YOU
LOWER TRADE COMMISSIONS
THAN SCHWAB, TD AMERITRADE,
AND ETRADE.
I'M MONICA SANTIAGO
OF FIDELITY INVESTMENTS,
AND LOW FEES AND COMMISSIONS
ARE ANOTHER REASON
SERIOUS INVESTORS
ARE CHOOSING FIDELITY.
NOW GET 200 FREE TRADES
WHEN YOU OPEN AN ACCOUNT.
>>> THEY'RE MAD AT JOE OVER
COFFEE.
HE SAYS BEAN COUNTERS WANT TO
SHUT HIM DOWN, THEY SAY IT IS
ABOUT THE BOTTOM LINE.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT OBAMA
CALLS SMALL BUSINESSES THE
BACKBONE OF OUR ECONOMY.
>> THEY'RE THE FORCE BEHIND OUR
FREE ENTERPRISE SYSTEM, AND THAT
FREE ENTERPRISE SYSTEM IS THE
GREATEST ENGINE OF GROWTH AND
PROSPERITY THE WORLD HAS KNOWN.
>> Reporter: BUT HE IS AMONG
DOZENS OF INDEPENDENT
CONTRACTORS GOING OUT OF
BUSINESS BECAUSE OF THE
GOVERNMENT.
HIS COFFEE SHOP WITH DOZENS OF
OTHERS THAT OPERATE IN VETERANS
HOSPITALS ACROSS THE NATION ARE
BEING REPLACED WITH A FEDERALLY
RUN CHAIN CALLED PATRIOT BREW.
AFTER 15 YEARS SERVING JAVA AND
FRIENDLY BANTER, HE IS OUT AT
THE END OF THE MONTH.
>> MUCH HARDER SMALL COFFEE SHOP
GOING OUT OF BUSINESS, IT IS
CONCERN FOR THE VETERANS, 160
OTHER COFFEE SHOPS NATIONWIDE.
>> Reporter: ADMINISTRATORS WITH
VETERAN'S AFFAIRS SAY
ELIMINATING MOM AND POP SHOPS
AND HANDLING COFFEE THEMSELVES
WILL SAVE MONEY AND RESULT IN A
CONSISTENT ASSORTMENT OF SNACKS
AND BEVERAGES, INCLUDING
STARBUCKS BRAND COFFEE.
THEIR STATEMENT GOES ON TO SAY,
QUOTE, THE COFFEE SHOP
CONVERSIONS HAVE BEEN WELL
RECEIVED BY EMPLOYEES, VETERANS,
AND THEIR FAMILIES AT LOCATIONS
WHERE IT HAS BEEN INTRODUCED.
BUT GILMORE SAYS THE SWITCH
MEANS HIGHER PRICES THAN THE
DOLLAR A CUP HE CHARGES.
WHILE THIS NAVY VET SAYS HE'LL
MISS THE MAN MORE THAN THE
COFFEE.
>> GET MORE THERAPY TALKING WITH
KEN THAN I DO GOING TO P.T.S.D.
GROUPS I ATTEND.
>> HE AND OTHERS WONDER IF
THEY'LL OFFER AS MUCH CUSTOMER
SERVICE AS KEN GILMORE DID MORE
THAN A DECADE.
800 PEOPLE SIGNED A PETITION TO
LET HIM STAY OPEN.
THERE'S NO RESPONSE FROM THE VA
WHICH IS MOVING AHEAD WITH
DOZENS MORE COFFEE SHOP
CONVERSIONS.
IN SACRAMENTO, CLAUDIA COWAN,
FOX NEWS.
>>> WHEN IT COMES TO HIGH
ADRENALINE WATER SPORTS, URBAN
CLIFF DIVING IS POPULAR THESE
DAYS.
THE RED BULL WORLD SERIES OF
CLIFF DIVING MADE ITS ONLY U.S.
STOP IN BOSTON THIS WEEKEND.
IT HAS BEEN A EUROPEAN FAVORITE
FOR DECADES.
JUDGING BY THE NUMBER OF BOSTON
SPECTATO
SPECTATORS, IT MAY COME TO
AMERICA.
THESE COMPETITORS TOOK THE
PLUNGE FROM A BUILDING PLATFORM
90 FEET ABOVE THE WATERFRONT.
EARLIER THIS HOUR ON LIVE REPORT
FROM A RAGING WILDFIRE, WENT OFF
THE AIR WITH SMOKE HITTING OUR
CREW, TECHNICAL ISSUES THERE
CAUSED BY THE SMOKE.
THEY HAD TO MOVE.
BUT THEY'RE MOVING PEOPLE,
FAMILIES, RESIDENTS IN THAT TOWN
RIGHT NOW.
THE MONSTER INFERNO IS ON.
DOMINIC TELLS ME HE IS READY TO
GIVE AN UPDATE AFTER THIS
COMMERCIA
THAT'S THE POWER
OF GERMAN ENGINEERING.
[ SHIP HORN BLOWS ]
NO, NO, NO!
STOP!
HUMANS.
ONE DAY WE'RE COMING UP
WITH THE THEORY OF RELATIVITY,
THE NEXT...
NOT SO MUCH.
BUT THAT'S OKAY --
YOU'RE COVERED
WITH GREAT IDEAS LIKE OPTIONAL
BETTER CAR REPLACEMENT
FROM LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
TOTAL YOUR CAR
AND WE GIVE YOU THE MONEY
TO BUY ONE A MODEL YEAR NEWER.
LEARN ABOUT IT
AT LIBERTYMUTUAL.COM.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT'S YOUR POLICY?
LIKE CARPOOLS...
POLLY WANTS TO KNOW
IF WE CAN PICK HER UP.
YEAH,
WE CAN MAKE ROOM.
YEAH.
[ Male Announcer ]
...OFFICE SPACE.
YES, WE'RE LOVING THIS
COMMUNAL SEATING. IT'S GREAT.
[ Male Announcer ]
THE BEST THING TO SHARE?
A DATA PLAN.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
ONE BUCKET OF DATA
FOR EVERYONE ON THE PLAN,
UNLIMITED TALK AND TEXT
ON SMART PHONES.
NOW, EVERYONE'S IN THE SPIRIT
OF SHARING.
HEY, CAN I BORROW YOUR BOAT
THIS WEEKEND?
NO.
[ Male Announcer ]
SHARE MORE. SAVE MORE.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
♪
AT&T MOBILE S♪ARE FOR BUSINESS.
And now there's a new way to do
the same for your dog.
Introducing NEW Purina Dog Chow
Light & Healthy.
It's a no-sacrifices,
calorie-light way to help keep
him trim...
...with a deliciously tender and
crunchy kibble blend he'll
love...
...and 20% fewer calories than
Dog Chow.
Discover the lighter side of
strong.
New Purina Dog Chow Light &
Healthy.
>>> IT IS THE SIZE OF THE CITY
OF CHICAGO BURNING IN THE
YOSEMITE NATIONAL FOREST.
DOMINIC DI-NATALE IS WITH US.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN SEE THE
PLUME IN THE SKY, IT DISSIPATED
IN THE PAST FEW MINUTES BECAUSE
THE NATIONAL GUARD SENT IN A
MASS AIR TANKER TO SPRAY OVER
THE AREA.
WE UNDERSTAND FROM CAL FIRE,
THERE ARE MITIGATION EFFORTS TO
GET THAT FIRE IN CHECK.
IT IS SO CLOSE TO THE TOWN.
HAVEN'T HEARD FROM THE DIRECTOR
ON THE GROUND TACKLING THE FIRE.
HE'S SUPPOSED TO PHONE IN ANY
TIME TO TELL US WHAT EXACTLY THE
STATE OF THE FIRE IS.
WE STILL HAVE AN EVACUATION
ADVISORY IN.
THE BIG ISSUE, WILL IT CHANGE TO
EVACUATION WARNING THAT IS
ISSUED BEFORE IMMINENT
EVACUATION ORDER IS PUT IN PLACE
WHERE PEOPLE HAVE TO CLEAR TOWN.
BACK TO YOU, HARRIS.
>> DOMINIC DI-NATALE, CAUGHT IN
THE MOVEMENT AS PEOPLE TRY TO
GET TO SAFER GROUND.
WE APPRECIATE YOUR REPORTING.
THANK YOU.
>>> A BIG DAY AT THE BARKLEY'S
FOR THE MASTERS.
PETER SCHRAEGER IS HERE.
GOLF, GOLF, GOLF.
>> THIS IS ADAM SCOTT, HE WON
THE MASTERS.
CAME INTO THE TOURNAMENT, TIGER
WOODS SUNDAY WAS IN THE MIX,
TIED FOR SECOND, ADAM SCOTT
WINS.
HE JUST DIDN'T SCREW UP.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
THE REST OF THE GUYS WERE
BOGEYING DOWN THE STRETCH.
SCOTT PLAYED SOLID, WINS BY
THREE STROKES, TIGER WOODS,
SECOND PLACE.
>> I USUALLY DON'T FOLLOW THAT
MUCH LITTLE LEAGUE.
WHEN IT IS JAPAN AGAINST US, THE
UNITED STATES, CALIFORNIA, I
HAVE TO GET IN ON THAT.
>> IT WAS A GREAT GAME.
JAPAN PLAYED CHULA VISTA.
USA WAS UP EARLY, JAPAN WINS
6-4.
THEIR 14th TITLE.
23rd TIME A TEAM FROM CALIFORNIA
WAS IN THE CHAMPIONSHIP GAME,
DID NOT WIN.
IT WAS A WELL PLAYED GAME.
HERE ARE THE YOUNG KIDS
CELEBRATING.
>> LOOK AT THEM.
>> HERE ON THE EAST COAST,
EVERYBODY IS TALKING ABOUT THE
JETS, THE QUARTERBACK SITUATION.
ALL OVER THE PAPERS TODAY.
WHAT IS THE DEAL.
>> OUT THERE LAST NIGHT, JETS
PLAYED THE GIANTS IN A PRESEASON
FOOTBALL GAME.
QUARTERBACK MARK SANCHEZ WAS
INSERTED LATE IN THE GAME,
FOURTH QUARTER, GOES DOWN.
MRI TODAY, SHOULDER INJURY.
REPORT IS DAY TO DAY, THAT'S
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING.
NOW THEY'RE LEFT WITH ROOKIE
GINO SMITH, THREW THREE
INTERCEPTIONS LAST NIGHT.
IT IS A BIT OF A MESS.
SEASON STARTS IN LESS THAN TWO
WEEKS.
>>> I WANT TO TELL EVERYBODY,
FOX SPORTS WON, ON THE MAP.
TOMORROW NIGHT, BIG INTERVIEW.
LET ME PLUG YOU, FOR GOODNESS
SAKES.
WE HAVE A BIG INTERVIEW.
>> ONE ON ONE WITH JOE FLACCO.
FOX SPORTS LIVE, FLAGSHIP SHOW,
11:00 P.M. EASTERN, 8:00
PACIFIC.
TOMORROW, FLACCO, WATCH IT.
>> TOMORROW, PETE SCHRAEGER,
LOVE IT.
FEEL THAT SYNERGY?
>> THEY LOVE IT HERE AT THE NEWS
CORP. BUILDING.
>>> AN UPDATE TO THE U.S.
VERSION OF SPAIN'S RUNNING OF
THE BULLS.
TOLD YOU LAST NIGHT, THE GREAT
BULL RUN KICKED OFF IN VIRGINIA.
FIRST WITH A MISHAP IN THE SKY.
I THOUGHT IT WOULD HAVE TO DO
WITH BULLS.
IT DIDN'T.
A DRONE WITH VIDEO CAMERAS TO
FILM THE RUN CRASHED INTO THE
STANDS.
PEOPLE WERE RUNNING, BUT FROM
THAT THING.
ONE SPECTATOR WAS HIT IN THE
FACE.
TWO RUNNERS RUSHED TO THE
HOSPITAL, AT LEAST ONE WAS
TRAMPLED.
WE'RE TOLD EVERYBODY SURVIVED.
THIS WAS THE FIRST OF NINE BULL
RUNNING EVENTS HAPPENING ACROSS
THE THE COUNTRY.
WHAT'S NEXT, TEXAS I THINK?
AND FLORIDA.
WE GOT TO GO SEE THAT.
BEWARE OF THE DRONES.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT'S HOW FOX REPORTS THIS
SUNDAY, AUGUST 25th, 2013.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO MY MOM.
I CAN'T TELL YOU HER AGE BECAUSE
SHE WON'T TELL ME.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
HAVE A GREAT WEEK EVERYBODY.
"HUCKABEE" STARTS.
>>> TONIGHT ON "HUCKABEE," WITH
HIS SIGNATURE LEGISLATION
BROKEN, THE PRESIDENT CONTINUES
TO BLAME REPUBLICANS.
>> THE ONE UNIFYING PRINCIPLE IN
THE REPUBLICAN PARTY AT THE
MOMENT IS MAKING SURE THAT 30
MILLION PEOPLE DON'T HAVE HEALTH
CARE.
>> BUT IT IS NOT JUST THE GOP
THAT DOESN'T LIKE OBAMA CARE.
>> I JUST SEE A HUGE TRAIN WRECK
COMING DOWN.
>> I'M OF THE BELIEF THE ACA IS
PROBABLY THE MOST COMPLEX PIECE
OF LEGISLATION EVER PASSED BY
THE UNITED STATES CONGRESS.
>> DEMOCRATS, THE IRS, AND EVEN
UNIONS HAVE MAJOR ISSUES WITH
OBAMA CARE.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS NO ONE HAS A
BETTER PLAN.
>> WHAT ARE THE SOLUTION