OF
INVULNERABILITY.
SERVICE.
THANK YOU FOR INVITING US
INTO YOUR HOME TONIGHT.
THAT'S IT FOR THIS "SPECIAL
REPORT," FAIR, BALANCED AND
UNAFRAID.
AS THE FBI CONTINUES THEIR
SEARCH FOR THESE TWO MEN.
>> Bill: BREAKING NEWS NOW
AS I'M BILL HEMMER IN FOR
SHEPARD SMITH.
WE ARE WATCHING ENORMOUS
DEVELOPMENT IN A MARATHON
ATTACK ONLY TWO HOURS AGO
THE FBI RELEASING VIDEO OF
TWO SUSPECTS AT THE SCENE
OF MONDAY'S BOMBINGS AND
THEY CALLED THEM SUSPECTS.
THAT VIDEO SHOWS TWO MEN IN
BASEBALL CAPS.
WALKING DOWN BOYLSTON
STREET IN THE DIRECTION OF
THE MARATHON FINISH LINE.
THE FBI HAS NAMED THEM
SUSPECT ONE AND SUSPECT 2
SUSPECT 1 WEARING A DARK
HAT, SUSPECT 2 A WHITE HAT.
THEY ARE BOTH CARRYING
BAGS.
AND THE FBI SPECIAL AGENCY
IN CHARGE SAID THAT SUSPECT
2 IN THE WHITE HAT SET DOWN
A BACKPACK AT THE SITE OF
THE SECOND EXPLOSION IN
FRONT OF THE FORUM
RESTAURANT AT 755 BOYLSTON
STREET.
BOTH SUSPECTS ARE PERHAPS
THE MOST WANTED MEN IN
AMERICA.
YOU WILL SEE THESE IMAGES
MANY TIMES IN THE COMING
HOURS.
AND DAYS UNTIL THESE MEN
ARE CAUGHT.
SO STUDY THEM CAREFULLY.
BECAUSE AS THE FBI PUT IT
TODAY, SOMEBODY KNOWS WHO
THESE GUYS ARE.
>> WE KNOW THE PUBLIC WILL
PLAY A CRITICAL ROLE IN
IDENTIFYING AND LOCATING
THESE INDIVIDUALS.
SOMEBODY OUT THERE KNOWS
THESE INDIVIDUALS AS
FRIENDS, NEIGHBORS
CO-WORKERS, OR FAMILY
MEMBERS OF THE SUSPECTS.
THOUGH IT MAY BE DIFFICULT
THE NATION IS COUNTING ON
THOSE WITH INFORMATION TO
COME FORWARD AND PROVIDE IT
TO US.
>> WELL, THE FBI CONSIDERS
BOTH MEN ARMED AND
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
IF YOU KNOW THEM OR SEE
THEM, YOU CAN LET THE FEDS
KNOW BY DIALING
1-800-CALL-FBI.
ALSO ON ITS WEB SITE,
BOSTON MARATHON TIPS DOT
FBI.GOV.
WE HAVE TEAM FOX COVERAGE
WITH CATHERINE HERRIDGE
LIVE IN WASHINGTON.
BUT FIRST WANT TO GO TO
RICK LEVENTHAL LIVE IN
BOSTON.
RICK, I THINK IT SAYS AN
AWFUL LOT THAT THE FBI IS
RELEASING THESE IMAGES NOW.
GOOD EVENING.
>> GOOD EVENING, BILL.
CLEARLY THE FBI AND THE
OTHER MEMBERS OF THE JOINT
TERRORISM TASK FORCE HAVE
SPENT THE BETTER PART OF
THE LAST 48 HOURS TRYING TO
IDENTIFY AND CAPTURE THESE
TWO MEN ON THEIR OWN.
AND THEY WEREN'T ABLE TO DO
THAT.
AND THAT'S WHAT CLEARLY
PROPELLED THEM TO RELEASE
THESE IMAGES WEIGHING,
LETTING THESE GUYS KNOW
THAT THEY WERE BEING HUNTED
AGAINST TRYING TO GENERATE
MORE INTEL AND MORE
INFORMATION AND POSSIBLY
NAMES AND ADDRESSES FOR THE
TWO GUYS THAT WE ARE NOW
SEEING IN THIS VIDEO AND IN
THESE STILL PICTURES AS YOU
MENTIONED THEY ARE ONLY
BEING IDENTIFIED AS
SUSPECTS NUMBER 1 AND 2.
NUMBER ONE IN THE DARK
JACKET WITH THE DARK HAT
WITH KHAKIS AND A BACKPACK.
SUBJECT NUMBER 2 WITH A
WHITE HAT WORN BACKWARDS
ALSO WEARING A DARK JACKET
AND JEANS.
HE, SUSPECT NUMBER 2 SET
DOWN THE BACKPACK AT THE
SITE OF THE SECOND
EXPLOSION AND THEN WENT
WALKING WEST ON BOYLSTON
STREET AFTER PLANTING THE
BOMB.
AGAIN, THE FBI ENCOURAGING
PEOPLE TO CALL OR CONTACT
AUTHORITIES AND NOT TRY TO
TAKE THESE GUYS INTO
CUSTODY THEMSELVES.
>> WE CONSIDER THEM TO BE
ARMED AND EXTREMELY
DANGEROUS.
NO ONE SHOULD APPROACH
THEM.
NO ONE SHOULD ATTEMPT TO
APPREHEND THEM EXCEPT LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
LET ME IT RATE -- REITERATE
THAT CAUTION.
DO NOT TAKE ANY ACTION ON
YOUR OWN.
>> BILL, THE FBI HAS
ALREADY PROCESSED THOUSANDS
OF LEADS AND TIPS AND NO
DOUBT WILL GET MANY
THOUSANDS MORE.
>> INDEED.
AND THEY ARE SET UP FOR
THAT, WE DO BELIEVE RICK.
ANYTHING ELSE ABOUT THESE
PEOPLE THAT PEOPLE, RATHER,
SHOULD PAY ATTENTION TO
THAT YOU ARE HEARING?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
EVERYONE SHOULD LOOK AT THE
HATS THESE GUYS ARE WEARING
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT THEY
BOUGHT THEM FOR THAT DAY
MONDAY THE ATTACK AT THE
MARATHON.
THEY SHOULD LOOK AT THE
JACKETS THEY ARE WEARING.
LOOK AT THE WALK.
THE ONES GUY'S WALK MIGHT
BE DISTINCTIVE TO SOMEONE
AS YOU SEE THEM COMING DOWN
THE STREET.
PEOPLE SHOULD REMEMBER WHY
THE FBI IS HUNTING THESE
TWO AND ONE OF THEM, AGAIN
YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE HIS
PROFILE IN ONE OF THOSE
PHOTOGRAPHS.
AND, BY THE WAY, ALL OF
THOSE PHOTOGRAPHS VIDEOS
THAT HAVE BEEN SUBMITTED
SOME PEOPLE MAY NOT HAVE
SUBMITTED PICTURES THAT
THEY THOUGHT WOULD NOT BE
VALUABLE TO THE
INVESTIGATION NOW SEEING
THESE GUYS, IF YOU LOOK AT
THEIR HATS LOOK AT THEIR
CLOTHING, LOOK AT THEIR
FACES, PERHAPS YOU HAVE A
PHOTO IN YOUR CAMERA IF YOU
WERE AT THE MARATHON ON
MONDAY THAT WOULD BE EVEN
MORE VALUABLE TO THE FBI.
AN EVEN BETTER ANGLE OF ONE
OR BOTH OF THESE MEN.
YOU SHOULD FORWARD THAT TO
THE FBI.
HERE IS MORE FROM THE
SPECIAL AGENT IN CHARGE OF
THE BOSTON OFFICE.
>> IDENTIFYING AND LOCATING
THOSE RESPONSIBLE IS NOW
OUR HIGHEST PRIORITY.
NO OTHER DETAILS OF THE
INVESTIGATION WILL BE
RELEASED AT THIS TIME
BECAUSE THIS IS OUR FOCUS
NOW.
IT CONTINUES TO BE AN
ONGOING ACTIVE
INVESTIGATION.
>> THE FBI SAYS IT WILL
CONTINUE TO WORK TO ENHANCE
THE IMAGES THAT IT HAS
BILL.
WE CAN'T STRESS ENOUGH HOW
IMPORTANT OTHER IMAGES
MIGHT BE TO THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> LATE LAST NIGHT, RICK.
AND YOU AND I HAVE HAD A
LOT OF LATE NIGHTS PAST
WEEK IN BOSTON.
YOUR SOURCE TOLD YOU
SOMETHING TWO DAYS AGO YOU
SAID ABOUT A GUY WEARING A
WHITE BASEBALL CAP THAT WAS
TURNED BACK WARDZ.
WHAT DO YOU RECALL BASED ON
THAT CONVERSATION NOW?
>>
>> A SOURCE OF MINE WITH
THE FEDERAL BUREAU OF
INVESTIGATION WAS LOOKING
AT A PICTURE OF WHAT WE
BELIEVE IS SUBJECT NUMBER 2
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 WEARING
THE WHITE BASEBALL CAP
BACKWARDS.
HE WAS DESCRIBING THAT
PHOTO IT TO ME ON TUESDAY
MORNING THAT HAVE BEEN SIR
CIRCUITING AMONG THE
TBILISI THEY HAVE KNOWN
THIS GUY FOR THE PAST
COUPLE OF DAYS.
HE REMINDED ME THIS SUSPECT
PLACED A BACK NEXT TO
8-YEAR-OLD MARTIN RICHARD.
HE WAS STANDING, THE LITTLE
BOY WAS ON THAT LITTLE
BARRICADE NEXT TO HIS
LITTLE SISTER WHOSE LEG WAS
BLOWN OFF AND HIS MOTHER
WHO HAD SURGERY ON HER
BRAIN.
THIS GUY, BELIEVED TO BE
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 SOMEONE
THE FBI BELIEVES IT MIGHT
BE THIS PERSON PLACED THAT
BACK BACK TOWN NEXT TO THAT
LITTLE BOY WAITING TO SEE
HIS FATHER CROSS THE FINISH
LINE.
BOY LOST HIS LIFE AND
SISTER LOST HER LEG AND
MOTHER HAS DAMAGE TO HER
BRAIN.
WHAT THIS GUY DID THREE
LIVES LOST AND HORRIFIC
INJURIES BILL.
>> Bill: WE REMEMBER ALL OF
THOSE VICTIMS HERE TONIGHT
IN BOSTON.
STABBED BY THERE ACROSS
TOWN.
OUR TEAM FOX COVERAGE
CONTINUES WITH CATHERINE
HERRIDGE.
SHE IS LIVE IN WASHINGTON
NOW.
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING DOWN
THERE TONIGHT.
>> WITH THE FBI CALLING FOR
THE PUBLIC'S HELPY THE U.S.
TELLING CONGRESS THE
INVESTIGATION IS WIDE OPEN.
WE DON'T KNOW WHETHER THE
PLAN WAS FOREIGN OR
DOMESTIC OR INDIVIDUAL ACT.
LONE WOLVES, DOMESTIC
EXTREMISTS AND I JIHAD
INSPIRED GROUPS.
>> THE FBI'S CRIME LAB IN
QUANTICO, VIRGINIA ONGOING.
NOW AT LEAST FUR TRACKS IN
THIS INVESTIGATION THAT WE
KNOW OF, THE BOMB
COMPONENTS, THE VIDEOS, THE
STILLS AND THEN ALSO SOCIAL
MEDIA, BILL.
>> Bill: WHAT MORE DO WE
KNOW ABOUT THAT SOCIAL
MEDIA HAVE YOU BEEN TALKING
ABOUT THE 24 HOURS BEFORE
THE BOMBS WENT OFF AND THE
24 HOURS THAT FOLLOWED.
WHAT HAPPENED AND WHAT WAS
GATHERED DURING THAT
48-HOUR PERIOD?
>> AN INVESTIGATIVE SOURCE
STEM CELLS FOX NEWS THERE
IS FOOTPRINT PROVIDING NEW
LEADS FOR INVESTIGATORS.
MORE THAN 30,000 SOCIAL
MEDIA MESSAGES WERE
COLLECTED WITHIN A ONE MILE
RADIUS OF THE FINISH LINE
FROM 24 HOURS BEFORE TO 24
HOURS AFTER THE EXPLOSIONS
MESSAGES THAT SEEMED OUT OF
PLACE WERE CODED INCLUDING
TWEETS ABOUT TWO BOSTON
HOTELS WERE ANNUALIZED
FURTHER.
>> IN UNCONVENTIONAL
WARFARE WHAT YOU ARE
STARTING TO SEE MORE AND
MORE OF IS THE USE OF
SOCIAL MEDIA TO
COMMUNICATE.
TO SPREAD MESSAGES INSTEAD
OF USING WHAT WE WOULD
TYPICALLY SEE ON THE
BATTLEFIELD WHICH IS RADIO
COMMUNICATION.
>> ONE OF THE ISSUES THAT
WE HEARD REPEATEDLY HERE ION ON CAPITOL
HILL
WAS WHETHER THIS COULD BE A
LONE WOLF, WHAT'S CLEAR
FROM THE RELEASE OF THE   TONIGHT
IS THAT IT
WAS A CONSPIRACY OF AT LEAST TWO PEOPLE
BILL.
>> Bill: YEAH, CATHERINE
STAND BY AS WELL.
BECAUSE THERE IS MORE TO
TALK ABOUT TOO ON THE
FORENSIC SIDE OF THIS AND
ALSO WHERE THIS
INVESTIGATION GOES.
RICK, I WANT TO MENTION
THIS TO YOU.
MASSACHUSETTS STATE POLICE
A SHORT TIME AGO TWEETED
THE FOLLOWING.
AND THEY TALKED ABOUT
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 THAT YOU
WERE JUST TALKING ABOUT.
SUSPECT NUMBER 2
HIGHLIGHTED AND PROFILED
THE TWEET READS NOTE
PRONOUNCED JAW NOSE, DARK
HAIR AND THEN 1-800-CALL
FBI WITH INFO.
THE POINT TO BE MADE HERE,
RICK, IS THAT THEY CANNOT
SOLVE THIS CASE WITHOUT
HELP FROM THE PUBLIC NOW
CAN THEY?
>> BY THE FACT THAT THEY
RELEASED THESE IMAGES AND
ARE ASKING FOR HELP.
OBVIOUSLY ANYONE WHO MAY
RECOGNIZE THEM SHOULD CALL
THE FBI.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE
GETTING A LOT OF FALSE
LEADS, BILL.
THEY HAVE HAD TO DEAL WITH
THOSE OVER THE LAST FEW
DAYS.
THAT'S COMMON IN ANY
INVESTIGATION.
ESPECIALLY ONE THAT'S THIS
HIGH PROFILE.
BUT, YOU CAN SEE THESE
MEN'S FACES.
CAN YOU GET A PRETTY GOOD
LOOK AT THEM.
IF THEY SPENT ANY TIME IN
THE BOSTON AREA, OR ANY
TIME IN THE UNITED STATES,
THEN SOMEONE INTERACTED
WITH THEM.
ANY NUMBER OF PEOPLE MIGHT
RECOGNIZE THEM OR THINK
THEY KNOW THEM AND THAT'S
HOT FBI IS HOPING TO TALK
TO.
>> Bill: YEAH WITH
CATHERINE WORKING THE
STORY, TOO THROUGH HER
SOURCES IN WASHINGTON.
CATHERINE, IN SOME OF THESE
IMAGES, IT'S CLEAR THAT AT
LEAST SUSPECT NUMBER 2 IS
TALKING ON A PHONE.
ONE OF THE IMAGES IT LOOKS
LIKE SUSPECT NUMBER 1 IS
EAR PHONES IN HIS EARS AS
HE WALKS DOWN THAT
SIDEWALK.
BUT SPECIFICALLY ON THE
CELL PHONE EVIDENCE, IS IT
TRUE THEY CAN PIN POINT
EVERY CALL OF EVERY MOMENT
AT THAT HOUR OF THE DAY
FROM 2:00 TO 3:00 ON MONDAY
AFTERNOON AND IF THEY CAN
CAN THEY TRACE IT?
>>
>> WHAT WE REPORTED EARLIER
HERE AT FOX IS THAT THE FBI
WAS SCRUBBING OR SCANNING
THE CELL PHONE TOWER
RECORDS LOOKING FOR
POSITIVE HITS AT THE POINT
OF DETONATION.
IN OTHER WORDS WERE THERE
PHONE CALLS GOING THROUGH
CELL PHONE TOWERS AT THE
VERY MOMENTS THAT THEY KNOW
THE BOMBS WERE BEING
DETONATED, THEY CAN USE
THAT INFORMATION TO TRACE
IT BACK TO A PHONE NUMBER.
BUT ANY TERRORIST BECAUSE
THAT'S WHAT THESE TWO
PEOPLE ARE WORTH THEIR
SAWLTD SALT, IF THEY ARE
USING CELL PHONES FOR
DETONATION WOULD BE USING
DISPOSABLE CELL PHONES THAT
THEY PURCHASED AT
CONVENIENCE STORE.
EVEN FINDING THAT NUMBER IF
THAT WAS THE METHOD OF
DETONATION IS NOT
NECESSARILY GOING TO LEAD
BACK TO AN INDIVIDUAL IN
THIS CASE UNLESS YOU HAVE A
SUPER ALERT CONVENIENCE
STORE CLERK WHO MAY
REMEMBER THESE GUYS.
>> YEAH.
AND THE INVESTIGATION AS IT
MOVES FORWARD, YOU WONDER,
CATHERINE, WHY THE FBI WAS
QUIET FOR TWO DAYS.
IS THERE A REASONABLE
EXPLANATION OR WHAT ARE WE
HEARING ABOUT WHAT EXPLAINS
THAT OVER THE PAST 48
HOURS?
>> THEY HAVEN'T OFFERED AN
EXPLANATION.
BUT I THINK RICK WOULD
AGREE WITH ME THAT OUR
EXPERIENCE WOULD TELL YOU
THAT THINGS WERE MOVING AT
A VERY FAST PACE AND IT WAS
EXTREMELY FLUID.
THE DECISION TO RELEASE THE
PICTURES HAS BENEFITS.
IF THE SUBJECTS ARE
IDENTIFIED, BUT THEY ARE
ALSO RISKS BECAUSE IT TIPS
THE FBI'S HAT TO THESE
INDIVIDUALS AND IT MAKE
CAUSE SOME TO FLEE.
BUT IF WE WANT TO SORT OF
LOOK AT WHAT I THINK IS THE
LEADING EDGE OF THIS STORY
NOW IS THAT THERE ARE TWO
INDIVIDUALS, BUT THEY HAD
TO HAVE SOME KIND OF HELP.
IT WOULD BE CALLED A
SUPPORT NETWORK FOR THEIR
OPERATIONS IN BOSTON.
WERE THESE PEOPLE PART OF
THE CONSPIRACY OR WAS --
WERE THEY SORT OF
UNWITTINGLY HELPING THESE
INDIVIDUALS, BILL?
>> Bill: TO THAT POINT
CATHERINE, THE FBI AGENT IN
CHARGE, AND I WILL BRING
RICK IN FOR A COMMENT ON
THIS AS WELL.
BE
DIFFICULT BUT PLEASE COME
FORWARD.
ESSENTIALLY, RICK, THAT WAS
AN APPEAL TO FAMILY OR
FRIENDS THAT YOU MAY KNOW
THESE INDIVIDUALS BUT WE
NEED TO KNOW WHO THEY'RE
AND DON'T HOLD BACK.
>> AND PEOPLE NEED TO BE
REMINDED OF THE HORRORS OF
THAT DAY AND THE PAIN AND
ANGUISH AND AWFUL INJURIES
THAT THESE TWO SUSPECTS
ALLEGEDLY INFLICTED.
I MEAN SOMEBODY PUT THESE
BOMBS DOWN THERE AND THE
FBI SEEMS PRETTY SURE THAT
IT'S THESE TWO GUYS.
BILL, ONE OTHER THING, A
LOT OF-LY TO HAS BEEN A LOT
OF CRITICISM ABOUT ALL OF
THESE SURVEILLANCE CAMERAS
POSTED AROUND ALL OF THESE
BIG CITIES IN AMERICA.
IF THOSE CAMERAS WEREN'T
THERE THEY WOULDN'T HAVE
THE IMAGES OF THESE TWO
GUYS AND IT WOULD BE A LOT
HARDER TO TRACK THEM DOWN.
>> RICK, THANK YOU FOR
THAT.
RICK LEVENTHAL.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE WITH ME
TONIGHT.
BACK TO BOTH OF THEM WHEN
WE GET MORE NEWS THAT
BREAKS THROUGHOUT THE HOUR
HERE.
IN A MOMENT, WE WILL HEAR
THOUGH FROM A MAN WHO WAS
WORKED INSIDE THE FBI
FIGHTING TERRORISM.
AND HEAR WHAT HE THINKS OF
TODAY'S LATEST DEVELOPMENTS
AND THE EFFORTS TO CATCH
THESE TWO MEN.
THAT'S COMING UP TONIGHT ON
THE FOX REPORT LIVE FROM
BOYLSTON STREET IN BOSTON.
ONLY A FEW DAYS AFTER THE
MARATHON ATTACKS THAT LEFT
THREE PEOPLE DEAD, MORE
THAN 170 WOUNDED AND A CITY
AND A NATION THAT IS
MOURNING FOR THESE THREE.
TONIGHT.
@  [ alarm clock ringing ]    [ Female
Announcer ] IF YOU    HAVE RHEUMATOID
ARTHRITIS,    CAN YOUTART THE DAY
THE WAY YOU WANT?    CAN ORENCI(ABATACEPT)
HELP?    COULD YOUR "I WANT"    BECOME
"I CAN"?    TALK TO YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST.
ORENCIA REDUCES    MANY RA SYMPTOMS
LIKE PAIN, MORNING STIFFNESS    AND
THE PROGRESSION    OF JOINT DAMAGE.
IT'S HELPED NEW RA PATIENTS    AND
THOSE NOT HELPED ENOUGH    BY OTHER
TREATMENTS.    DO NOT TAKE ORENCIA
WITH ANOTHER BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
FOR RA    DUE TO AN INCREASED RISK
OF SERIOUS INFECTION.    SERIOUS SIDE
EFFECTS CAN OCCUR    INCLUDING FATAL
INFECTIONS.    CASES OF LYMPHOMA AND
LUNG CANCER HAVE BEEN REPORTED.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU ARE    PRONE
TO OR VE ANY INFECTION    LIKE AN
OPEN SORE OR THE F    OR A HISTORY
OF COPD,    A CHRONIC LUNG DISEASE.
ORENCIA MAY WORSEN YOUR COPD.    [
Male Announcer ]    NOW LEARN ABOUT
A PROGRAM    COMMITTED TO YOU    AND
COPAY ASSISTANCE THAT CAN    REDUCE
MONTHLY ORENCIA    OUT-OF-POCKET
DRUG COST TO $5.    IF YOU'RE    NOT
SATISFIED    AFTER 6 MONTHS,    YOU
GET    THAT MONEY BACK.    CALL 1-800-ORENCIA.
>> Bill: BACK TO IT OUR
BREAKING NEWS NOW HERE IN
BOSTON.
THE FBI RELEASING PHOTOS
AND VIDEO OF TWO MEN
CALLING THEM SUSPECTS AFTER
MONDAY'S MARATHON BOMBINGS.
WITH ME NOW TERRY FORMER
DEPUTY ASSISTANT DIRECTOR
OF THE COUNTER TERRORISM
DIVISION OF THE FBI.
AND, SIR, GOOD EVENING TO
YOU.
I WANT YOU TO TAKE ME AND
OUR VIEWERS NEED THE FBI'S
INVESTIGATION NOW.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
KNOWING THAT THEY ARE GOING
PUBLIC WITH THIS
INFORMATION AS OF 5:15
EASTERN TIME TWO HOURS AGO?
>> THEY SPENT MANY HOURS
DISCUSSING THIS AND
ANALYZING AND ASSESSING
WHAT THEY HAD AND THEY
DECIDED THAT IT THEY WERE
NO LONGER GOING TO HAVE
TIME TO IDENTIFY THESE
PEOPLE ON THEIR OWN.
SO IT'S TIME TO GO BACK TO
THE PUBLIC.
REMEMBER, THIS IS A VERY
VERY FAST-MOVING CASE.
AND IT'S FAST MOVING
BECAUSE OF THE PUBLIC'S
HELP.
IF YOU HAVE VIDEO,
PICTURES, CAMERA CELL
PHONES ANYTHING LIKE THAT,
TURN IT OVER TO THE FBI
BOSTON LAW ENFORCEMENT.
NOW THE FOCUS IS ON THESE
FACES AND THESE TWO PEOPLE.
AND THE THEY KEPT STRESSING
THAT THINK ABOUT THESE TWO
PEOPLE AND IF YOU WERE IN
TOWN, IF YOU WERE ON ROADS
HIGHWAYS LEADING INTO TOWN,
LET'S TAKE AN EXAMPLE, IF
YOU WERE LEASING ROOMS TO
PEOPLE THINK ABOUT THESE
FACES.
ABOUT D. THESE PEOPLE STAY
WITH YOU IN A ROOM.
RENT A ROOM MAYBE TWICE IN
THE LAST FEW WEEKS.
IF THEY DID CALL.
WHEN WE WENT BACK AND
STARTING INVESTIGATED THE
"U.S.S. COLE" BOMBING, THE
BAD GUYS HAD LEASED A ROOM
HAD A SAFE HOUSE NOT FARM
FROM THE HARBOR.
WE KNOW THESE KIND OF
THINGS OCCUR.
IF YOU ARE A BUS DRIVER, IF
YOU RENT CARS, IF YOU WORK
AT A GAS STATION OR A
COFFEE SHOP, WE KNOW THAT
THEODORE KOSINSKI GOT ON A
BUS WITH UNSTABLE BOMBS AND
WENT FROM POINT A TO POINT
B.
ERIC RUDOLPH TOOK HIS CAR
AND LEFT THE SCENE OF THE
CRIME.
WE KNOW WHAT THESE PEOPLE
DO.
NOW WE HAVE TO FOCUS THE
PUBLIC AND FOCUS THEM ON A
MAN'S DAILY ROUTINE AND A
MAN'S DAILY BEHAVIOR.
EVEN THOUGH THESE TERRIBLE
CRIMES COMMITTED.
THESE PEOPLE ENGAGED IN
CRIMES BEFORE THEY CAME TO
BOSTON.
LOOK AT THESE FACES LOOK
AT THESE PEOPLE.
LOOK AT THESE CAPS.
I THINK I HEARD EARLIER ONE
OF YOUR REPORTERS EARLIER
MENTIONED THINK ABOUT THE
CAPS.
THEY MAY HAVE BEEN BOUGHT
IN THE VICINITY.
MAYBE IN THE VICINITY OF A
HOTEL WHERE THESE GUYS
STAYED.
IF YOU ARE IN ANY OF THOSE
PROFESSIONS OR OCCUPATIONS
THINK ABOUT THESE PEOPLE
AND CALL IF YOU HAVE ANY
INTICKET THAT I THINK I SAW
THESE TWO PEOPLE OR I THINK
I RENTED A ROOM TO THEM.
>> Bill: EXCELLENT
EXCELLENT POINTS TERRY.
SHOULD WOULD HE BE
SURPRISED IN ANY WAY THAT
THESE IMAGES ARE OUT THERE
NOW OR PERHAPS THE BETTER
PART OF THAT QUESTION IS
WHAT DOES THAT SAY ABOUT
WHERE THEY ARE IN THIS
INVESTIGATION?
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL I AM
REALLY DELIGHTED THAT THE
FBI IS MORE NOW 10 YEARS
AGO OR 20 YEARS OR WHEN I
WAS WORKING ON UNIBOMB
THEY ARE INTO AND
UNDERSTAND HOW TO UTILIZE
AND COMMUNICATE TO THE
PUBLIC THROUGH THE MEDIA.
AND I KNOW THAT THERE IS A
LOT OF CONSTERNATION OVER
WHY NOW OR WHATEVER.
LOOK, THEY HAD THESE
PICTURES.
THEY DEVELOPED THEM AND NOW
THEY ARE TRYING TO FOCUS
PEOPLE ON TAKING THEM DOWN
THE TRAIL OF WHERE THESE
PEOPLE MIGHT HAVE COME FROM AND WHERE
HO THEY MIGHTE.
>> Bill: UNDERSTOOD.
SOMEONE FROM THE PUBLIC HAS
TO COME FORWARD NOW.
IT'S CLEAR THAT THEY STILL
NEED THE PUBLIC'S HELP IN
.
TERRY, THANK YOU.
TERRY TURCHIE FORMER
COUNTER TERRORISM DIRECTOR
OF THE FBI.
BACK ON THE STREETS OF
BOYLSTON IN A MOMENT.
NEWLY RELEASED PHOTOS AMEND
THE VIDEO.
THEY COULD PROVE CRITICAL
IN SOLVING THIS CASE.
LOOK AT JUST HOW CRITICAL
IN A MOMENT AS OUR COVERAGE
CONIGHT.
IN BOSTON.
[ Female Announcer ] A CLASSIC
MEATLOAF RECIPE FROM STOUFFER'S
STARTS WITH GROUND BEEF    ONIONS
AND PEPPERS    BAKED IN A KETCHUP
GLAZE    WITH SAVORY GRAVY    AND
MASHED RUSSET POTATOES.    WHAT MAKES
STOUFFER'S MEATLOAF    BEST OF ALL?
THAT MOMENT YOU ENJOY IT    AT HOME.
STOUFFER'S.    MADE WITH CARE,
FOR YOU OR YOUR FAMILY.
I think Ford service  is great  but
I wondered what a  customer thought?
Describe the first  time you met
As soon as I met Fiona and I  was
describi problem
we were having with  our rear brakes,
she ely triaged  the situation,
knew exactly what was  wrong with
it,
the car was diagnosed properly  it
was fixed correctly
I have confidence knowing that  if
I take to Ford it's going to
be done correctly with the right
parts and the right people.
Get a free brake inspection and
brake pads installed for just
49.95 after rebates when you
use the Ford Service Credit    Card.
Did you tell him to say  all of that?
No
he's right though...
[ HEART BEATING,  MONITOR BEEPING
]  Woman: WHAT DO YOU MEAN,  HOMEOWNERS
INSURANCE
DOESN'T COVER FLOODS?
[ HEART RATE INCREASES ]
Man: A FEW INCHES OF WATER  CAUSED
ALL THIS?
[ HEART RATE INCREASES ]
Woman #2: BUT I DON'T EVEN LIVE  NEAR
THE WATER.
WHAT YOU DON'T KNOW ABOUT FLOOD
INSURANCE MAY SHOCK YOU --
INCLUDING THE FACT    THAT A PREFERRED
RISK POLICY
STARTS AS LOW AS $129 A YEAR.
FOR AN AGENT, CALL THE NUMBER
THAT APPEARS ON YOUR SCREEN.
>> Bill: BACK TO OUR
BREAKING NEWS NOW IN BOSTON
A COUPLE OF HOURS AGO.
THE FBI RELEASING VIDEO AND
IMAGES OF TWO S
THE SCENE OF MONDAY'S
BOMBINGS
AND THEY CALLED THEM
SUSPECTS.
YOUNG MEN IN BASEBALL CAPS
FROM THE FBI IS CALLING  1 SCREEN
LEFT.
RIGHT.
AND NOW THE OFFICIALS
ASKING FOR YOUR
IDENTIFYING THEM.
WITH ME NOW MY COLLEAGUE
FOX NEWS ANCHOR GREG
JARRETT, ALSO AN ATTORNEY.
GREG, GOOD EVENING TO YOU
THERE IN NEW YORK.
IT IS IMPORTANT TO STRESS
HOW CRITICAL AND VITAL AT
THIS POINT IN THE
INVESTIGATION THESE IMAG
AND THE VIDEO AND HOW VITAL
THEY CAN
>> YOU ARE RIGHT BILL.
THEY ARE K. NOT ONLY
ALLEGEDLY IDENTIFY THE
IN THE COURSE OF A TRIAL
THEY PROVIDE THE SEQUENCE
OF CONVENIENCE LEADING UP
TO THE EXPLOSION.
REMEMBER, YOU SEE TWO GUYS,
ONE OF
VAD YES TAPE ACCORDING TO
THE FBI LITERALLYE BACKPACK WHERE
THERE WAS AN EXPLOSION AND  TS
BE.
THAT IS INCOWERFUL
CIRCUMSTANTIAL EVIDENCE.
IT ALSO SHOWS FLIGHT AS
CONSCIOUSNESS OF GUILT
BILL.
>> Bill: WELL, THAT IS
INTERESTING.
BECAUSE THE FBI SAID THAT
COMMENT TONIGHT ABOUT
SUSPECT NUMBER 2.
AND THEY SAY THEY HAVE
VIDEOTAPE EVIDENCE OF H
LEAVING THAT BOMB AT THE
SCENE.
NOW, WHAT OTHER EVIDENCE
COULD BE IMPORTANT HERE,
GREG?
>> Greg: THE DEBRIS FIELD
IS A WEALTH OF DIRECT
EVIDENCE BECAUSE IN
PARTICULAR THEY MAY BE AGE
TO IDENTIFY THE LABORATORY
UNDERWRITER ON ONE OR MORE
OF THE PRESSURE COOKERS
THAT COULD LEAD TO WHERE IT   THE
PEOPLE WHO
PURCHASED IT.
1993 IN THE WORLD TRADE
CENTER BOMBING, IT WAS A
SMALL IDENTIFICATION NUMBER
IN THE DEBRIS FIELD FOUND
ON THE AXLE OF T
EXPLODING VAN THAT
THE RYDER TRUCK RENTAL IN
NEW JERSEY AND THAT'S HOW
THEY NABBED THE KILLERS.
>> Bill: AS WE MOVE
FORWARD, IF THERE IS AN
ARREST, IF THERE IS AN
APPREHENSION, WH
CHARGES COULD BE FILED IN A
CASE LIKE THIS?
>> THE FEDS COULD FILE
TERRORISM CHARGES AGAINST
THESE SUSPECTS.
THAT IS, YOU KNOW, AN ACT
OF VIOLENCE INTENDED TO
COERCE THE GOVERNMENT OR
INTIMIDATE THE GENERAL
POPULATION.
THAT CARRIES THE DEATH
PENALTY AS WELL AS
EXPLODING A WEAPON OF MASS
DESTRUCTION.
THE STATE COULD CHARGE,
MURDER CHARGES UP TO 200
ATTEMPTED MURDER CHARGES
BUT, REMEMBER,
MASSACHUSETTS ABOLISHED THE
DEATH PENALTY IN 1984, SO
ONLY THE FEDS CAN SEEK
DEATH.
>> Bill: THANK YOU GREG.
GREG JARRETT IN OUR STUDIOS
THERE IN NEW YORK.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, GREG.
APPRECIATE THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE HAVE A
SERIES OF IMAGES NOW
CIRCULATING AROUND THE
WORLD AT BREAK NECK SPEED
AS FEDERAL INVESTIGATORS
SEEK TO IDENTIFY THESE
SUSPECTS.
THE LATEST ON THE FBI'S
DIRECTOR APPEAL TO EACH AND
EVERY ONE OF US.
TONIGHT.
THAT IS COMING UP NEXT.
WE KNOW ALL YOUR INVESTMENTS  MAY
NOT BE WITH FIDELITY  BUT WE CAN STILL
HELP YOU SEE  YOUR BIG PICTURE.
WITH THE FIDELITY  GUIDED PORTFOLIO
SUMMARY
YOU CHOOSE  WHICH ACCOUNTS TO TRACK
AND USE FIDELITY'S ANALYTICS  TO SPOT
TRENDS
GAIN INSIGHTS, AND FIGURE OUT  WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO NEXT.
ALL IN ONE PLACE.
I'M MEREDITH STODDARD
AND I HELPED CREATE
THE FIDELITY GUIDED  PORTFOLIO SUMMARY.
IT'S ONE MORE INNOVATIVE REASON
SERIOUS INVESTORS
ARE CHOOSING FIDELITY.
NOW GET 200 FREE TRADES    WHEN YOU
OPEN AN ACCOUNT.
>> Bill: I'M BILL HEMMER IN
FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
BREAKING NEWS FROM BOSTON.
WE NOW HAVE PICTURES OF TWO
SUSPECTS AND THE TERROR
ATTACK AT THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
THE FBI RELEASED THESE
IMAGES ONLY TWO HOURS AGO
AND BOTH MEN CARRYING BAGS
AND WEARING BASEBALL CAPS.
THE FBI SPECIAL AGENT
LEADING THE INVESTIGATION
SAYS THAT ANYONE WITH ANY
INFORMATION ON THE SUSPECTS
NEEDS TO STEP FORWARD NOW.
AS HE PUT IT, THE NATION IS
COUNTING ON IT.
MIKE TOBIN WITH ME NOW.
TONIGHT, MIKE, WHAT DO YOU
TAKE FROM THESE LATE
DEVELOPMENTS THAT WE HAVE
BEEN WATCHING HERE IN
BOSTON?
>> WELL, BILL, ONE OF THE
FIRST THINGS THAT STRUCK ME
IS GONE IS THIS DISCUSSION
OF PERSON OF INTEREST OR
PEOPLE WITH WHOM THE
FEDERAL INVESTIGATORS WANT
TO SPEAK.
THE SPECIAL AGENT IN CHARGE
OF THE BOSTON OFFICE HERE
CAME RIGHT OUT AND USED THE
WORD SUSPECT.
FOLLOWING ON WHAT WE HAD
REPORTED EARLIER THAT
FEDERAL SOURCE HAD
INDICATED THEY HAD A CLEAR
IMAGE OF SOMEONE PLACING A
DEVICE AT THE SCENE WHERE
ONE OF THE EXPLOSIONS TOOK
PLACE.
WE NOW KNOW FROM THE FEDS
HERE IN BOSTON THAT THAT
WAS A BACKPACK PLACED AT
THE SITE OF ONE OF THOSE
EXPLOSIONS.
>> SUSPECT 2 SET DOWN A
BACKPACK AT THE SITE OF THE
SECOND EXPLOSION JUST IN
FRONT OF THE FORUM
RESTAURANT.
WE STRONGLY ENCOURAGE THOSE
WHO WERE AT THE FORUM
RESTAURANT WHO HAVE NOT
CONTACTED US YET TO DO SO
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 IS THE
INDIVIDUALS IN THE WHITE
BALL CAP.
OUR FOX AFFILIATE OUT HERE
IS LINKING THAT TO A POLO
BALL CAP WITH THE NUMBER
THREE EMBROILED ON THE
SIDE.
A BALL CAP TURNED BACKWARDS
THAT WAS NEAR THE FORUM
RESTAURANT OR THE FINISH
LINE AT THAT TIME WHEN THE
EXPLOSIONS TOOK PLACE MAYBE
HAS SOME PHOTOGRAPHS COULD
GO RE-EXAMINE THEIR
PHOTOGRAPHS AND LOOK AT
THIS INDIVIDUAL WITH THE
WHITE BALL CAP TURNED
BACKWARDS.
THIS IS THE INDIVIDUAL
DESCRIBED TO US EARLIER BY
FBI CONTACTS AS VERY YOUNG
AND CAUCASIAN.
NOW TURNING UP IN THE
IMAGES THAT THE FBI HAS
RELEASED.
BRIDGESTONE BALL CAP.
THE BODY LANGUAGE THEY LOOK
FOR.
IMKNOWLEDGE NOW RELEASED BY
THE FBI.
INDICATES CLEARLY BILL THAT
THESE TWO WERE ASSOCIATED.
>> YEAH.
ALSO THE PROFILE IMAGE OF
THE SECOND SUSPECT IS QUITE
TELLING.
AND THE MASSACHUSETTS STATE
POLICE, THE POINTING OUT
CERTAIN FEATURES ON HIS
FACES A YOU LOOK AT HIS
PROFILE AND THEY COULD BE
QUITE REVEALING TOO THROUGH
THE THIS INVESTIGATION
MIKE.
THE FBI IS LAUNCHING A
SERIOUS APPEAL TO THE
PUBLIC, ARE THEY NOT?
>> THEY ARE.
AND THE BAD NEWS WHEN YOU
HEAR THEM GOING PUBLIC,
THAT TELLS YOU THAT THEY
HAVE EXHAUSTED ALL OF THE
LEADS THEY HAD TO THIS
POINT AND THEY DON'T KNOW
EXACTLY WHO THESE
INDIVIDUALS ARE.
BUT YOU HEARD FROM THE FEDS
VERY CLEARLY IN THIS PRESS
CONFERENCE THAT SOMEONE OUT
THERE KNOWS WHO THESE
INDIVIDUALS ARE.
THE IMAGES ARE VERY CLEAR
THAT THEY HAVE DISPLAYED.
THAT THE BLESSING WE HAVE
WITH THE PROLIFERATION WITH
CAMERAS, SECURITY CAMERAS
iPHONE CAMERAS THAT ARE
EVERYWHERE NOW IS THAT YOU
DO GET VERY GOOD IMAGES OF
THESE PEOPLE.
WHEN THAT KIND OF THING
COMES OUT.
SOMEONE KNOWS WHO THEY'RE.
THE DIFFICULTY IS THAT YOU
NOW HAVE TO COMPETE WITH
ALL OF THE BAD IMAGES
FLOATING AROUND ON THE
INTERNET.
FOR CLARITY THESE IMAGES
SHOULD BE THE ONLY ONES, I
EMPHASIZE THE ONLY ONES
THAT THE PUBLIC SHOULD VIEW
TO ASSIST US.
OTHER PHOTOS SHOULD NOT BE
DEEMED CREDIBLE AND UN --
THEY UNNECESSARILY DIVERT
THE PUBLIC'S ATTENTION IN
THE WRONG DIRECTION AND
CREATE UNDUE WORK FOR VITAL
RESOURCES.
>> THE BLAST LOCATION HERE
ON BOYLSTON STREET STILL
VERY MUCH AN ACTIVE CRIME
SCENE.
INVESTIGATORS COULD BE
SCENE THROUGHOUT THE DAY
SIFTING THROUGH THE DEBRIS
OF THAT BOMBING.
WEARING THE WHITE SUITS.
PULLING UP PIECES OF THE
ASPHALT.
THE LITTLE BITS OF EVIDENCE
THEY PULL FROM THAT BECOME
PIECES TO THE PUZZLE.
ONCE YOU HAVE THE SUSPECTS,
THE PIECES OF THE PUZZLE
FALL TOGETHER.
BILL?
>> Bill: YOU KNOW, MIKE,
THAT COMMENT THAT WAS MADE
BY THE FBI I THINK IS SO
TELLING.
WE HAVE VIDEO EVIDENCE OF
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 LEAVING A
BACKPACK AT THE SCENE OF
HIS SECOND EXPLOSION YOU
THINK ABOUT THE COMMENT AND
WHERE THE PRESS CONFERENCE
STARTED.
WE HAD A SINGLE PERSON OF
INTEREST AND WE WERE
WORKING TO CONFIRM WHETHER
OR NOT THIS PERSON WAS
WORKING BY HIMSELF OR WITH
SOMEONE ELSE.
MAYBE ANOTHER PERSON MAYBE
A THIRD PERSON AT THE
SCENE.
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT THE
INVESTIGATION WORKED FROM
THE POINT OF THE EXPLOSION
AND WORKED ITS OUTWARD.
AND NOW WE HAVE TWO IMAGES
THAT ARE NOW PUBLIC.
MIKE?
>> Mike: EXACTLY BILL.
AND GUN ONCE YOU GET THE
PUBLIC APPEAL, HAVE YOU
IMAGES THIS GOOD.
YOU HAVE TO GO BACK TO WHAT
THE FEDERAL INVESTIGATORS
SAY.
SOMEONE OUT THERE KNOWS WHO
THEY ARE.
THEY PUT OUT A WORD OF
CAUTION AS THEY HAVE TO AN
EXTENT.
DEPOSIT PEW ADVERTISE THE
GENERAL PUBLIC.
THE WORD OF CAUTION YOU
KNOW THESE INDIVIDUALS HAVE
KILLED THUS FAR.
AT LEAST ACCORDING TO THE
FEDERAL INVESTIGATORS IF
THEY INDEED ARE
RESPONSIBLE.
THEY ARE VIOLENT.
YOU HAVE TO ASSUME THEY'RE
VIOLENT AND THE FEDERAL
INVESTIGATORS WANT TO GET
INFORMATION ABOUT THESE
INDIVIDUALS.
THEY CERTAINLY DON'T WANT
ANYONE TO APPROACH THEM,
BILL?
>> Bill: MIKE, THANKS, MIKE
TOBIN WITH ME TONIGHT HERE
IN BOSTON AS WELL.
SO WHAT ARE LAW
ENFORCEMENT EXPERTS TELLING
US ABOUT WHERE WE ARE IN
THE INVESTIGATION?
"THE FOX REPORT'S"
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
IS LIVE IN OUR NEWSROOM IN
NEW YORK WITH MORE ON THIS.
JONATHAN, GOOD EVENING TO
YOU.
>> GOOD EVENING, BILL.
ANY LAW ENFORCEMENTICS PERT
WILL TELL YOU THAT
INVESTIGATORS WOULD HAVE
FAR PREFERRED TO MOVE IN
QUIETLY TO QUIETLY PICK UP
THESE GUYS WITHOUT
APPEALING FOR HELP FROM THE
PUBLIC IT HE WILLS YOU THUS
FAR IN THAT EFFORT THEY
HAVE CLEARLY DRAWN A BLANK
IN TRACKING THESE TWO MEN.
NOW THEY NEED THE PUBLIC'S
HELP.
YOU COMPARE THIS, FOR
INSTANCE, IN THE PUBLIC
APPEAL HERE TO THE CASE OF
FIESEL SHAH SAD.
A PAKISTANI CITIZEN WHO
ATTEMPTED TO SET OFF A CAR
BOMB IN TIMES SQUARE IN MAY
OF 2010.
POLICE HAVE VIDEO OF HIM.
THEY HAD AN I.D.
THEY DID NOT FEEL IT
NECESSARY TO PUT THAT OUT
PUBLICLY.
THEY SIMPLY TAILED HIM.
HE THEY PUT HIM ON A NO FLY
LIST.
I'M NOT QUITE SURE WHY WE
ARE SEEING THE BOSTON
SUSPECTS HERE.
WE ARE TALKING ABOUT FIESEL
SHAH SAD.
THEY SURVEILLED HIM.
THEY TRACKED HIM IN THE END
AND HE WAS FOUND TRYING TO
GET ON A FLIGHT OUT OF
COUNTRY AT JFK.
SO, WHAT WE KNOW FROM THIS
NOW IS THAT THEY NEED THE
HELP OF THE AMERICAN
PUBLIC, BILL.
LAW ENFORCEMENT EXPERTS
WOULD TELL YOU IT WOULD
SUGGEST THERE WAS A FAIR
DEGREE OF PLANNING IN THE
PLOT BY THESE TWO MEN IF,
INDEED, THEY ARE THE TWO
WHO CARRIED IT OUT.
THERE WAS A DEGREE OF
PLANNING FOR AN ESCAPE
ROUTE.
THEY WOULD ALSO SAY THAT IT
TELLS YOU IT MAY MEAN THAT
THEY HAVE HAD HELP IN
STAYING AT LARGE.
IT ALMOST CERTAINLY MEANS
ACCORDING TO LAW
ENFORCEMENT EXPERTS I HAVE
SPOKEN TO TONIGHT THAT
THESE TWO WERE NOT
PREVIOUSLY ON ANYONE'S
RADAR AS POTENTIAL
TERRORISTS.
BUT I THINK IT'S IMPORTANT
TO POINT OUT AS WELL, BILL,
AS WELL ASPECTS EXPLODES
ACROSS THE INTERNET TONIGHT
WHILE THESE IMAGES THAT WE
ARE LOOKING AT NOW CLEARLY
TELL US WHAT THESE TWO LOOK
LIKE, THEY TELL US
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
DEFINITIVELY ABOUT
MOTIVATION OR AFFILIATION
BILL.
>>
>> Bill: THANK YOU
JONATHAN.
JONATHAN HUNT LIVE IN NEW
YORK TONIGHT.
THE FBI SAYING HERE IN
BOSTON HOURS AGO QUOTE:
EACH PIECE OF EVIDENCE
MOVES US FORWARD TO
JUSTICE.
IF YOU HAVE INFORMATION
TIPS EVIDENCE, ANYTHING
THAT MAY HELP,
1-800-CALL-FBI 225-5324
THE NUMBER THAT IS NOW
PUBLIC AS WELL.
WE'RE WATCHING THIS TRAGEDY
IN TEXAS TONIGHT.
AND WHAT A SCENE THIS IS
TINY TOWN OF WEST TEXAS.
POLICE SAY THERE IS NO
TELLING HOW MANY PEOPLE DIE
WHEN A FERTILIZER PLANT
THERE CAUGHT FIRE AND
EXPLODED.
[EXPLOSION]
>>
>> Bill: THE BLAST AS
POWERFUL AS A SMALL
EARTHQUAKE.
>> THE SONIC BOOM, AT LEAST
THAT'S WHAT IT FELT LIKE.
>> THREW YOU DOWN ON THE
GROUND.
>> IF I HAD BEEN ON THAT
COUCH I WOULD BE DEAD.
>> Bill: SPREADING
DEVASTATION IN EVERY
DIRECTION.
>> THERE ARE HOMES LEVELED.
>> IT BLEW THE WINDOWS OUT.
>> THERE ARE BUSINESSES
LEVELED.
>> NO WINDOWS, NO DOORS
CEILING IS DOWN.
EVERYTHING IN THE HOUSE IS
JUST FLIPPED AROUND.
>> Bill: TONIGHT THE SEARCH
FOR VICTIMS AND THE SEARCH
FOR ANSWERS.
C-MAX two.
That's a super fuel-  efficient hybrid
for me.
And a long range  plug-in hybrid for
you.
Now, let's review.
Introducing the  Ford C-MAX Hybrid
and
the Ford C-MAX  Energi plug-in Hybrid.
Say hi to the  C-MAX Hybrids.
[ Female Announcer ]    THE ONLY PATCH
FOR THE TREATMENT    OF MILD TO MODERATE
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE    IS EXELON PATCH.
NOW WITH    MORE TREATMENT OPTIONS
EXELON PATCH MAY IMPROVE    OVERALL
FUNCTION AND COGNITION.    YOUR LOVED
ONE CAN GET    A FREE 30-DAY TRIAL.
AND YOU CAN HAVE    ACCESS TO NURSES.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE    HOW THE DISEASE
PROGRESSES.    HOSPITALIZATION
AND RARELY DEATH,    HAVE BEEN REPORTED
FROM WEARING    MORE THAN ONE PATCH
AT A TIME.    THE MOST COMMON SIDE
EFFECTS    ARE NAUSEA, VOMITING, DIARRHEA
FALL, LOSS OF APPETITE    OR WEIGHT,
APPLICATION SITE REDNESS,    AND URINARY
TRACT INFECTION.    THE LIKELIHOOD
AND SEVERITY    OF THESE SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCREASE    AS THE DOSE INCREASES
OR IF PATIENTS    WEIGH LESS THAN
110 POUNDS.    PEOPLE AT RISK    FOR
STOMACH ULCERS    WHO TAKE    CERTAIN
OTHER MEDICINES    SHOULD TALK TO
THEIR DOCTOR    AS SERIOUS STOMACH
PROBLEMS    SUCH AS BLEEDING MAY WORSEN.
PATIENTS MAY EXPERIENCE    SLOW HEART
RATE.    FREE TRIAL OFFER FOR THEM.
NURSES TO TALK TO FOR YOU.    VISIT
EXELONPATCHOFFER.COM.  ♪ ♪
WITH WILL MORE IN A MOMENT
IN THE BREANTS IN BOSTON.
THE FBI RELEASING PICTURES
OF THE MEMBER IT CALLS
SUSPECTS.
SUSPECTS FOR THE FIRST TIME
AFTER THE BOMBING ON MONDAY
IN THE BOSTON MARATHON.
THE MASSIVE EXPLOSION THAT
SHATTERED A SMALL TOWN IN
TEXAS.
AND TONIGHT INVESTIGATORS
SAY THEY STILL DON'T KNOW
HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE DEAD.
BUT THEY KNOW MORE THAN 160
ARE HURT.
AND THE SEARCH GOES ON FOR
EVEN MORE VICTIMS NOW.
IT ALL STARTED LAST NIGHT
WHEN A FIRE BROKE OUT AT A
FERTILIZER PLANT IN THE
TOWN OF WEST, TEXAS.
THAT'S ABOUT 20 MILES NORTH
OF WACO.
ONE MAN WAS SHOOTING CELL
PHONE VIDEO OF THE FIRE
WHEN THE PLANT BLEW UP.
WATCH?
[EXPLOSION]
>> Bill: HE SAYS HE WAS
200 FEET AWAY AND GOT OUT
OF THERE AS FAST AS HE
POSSIBLY COULD.
>> IT WAS A GIANT FORCE OF
PRESSURE PUSHED ME BACK AND
THERE WAS SHRAPNEL FLYING
EVERYWHERE.
STILL SHAKEN UP.
I HAVE BEEN SHAKEN UP SINCE
THE WHOLE THING HAPPEN.
PROBABLY THE WORST THING I
HAVE EVER SEEN IN MY LIFE.
>> Bill: PEOPLE SAY THEY
HEARD AND FELT THE
EXPLOSION ABOUT 50 MILES
AWAY.
JUST THINK ABOUT THAT
NEIGHBORS SAY IT BLEW THEM
RIGHT OFF THEIR FEET,
LEVELING HOMES AND
BUSINESSES IN A FOUR BLOCK
AREA SURROUNDING THAT
PLANT.
>> IT PICKED US UP AND
THREW US DOWN ON THE
GROUND.
IT BLEW THE SHRUBS THAT I
HAVE DOWN ON MY HOUSE
PARALLEL.
IT UP SOUND THE LIKE
PEBBLES BEING THROWN
THROUGH THE AIR IT WAS
HORRIFIC.
>> I WAS PICKED UP AND
THROWN.
I WENT UPSTAIRS.
IF I HADN'T, THE COUCH THAT
I HAD BEEN ON WHEN I CAME
DOWN, I LOOKED AT IT, THE
COUCH WASN'T THERE.
IT WAS RIGHT IN FRONT OF A
BIG BAY WINDOW AND IT WAS
SHREDDED FROM THE GLASS
FROM THE BAY WINDOW.
IF I HAD BEEN ON THAT
COUCH, I WOULD BE DEAD.
>> HE IS ONE LUCKY MAN.
HERE IS A LOOK AT HOW FAR
THE DEVASTATION EXTENDED.
POLICE SAY THE BLAST
DAMAGED OR DESTROYED DOZENS
OF HOME AN APARTMENT
COMPLEX AND SCHOOLS.
DOMINIC DI-NATALE LIVE IN
WEST, TEXAS.
WHAT IS THE LATEST ON THE
RECOVERY EFFORT THAT'S
ONGOING THERE TONIGHT?
>> BILL, THE AUTHORITIES
HAVE SPENT THE DAY DOING
WHAT THEY DESCRIBE AS A
METICULOUS INCH BY INCH
SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS AND
THE BODIES OF THE DEAD HERE
IN WEST, TEXAS.
IT'S A GRUELING EFFORT
HERE.
YOU HAVE HOUSES THAT HAVE
BEEN SPLINTERED TO DEATH.
WIPED OUT AND CARE HOME
THAT'S BEEN DEVASTATED AS
WELL.
THIS IS HOW THE AUTHORITIES
DESCRIBE THE SCENE AND
EFFORT UNDERWAY.
TAKE A LISTEN, BILL.
>> WE NEED EVERY AMBULANCE
WE CAN GET THIS WAY.
A BOMB JUST WENT OFF INSIDE
HERE.
IT'S PRETTY BAD.
WE HAVE A LOT OF THE
FIREMEN DOWN.
>> FIREFIGHTERS DOWN.
THERE HAS BEEN AN
EXPLOSION.
THERE ARE FIREFIGHTERS
DOWN.
>> THE REST HOME HAS BEEN
SERIOUSLY DAMAGED.
WE HAVE MANY PEOPLE DOWN.
PLEASE RESPOND.
>> I'M GETTING YOU
EVERYBODY I CAN.
YOU HAVE DEPUTIES.
YOU HAVE FIRE.
YOU HAVE EMS.
I AM SENDING EVERYBODY I
HAVE GOT.
>> SORRY, THAT WAS THE
EMERGENCY SERVICES AND HOW
THEY RESPONDED IN THE
IMMEDIATE AFTERMATH OF THE
NEWS OF THE EXPLOSION
TAKING PLACE THE
AUTHORITIES HERE SAYING
THEY ARE DOING ABSOLUTELY
EVERYTHING THEY CAN.
A FOUR BLOCK AREA.
A LARGE AREA FOR THEM TO
HAVE TO DEAL WITH.
THERE ARE SO MANY PEOPLE
BELIEVED TO BE EITHER
BURIED ALIVE OR MANY OF
THEM SUSPECTED NOW AFTER
THIS AMOUNT OF TIME TO BE
DEAD BILL.
>> Bill: WOW, YOU LOOK AT
THESE HOMES AND YOU HOW
THEY HAVE BEEN DAMAGED AND
YOU IMAGINE THE FORCE OF
THAT BLAST AND THE HEAT
THAT CAME OFF THAT PLANT AS
WELL.
WE'RE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT CAUSED THIS.
DO WE KNOW AT THIS POINT?
ARE WE ANY CLOSER TO THAT
ANSWER DOMINIC?
>> WHAT CAUSED THE BLAST
WELL IT APPEARS THAT WHEN
FIREFIGHTERS ATTENDED A
FIRE AT THE SCENE EARLIER
IN THE EVENING.
THEY STARTED POURING WATER.
THIS WAS AMMONIUM FACTORY.
WHEN AMMONIUM IS MIXED WITH
WATER IT BECOMES VERY
HAZARDOUS, THAT'S VERY MUCH
KNOWN.
THE SUSPICION AT THIS TIME
IS THAT MAY BE THE CAUSE OF
THE EXPLOSION.
WHAT WAS CAUSE OF THE
ORIGINAL FIRE, WE DON'T
ACTUALLY KNOW.
BACK IN JANUARY THERE WAS A
REPORT THAT THERE HAD BEEN
THE FACT THE PLANT HAD BEEN
BURNING PALLETS AND BRUSH
AND THEY HADN'T NOTIFIED
THE AUTHORITIES AND THAT A
LOCAL SCHOOL WAS EVACUATED
AS A RESULT OF THAT NO
DOUBT THE AUTHORITIES
LOOKING INTO WHETHER THERE
IS ANYTHING IN THAT AT ALL.
AT THIS TIME THEY STILL
DON'T KNOW.
BACK TO YOU, BILL.
>> Bill: THAT IS A
NIGHTMARE OF LIVING HELL
LAST NIGHT.
DOMINIC DI-NATALE, THANK
YOU, REPORTING IN THE TOWN
OF WEST, TEXAS FOR US.
ABOUT A 20 MINUTE DRIVE
SOUTH OF THAT BLAST SITE IS
THE TOWN OF WACO TEXAS.
20 YEARS AGO TOMORROW,
DAVID KARESH AND 75 MEMBERS
OF HIS BRANCH DA
INDIVIDUALIAN CULT DIED
THERE IN A HIGHLY
CONTROVERSIAL STANDOFF WITH
FEDERAL AGENTS.
THEY ATTEMPTED TO CARRY OUT
A SEARCH WARRANT.
WHAT FOLLOWED WAS A 50 DAY
SIEGE THAT ENDED WHEN THE
FEDS RAIDED THE PLACE AND
THE CULT'S COMPOUND BURNED
TO THE GROUND.
ALMOST EVERYONE INSIDE DIED
INCLUDING 20 CHILDREN.
THIS WEEK ALSO MARKS 66
YEARS SINCE THE DEADLIEST
INDUSTRIAL DISASTER IN OUR
NATION'S HISTORY.
IT ALSO HAPPENED IN THE
STATE OF TEXAS OUTSIDE OF
HOUSTON.
A FIRE ON BOARD A SHIP FULL
OF FERTILIZER KILLED NEAR
600 THERE.
THAT BLAST ALSO BLEW TWO
SMALL PLANES OUT OF THE SKY
AND CAUSED A 15-FOOT TITLED
TIDAL WAVE.
MANY OF THE VICTIMS OUTSIDE
OF HOUSTON THAT DAY WERE
NEVER FOUND.
BACK TO THE BREAKING NEWS
OF THE DAY HERE IN BOSTON.
THE HUNT FOR THE TWO
SUSPECTS FROM THE BOMBING
HERE.
AND IN A MOMENT WE WILL
TALK WITH ONE FORMER FBI
MAN WHO KNOWS A WHOLE ABOUT
TRACKING DOWN TERRORIST
SUSPECTS.
ONE TIME TOP AGENT IN NEW
YORK CITY.
THAT'S NEXT AS FOX REPORTS
LIVE TONIGHT AGAIN ON THIS
THURSDAY NIGHT IN BOSTON.
>> Bill: CONTINUING
COVERAGE NOW THE BREAKING
NEWS WE ARE WATCHING
TONIGHT IN BOSTON.
THE FBI ASKING FOR HELP NOW
TRACKING DOWN TWO SUSPECTS
IN MONDAY'S BOMBINGS AT THE
MARATHON HERE IN BOSTON.
BILL GOOD AFTERNOON FORMER
ASSISTANT DIRECTOR IN
CHARGE THE FBI IN NEW YORK
NOW MAKES HIM HOME HERE IN
NEW YORK.
WE SPOKE 11 HOURS AGO IN
AMERICA'S NEWSROOM ABOUT
WHAT COULD COME NEXT FROM
THE FBI.
IS THIS WHAT YOU EXPECTED?
>> YES BILL, IT IS WHAT I
EXPECTED THAT THE PHOTOS
WOULD BE RELEASED BECAUSE
IT TOOK THEM THAT LONG TO
SIFT THROUGH THE WHOLE
CO-LODGE OF PHOTOS THEY HAD
AND FILM ALL THE WAY BEFORE
THE FINISH LINE TO THE
FINISH LINE.
BILL, THE IMPORTANT THING
RIGHT NOW IS THAT ANYBODY
THAT WAS IN THE AREA AFTER
THE FINISH LINE OUGHT TO BE
LOOKING AT THEIR FILM THAT
THEY THOUGHT WAS IRRELEVANT
PRIOR TO THIS EVENT BECAUSE
THESE INDIVIDUALS DROPPED
THE BOMBS ON THE STREET AND
KEPT ON WALKING.
SO, RIGHT BEYOND THEM DOWN
BOYLSTON STREET WE HAVE
SUBWAY ENTRANCES TO TWO
DIFFERENT SUBWAY STATIONS
AND PEOPLE COULD HAVE SEEN
THEM GOING INTO THE SUBWAY
STATION PEOPLE COULD HAVE
BEEN TAKING PICTURES FROM
BEYOND THE FINISH LINE AND
SEEN THESE FOLKS THERE.
THAT'S VERY IMPORTANT FOR
THEM TO LOOK AT THE FILM
AGAIN IF THEY HAD ANYTHING.
>> Bill: THAT'S A GREAT
POINT THERE IS A SUBWAY
STOP 30 YARDS WHERE WE ARE
GOING TONIGHT IN BOYLSTON
STREET.
BILL, YOU HAVE WORKED THESE
STORIES AND BEEN IN THOSE
INVESTIGATIVE ROOMS.
WHAT ELSE DO WE HAVE THAT
WE HAVE NOT YET SEEN?
>> WELL, I THINK BILL,
PROBABLY YOU ARE NOT GOING
TO COME OUT AND TELL THE
PUBLIC EVERYTHING THAT YOU
HAVE.
YOU NORTH GOING TO HIDE
EVERYTHING TO TRY TO FOOL
THE PUBLIC BUT WHAT YOU ARE
GOING TO DO IS KEEP SOME
THINGS IN RESERVE THAT ONLY
SOMEBODY WOULD KNOW WHO HAD
BEEN THERE.
THE OTHER SIDE OF THAT COIN
IS, THEY NEED TO -- THEY
NEED TO LOOK AT EVERYTHING
THAT IS THERE.
AND SOME OF THESE THINGS
THEY ARE USING TO FILTER
SOME OF THE CALLS THAT ARE
COMING IN.
THEY ARE GETTING THOUSANDS
OF CALLS RIGHT NOW.
THERE ARE SOME THINGS THAT
THEY KNOW THAT THEY HAVEN'T
PUT OUT WHEREBY THEY COULD
DISCOUNT SOME THE CALLS
THEY THAT THEY ARE
RECEIVING.
>> Bill: THEY HAD TO BE RED
JR. TO THE ENACT THAT THEY
COULD GET AN ABSOLUTE AFTER
LANCASTER OF -- AFTER    --
AVALANCHE.
HAVE YOU BEEN THERE SINCE
THE BEGINNING LIKE THE
ENERGIZER BUNNY.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS THEY
HAVE A TO BE OF PEOPLE IN
RESERVE AND HAVE THESE
ELECTRONIC THINGS SET UP.
THEY DON'T NECESSARILY HAVE
TO TAKE THE CALLS IN THE
BOSTON AREA.
THEY CAN TAKE THEM ANY
PLACE IN THE COUNTRY
THAT'S HOW THEY ARE GOING
TO HANDLE IT.
>> Bill: BILL, THANK YOU.
BILL GAVIN WITH US AGAIN
TONIGHT IN BOSTON.
FORMER ASSISTANT DIRECTOR
IN CHARGE OF THE FBI IN NEW
YORK CITY.
LET'S GET A BREAK HERE IN A
MOMENT OUR COVERAGE
CONTINUES OF THE BOMBINGS
AT THE BOSTON MARATHON.
THESE ARE SIGNIFICANT
DEVELOPMENTS.
ONES THAT WE HAVE BEEN
WAITING DAYS FOR.
THE FBI NOW SEARCHING FOR
TWO SUSPECTS.
AND THEY ARE ASKING FOR
YOUR HELP.
TWO MEN, THE FEDS NOW SAY
ARE CONNECTED THE ATTACK
THAT KILLED THREE PEOPLE.
AND SEPTEMBER NEARLY 200
OTHERS TO THE HOSPITAL HERE
IN BOSTON.
MORE ON THAT AS OUR
COVERAGE CONTINUES IN
BOYLSTON STREET AS WE
REMEMBER THE THREE WHO WILL
NO LONGER BE WITH US HERE
IN BOSTON.
[ Male Announcer ]    DUNES, DESERT,
OR TRAIL    ONLY RZR DELIVERS.
NOW'S THE TIME TO BUY    DURING THE
POLARIS    XP SALES EVENT.    TAKE
YOUR PICK    OF OUR NEW LIMITED EDITION
RZRs    AND GET FINANCING    AS LOW
AS 2.99%.    SAVE EVEN MORE    WITH
REBATES UP TO $500...    OR TOTALLY
CUSTOMIZE    YOUR NEW RZR    WITH
UP TO $500    OF FREE POLARIS ACCESSORIES.
RAZOR SHARP PERFORMANCE    IS WAITING
FOR YOU    DURING THE POLARIS    XP
SALES EVENT.
♪ ♪    [ Male Announcer ]    FROM
THE WAY THE BRISTLES MOVE    TO THE
WAY THEY CLEAN,    ONCE YOU TRY AN
ORAL-B    DEEP SWEEP POWER BRUSH,
YOU'LL NEVER GO BACK    TO A REGULAR
MANUAL BRUSH.    ITS THREE CLEANING
ZONES    WITH DYNAMIC POWER BRISTLES
REACH BETWEEN TEETH    WITH MORE BRUSH
MOVEMENTS    TO REMOVE    UP TO 100%
MORE PLAQUE    THAN A REGULAR MANUAL
BRUSH.    AND EVEN 76% MORE PLAQUE
THAN SONICARE FLEXCARE    IN HARD
TO REACH AREAS.    ORAL-B DEEP SWEEP
5000    POWER BRUSH.    LIFE OPENS
UP WHEN YOU DO.
>> Bill: UPDATING TOP STORY
TONIGHT.
HUGE DEVELOPMENT IN THE
INVESTIGATION OF THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBING.
JUST A COUPLE HOURS AGO THE
FBI RELEASING THE
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO OFF THE
BOMBING SUSPECTS.
THE IMAGES OF TWO MEN IN
BASEBALL HATS WALKING DOWN
BOYLSTON STREET WITH
BACKPACKS IN THE DIRECTION
OF THE MARATHON FINISH
LINE.
ALL OF THIS SHORTLY BEFORE
THE DEADLY BLAST WENT OFF.
THE FBI HAS NAMED THEM
SUSPECT ONE WITH A DARK
HAT, SUSPECT 2 WITH THE
WHITE HAT.
AND INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY
CONSIDER THE SUSPECT ARMED
AND EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
CRAIG BOSWELL LIVE HERE IN
BOSTON WITH US HERE AGAIN
TONIGHT.
CRAIG, GOOD EVENING.
>> WILL, GOOD EVENING TO
YOU.
ADDING TO THAT FBI SAYS IF
YOU SEE THEM, YOU KNOW
THEM, DO NOT APPROACH THEM.
DO NOT TRY TO APPREHEND
THEM.
ALSO, THIS IS COMING ON AN
ENORMOUSLY BUSY NEWS DAY
HERE IN BOSTON.
THIS VIDEO AND I DON'T
THINK WE CAN SHOW THIS TO
YOU ENOUGH.
THIS VIDEO AND THESE
PHOTOS.
INCREDIT DIB CLEAR THESE
TWO SUSPECTS AT ONE POINT
THEY ARE SEEING ONE WALK
BEHIND THE OTHER NEAR THE
FINISH LINE.
ONE IN A BLACK HAT, THE
GENTLEMAN IN THE BLACK HAT
AND A WHITE COLLARLESS
SHIRT.
THE OTHER A WHITE HAT
TURNED AROUND BACKWARDS
THAT IS SUSPECT NUMBER 2.
THAT IS IN THE AREA OF THE
SECOND BOMB BLAST.
THEY HAVE SEEN HIM OF VIDEO
OF ACTUALLY SETTING THAT
JACKET DOWN THERE OR THAT
WITH THAT BOMB ENCASED IN
THAT.
THAT'S THE ONE THAT THE TWO
GENTLEMEN WANT YOU TO CALL
IN DO NOT APPROACH THEM AND
LET THEM KNOW IF YOU KNOW
THESE TWO GENTLEMEN,
SOMEONE KNOWS THEM AND SEES
WHO WILL HE THEY ARE.
>> Bill: CRAIG BOSWELL
THANKS.
DOWN THE STREET HERE FROM
OUR LOCATION.
A MOVING SCENE AT LAST
NIGHT'S BOSTON BRUINS
HOCKEY GAME.
THE FIRST MAJOR SPORTING
EVENT OF ANY KIND HERE
SINCE THE BOMBINGS AND
BEFORE THE PUCK WAS
DROPPED.
THAT TEAM PAID TRIBUTE TO
THE VICTIMS, THE FIRST
RESPONDERS AND ALL THOSE
AFFECTED.
BOSTON STRONG DISPLAYED ON
THE ICE AND THROUGH THE
ARENA.
FOLKS BROUGHT FLAGS AND
HAND MADE SIGNS.
WHEN IT CAME TIME FOR THE
STAR SPANGLED STAR-SPANGLED
BANNER TO START.
LONG TIME SINGER STARTED
BUT THE FANS HANDLED THE
REST.
♪ O SAY DOES THAT
STAR-SPANGLED BANNER YET
WAVE
♪ OVER THE LAND OF THE FREE
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE BRAVE
[CHEERS AND APPLAUSE]