FORMER TEXAS GOVERNOR HAD
ALREADY MADE NORRIS AN HONORARY
TEXAS RANGER.
WHAT IS BETTER, A RANGER OR
CITIZEN?
HERE'S SHEP.
>> Shepard: FIRST FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK, A PIVOTAL MOMENT FOR
THE UNITED STATES AND A WORLD.
A MAJOR SHIFT FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP HIMSELF THIS AFTERNOON
DURING A JOINT NEWS CONFERENCE
WITH JORDAN'S KING ABDULLAH.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THE LATEST
ACTS OF BARBER AL-ASSAD CAN'T BE
TOLERATED.
>> THAT ACT ON CHILDREN HAD A
BEEN IMPACT ON ME.
IT WAS A HORRIBLE THING.
I'VE BEEN WATCHING IT AND SEEING
IT.
IT DOESN'T GET ANY WORSE THAN
THAT.
I HAVE THAT FLEXIBILITY, AND
IT'S VERY, VERY POSSIBLE -- AND
I WILL TELL YOU, IT'S ALREADY
HAPPENED -- THAT MY ATTITUDE
TOWARD SYRIA AND ASSAD HAS
CHANGED VERY MUCH.
>> IT'S ALREADY HAPPENED, HIS
ATTITUDE AND SYRIA AND ASSAD HAS
CHANGED.
DOES THAT MEAN THAT THE UNITED
STATES WILL BECOME FOR ENGAGED
IN THE CONFLICT?
THE PRESIDENT WAS NOT SPECIFIC.
WHEN ADD IN SYRIA'S ACTIONS
CROSSED A RED LINE, HE SAID
THIS.
>> IT CROSSED A LOT OF LINES FOR
ME.
WHEN YOU KILL INNOCENT CHILDREN,
INNOCENT BABIES, BABY, LITTLE
BABIES, WITH A CHEMICAL GAS THAT
IS SO LETHAL THAT PEOPLE WERE
SHOCKED TO HEAR WHAT GAS IT WAS,
THAT CROSSES MANY, MANY LINES,
BEYOND A RED LINES.
>> Shepard: BEYOND A RED LINE.
THE BACKGROUND HERE IS
IMPORTANT.
YOU MAY REMEMBER PRESIDENT OBAMA
IN 2012 WARNED THAT BARBER
AL-ASSAD CROSSED A RED LINE
SHOULD HE USE CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
THE DICTATOR DID USE THEM
ANYWAY.
PRESIDENT OBAMA RESPONDED WITH
DIPLOMACY AND STEAD OF MILITARY
ACTION.
>> THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION HAD
AN OPPORTUNITY TO SOLVE THIS
CRISIS WHEN HE SET THE RED LINE
IN THE SAND.
WHEN HE DIDN'T CROSS THAT RED
LINE AFTER MAKING THE THREAT,
THAT SET US BACK A LONG WAYS NOT
ONLY IN SYRIA BUT IN MANY OTHER
PARTS OF THE WORLD.
BECAUSE IT WAS A BLANK THREAT.
I THINK IT WAS SOMETHING THAT
WAS NOT ONE OF OUR BETTER DAYS
AS A COUNTRY.
>> THAT WAS 2012.
AND CITIZEN TRUMP URGED OBAMA
NOT TO INTERVENE IN SYRIA.
HE TWEETED THIS.
HE ALSO TWEETED --
>> Shepard: NOW THE PRESIDENT
SAYS HE'S CHANGED HIS MIND.
THAT IT'S NOW HIS
RESPONSIBILITY, AND THAT HE WILL
ACT.
THIS IS THE FIRST TIME THE
PRESIDENT HAS BLAMED BARBER
AL-ASSAD FOR KILLING HIS OWN
PEOPLE.
YESTERDAY THE ATTACK WAS
LAUNCHED KILLING DOZENS OF
PEOPLE INCLUDING CHILDREN ASLEEP
IN THEIR BEDS.
RUSSIA HAS BLAMED IT ON THE
SYRIAN REBELS.
THEY'RE SUPPORTED BY THE UNITED
STATES.
OFFICIALS IN MOSCOW SAYS A
SYRIAN AIR STRIKE HIT A WEAPONS
DUMP THAT RELEASED THE DEADLY
CHEMICALS.
HERE'S THE BIG PICTURE.
THIS SORT OF THING HAS BEEN
HAPPENING FOR YEARS.
THE SYRIAN DICTATOR'S BARREL
BOMBS HAVE KILLED TENS OF
THOUSANDS IF NOT HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF INNOCENT VICTIMS
INCLUDING WOMEN AND BABIES IN
THEIR BEDS.
THAT TOO IS A WAR CRIME.
BUT IT'S A HORRIFIC VIDEO THAT
THE PRESIDENT SAID CHANGED HIS
MINDS AND THE NATION'S POLICY
TOWARDS THIS CONFLICT.
WE HAVE NO WAY TO KNOW WHETHER
THE PRESIDENT WAS SIGNALLING AN
IMMEDIATE MILITARY RESPONSE.
OF THIS WE'RE SURE.
THE SYRIAN REGIME IS BACKED BY
THE RUSSIANS.
THE RUSSIANS ARE FIGHTING WITH
THEM AS ARE IRANIANS.
SHOULD THE UNITED STATES ENTER
THIS CONFLICT, SUPPORTING
MILITARILY THE REBELS, FIGHTING
AGAINST THE SYRIANS, WE WOULD BE
FIGHTING THE RUSSIANS AND THE
IRANIANS.
THE CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JOHN ROBERTS IS
LIVE AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
HE WAS NOT SPECIFICALLY AND
CAREFULLY NOT SO.
>> HE'S BEEN STUDIOUSLY
NONSPECIFIC ABOUT WHAT ACTION HE
WILL TAKE ACROSS THE WORLD.
HE'S BEEN VERY STUDIOUS SAYING
TOO OFTEN THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION WAS TELEGRAPHING
WHAT SORT OF ACTION THEY WOULD
TAKE.
HE GOES BACK TO MOSUL.
THEY TELEGRAPHED WHAT THEY WOULD
DO IN MOSUL TELLING LEADERS WHAT
THEY WOULD DO TO DIG IN OR GET
OUT.
IT'S CLEAR THIS ATTACK YESTERDAY
IN SYRIA HAS HAD A PROFOUND
IMPACT ON THE PRESIDENT.
HE TALKED ABOUT THE IMAGES OF
LITTLE CHILDREN, LITTLE BABIES
DYING AND SUFFERING HORRIBLY IN
THE WAKE OF IN GAS ATTACK.
SAYING THAT IT HAS CROSSED A
NUMBER OF LINES, NOT JUST A RED
LINE, AND IT WOULD SEEM CLEAR
THAT HE WOULD HAVE TO TAKE SOME
SORT OF ACTION IN THE WAKE OF
ALL OF THIS.
TALKING ABOUT IT IN THE STRIDENT
TERMS THAT HE HAS BEEN, BUT
BEING DELIBERATELY AMBIGUOUS
ABOUT WHAT THE UNITED STATES'
RESPONSE MIGHT BE.
HERE'S THE PRESIDENT.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS YOU'VE
NOTICED ABOUT ME IS MILITARILY,
I DON'T LIKE TO SAY WHERE I'M
GOING, WHAT I'M DOING.
I WATCHED ATTACK ADMINISTRATIONS
SAYING WE WILL ATTACK SUCH AND
SUCH A DAY AND SUCH AND SUCH AN
HOUR.
I'M NOT SAYING I'M DOING ONE
THING.
I'M NOT GOING TO TELL YOU, AS
MUCH AS I RESPECT YOU.
>> THIS COULD BE A GAME CHANGER
IN THE POSTURE TOWARDS SYRIA.
THE ADMINISTRATION SAID THAT
REGIME CHANGE WAS NOT A
PARTICULAR PRIORITY FOR THE U.S.
NOW IT LOOKS LIKE THE PRESIDENT
MAY BE CHANGING HIS MIND, IF NOT
ON REGIME CHANGE, AT LEAST IN
THE UNITED STATES APPROACH TO
AL-ASSAD.
IT LOOKS LIKE HE HAS A POWERFUL
ALLY WITH THE KING OF JORDAN
STANDING AT THE PRESIDENT'S
STRIDE WHO IS STRIDENT IN HIS
CONDEMNATION OF WHAT HAPPENED IN
SYRIA.
>> AND THE PRESENCE OF KING
ABDULLAH GAVE THIS MORE GRAVITY.
SPEAKING ON A WORLD STAGE AND
CERTAINLY ON LIVE TELEVISION.
WHEN YOU CAN CONSIDER WHAT THE
OPTICS OF THIS ARE, JORDAN, THE
UNITED STATES, SYRIAN REBELS
AGAINST THE RUSSIANS AND
IRANIANS.
THAT'S WORLD WAR DEFINED.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AT IN FROM THE
30,000 FOOT LEVEL, IT'S CLEAR
WHAT TRANSPIRED IN THE LAST HOUR
AT THE WHITE HOUSE WILL HAVE A
PROFOUND IMPACT ON EVERYTHING
GOING ON IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID IN THE
PAST, AS A CANDIDATE AND AS
PRESIDENT THERE'S A PROBLEM WITH
REGIME CHANGE.
THIS IS PURSUED BY.
PRESIDENTS BEFORE HIM.
WHEN YOU HAVE A REGIME CHANGE,
YOU WIND UP IN A WORSE SPOT THAN
YOU DID BEFORE EXACTING A CHANGE
AT THE TOP.
HE SAID WHO ARE THESE PEOPLE
FIGHTING IN SYRIA?
WE DON'T FLOW WHO THEY ARE.
WHILE THIS MAY HAVE CHANGED HIS
APPROACH TO BASSER AL-ASSAD, IT
SHOWS HE DOESN'T HAVE ANY TRUST
OF THE PLAYER THERE'S IN SYRIA.
UNCLEAR WHAT HE WILL DO.
>> JOHN ROBERTS, THANK YOU.
LET'S TURN TO JOSH LETTERMAN.
HE'S A FOREIGN POLICY REPORTER
FOR THE FOREIGN PRESS.
IT WOULD APPEAR THAT WE'RE TO
TAKE HIM LITERALLY AND
SERIOUSLY, SEEMS LIKE A MAJOR
FOREIGN POLICY SHIFT.
>> IF HE IS INDEED CHANGING THE
WAY HE VIEWS ASSAD AND CHANGING
FROM JUST A FEW DAYS AGO WHEN
MULTIPLE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS WERE SAYING THAT IT
WAS NO LONGER A U.S. PRIORITY TO
GET RID OF ASSAD IN SYRIA, THAT
WOULD BE A MAJOR SHIFT.
WHAT WE DON'T KNOW YET FROM
TRUMP, WHAT IS HE GOING TO DO
ABOUT IT.
THAT IS WHY THIS IS SUCH A
DEFINING MOMENT FOR HIM.
IT'S ONE OF THE FIRST MAJOR
OVERSEAS CRISES THAT HE'S HAD TO
DEAL WITH AND THE FIRST TIME
HE'S HAD TO TRANSLATE THE TOUGH
TALK ABOUT DEALING WITH
ADVERSARIES AND DEALING WITH
DIFFICULT DECISIONS INTO ACTUAL
ACTION.
WE'RE DEFINITELY SEEING ALREADY
COUNTRIES AROUND THE WORLD THAT
ARE LOOKING TO THE U.S. FOR
LEADERSHIP.
ONE TO KNOW IF THIS IS A SIGNAL
OF A MILITARY RESPOND THE U.S.
CONSIDERING AS NIKKI HALEY
SEEMED TO SUGGEST AT THE
SECURITY COUNCIL OR IF IT'S
GOING TO BE MORE RHETORIC THAT
DOESN'T AMOUNT TO ANYTHING.
TRUMP VERY RELUCTANT TO SHOW ANY
LEG ON THAT AT THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY.
>> Shepard: JOSH, BASED ON YOUR
REPORTING, HUGH WOULD A
STATEMENT LIKE THIS IN THAT
SETTING, ACCOMPANIED BY THAT
WORLD LEADER, BE RECEIVED IN
TEHRAN, MOSCOW, DAMASCUS?
>> I THINK WITH SOME UN
CERTAINTY.
PEOPLE ARE HEARTENED TO HEAR THE
PRESIDENT SO FORCEFULLY, TALKING
IN EMOTIONAL TERMS ABOUT THE
VICTIMS OF THE ATTACK.
BUT TALK IS TALK.
REALLY WHAT PEOPLE WANT TO SEE
IS THERE GOING TO BE A
DIFFERENCE FROM THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION IN WHAT ACTUALLY
HAPPENS ON THE GROUND.
IS THE U.S. GOING TO TRY TO
STRIKE ASSAD TO DEAL WITH HIS
ABILITY TO CARRY OUT THE
ATTACKS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ACKNOWLEDGED,
HE'S BEEN VERY RELUCTANT TO FIRE
THE U.S. IN CONFLICTS IN THE
MIDDLE EAST BUT HE HAS SAID HIS
VIEW HAS CHANGED DRAMATICALLY.
IT'S EARLY TO KNOW WHETHER THIS
WILL AFFECT HOW TRUMP IS
AFFECTING THE CIVIL WAR IN SYRIA
AND THE FIGHT AGAINST THE
ISLAMIC STATE GROUP IN SYRIA,
WHICH PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS SAID
IS HIS TOP PRIORITY.
>> JOSH LEDDERMAN AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THANK YOU.
LET'S GO TO CHARLES HANDLEMAN
FROM THE BROOKINGS INSTITUTE IN
WASHINGTON.
WHAT DOES THIS SIGNAL TO YOU AND
HOW WOULD THIS SIGNAL BE
RECEIVED IN YOUR MIND IN THOSE
CAPITOLS OF DAMASCUS, MOSCOW AND
BEYOND?
>> THERE ARE WAYS FOR.
TRUMP TO BE VERY TOUGH ON ASSAD
WITHOUT CHANGING HIS PREVIOUS
POLICY.
I AGREE WITH THE DISCUSSION THAT
YOU WERE JUST ENGAGED IN WITH
YOUR COLLEAGUES AND OTHERS ON
WHETHER TRUMP HAS TAKEN A WHOLE
NEW PERSPECTIVE ON ASSAD.
CLEARLY HE HAS.
BUT IT DOESN'T MEAN HE NEEDS TO
MAKE ASSAD THE FOCUS OPEN
AMERICAN REGIME CHANGE.
WE HAVE ATTEMPTED THAT FOR SIX
YEARS.
IT HASN'T WORKED.
WE'VE HAD THAT AS OUR FORMAL
POLICY SINCE PRESIDENT OBAMA
ARTICULATED THAT IN 2007.
WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP COULD SAY,
I WANT TO PROTECT THE SAFE
HAVENS THAT HE'S TALKED ABOUT.
TURN THEM INTO AUTONOMOUS PARTS
OF SYRIA OVER TIME AND HELP THE
REGIONS IF WE EVER GET TO A
PEACEFUL PERIOD TO HELP
RECONSTRUCT THEMSELVES, HE
DOESN'T HAVE TO GIVE ANY MONEY
OR DIPLOMATIC SUPPORT AND HOPE
THAT SOME OTHER PROCESS PUSHES
HIM OUT OF POWER.
THAT MAY NOT WORK ANY TIME SOON
BUT IT WOULDN'T BE UN PRECEDE
PRECEDENTED.
LIKE SERBIA AND BOSNIA AND
KOSOVO.
WE DID NOT MAKE REGIME CHANGE A
FOREIGN POLICY GOAL.
HIS OWN PEOPLE UNSEEDED HIM AND
ENDED UP IN A WAR TIMES TRIAL
BEFORE HIS DEATH.
THERE'S A NUMBER OF WAYS TO
THINK THIS THROUGH THAT ALLOW
YOU TO BE TOUGH ON ASSAD AND
KNOW IT'S TOUGH TO OVERTHROW
HIM.
>> Shepard: IT'S HARD TO KNOW
WHAT HAS CHANGED.
IT'S WITHOUT QUESTION THAT THE
SYRIAN REGIMES TO USE BARREL
BOMBS TO KILL BABIES IN THEIR
BEDS BY THE HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS IN WHAT IS
UNQUESTIONABLY A SERIES OF WAR
CRIMES.
NOW THERE'S VIDEO OF THIS AS
HORRIFIC AS IT IS, THERE IS NO
CHANGE IN ACTION AND ATTITUDE.
THIS IS A CONTINUATION OF A
THEME.
>> I AGREE WITH THAT 100%.
I THINK WHAT YOU'RE SEEING IS
THE EDUCATION OF AN AMERICAN
PRESIDENT.
ALL OF US HAS BEEN HARDENED BY
THE WARS OF THE MIDDLE EAST TO
THE POINT THAT IT WAS EASIER TO
FRANKLY TURN OFF THE TELEVISION
AND NOT PAY ATTENTION TO THESE
TRAGEDIES BECAUSE WE BEGAN TO
DOUBT IF WE CAN DO ANYTHING
ABOUT THEM ANYWAY.
OF COURSE, FOR MANY REPUBLICANS,
IT WAS PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
POLICIES THAT WERE CAUSING THE
PROBLEMS PREVIOUSLY.
WE'VE HEARD SEAN SPICER SAY THAT
THIS WEEK.
BUT TODAY OR YESTERDAY,
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAD TO CONFRONT
THIS VISUAL BEFORE HIS OWN EYES
ON HIS WATCH.
I THINK IT'S GOT TO FEEL
DIFFERENT WHEN YOU'RE SITTING IN
THAT OVAL OFFICE THAN IT WOULD
HAVE EVER FELT AS A CONSUMER OF
THE NECESSARY.
THAT'S WHAT'S CHANGED.
IT'S THE WAY IN WHICH MR. TRUMP
HIMSELF HAS BECOME ENGAGED IN
THE WHOLE PROCESS.
>> Shepard: THANKS, MICHAEL.
I APPRECIATE IT.
THE PRESIDENT NOW TELLS "THE NEW
YORK TIMES" WITH NO EVIDENCE TO
BACK IT UP THAT THE FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR SUSAN
RICE MAY HAVE COMMITTED A CRIME.
THE IDENTITIES WERE REVEALED IN
INTELLIGENCE REPORTS AFTER THEY
WERE MENTIONED IN INTERCEPTED
COMMUNICATIO
COMMUNICATIONS.
THE PRESIDENT DID NOT OFFER A
SLIVER OF EVIDENCE AND REFUSED
TO SAY IF HE'S SEEN ANY NEW
INTELLIGENCE THAT WOULD BACK
THIS UP.
THAT'S COMING UP FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK ON A WEDNESDAY
AFTERNOON.
Over hereNo!ver here!
(Dog barking)
Whoever threw it
has to go get it.
Not me!
Somebody will get it...
♪
(Dog barking)
Anyone can dream.
Making it a reality
is the hard part.
From the B-2 to
the upcoming B-21,
Northrop Grumman
stealth bombers give
America an advantage
in a turbulent world.
And we're looking for a
few dreamers to join us.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
HE THINKS THE FORMER NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISERS SUSAN RICE MAY
HAVE COMMITTED A CRIME WHEN SHE
ASKED FOR THE NAMES OF THE
PEOPLE CAUGHT UP IN FOREIGN
SURVEILLANCE.
THE NEW YORK TIMES BROKE THE
STORY.
THE TIMES REPORTS THE PRESIDENT
DID NOT SUPPORT ANY OWED TO
SUPPORT HIS CLAIMS.EY WERE SURV
TARGETS AND THE NAMES OF PEOPLE
WITHIN TRUMP'S ORBIT SHOWED UP.
ANALYSTS SAY IT IS LEGAL FOR A
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR TO ASK
FOR THE NAMES OF AMERICANS
MENTIONED IN INTELLIGENCE
REPORTS.
SHE SAYS THAT'S WHAT SHE DID.
RICE SAID SHE HAD TO DO THAT AS
PART OF HER JOB.
SHE DENIED SHE LEAKED ANY
INFORMATION TO ANYONE.
SO FAR THERE IS NO PROOF OF ANY
KIND OF WHICH FOX NEWS IS AWARE
THAT SHE DID.
THE CHIEF NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE
CORRESPONDENCE CATHERINE
HERRIDGE IS IN WASHINGTON.
HOW DOES THIS UNMASKING WORK?
>> OKAY.
UNMASKING IS A SIMPLE PROCESS.
IN THIS CASE, THE NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER, SUSAN RICE,
WOULD HAVE CONTACTED THE NSA,
THE AGENCY THAT RUNS
SURVEILLANCE AND ASKED TO HAVE
U.S. PERSON 1 OR AMERICAN 1
IDENTIFIED BY THEIR NAME.
THE NSA WOULD HAVE TO BE
SATISFIED THAT THIS IS A
REASONABLE RE-QUEST AND HAS A
NATIONAL SECURITY FOUNDATION FOR
THEM TO IDENTIFY THAT AMERICAN.
WHAT IS ILLEGAL HERE IS IF THOSE
NAMES, ONCE THEY'RE IDENTIFIED,
ARE THEN GIVEN TO THE MEDIA OR
TO INDIVIDUALS WHO DON'T HAVE A
NEED TO KNOW.
THERE'S ANOTHER DEVELOPMENT ON
THIS, WHICH DOES RAISE QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHAT SUSAN RICE SAID TO
NBC YESTERDAY.
SHE SAID THIS WAS ALL IN THE
COURSE OF THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
WHILE WE CAN'T INDEPENDENTLY
REVIEW THE DOCUMENTS,
CONGRESSMAN PETER KING, A
REPUBLICAN ON THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE WAS
BRIEFED ON THE DOCUMENTS AND HE
SAID NOTHING IN THEM RELATED TO
RUSSIA AND THE DETAILS WERE
HIGHLY PERSONAL IN NATURE.
>> THIS IS INFORMATION ABOUT
EVERYDAY LIVES, WHO THEY WERE
TALKING TO, MEETING TO EAT,
NOTHING OF ANY SUBSTANCE OF
VALUE UNLESS YOU'RE TRYING TO
LAY SOMETHING OUT ON SOMEBODY.
>> IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO REACH
CONCLUSIONS WHO HAS MORE MERIT
TO THE STORY UNTIL WE CAN SEE
THE DOCUMENTS, IF THEY'RE EVER
DECLASSIFIED.
THIS SEEMS TO ME A CLASSIC CASE
OF THE GLASS BEING HALF FULL,
HALF EMPTY.
THOSE THAT SUPPORT THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION SAID THEY WERE
DOING DUE DILIGENCE.
THOSE THAT SUPPORT THE PRESIDENT
SAID IT AMOUNTED TO POLITICAL
SPYING.
>> Shepard: MIGHT SHE BE CALLED
AS A WITNESS?
>> IT'S HIGHLY LIKELY.
WE HEARD FROM A RANKING
DEMOCRAT.
HE WAS SPOKING TO CNN THIS
MORNING AND HE SAID THAT THEY
WOULD BE OPEN TO HAVING RICE
TESTIFY, BUT HE DIDN'T SPEAK TO
THE MERITS OF WHAT HER TESTIMONY
WOULD BE.
>> THAT'S A FAR CRY FROM ANY
SUGGESTION THAT BARACK OBAMA WAS
WIRETAPPING DONALD TRUMP.
THEY'RE TRYING TO THROW UP THIS
SMOKE SCREEN IN AN EFFORT NOT
ONLY TO DIVERT THE ATTENTION OF
OUR COMMITTEE FROM THE RUSSIAN
INVESTIGATION BUT TO SOMEHOW
JUSTIFY THESE UNJUSTIFIABLE
COMMENTS BY THE PRESIDENT.
>> THAT WASN'T THE SOUND BITE I
WAS EXPECTING.
HE SAID THAT HE WAS OPEN TO
HAVING HER.
RIGHT THERE HE'S SAYING THIS IS
AN EFFORT BY THE WHITE HOUSE TO
CHANGE THE MEANING.
HE SAID HE WOULD BE OPEN TO
HAVING RICE TESTIFY BUT IT'S
GOING TO DEPENDS ON WHAT THEY
FIND IN THE COURSE OF THEIR
INVESTIGATION.
SUSAN RICE SAYS SHE NEEDS TO SEE
HOW THINGS DEVELOP BEFORE SHE
WOULD MAKE THAT KIND OF
COMMITMENT.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE HERRIDGE
IN WASHINGTON, THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Shepard: AT THE ROOT OF THIS,
THE RUSSIANS INTERFERED IN THE
UNITED STATES PRESIDENTIAL
ELECTION.
THAT IS NOT IN QUESTION.
THEY WORKED TO HELP DONALD
TRUMP'S CHANCES OF BECOMING
QUESTION AND HURTING HILLARY
CLINTON'S CHANCES.
THERE'S THREE SEPARATE
INVESTIGATIONS INTO THIS NOW IN
THE HOUSE, THE SENATE AND BY THE
FBI ON A CRIMINAL LEVEL AND THE
QUESTION REMAINS WAS THERE
COLLUSION BETWEEN TEAM TRUMP AND
THE EFFORTS TO INTERFERE IN THE
ELECTION.
THAT'S THE MATTER BEING
INVESTIGATED.
THE NEWS CONTINUES AFTER THIS.
Umbrellas!!
You need one of these.
You wouldn't put up
with an umbrella
that covers you part way,
so when it comes to
pain relievers,
why put up with
just part of a day?
Aleve, live whole not part.
Tell you what,
I'll give it to
you for half off.
on a perfect car,
then smash it into a tree.
Your insurance company
raises your rates.
Maybe you should've done
more research on them.
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't
raise your rates due to
your first accident.
And if you do have an accident,
our claims centers are
available to assist you 24/7.
Call
for a free quote today.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>> Shepard: IVANKA TRUMP SAYS
WHERE SHE'S DISAGREES WITH HER
FATHER, HE KNOWS IT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP RESPONDED TO
QUESTIONS WHY SHE HASN'T COME
OUT AGAINST SOME OF HER FATHER'S
AGENDA.
>> I RESPECT THE FACT THAT HE
ALWAYS LICENSE.
THAT'S HOW HE WAS IN BUSINESS,
THAT'S HOW HE IS AS PRESIDENT.
I SPEAK UP FREQUENTLY.
MY FATHER AGREES WITH ME ON SO
MANY ISSUES.
WHERE HE DOESN'T, HE KNOWS WHERE
I STAND.
>> LAST WEEK IVANKA TRUMP TOOK
AN UNPAID ROLE IN THE WHITE
HOUSE.
AFTER THE ELECTION, SHE SAID SHE
WOULD NOT BE WORKING IN THE
ADMINISTRATION.
SOME PEOPLE CRITICIZED HER
SAYING SHE WAS ADVISING THE
PRESIDENT WITHOUT HAVING
GOVERNMENT ETHIC RULES.
SHE SAID SHE TOOK THE OFFICIAL
TITLE TO SHOW SHE'S HOLDING
HERSELF TO THE HIGHEST ETHICAL
STANDARDS.
JONATHAN HUNT WITH THIS.
WHAT ELSE DID THE FIRST DAUGHTER
HAVE TO SAY?
>> WELL, SHEP, THE MAIN FOCUS IS
THIS ISSUE OF NOT SPEAKING OUT
PUBLICLY.
IVANKA TRUMP SAID PUBLIC SILENCE
DOESN'T MEAN SHE'S SILENT IN
PRIVATE.
>> I THINK THERE'S MULTIPLE WAYS
TO HAVE YOUR VOICE HEARD.
IN SOME CASES, IT'S PROTEST,
GOING ON THE NIGHTLY NEWS AND
TALKING ABOUT OR DENOUNCING
EVERY ISSUE YOU DISAGREE WITH.
OTHER TIMES IT'S QUIETLY AND
DIRECTLY AN CANDIDLY.
>> SHE WAS ASKED IF SHE FELT
COMPLICIT AS SHE'S BEING
PARODIED AS PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
HARSHER POLICIES.
>> IF BEING COMPLICIT IS WANTING
TO BE A FORCE FOR GOOD AND TO
MAKE A POSITIVE IMPACT, THEN I'M
COMPLICIT.
I DON'T KNOW THAT THE CRITICS
THAT MAY SAY THAT OF ME, IF THEY
FOUND THEMSELVES IN THIS UNIQUE
AND UNPRECEDENTED SITUATION THAT
I'M NOW IN WOULD DO ANY
DIFFERENTLY THAN I'M DOING.
>> TO A LOT OF PEOPLE, SHEP,
THAT ANSWER IN PARTICULAR
SOUNDED LIKE A YOUNG WOMAN STILL
WORKING HER WAY THROUGH WHAT IS,
AS SHE PUT IT, AN UNPRECEDENTED
SITUATION.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: WHAT ABOUT ETHICAL
COMPLICATIONS OF KEEPING HER
BUSINESS WHILE WORKING AT THE
WHITE HOUSE?
>> WELL, SHE HAS OF COURSE PUT
THAT BUSINESS IN TRUST.
IT'S RUN BY FAMILY MEMBERS.
SHE SAID IF HER AIM WAS TO MAKE
MONEY FROM HER FATHER'S
POSSESSION, THERE'S AN EASIER
WAY TO DO IT.
>> I WOULD ARGUE IF I HAD NOT
COME TO WASHINGTON D.C. AND IF I
WAS IN NEW YORK GROWING MY
BUSINESS, I WOULD BE DOING FAR
BETTER THAN BY PLACING A
RESTRICTIONS I'VE PLACED ON MY
TEAM AND ENSURING THAT ANY
GROWTH IS DONE WITH EXTREME
CAUTION.
>> NOW SHE ALSO GAVE A GLIMPSE
OF A NEW FAMILY LIFE IN D.C. AND
SHE'S TAKEN HER FAMILY TO
MUSEUMS.
AND SHE HAS NOT SAID WHETHER
SHE'S DITCHING THE YANKEES FOR
THE NATIONALS.
>> THANKS, JONATHAN.
MORE AHEAD ON THE MASSIVE
DEVELOPMENT OF THE U.S. FOREIGN
POLICY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP NORTH KOREA AND
ITS DICTATOR A BIG PROBLEM IN
THE WAKE OF THE LATEST MISSILE
LAUNCH.
IT ALSO COMES AHEAD OF A VERY
IMPORTANT MEETING BETWEEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND CHINA'S
LEADER.
REMEMBER, THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID
THAT THE UNITED STATES IS READY
TO GO IT ALONE IN NORTH KOREA IF
NECESSARY.
SO WHAT TO EXPECT NOW?
WE'RE APPROACHING THE BOTTOM OF
THE HOUR AND THE TOP OF THE
NEWS.
Ooh...
Psst.
Hey...
...where you going?
We've got that thing!
You know...Diarrhea?
Abdominal pain?
But we said we'd be there...
Woap, who makes the
decisions around here?
It's me.
Don't think I'll make it.
Stomach again...Send!
If you're living with frequent,
unpredictable diarrhea
and abdominal pain,
you may have Irritable Bowel
Syndrome with Diarrhea
or IBS-D - a condition that can
be really frustrating.
Talk to your doctor
about VIBERZI...
a different way to treat IBS-D.
VIBERZI is a
prescription medication
you take every day
that helps proactively manage
both diarrhea and abdominal pain
at the same time.
So you stay ahead
of your symptoms.
VIBERZI can cause new or
worsening abdominal pain.
Do not take VIBERZI if you have
or may have had:
pancreas or
severe liver problems,
problems with alcohol abuse,
long-lasting or
severe constipation,
or a blockage of your bowel
or gallbladder.
If you are taking VIBERZI,
you should not take medicines
that cause constipation.
The most common side effects of
VIBERZI include
constipation, nausea, and
abdominal pain.
Stay ahead of IBS-D
with VIBERZI.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
AN UPDATE ON AN F-16 CRASH THAT
HAPPENED THIS MORNING.
THE PILOT SAFELY EJECTED AFTER
HIS JET WENT DOWN IN A TRAINING
MISSION.
THE CRASH HAPPENED IN THE WOODS
IN MARYLAND.
MILITARY OFFICIALS SAY THE PILOT
IS IN GOOD CONDITION WITH MINOR
INJURIES AND NOBODY ELSE WAS ON
BOARD THAT JET.
A WITNESS TOLD OUR LOCAL FOX
STATION THAT HE WAS SITTING ON
HIS PORCH WHEN HE HEARD AN
EXPLOSION.
>> I HEARD THIS LOUD NOISE.
I LOOKED UP, THE JET WAS ON
FIRE.
AT THAT TIME IT BLEW UP.
THE PILOT EJECTED.
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT OF THE
PLANE.
THE BIGGEST FIREBALL I'VE EVER
SEEN.
>> HE ALSO SAID THE PILOT ASKED
IF ANYBODY ELSE IN THE AREA WAS
HURT SINCE HE HAD LIVE ROUNDS ON
BOARD.
THERE'S NO REPORTS OF ANY
INJURIES ON THE GROUND.
A FIRE DEPARTMENT TOLD LOCAL
MEDIA THAT CREWS HAVE EVACUATED
NEARBY HOMES.
THE NEWS CONTINUES WITH SHEPARD
SMITH AFTER THIS.
ontrol.
So I asked
about Tresiba®.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
Tresiba®
is a once-daily,
long-acting
insulin
that lasts
even longer
than 24 hours.
I need to shave
my A1C.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
Tresiba® works
like my body's
insulin.
Releases slow
and steady.
providing
powerful
A1C reduction.
I'm always on call.
An insulin that fits
my schedule is key.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
I can take Tresiba®
any time of day.
So if I miss
or delay a dose,
I take it when I remember,
as long as there's at least
8 hours between doses.
Once in use,
it lasts 8 weeks
with or without
refrigeration,
twice as long
as the Lantus® Pen.
(announcer) Tresiba® is used
to control high blood sugar
in adults with diabetes.
Don't use Tresiba® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during episodes
of low blood sugar,
or if you are allergic to any
of its ingredients.
Don't share needles
or insulin pens.
Don't reuse needles.
The most common side effect
is low blood sugar,
which may cause dizziness,
sweating, confusion,
and headache.
Check your blood sugar.
Low blood sugar can be serious
and may be life-threatening.
Injection site reactions
may occur.
Tell your prescriber
about all medicines you take
and all your medical
conditions.
Taking TZDs
with insulins like Tresiba®
may cause serious side effects
like heart failure.
Your insulin dose
shouldn't be changed
without
asking your prescriber.
Get medical help right away
if you have trouble breathing,
fast heartbeat,
extreme drowsiness,
swelling of your face, tongue,
or throat,
dizziness or confusion.
Ask your health care provider
if you're Tresiba® ready.
Covered by most insurance
and Medicare plans.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
REMEMBER HERE AT ALLY,
NOTHING STOPS US FROM DOING
RIGHT BY OUR CUSTOMERS.
WHO'S WITH ME?
WE'RE LIKE A BASKETBALL
TEAM HERE AT ALLY.
IF A BASKETBALL
TEAM HAD OVER 7...
I'M IN.
7,000 PLAYERS.
OUR PLAYS ARE A
LITTLE UNORTHODOX.
BUT TO BEAT THE BIG BOYS,
YOU NEED SMARTER WAYS
TO SAVE PEOPLE MONEY.
WE KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
FROM A FINANCIAL COMPANY
AND WE'LL STOP AT...
NOTHING TO MAKE SURE YOU GET IT.
ONE, TWO...
AND WE MEAN NOTHING.
♪  ♪
>> Shepard: BOTTOM OF THE HOUR,
TOP OF THE NEWS.
NORTH KOREA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP CALLED THEM A
BIG PROBLEM.
THEY SAID KIM JONG-UN IS
SOMEBODY THAT IS NOT DOING THE
RIGHT THING.
THE PRESIDENT LIKE HIS SECRETARY
OF STATE KEEPING IT BRIEF.
ANALYSTS SAY NORTH KOREA MAY BE
LOOKING FOR ATTENTION THIS WEEK.
IN A STATEMENT, REX TILLERSON
SAID NORTH KOREA LAUNCH ANOTHER
INTERMEDIATE RANGE MISSILE.
THE UNITED STATES HAS SPOKEN
ENOUGH ABOUT NORTH KOREA.
WE HAVE NO FURTHER COMMENT.
ACCORDING TO THE U.S. MILITARY
OFFICIALS, THE MISSILE CAME FROM
A FACILITY NEAR THE NORTH KOREAN
TOWN OF SHIN-PO.
IT LANDED IN THE WATER OFF THE
EAST COAST.
OFFICIALS TELL FOX NEWS THAT THE
LAUNCH LOOKED LIKE A FAILURE AND
THE MISSILE DID NOT GO AS FAR AS
PLANNED.
ANALYSTS SAY THE TIMING OF THE
LAUNCH IS WHAT REALLY MATTERS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS GETTING READY
TO HOST CHINA'S PRESIDENT.
IN AN INTERVIEW THIS WEEK, THE
PRESIDENT SAID THE UNITED STATES
IS READY TO GO IT ALONE WITH
NORTH KOREA IN CHINA DOES NOT
TAKE A STRONGER STANCE ON NORTH
KOREA.
JENNIFER GRIFFIN IS AT THE
PENTAGON.
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING ABOUT THE
LAUNCH?
>> PENTAGON OFFICIALS WE'VE
SPOKEN TO TODAY SAID THE MISSILE
DID NOT GO AS FAR AS INTENDED.
IT WENT 40 MILES.
DID NOT EVEN REACH JAPANESE
WATERS AND MAY HAVE PINWHEELED
IN FLIGHT.
WHAT IS MORE, THE NORTH KOREAN
MISSILE MIGHT NOT BEEN THE LAND
VERSION OF THE SUBMARINE
LAUNCHED BALLISTIC MISSILE THAT
LAUNCHED IN FEBRUARY WHEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP HOSTED THE
JAPANESE PRIME MINISTER IN
FLORIDA.
IT'S THOUGHT TO HAVE BEEN A SCUD
MISSILE.
AND NORTH KOREA WILL BE TOP OF
THE AGENDA AS THE PRESIDENT
MEETS CHINA'S PRESIDENT IN
MAR-A-LARGO.
>> Shepard: THERE'S NO
COINCIDENCES ON THIS.
WE REPORTED IT LAST WEEK WHEN WE
REPORTED CHINA'S PRESIDENT ON
THE SCHEDULE.
YOU COULD PUT A CHECK MARK THAT
NORTH KOREA DOES SOMETHING.
>> IT'S NOT JUST THE MEETING
WITH THE CHINESE PRESIDENT
TOMORROW.
EVERY YEAR AT THIS TIME, NORTH
KOREA TEST AS SERIES OF
BALL COINCIDE
WITH AN ANNUAL LARGE SCALE U.S.
AND SOUTHERN KOREAN EXERCISE.
THIS YEAR IS NO DIFFERENT.
THE U.S. DEPLOYED THE SAD
MISSILE SYSTEM SHOWN HERE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS NOW WEIGHING
WHETHER TO CHANGING U.S. POLICY
TOWARDS PYONGYANG AND SAID HE
WILL PRESSURE THE CHINESE
PRESIDENT ON THE ISSUE DURING
THEIR SUMMIT.
THE HEAD OF THE U.S. STRATEGIC
COMMAND ADMITTED THEY COULD NOT
SHOOT DOWN A NORTH KOREAN
MISSILE AFTER LAUNCH.
>> WE DON'T HAVE ANY BOOST PHASE
INTERCEPT CAPABILITY.
IT'S A CHALLENGING TECHNOLOGY.
YOU BASICALLY HAVE TO BE
PROPERLY POSITIONED WITH THE
RIGHT KIND OF WEAPONS CAPABILITY
IN ORDER TO RESPOND TO AN
IMMEDIATE LAUNCH.
>> A STARK ADMISSION AFTER THE
PENTAGON HAS SPENT BILLIONS ON
MISSILE DEFENSE TECHNOLOGY,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS.
GORDEN CLANG IS HERE WITH US,
AUTHOR OF "NUCLEAR SHOW DOWN."
WE TALK ABOUT THEIR LAUNCHES AND
HOW UNSTABLE THE REGIME IS.
WHAT IS DIFFERENT NOW THAN A
YEAR AGO?
>> THE WHITE HOUSE HAS ISSUED
TWO THREATS TO USE FORCE.
THE CLOCK RUNNING OUT, ALL
OPTIONS ON THE TABLE.
THEY'RE A THREAT TO USE FORCE
NOW.
YOU TALK ABOUT WHAT HAS HAPPENED
IN SYRIA.
THE PRESIDENT MENTIONED THAT THE
OBAMA'S FAIL RED LINE.
INDICATING HE SHOULD HAVE DONE
SOMETHING.
THAT IS A THREAT.
MAYBE MORE SUBTLE, BUT CLEARLY
ASSAD UNDERSTANDS WHAT HE'S
TALKING ABOUT.
>> AND DOES KIM JONG-UN TAKE
SOMETHING FROM THAT?
DO WE HAVE A WAY TO KNOW?
>> Shepard: WHAT KIM JONG-UN
WOULD DO, HE HAS LINKS WITH IRAN
AND SYRIA WHICH ARE ESTABLISHED.
THAT I HAVE CHINA IN THE
BACKGROUND.
THE PROBLEM HERE IS THAT IF HE
THINKS THE U.S. IS GOING TO
COMMIT MILITARY FORCE IN THE
MIDDLE EAST, HE KNOWS THAT WE'RE
NOT GOING TO DO VERY MUCH IN
NORTH ASIA, WHICH MEANS HE COULD
STARTING A PROVOCATION AGAINST
SOUTH KOREA.
THAT'S HOW THESE THINGS REALLY
SORT OF SPREAD FROM ONE REGION
TO THE OTHER.
THIS LOOKS LIKE 1914 WHEN THINGS
GET OUT OF CONTROL.
>> Shepard: IS THAT HOW IT
FEELS?
>> VERY MUCH SO.
CLEARLY TWO PREDECESSORS DEALT
HIM A BAD HAND.
YOU HAVE A SITUATION RIGHT NOW
THAT IS VOLATILE.
ANYTHING CAN HAPPEN.
THAT IS THE REASON WRITE THE
CHINESE PRESIDENT IS
CONSEQUENTIAL.
THEY'LL HAVE A DISCUSSION ABOUT
THE USE OF FORCE IN NORTH KOREA.
>> A KOREAN WAR, ANOTHER KOREAN
WAR, COULD BE THE DEATH OF
MILLIONS.
>> CLEARLY.
YOU HAVE 25 MILLION SOUTH
KOREANS THAT LIVE IN SEOUL.
NORTH KOREA HAS THE WORLD'S
FOURTH LARGEST ARMY.
ABOUT 70% OF THAT ARMY IS FOR
WARNED DEPLOYED BY THE DMZ.
THEY HAVE HIGH EXPLOSIVES,
CHEMICAL WEAPONS, BIOLOGICAL
AGENTS AND NUKES.
THE CASUALTIES ON THE FIRST
HOURS WOULD BE IN THE HUNDREDS
OF THOUSANDS.
YOU TALK ABOUT A FULL SCARE WAR,
WE HAVE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
THIS BEFORE.
>> Shepard: AND CHINA CAN HELP
US HOW?
>> CHINA CAN HELP US.
THEY CAN CUT OFF NORTH KOREA'S
FLOWS OF CASH.
>> Shepard: MONEY.
>> BUT CLEARLY THEY'RE NOT GOING
TO DO THAT BECAUSE THEY HAVE
BEEN BEHIND NORTH KOREA.
THEY'VE GIVEN THEM MUCH OF THE
TECHNOLOGY.
FOR INSTANCE, THEIR MOBILE
MISSILES ARE RIDING ON CHINESE
LAUNCHES AND THE MISSILES THAT
NORTH KOREA TESTED LOOK SIMILAR
TO THE JL-1.
TRUMP NEEDS TO ASK THEM HOW THAT
HAPPENED.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: MORE THAN 100 NAVY
INSTRUCTOR PILOTS HAVE GONE ON
STRIKE REFUSING TO FLY SINCE
LATE LAST WEEK.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO THE
EXCLUSIVE REPORTING OF OUR
JENNIFER GRIFFIN.
THE NAVY IS NOW RESPONDED BY
GROUNDING SOME TRAINING JETS.
FOX REPORTS THE INSTRUCTOR
PILOTS SAY THAT THEY'RE UPSET
BECAUSE DEFENSE OFFICIALS HAVE
FAILED TO FIX AN ISSUE WITH THE
OXYGEN SYSTEMS ON THEIR TRAINING
JETS.
MULTIPLE FLIGHT INSTRUCTORS HAVE
TOLD FOX NEWS THAT POISON IN THE
OXYGEN SYSTEMS CAN STRIKE
WITHOUT WARNING CAUSING THEM TO
BECOME DISORIENTED.
NAVY OFFICIALS HAVE ADMITTED TO
FOX NEWS THAT THE OXYGEN SYSTEMS
ARE A PROBLEM AND THAT THEY ARE
WORKING TO ADDRESS THE ISSUE.
REPORTERS GRIFFIN AND TOMLINSON
WERE ADVISING VICE PRESIDENT
MIKE PENCE'S SON, THE MARINE
FIRST LIEUTENANT, MICHAEL PENCE,
IS AMONG THE HUNDREDS OF
STUDENTS PILOTS THE STRIKE HAS
AFFECTED.
NOW FOR A LIVE LOOK AT THE DOW.
WHEN THE PRESIDENT SPOKE EARLIER
TODAY, THE DOW WAS UP ABOUT 160
POINTS.
SINCE THEN, IT HAS NOSE DIVED
AFTER A NEW REPORT THAT CLAIMED
THAT AMERICAN BUSINESS ADDED
263,000 JOBS LAST MONTH.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO ADP A
COMPANY THAT PROCESSES PAYROLL.
THAT'S NEARLY 80,000 MORE JOBS
THAN ANALYSTS PREDICTED.
THAT'S WHY THE MARKET WENT UP
THIS MORNING AND THROUGHOUT THE
AFTERNOON.
THIS IS A GRAPH OF THE ADP'S JOB
NUMBERS SINCE THE RECESSION.
THE LABOR DEPARTMENT'S OFFICIAL
MONTHLY JOBS REPORT CAME OUT
FRIDAY.
IN THE PAST, THE ADP'S NUMBERS
HAVE DIFFERENT FROM THE
GOVERNMENT'S OFFICIAL COUNT.
THE BIG NEWS HERE, WHAT HAS
HAPPENED SINCE THE PRESIDENT
SPOKE.
JERRY WILLIS IS WITH US.
THIS MOST RECENT REPORT IS AN
INTERESTING ONE.
TO ME, GERRI, WHAT HAS HAPPENED
SINCE THE PRESIDENT SPOKE, A
180-POINT DIVE IS DIRECTLY
RELATED, RIGHT?
>> YEAH, SOME RELATION.
WE STARTED OUT 180 POINTS.
A BIG GAIN DUE TO THE ADP
REPORT.
WHY IS IT SO IMPORTANT?
IT'S REALLY THE CRYSTAL BALL
FRIDAY'S JOB REPORT.
THE NUMBERS, THE BIGGEST GAINS
SINCE DECEMBER 2014.
ALL EYES ON THE REPORT TODAY.
COULDN'T HOLD THE GAINS, NOT AT
ALL.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK AT THE SECTORS
DOING WELL HERE.
PROFESSIONAL SERVICES.
BY THAT, I MEAN WHITE COLLARED
JOBS, BACK OFFICE JOBS, UP A
BUNCH.
HOSPITALITY LOOKING GOOD HERE.
THAT SPEAKS WELL TO TOURISM.
HEALTHCARE UP.
TYPICALLY IS.
TYPICALLY DOES WELL.
THE SHOCKER.
MANUFACTURING UP 30,000.
THAT'S THE SECTOR THAT TRUMP
TALKS ABOUT OVER AND OVER AND
OVER AGAIN.
OF COURSE, WE TALK ABOUT THE
LEADING SECTORS, WE'LL SEE MORE
DETAIL FRIDAY BECAUSE THAT'S
WHEN WE GET PRIVATE AND PUBLIC
SECTOR JOBS TOGETHER.
WE'LL SEE BOTH COMING IN.
LET'S SEE IF WE CAN HANG ON TO
THE MEAGER GAINS AT THIS HOURS,
WHICH ARE NOT AS GREAT.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, SHEP,
LOOKING AT THE NUMBERS,
EXPECTATIONS FOR FRIDAY, GAINS
OF 180,000 JOBS AND WE WILL
STICK AT 14.7%.
THAT'S THE EXPECTATION OUT
THERE.
>> Shepard: YOU KNOW WHERE I'M
GOING TO LOOK FOR YOU?
>> WHERE'S THAT?
>> Shepard: ON KENNEDY TONIGHT.
FOR OUR VIEWERS THAT KNEW -- I
WAS IN STUDIO JUST A FEW MINUTES
AGO.
YOU DIDN'T KNOW IT.
>> I DIDN'T.
>> Shepard: GERRI'S IS KENNEDY'S
GUEST TONIGHT ON THE FOX
BUSINESS NETWORK.
CANDY DEAD A PROGRAM EVERY NIGHT
AT 8:00, RIGHT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Shepard: AND A WHOLE
DIFFERENT GERRI WILLIS.
OUR SURVIVOR AND HERO WILL BE
THERE TALKING ABOUT HER LIFE.
YOU HAVE TO SEE IT.
I KNOW 8:00 IS A BUSY HOUR FOR
EVERYBODY, BUT IF YOU CAN'T GO
SEE IT, DVR IT.
>> TUNE IN.
IT'S KENNEDY, KENNEDY, KENNEDY.
>> Shepard: YOU CAN DVR WHATEVER
ELSE IS GOING ON.
YOU WANT TO SEE THIS.
YOU GOT TO SEE IT.
GERRI, GOD BLESS YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: THE WHITE HOUSE
TAKING ANOTHER WHACK AT
HEALTHCARE.
MIKE PENCE IS ON THE HILL WITH
LAWMAKERS.
THIS BATTLE IS STARTING TO SOUND
LIKE A BROKEN RECORD WITH THE
SAME OLD PROBLEM.
HEALTHCARE NEXT.
>> Shepard: THE WHITE HOUSE
TOUTING WHAT IT CALLS PROGRESS
ON A NEW HEALTHCARE BILL AFTER
VICE PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE AND
MET WITH REPUBLICAN LAWMAKERS ON
CAPITOL HILL LAST NIGHT.
BUT ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS
WILL NOT PUT A TIMELINE ON ANY
OF THIS.
CONSERVATIVE FREEDOM CAUCUS
CHAIRMAN MARK MEADOWS SAID
REPUBLICANS LEFT WITHOUT AN
AGREEMENT.
BUT BOTH CONSERVATIVE AND
MODERATE REPUBLICANS SAID
THEY'RE MAKING PROGRESS AND THAT
IT WAS A GOOD TALK.
BOTH SIDES ARE AT ODDS ABOUT
REPEALING SOME OBAMACARE
REGULATION.
MEMBERS OF THE FREEDOM CAUCUS
SAID THE LAST BILL DIDN'T GO FAR
ENOUGH TO ROLL BACK REGULATIONS
AND MODERATES SAY WE DON'T WANT
TO LOSE THE BENEFITS, WHICH IS
EXACTLY WHAT THEY SAID THIS DAY
THIS STARTED.
THE NATIONAL REPORTER FROM
POLITICO IS OUT.
PAUL RYAN SAID YEAH, WE'RE
MAKING PROGRESS BUT NO TIME
LINE.
IT SOUNDS LIKE THIS IS NOT A
REAL THING, DOESN'T IT?
>> IT DOES.
IT'S CONTINUING TO HAVE THE SAME
SORTS OF CONVERSATION.
IT'S PROGRESS AND THEY'RE MAKING
PROGRESS.
BUT IT SEEMS LIKE THEY -- THE
CONSERVATIVES IN THE HOUSE
FREEDOM CAUCUS AND THE MODERATES
IN THE TUESDAY GROUP REALLY HAVE
FUNDAMENTALLY DIFFERENT GOALS
HERE.
THE MEMBERS OF THE FREEDOM
CAUCUS ARE PRIORITIZING
STRIPPING BACK THE REGULATIONS
IN THE OBAMACARE AND THEY THINK
THE ORIGINAL BILL DIDN'T GO FAR
ENOUGH.
THE MODERATES IN THE TUESDAY
GROUP HAVE A DIFFERENT PRIORITY.
THEY WANT TO MAXIMIZE HEALTH
INSURANCE.
THERE'S NOT A THEORETICAL
PROCESS THAT ONE BILL CAN'T DO
BOTH.
BUT WHITE HOUSE AT LEAST RIGHT
NOW HASN'T PUT FORWARD A BILL
THAT WOULD DO BOTH THINGS AND
SATISFY BOTH GROUPS.
>> SO THEY TALK AND THEY SAY
THAT TALKING IS GOING WELL, BUT
IT SOUNDS LIKE TO HEAR FROM PAUL
RYAN, THEY'RE NOT GETTING
ANYWHERE.
THIS COMPLICATES MATTERS FOR THE
BUDGET.
THEY COULD HAVE SAVED $880
BILLION.
NOW THEY CAN'T.
I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU DO BUDGET
NOW.
>> THAT WAS THE SPEAKER'S CASE
FOR GOING HEALTHCARE FIRST.
THAT BY SAVING MONEY, BY
STRIKING A HEALTHCARE DEAL, IT
WOULD MAKE IT EASIER TO DO TAX
REFORM AND DO A BUDGET.
BECAUSE YOU WOULD MAKE PROGRESS
IN CHIPPING AWAY AT THE SAVINGS
YOU'D GET FROM DOING IT.
ONE INTERESTING THING THAT
EMERGED FROM THE TALKS IS THAT
THE TUESDAY GROUP AND THE
FREEDOM CAUCUS EMERGED WITH
DIFFERENT UNDERSTANDINGS OF WHAT
EXACTLY THIS BILL WOULD LOOK
LIKE.
>> Shepard: YOU KNOW HOW THAT
HAPPENED.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE THROUGH MIKE
PENCE PITCHED THEM TWO DIFFERENT
BILLS OR IF THE MEMBERS HAD
DIFFERENT UNDERSTANDINGS.
BUT IF TWO DIFFERENT PIECES WERE
PITCHED, THAT'S AN OVERSIGHT BY
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> Shepard: WASN'T THIS A CASE
OF WE'LL TELL YOU WHAT YOU WANT
TO HEAR, DON'T LOOK?
THEY TOLD THE CONSERVATIVE SIDE,
YEAH, WE'RE SAVING MONEY.
THEY TOLD THE OTHER SIDE, IF YOU
WANT IT, YOU CAN KEEP IT.
NEITHER ONE OF THOSE THINGS ARE
TRUE AND THEY READ IT AND WENT
WOW.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE READ IT AND
17% SUPPORTED.
AND NOW THEY'RE SAYING WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT IT BUT NOT DOING
ANYTHING BUT TALKING ABOUT IT.
IS THAT FAIR?
WHAT IS THAT?
>> AT THE VERY LEAST, THE
MEMBERS OF TWO GROUPS HAD
DIFFERENT UNDERSTANDINGS WHAT
WOULD BE IN THE LEGISLATION.
AS MY COLLEAGUE PUT IT, IT WAS
EITHER A CASE OF THE
ADMINISTRATION PITCHING TWO
DIFFERENT THINGS TO THE
DIFFERENT GROUPS OR THE MEMBERS
HEARING WHAT THEY WANTED TO HEAR
FROM THE VICE PRESIDENT.
WHATEVER THE CASE, NO SUCCESSFUL
COMPROMISE REACHED.
SO WE'RE NO FURTHER ALONG THAN
WHERE WE WERE AT DAY ONE.
>> Shepard: GREAT TO TALK TO
YOU.
THANK YOU.
ENJOY YOUR WEDNESDAY.
JOINING MAN AND MACHINE.
WANT TO UPGRADE YOUR MEMORY SO
YOU STOP FORGETTING BIRTHDAYS?
HOW ABOUT ADDING ARTIFICIAL
INTELLIGENCE TO MAKE MATH
HOMEWORK EASIER?
SCIENTISTS SAY NOT IF WE DO IT
BUT WHEN WE DO IT.
KENNEDY IS HERE NEXT.
>> YOU CAN UPGRADE YOUR CAR,
YOUR PHONE, YOUR HOUSE.
YOU CAN SEEN UPGRADE YOURSELF.
THAT'S WHAT MARKET WATCH SAYS.
AS SOON AS 60 YEARS FROM NOW --
THAT MAY BE A STRETCH -- PEOPLE
WILL BE ABLE TO BUY THEMSELVES
THE HUMAN EQUIVALENT OF
PERFORMANCE ENHANCING APPs.
A LARGER HARD DRIVE.
KENNEDY IS HERE.
SHE HOSTS "KENNEDY" AT 8:00
EASTERN WITH GERRI WILLIS.
>> WE ALREADY HAVE IT.
IT'S AN EXTERNAL WAYS OF
ACCESSING INFORMATION ALMOST
IMMEDIATELY.
THERE'S STUDIES THAT SHOW THAT
WE'RE COMPROMISING OUR OWN
MEMORIES BY CONSTANTLY ACCESSING
THINGS ON THE WEB.
>> Shepard: THERE'S NO DOUBT.
>> SO WHY NOT CUT OUT THE
MIDDLEMAN AND PUT THE HARDWARE
INTO YOUR BRAIN TO BEGIN WITH.
>> Shepard: YOU KNOW PHONE
NUMBERS?
I USED TO KNOW 100 OF THEM.
I KNOW TWO NOW.
I KNOW TWO NUMBERS.
>> UNFORTUNATELY ONE IS 911.
YOU HAVE TO CALL THEM.
YOU'RE ON FIRE TODAY.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
SO IF YOU PUT IT IN THERE,
ATTACH THE PHONE LIKE -- THEN
YOU HAVE IT IN THERE.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO ANYTHING.
>> IT'S NOT YOU DON'T HAVE TO DO
ANYTHING.
THINK OF THE COOL STUFF THAT YOU
CAN ACCESS AND THE INFORMATION
YOU'LL HAVE.
A VERY SHORT LEAP FROM HAVING
SOME SORT OF A MECHANICAL HARD
DRIVE IMPLANTED IN YOUR
PHYSIOLOGY IS THE ABILITY TO
FLY.
HOW GREAT WOULD THAT BE?
IT'S LIKE A LIVING, LUCID DREAM.
YOU WON'T NEED THE MATRIX.
YOU WON'T NEED TO BE PLUGGED IN
TO A VIDEO GAME.
YOU'LL FLY ALL OVER THE PLACE.
TO THE GRAND CANYON NOW.
>> WE'RE IN THE MATRIX NOW.
>> WE COULD BE.
THERE'S PHILOSOPHIES --
>> Shepard: WE'RE AN ANT FARM.
LIKE A CHILD ANT FARM SOMEWHERE
IN ANOTHER WORLD.
I BET THAT KID IS LAUGHING.
I FEEL LIKE IT'S THE ONLY THING
TO EXPLAIN IT ALL.
WE'RE AN ANT FARM OF SOME KID --
>> AND THAT COULD BE AN
EXPLANATION, THAT WE ARE PART OF
A MASSIVE COMPUTER MODEL.
WE'RE REALLY JUST -- WHAT DID
SPENOZA CALL HIM?
LIKE NOADS OR SOMETHING LIKE
THAT.
THEY GO -- AND SET INTO MOTION
AND WE HAVE NO CONTROL OVER OUR
LIVES.
>> Shepard: IF WE WERE TO CALL
I.T., THEY'D SAY UNPLUG IT AND
PLUG IT BACK IN.
MAYBE THAT WOULD FIX IT.
SEE YOU TONIGHT AT 8:00.
>> OUR BRAINS AND COMPUTERS
COMBINED.
you a bonus check
for every six months
you're accident free.
Silence.
It's good to be IN, Good Hands.
Pcountries thatk
mewe traveled,t
what is your
nationality and
I would always
answer Hispanic.
So when I got my Ancestry DNA
results it was a shocker.
I'm everything.
I'm from all nations.
I would look at forms
now and wonder
what do I mark?
Because I'm everything.
And I marked other.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
>> Shepard: ON THIS DAY IN 1987,
THE FOX BROADCASTING COMPANY
MADE ITS PRIME TIME DEBUT.
AT THE TIME ONLY THE BIG THREE
DOMINATED TV.
FOX SHOOK THINGS UP WITH
"MARRIED WITH CHILDREN" GEARED
TO A YOUNGER HIPPER AUDIENCE.
FOX WENT ON TO BECOME A POWER
HOUSE WITH HITS LIKE "SIMPSONS",
"X FILES" AND "AMERICAN IDOL."
AND TV GOT MORE FUN WHEN FOX
CAME TO PRIME TIME 30 YEARS AGO
TODAY.
DISRUPTERS!
WHEN NEWS BREAKS OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
BREAKING NEWS CHANGES EVERYTHING
ON THE FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
"YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL CAVUTO
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> WHEN YOU KILL INNOCENT
CHILDREN, INNOCENT BABIES,
BABIES, LITTLE BABIES, WITH A
CHEMICAL GAS THAT IS SO LETHAL
THAT PEOPLE WERE SHOCKED TO HEAR
WHAT GAS IT WAS, THAT CROSSES
MANY, MANY LINES BEYOND A RED
LINE.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT.
THAT PROMPTED AND SET IN MOTION
A LOT OF SELLING.
NOT EXACTLY PEGGED TO THAT, BUT
A TRIFECTA OF TRYING EVENTS FOR
THIS MARKET THAT HAD BEEN UP
ABOUT 180 POINTS, FINISHING DOWN
ABOUT 41 POINTS.
WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO ABOUT
SYRIA AND THE LARGE UNKNOWN
AROUND THAT WAS ONE THING.