JUDGE GORSUCH REPLACES THE LATE
ANTONIN SCALIA.
I'M MELISSA FRANCIS.
HERE'S SHEP.
>> IT'S NOON ON THE WEST COAST,
3:00 IN WASHINGTON.
10:00 P.M. IN DAMASCUS.
WE'RE WAITING TO HERE HOW BASHAR
AL-ASSAD WILL RESPOND TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S MISSILE
STRIKES.
AL-ASSAD IS NOT THE ONLY ONE
WATCHING NOW.
FOX NEWS HAS LEARNED THAT A
RUSSIAN NAVAL SHIP IS HEADING TO
THE REGION.
EXPERTS SAY IT'S OF NO CONCERN.
WE'LL HERE FROM GENERAL JACK
KEANE AND CHRIS WALLACE.
THE PRESIDENT IS MONITORING THE
AFTERMATH.
WE'LL GET REACTION FROM AROUND
THE WORLD AND HEAR WHAT
LAWMAKERS FROM BOTH SIDES HAVE
TO SAY.
TWO OTHER MAJOR STORIES.
THE CONFIRMATION VOTED FOR NEIL
GORSUCH AND ATTACKS IN SWEDEN.
A DRIVER PLOWING HIS TRUCK INTO
A DEPARTMENT STORE, A LOT OF
NEWS.
LET'S GET TO IT.
AND FIRST FROM THE DECK THIS
FRIDAY AFTERNOON, WE BEGIN WITH
A STARK WARNING FROM RUSSIA.
THE RUSSIAN PRIME MINISTER IS
NOW SAYING THAT THE SYRIAN
STRIKES HAVE PUT THE UNITED
STATES ON THE VERGE OF A
MILITARY CLASH.
QUOTING HERE "THE LAST REMAINING
ELECTION FOG HAS LIFT.
INSTEAD OF A OVERWORKED
STATEMENT ABOUT A JOINT FIGHT
BETWEEN THE ENEMY, ISIS, THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION PROVED THAT
THEY WILL FIGHT THE LEGITIMATE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT IN A TOUGH
CONTRADICTION WITH INTERNATIONAL
LAW AND WITHOUT U.N. APPROVAL.
HE WRITES THE STRIKES HAVE PUT
THE UNITED STATES ON THE VERGE
OF A MILITARY CLASH WITH RUSSIA.
THAT AS WE GET WORD THAT A
RUSSIAN WARSHIP IS HEADED TOWARD
THE TWO UNITED STATES NAVY
DESTROYERS USED IN THE STRIKES
ON SYRIA.
WE'RE NEARING 24 HOURS NOW SINCE
THE PRESIDENT ORDERED THE
STRIKES ON THAT AIR BASE IN
SYRIA.
A RESPONSE HE SAYS TO THIS
WEEK'S DEADLY GAS ATTACK IN
SYRIA THAT KILLED DOZENS,
INCLUDING WOMEN AND CHILDREN.
AN ATTACK WHICH THE PRESIDENT
SAYS THERE'S NO DOUBT THE
MURDEROUS SYRIAN DICTATOR BASHAR
AL-ASSAD ORDERED.
THE STRIKES HITTING OVERNIGHT IN
SYRIA.
THE U.S. NAVY FIRING 60 TOMAHAWK
CRUISE MISSILES FROM TWO WAR
SHIPS.
SYRIA CLAIMS SEVEN ARE DEAD AND
WE'RE GETTING OUR FIRST APPARENT
LOOK AT THE BASE AFTER THE
STRIKES.
THIS IS RUSSIAN DEFENSE VIDEO
TAKEN FROM THE COCKPIT OF A
DRONE.
MORE DRONE FOOTAGE FROM RUSSIAN
TELEVISION.
THIS TIME IN COLOR.
ACCORDING TO THE U.S. MILITARY,
THE TARGETS INCLUDING RUNWAY,
THE AIRCRAFT THEMSELVES, HANGERS
AND FUEL.
I'LL SHOW YOU ON SATELLITE
IMAGES.
AND THIS VIDEO FROM SYRIAN STATE
TELEVISION REPORTED THERE FROM
NEAR THAT VERY BASE.
IF YOU LOOK IN THE DISTINCTION
ANSWER THE, YOU CAN SEE SMOKE A
ON THE HORIZON.
FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP, THIS IS
CLEARLY HIS MOST DRAMATIC
MILITARY ORDER SINCE TAKING
OFFICE.
AND MORE IMPORTANTLY, PROBABLY
AS A NATION, IT'S A SIGNIFICANT
CHANGE FROM THE U.S. APPROACH IN
THAT WAR-TORN NATION AND DEALING
WITH THE TYRANT HIMSELF WHO FOR
YEARS HAS BEEN SLAUGHTERING HIS
OWN PEOPLE.
AL-ASSAD CALLED THE STRIKES
RECKLESS AND ACCUSED THE UNITED
STATES OF HELPING ISIS.
>> THE AGGRESSION OF THE U.S. ON
SYRIAN AIR FORCE TODAY IS A
PROOF THAT THE UNITED STATES IS
NOT INTENT ON FIGHTING TERRORISM
BUT HELPING TERRORISTS.
>> BEYOND SYRIA, THE WHITE HOUSE
IS IN A NEW WORLD WITH RUSSIA,
IT WOULD APPEAR, ALONG WITH
IRAN, AL-ASSAD'S BIGGEST BACKER
ALONG WITH THE RUSSIANS.
FOX LEARNED THAT A RUSSIAN
WARSHIP IS MAKING ITS WAY TO THE
AREA AND THIS IS NO LONGER A
CONFLICT BY PROXY.
VLADIMIR PUTIN SAID THAT THE
PRESIDENT ORDERED THE STRIKES
UNDER A FAR-FETCHED PRETEXT.
PUTIN SAYS THEY WILL REDUCE
COOPERATION WITH THE UNITED
STATES AND REINFORCE AL-ASSAD'S
AIR DEFENSES.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU WHAT THE THE
AIR STRIKES TARGETED.
HERE'S A SATELLITE IMAGE OF THAT
SYRIAN BASE.
IT'S A PRETTY EXPANSIVE PLACE.
YOU CAN SEE THE RUNWAYS AND THE
ACCESS LANES.
THEY'RE FROM IMAGE SAT
INTERNATIONAL.
A PRIVATE COMPANY.
LET'S ADD SOME COLOR TO THIS
MAP.
THIS WILL GIVE YOU A BETTER IDEA
OF WHAT EVERYTHING IS.
LET'S WATCH THE COLORS.
IN THE YELLOW OVER HERE, THOSE
ARE DESCRIBED AS DOUBLE HASHENED
AIR CRAFT HANGERS.
THERE'S 13 IN YELLOW.
ACCORDING TO THE MILITARY, THEY
HIT ALL 13.
IN ORANGE, THOSE ARE WORKSHOPS.
THE ONE DOT THERE.
FOR AIRCRAFT MAINTENANCE.
IF YOU LOOK IN THE BLUE DOWN
HERE, ALL OF THIS, THESE ARE
AMMO STORAGE AREAS.
YOU CAN SEE THAT THERE'S ROADS
THAT LEAD TO THEM FOR STORING
AMMO IN ALL OF THESE DIFFERENT
PLACES.
WHERE EACH BLUE CIRCLE IS,
THAT'S WHERE A TOMAHAWK MISSILE
STRIKES.
WE'RE TOLD ALL TEN STORAGE AREAS
WERE TAKEN OUT.
LET'S LOOK IN RED.
THE RED DOTS HERE AGAINST THESE
ROADS, THEY'RE DEFENSE AND
CONTROL SYSTEMS.
SO IN THESE AREAS, THEY'RE ABLE
TO CONTROL WHAT HAPPENS IN THE
FLIGHT PATTERN HERE.
IN GREEN, FUEL AND STORIES
RESERVOIRS.
LOOKS LIKE THERE'S THREE HERE.
OFFICIALS SAY THE STRIKES WIPED
OUT MOST OF THEM, BUT THEY SAY A
COUPLE ARE LEFT.
WE'LL HAVE COMPREHENSIVE
COVERAGE THROUGHOUT THE HOUR.
JENNIFER GRIFFIN HAS MORE.
THE PENTAGON IS INVESTIGATING
WHETHER MOSCOW WAS INVOLVED IN
THE STRIKE ON THE SYRIAN PEOPLE
WITH THE SARIN GAS.
WHAT DO WE KNOW?
>> WE WERE JUST TOLD THIS BY TWO
US IS SENIOR MILITARY
COMMANDERS.
LAST NIGHT ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS TOLD FOX NEWS THAT
THEY HAD EVIDENCE THAT RUSSIANS
WERE PRESENT WHEN THE SYRIANS
LOADED THOSE CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON
TO THAT WAR PLANE.
U.S. OFFICIALS TELL US A RUSSIAN
OR SYRIAN DRONE WAS SEEN FLYING
OVER A HOSPITAL WHERE THE
VICTIMS WERE TAKEN ON TUESDAY
SHORTLY BEFORE THAT HOSPITAL WAS
BOMBED.
THE RUSSIANS OR THE SYRIAN
REGIME WAS TRYING TO DESTROY AND
COVER UP EVIDENCE OF THE
CHEMICAL ATTACKS.
LAST NIGHT THERE WERE 12 TO 100
RUSSIAN MILITARY PERSONNEL AT
THE SYRIAN AIR BASE WHEN THE
U.S. MILITARY STRUCK.
THAT ACCORDING TO THOSE DEFENSE
OFFICIALS THAT JUST BRIEFED HERE
AT THE PENTAGON.
THE ALL IS MILITARY TOOK EFFORTS
NOT TO HIT THE BARRACKS.
THEY DON'T BELIEVE THERE WERE
ANY RUSSIANS KILLED.
THE U.S. SAID THEY GAVE RUSSIA
AN HOUR HEADS-UP.
ABOUT 20 SYRIAN AIRCRAFT WERE
DESTROYED AT THE BASE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT DO WE KNOW
ABOUT THE TIMING ON WHEN THE
PRESIDENT DECIDED TO TAKE THE
STRIKE?
>> WE'RE TOLD YESTERDAY AT 4:30
EASTERN TIME AFTER BEING BRIEFED
BUT THE NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM
AT MAR-A-LARGO, HE TOOK THE
DECISION.
GENERAL MATTIS AND HIS NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER FLEW DOWN
SEPARATELY FROM THEIR BOSS WITH
THE PLAN.
60 TOM HOUSE MISSILES WERE
LAUNCHED FROM THE EASTERN M
MEREDETARIAN SEA.
IT TOOKES 30 MINUTES TO LAUNCH
THE TOMAHAWKS.
SOME CIRCLED OVERHEAD AND THEN
AN HOUR LATER AT 8:40 P.M.
EASTERN, ALL 59 MISSILES HIT
WITHIN TWO TO THREE MINUTES WITH
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION SAID
THE NERVE AGENTS WERE LOADED ON
TO A RUSSIAN-MADE WAR PLANE.
WE JUST LEARNED THAT THAT
HOTLINE SET UP BETWEEN THE
RUSSIAN AND U.S. MILITARY TO
PREVENT MILITARY MISHAPS IN
SYRIA, THAT IS BEING SHUT DOWN
BY THE RUSSIANS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: JENNIFER GRIFFIN
WITH THE NEW DEVELOPMENTS.
THANK YOU.
LET'S TURN TO GENERAL JACK KEANE
FROM THE UNITED STATES ARMY.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE LAST NIGHT
AND TODAY.
>> GLAD TO BE HERE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: A COUPLE THINGS.
THIS RUSSIAN SHIP, THE RUSSIAN
DESTROYER ON THE MOVE TOWARD OUR
SHIPS, WHAT ARE WE TO MAKE OF
THAT?
AND THE BLUSTER FROM VLADIMIR
PUTIN AND HIS SPOKESPEOPLE?
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL, THE
RUSSIAN SHIP IS STAYING IN
INTERNATIONAL WATERS.
HAS A RIGHT TO BE THERE.
I DON'T THINK OUR MILITARY
LEADERS ARE ALL THAT CONCERNED
ABOUT IT.
RUSSIA DOES NOT WANT TO GO TO
WAR WITH THE UNITED STATES.
RUSSIA HAS BEEN POUNDING OUR
PROXIES INSIDE OF SYRIA, THE
SYRIAN MONITORS.
THE C.I.A. WAS THE FIRST ONE
THAT THEY BOMBED WITH THEIR AIR
CAMPAIGN.
IF THEY WERE GOING TO DO MORE,
THAT IT USE THEIR OWN BOMBERS.
SO UNLIKELY ANY CONFLICT BETWEEN
U.S. NAVY SHIPS AND RUSSIAN
SHIPS.
IN TERMS OF PUTIN'S BLUSTER,
WE'RE USED TO IT AND WE'LL HEAR
MORE OF IT.
FRANKLY, RUSSIA AND IRAN IS IN A
GOOD SPOT.
LET'S FACE IT.
THEY BEAT BACK THE OPPOSITE
FORCES OUT OF ALEPPO.
THEY CONSOLIDATED THE REGIME'S
HOLDING.
RUSSIA WAS ABLE TO SUCCEED AND
ACCOMPLISH WHAT THEY INTENDED TO
DO, PROP UP THE REGIME WHEN THEY
WERE IN DANGER OF BEING
OVERTHROWN IN 2015.
THEY ACCOMPLISHED WHAT THEY
WANTED.
I THINK FOR THEM TO DO ANYTHING
THAT WOULD AGGRAVATE THE
SITUATION FURTHER DOESN'T MAKE A
LOT OF SENSE TO ME.
>> AFTER 37 YEARS IN SERVICE AND
WE THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE A LOT OF GOOD CONTACTS.
I WONDER WHAT YOUR UNDERSTANDING
IS OF THE NEXT STEPS.
>> WELL, I THINK CERTAINLY AS
SAD IS CONTROLLING FATE HERE.
IF HE WANTS TO CONTINUE TO USE
WMD, WE'LL TAKE DOWN THOSE OTHER
FIVE AIR FIELDS AND MAKE CERTAIN
THAT ALL OF HIS AIRCRAFT ARE
GROUNDED PERMANENTLY.
SO HE HOLDS THAT FATE.
I DON'T BELIEVE THE RUSSIANS
WILL DO ANYTHING TO AGGRAVATE
THE SITUATION WITH THE UNITED
STATES.
THEY DO NOT WANT TO HAVE
CONFRONTATION OR CONFLICT WITH
THE UNITED STATES.
I THINK FROM OUR PERSPECTIVE,
WE'RE GOING TO FOCUS ON TAKING
ISIS DOWN.
THE PENTAGON HAS SUBMITTED PLANS
FOR THAT.
THE PRESIDENT HAS APPROVED THE
PLANS.
WE'LL SEE THE MANIFESTATION OF
THAT UNFOLD IN THE NEXT NUMBER
OF WEEKS.
HE'S NOT GOING TO TELL US HOW OR
WHEN HE'S DOING IT.
IT WILL UNFOLD AND THE MEDIA
WILL START REPORTING ON IT.
IN TERMS OF THE OVERALL STRATEGY
OBJECT SYRIA, LET'S BE FRANK
ABOUT IT.
THERE'S NOTHING EASY HERE.
THIS IS BY AND LARGE AN
INTRACTABLE SITUATION.
WE SQUANDERED ALL THE
OPPORTUNITIES, SHEP, TO DO
SOMETHING FAVORABLE HERE FOR THE
SYRIAN PEOPLE OVER THE LAST FIVE
OR SIX YEARS.
WE ARE OUT OF OPTIONS.
I THINK SAFE ZONES STILL MAKE
SOME SENSE BECAUSE IT WOULD BE A
WAY TO GET SOME OF THESE SYRIAN
PEOPLE AWAY FROM THESE BOMBS
THAT ARE GOING TO FALL ON THEM,
CONVENTIONAL BOMBS AND
ARTILLERY.
WE CAN PROTECT THEM WITH
INTERNATIONAL FORCES TO DO
SOMETHING.
I THINK THAT'S SOMETHING THAT WE
SHOULD WORK -- IT'S WORTH DOING.
>> Shepard: GENERAL JACK KEANE,
THANKS FOR THE INFORMATION.
>> THANKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THE STRIKE IN SYRIA
WAS A MESSAGE.
NOT ONLY TO THE SYRIAN DICTATOR
BUT TO OTHERS.
THE MISSILE MAY HAVE SENT A
POWERFUL WARNING TO NORTH KOREA.
ONE THAT THE UNITED STATES IS
WILLING TO GO IT ALONE.
SO WHAT DOES THIS MEAN FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP?
AS HE MEETS WITH THE LEADER OF
CHINA.
AN ALLY OF NORTH KOREA.
HOW IMPORTANT A MEETING THAT NOW
IS AS THE NEWS CONTINUES ON A
FRIDAY AFTERNOON FROM THE FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
So much lobster, so little time.
At Red Lobster's Lobsterfest
any of these 9 lobster dishes
could be yours.
So don't resist delicious new
Lobster Mix and Match
or Lobsterfest Surf and Turf
because you won't have this
chance for long.
.
>> AFTER ORDING THE STRIKE ON
SYRIA, THE PRESIDENT HAD DINNER
WITH XI JINPING.
THAT HAD ABOUT 30 GUESTS AT THE
PRESIDENT'S RESORT IN SOUTH
FLORIDA.
AN ANALYST SENT THE MESSAGE THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS WILLING TO GO
IT ALONE WHEN IT COMES TO TAKING
ON DANGEROUS DICTATORS, POSSIBLY
EVEN CHINA'S ALLY IN NORTH
KOREA.
JOHN ROBERTS IS LIVE IN
MAR-A-LARGO IN SOUTH FLORIDA.
EXPLAIN HOW THIS DECISION CAME
ABOUT, JOHN.
>> SHEP, GOOD AFTERNOON TO YOU.
CLEARLY A LOT CHANGED FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
BACK IN 2013, DONALD TRUMP URGED
PRESIDENT OBAMA NOT TO TAKE
MILITARY ACTION IN SYRIA IN
RESPONSE TO THAT AUGUST OF 2013
SARIN GAS ATTACK THAT KILLED 14.
BUT NOW HE LAUNCHED ATTACK HE
DID LAST NIGHT.
WHAT CHANGED?
HAVING TO WEIGHT OF COMMAND ON
HIS SHOULDERS, NOW HE'S
PRESIDENT PLAYED A LOT INTO IT.
SEEING THE HORRIFIC
CHILDREN DEAD, DYING OR
SUFFERING SO HORRIBLY PLAYED
INTO IT AND THEN THERE'S THIS
IDEA THAT IF BASHAR AL-ASSAD
WERE TO GET AWAY WITH IT, THE
USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS MIGHT
BECOME SOMEWHAT NORMALIZED AND
WOULD INCREASE THE CHANCE THAT
THEY WOULD BE USED AGAINST THE
UNITED STATES, WHICH PRESENTS
THAT URGENT NATIONAL SECURITY
THREAT THAT THE PRESIDENT CITED
LAST NIGHT.
THIS DECISION-MAKING PROCESS
UNFOLDED OVER THE COURSE OF 24
HOURS AT FOUR MEETINGS WITH THE
PRESIDENT AT 10:00 ON TUESDAY
MORNING CULMINATING WITH THE
MEETING HERE AT MAR-A-LARGO ON
THURSDAY AFTERNOON IN WHICH THE
PRESIDENT MADE THE DECISION TO
GO AHEAD AND DO IT AT 4:00 P.M.
I'M TOLD THE PRESIDENT IS VERY
PLEASED WITH THE WAY THE ATTACK
WAS CARRIED OUT, PRAISING THE
PERFORMANCE OF THE MILITARY
AMONG MEMBERS OF HIS STAFF AND
AS WELL, VERY HAPPY WITH THE
GLOBAL RESPONSE TO THIS, WHICH
MANY OF AMERICA'S ALLIES AND
MOST OF THE ARAB COUNTRIES OF
REGION OFFERING WORDS FOR
SUPPORT FOR THE ACTION TAKEN IN
SYRIA.
>> Shepard: JOHN, ONE COUNTRY
NOT SUPPORTING THIS IS RUSSIA.
WHAT IS HAPPENING WITH THAT
RELATIONSHIP?
>> AS JENNIFER GRIFFIN
MENTIONED, THIS DEACONFLICTION
LINE WILL BE TAKEN DOWN.
AND DESPITE ALL THIS PUBLIC
BLUSTER AND STATEMENTS, I'M TOLD
BY SOURCES THAT ALONG OFFICIAL
DIPLOMATIC LINES THERE'S VERY
LITTLE BLOW-BACK FROM THE
RUSSIANS.
SEAN SPICER WAS HERE.
I ASKED HIM ABOUT THAT.
>> THERE WAS NO CONTACT WITH
RUSSIA.
THE REST OF THE WORLD
UNDERSTANDS THAT WE TOOK
JUSTIFIABLE ACTION BASED ON THE
TRAGIC ACTIONS THAT THE ASSAD
REGIME TOOK.
THIS IS AN ACTION THAT CANNOT BE
TOLERATED.
>> HERE'S WHERE THE TALE WILL BE
TOLD.
REX TILLERSON IS HEADED TO
MOSCOW NEXT WEEK WHERE HE WILL
MEET WITH HIS RUSSIAN COUNTER
PART.
TALK ABOUT BEING A FLY ON THE
WALL, THAT WILL BE AN
INTERESTING ONE TO BE A
PARTICIPANT IN.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: STAY WARM, JOHN.
LOOKS NICE THERE, DOESN'T IT?
THE MISSILE STRIKE ON SYRIA WAS
A MEASURED STEP.
WE COULD SEE MORE OF IT.
THOSE WORDS FROM THE UNITED
NATIONS AMBASSADOR NIKKI HALEY
TODAY.
I'LL SPEAK WITH CHRIS WALLACE
ABOUT WHAT IS NEXT.
WE'LL HAVE LAWMAKERS LIVE HERE
TO DISCUSSION THEIR REACTIONS
AND HOW THIS COULD UNFOLD.
IT'S A BUSY NEWS DAY.
GLAD YOU'RE IN.
I'm Thomas and
I quit smoking
with CHANTIX.
I was very grateful
to have CHANTIX.
At times when I would
normally go smoke,
I just didn't.
It's kind of like
"Wait a minute,
I would normally
be running out
the door to go grab
a cigarette."
Along with support,
CHANTIX (varenicline) is proven
to help people quit smoking.
CHANTIX
reduced my urge to smoke.
Some people had changes
in behavior, thinking or mood,
hostility, agitation, depressed
mood and suicidal thoughts
or actions while taking or
after stopping CHANTIX.
Some reported seizures or
sleepwalking with CHANTIX.
If you have any of these,
stop CHANTIX and call your
doctor right away.
Tell your doctor about any
history of
mental health problems,
which could get worse
or of seizures.
Don't take CHANTIX
if you've had a serious
allergic or skin reaction to it.
If you have these, stop CHANTIX
and call your doctor right away
as some can be life-threatening.
Tell your doctor if you have
heart or blood vessel problems,
or develop new
or worse symptoms.
Get medical help right away
if you have symptoms
of a heart attack or stroke.
Decrease alcohol use
while taking CHANTIX.
Use caution driving
or operating machinery.
Most common side effect
is nausea.
Thank you CHANTIX.
Ask your doctor if CHANTIX
is right for you.
>> Shepard: IF YOU'RE GOING TO
SUPPORT A BLOODY DICTATOR, THE
WHOLE WORLD SHOULD KNOW IT.
THAT'S WHAT NIKKI HALEY TOLD
BOLIVIA.
SHE SAYS BOLIVIA'S AMBASSADOR
CALLED FOR A CLOSED DOOR MEETING
AFTER THE STRIKE.
BUT AS PRESIDENT OF THE COUNCIL,
SHE'S A DECIDER.
NIKKI HALEY IS HOLDING AN OPEN
DOOR MEETING INSTEAD.
ANY COUNTRY THAT CHOOSES TO
DEFEND THE ATROCITIES OF THE
REGIME WILL HAVE TO DO SO IN
PUBLIC VIEW FOR THE WORLD TO
HEAR.
THE BOLIVIAN AMBASSADOR WELCOMED
THE MEETING.
>> THE UNITED STATES TOOK A VERY
MEASURED STEP LAST NIGHT.
WE'RE PREPARED TO DO MORE.
BUT WE HELP THAT WILL NOT BE
NECESSARY.
IT IS TIME FOR ALL CIVILIZED
NATIONS TO STOP THE HORRORS THAT
ARE TAKING PLACE IN SYRIA AND
DEMAND A POLITICAL SOLUTION.
>> AMBASSADOR HALEY CALLED OUT
MOSCOW SAYING THE RUSSIANS HAVE
STOOD BESIDE SYRIA EVERY TIME
BASHAR AL-ASSAD HAS CROSSED THE
LINE OF HUMAN DECENCY.
LET'S TURN TO CHRIS WALLACE.
A LOT GOING ON AT THE U.N.
>> WELL, A LOT IS GOING ON WITH
THE TRUMP FOREIGN POLICY.
THINK ABOUT WHAT A DRAMATIC
STATEMENT THIS IS.
THIS IS A PRESIDENT WHO RAN
SAYING HE WASN'T GOING TO GET
INVOLVED AND THIS IS A PRESIDENT
TRYING TO REACH OUT AND CREATE A
NEW RELATIONSHIP WITH THE
KREMLIN.
OVER THE COURSE OF THE LAST 24,
48 HOURS, ALL THAT HAS GONE OUT
THE WINDOW.
THIS IS A PRESIDENT WHO IS
INVOLVED IN SETTING A VERY
BRIGHT -- YES, I'LL USE THE
EXPRESSION RED LINE IN SYRIA --
ABOUT THE BEHAVIOR OF ASSAD AND
HIS SECRETARY OF STATE AND U.N.
AMBASSADOR HAVE TAKEN ON RUSSIA
AND TALKED ABOUT THEIR
INVOLVEMENT AND COMPLICITY WITH
THE AL-ASSAD REGIME AND ATTACKS
ON CIVILIANS, A DRAMATIC
TURN-AROUND IN TRUMP FOREIGN
POLICY THIS WEEK.
>> Shepard: HAVE YOU LEARNED
ANYTHING ABOUT THE NEXT STEPS?
THE IF THEN POSSIBILITY.
IF ASSAD CARRIES OUT ANOTHER
ATTACK LIKE THIS, THEN WHAT?
>> I'M TOLD THERE'S QUITE A
SPLIT.
I'M TOLD BY A TOP U.S. OFFICIAL,
THERE'S QUITE A SPLIT INSIDE THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION, THAT
GENERAL MATTIS, SECRETARY OF
DEFENSE IS ONE OF THE HAWKS ON
THIS.
IN FACT, WANTED TO TAKE EVEN
MORE ACTION IN THIS ATTACK
YESTERDAY.
THIS IS A VERY MEASURED ATTACK.
YES, THEY FIRED 59 CRUISE
MISSILES BUT IT'S ALL AT ONE AIR
BASE AS GENERAL KEANE MENTIONED.
ASSAD HAS SIX AIR BASES AND
COULD HAVE GONE AT AFTER COMMAND
AND CONTROL AND THE PRESIDENT
PERSONALLY.
THE PRESIDENT JUST DECIDED TO GO
AFTER THE ONE BASE SPECIFICALLY
TIED TO THE CHEMICAL ATTACK IN
NORTHERN IRAQ AND THE CIVILIANS
THERE.
MATTIS IS ONE OF THE HAWKS IN
THIS REGARD AND STEVE BANNON,
ONE OF THE AMERICAN FIRSTERS AND
WHO IS ONE OF THE PEOPLE PUSHING
DURING THE CAMPAIGN THE IDEA
THAT WE SHOULDN'T GET INVOLVED
WITH OTHER COUNTRIES, WE SHOULD
BE LOOKING TO THIS COUNTRY, HAS
BEEN ONE OF THE PEOPLE PUSHING
FOR RESTRAINT, SEEMS THAT IN HIS
DECISION YESTERDAY, PRESIDENT
TRUMP TOOK THE KIND OF HALF
STEP.
I THINK IT'S EASY TO ANSWER PART
OF WHAT YOU'RE ASKING.
IF THERE WERE ANOTHER CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK, THERE'S NO DOUBT
THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP WOULD
RESPOND AND ESCALATE HIS ATTACK.
THE MORE INTERESTING QUESTION
IS, BECAUSE HE DIDN'T GO AFTER
THE REGIME, HE DIDN'T GET
INVOLVED IN THE CIVIL WAR, HE
MADE A STATEMENT ABOUT CHEMICAL
WEAPONS, WHAT HAPPENS IF ASSAD
GOES AFTER CIVILIANS IN NORTHERN
IRAQ WITH CONVENTIONAL WEAPONS?
THEN WHAT DOESPRESIDENT TRUMP
DO?
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ARE OVER THE
LINE BUT SLAUGHTERS THOUSANDS
WITH CONVENTIONAL WEAPONS ISN'T?
THAT AND MORE.
>> Shepard: CHRIS HAS A
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH ONE OF
THE MANS HELPED TRUMP PLAN THE
STRIKES.
LIEUTENANT GENERAL M.R.
McMASTER.
THIS WILL BE HIS FIRST INTERVIEW
SINCE GETTING THAT POSITION.
HE'S NOT DONE NATIONAL
TELEVISION.
HE WILL THIS WEEKEND ONLY ON
"FOX NEWS SUNDAY."
CHRIS WILL TALK TO JOHN CORNYN
OF TEXAS AND THE MAJORITY WHIP
AND A MEMBER OF THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE.
BEN CARDON OF MARYLAND, THE
RANKING FOREIGN RELATIONS
MINISTER.
IF YOU CAN CATCH ONE SHOW THIS
WEEKEND, "FOX NEWS SUNDAY" IS
THE WEAPON FOR YOU ON YOUR LOCAL
FOX STATION.
AND AHEAD, WE'LL SPOOK TO A
LAWMAKER FROM EACH PARTY AND
EACH PARTY'S ROLE IN THIS AND
WHETHER PRESIDENT TRUMP SHOULD
HAVE TO GO TO CONGRESS FOR
APPROVAL AS PRESIDENT TRUMP
SUGGESTED THAT BARACK OBAMA
SHOULD BACK IN THE DAY.
BUT FIRST, WHAT COULD HAVE BEEN
OUR TOP STORY ON ANY OTHER DAY?
THE NATION GETTING A NEW SUPREME
COURT JUSTICE.
IT'S NOT UNTIL THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR.
IT'S THE TOP OF THE NEWS THEN
AND WE'LL HAVE IT NEXT.
There's only one egg
that just tastes better.
Fresher.
More flavorful.
Delicious.
Only one egg
with better nutrition-
like more vitamins
D, E, and Omega 3s.
And 25% less saturated fat.
Only one egg good enough
for my family.
Because why have ordinary
when you can have the best.
Eggland's Best.
The only egg that
gives you so much more:
Better taste.
Better nutrition.
Better eggs.
America's veterans are
on the tour of their lives.
At DAV we're on a mission
to help veterans
of all generations
get the benefits they've earned.
Help us support
more victories for veterans.
Go to DAV.org.
>> THE FOX REPORT NOW ON THE
CONFIRMATION OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S SUPREME COURT NOMINEE.
THE SENATE VOTED 54-45 TO MAKE
JUDGE NEIL GORSUCH THE NEW
SUPREME COURT JUSTICE.
JUDGE GORSUCH'S CONFIRMATION WAS
PROMPTED BY THE NUCLEAR OPTION.
THE HISTORIC MOVE COULD CHANGE
THE SUPREME COURT AND THE SENATE
FOR GENERATIONS TO COME.
DEMOCRATIC LEADERS PROTESTED
SAYING IT WILL ONLY MAKE THE
SENATE MORE PARTISAN.
REPUBLICANS SAY DEMOCRATS DIDN'T
GIVE THEM A CHOICE.
MOST DEMOCRATS DID OPPOSE THE
NOMINATION.
SOME SAID IT WAS PARTLY BECAUSE
REPUBLICANS REFUSED TO HOLD A
HEARING FOR JUDGE MERRICK
GARLAND.
THE NEWS CONTINUES AFTER THIS.
.
I need to shave
my A1C
I'm always on call.
An insulin
that fits my
schedule is key.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
(announcer) Tresiba® is used
to control high blood sugar
in adults with diabetes.
Don't use Tresiba® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during episodes
of low blood sugar,
or if you are allergic to any
of its ingredients.
Don't share needles
or insulin pens.
Don't reuse needles.
The most common side effect
is low blood sugar,
which may cause dizziness,
swtiting, confusion,
and headache.
Check your blood sugar.
Low blood sugar can be serious
and may be life-threatening.
Injection site reactions
may occur.
Tell your prescriber
about all medicines you take
and all your medical
conditions.
Taking TZDs
with insulins like Tresiba®
may cause serious side effects
like heart failure.
Your insulin dose
shouldn't be changed
without
asking your prescriber.
Get medical help right away
if you have trouble breathing,
fast heartbeat,
extreme drowsiness,
swelling of your face, tongue,
orhrhroat,
dizziness, or confusion.
Ask your health care
provider
if you're Tresiba® ready.
Covered by most insurance
and Medicare plans.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
>> Shepard: THE TOP DEMOCRAT IN
THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES,
NANCY PELOSI, IS DEMANDING THAT
PAUL RYAN IS CALLING THE
REPRESENTATIVES BACK AFTER THE
AIR STRIKES LAST NIGHT.
SHE SAID CONGRESS MUST DEBATE AN
AUTHORIZATION OF USE OF MILITARY
FORCE AGAINST A SOVEREIGN
NATION.
AN AIDE SAID THE PRESIDENT'S
ACTIONS WERE WITHIN HIS
AUTHORITY BUT IT'S APPROPRIATE
TO CONSULT WITH CONGRESS WHEN
THEY CONSIDER NEXT STEPS FOR THE
CRISIS IN SYRIA.
LAWMAKERS ON BOTH SIDES ARE
CRITICIZING PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
DECISION TO STRIKE IN SYRIA
WITHOUT FIRST GOING TO CONGRESS.
IS OTHERS ARE PRAISING HIM FOR
TAKING THE ACTION.
LAST NIGHT THE PRESIDENT SAID
THE AIR STRIKES WERE IN THE
VITAL NATIONAL SECURITY INTEREST
OF THE UNITED STATES.
TWO CONGRESSMEN COMING NOW,
FIRST A DEMOCRAT, GREGORY MEEKS
OF NEW YORK.
HE'S A SENIOR MEMBER OF THE
HOUSE FOREIGN AFFAIRS COMMITTEE
AND RANKING MEMBER OF THE
EUROPE, EURASIA SUBCOMMITTEE.
GOOD TO HAVE YOU HERE.
>> THANKS TO BE HERE.
>> SHOULD THE PRESIDENT HAVE
CONSULTED CONGRESS?
>> THE ACTS OF MR. ASSAD, THERE
NEEDS TO BE A RESPONSE.
SO THE QUESTION IS WHAT IS THE
APPROPRIATE RESPONSE.
HAD HE COME TO CONGRESS FIRST,
WE WOULD KNOW WHAT THE PLAN IS
BECAUSE A RESPONSE IS NOT A
STRATEGY.
YOU WHETHER IT
WAS THE APPROPRIATE THING TO DO
OR NOT BECAUSE I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE STRATEGY IS.
THE PRESIDENT JUST A WEEK AGO
HAD A DIFFERENT PLAN OR AT LEAST
WHAT HE SAID HOW -- WHAT HE WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
SO I DO BELIEVE THAT THIS -- IT
IS IMPORTANT FOR THE PRESIDENT
NOW TO COME TO CONGRESS WITH
WHAT THAT STRATEGY IS AND IF
THERE'S ANY ADDITIONAL USE OF
MILITARY FORCE, THEN IT SHOULD
BE FIRST VOTED ON AND DEBATED BY
MEMBERS OF THE UNITED STATES
CONGRESS.
>> Shepard: SHOULD BASHAR
AL-ASSAD LAUNCH ANOTHER SARIN
GAS ATTACK ON HIS OWN PEOPLE
THIS EVENING KILLING WOMEN AND
BABIES, THE PRESIDENT SHOULD GO
TO CONGRESS BEFORE RETALIATING?
>> I WISH HE CAME BEFORE.
I BELIEVE I HAD THE OPPORTUNITY
TO VOTE WHEN PRESIDENT CLINTON
DECIDED TO DO AIR STRIKES ON
BOSNIA.
I HAD THE OPPORTUNITY TO VOTE.
WHEN PRESIDENT BUSH WENT INTO
AFGHANISTAN AND IRAQ, I HAD ANT
WANT THE OPPORTUNITY TO VOTE.
THAT'S HOW THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
HAVE THEIR VOICE AND THAT IS
WHAT THE CONSTITUTION DEMANDS.
>> Shepard: CONGRESSMAN, DID THE
PRESIDENT DO THE RIGHT THING
LAST NIGHT?
>> AGAIN, I SAID THAT IF THERE
IS A STRATEGY TO GO ALONG
WITH --
>> Shepard: JUST ON THE SURFACE
OF IT.
RETALIATING IN THAT WAY, IN THAT
MEASURED WAY.
>> IF IT'S JUST A RETALIATION,
IF IT'S JUST A MESSAGE WITH
NOTHING ELSE BEHIND IT, THEN I
WILL SAY NO.
IF IT IS AND THERE IS A STRATEGY
THAT IS BEHIND IT, THEN WE --
LET'S TALK.
I'M WILLING TO HAVE THAT
DIALOGUE.
I NEED TO KNOW THE FACTS.
THAT'S WHAT THE CONSTITUTION
DEMANDS.
THE HEAVIEST VOTE THAT A MEMBER
OF CONGRESS HAS IS TO DETERMINE
WHETHER OR NOT THAT WE ARE TO
AUTHORIZE MILITARY FORCE.
I DON'T WANT TO AVOID THAT
SITUATION.
I ASKED FOR IT ALSO WHEN
PRESIDENT OBAMA WAS
CONTEMPLATING UTILIZING MILITARY
FORCE.
PRESIDENT OBAMA CAME TO CONGRESS
ASKING THEM TO YOU'D LIES -- TO
GIVE THEM THE AUTHORITY AND
CONGRESS DECIDED NOT TO STEP UP
TO THE PLATE.
WE SHOULD STEP UP TO THE PLATE.
BECAUSE WHETHER IT'S THIS
PRESIDENT OR ANY PRESIDENT, WE
SHOULD NOT SHARE WHAT OUR
RESPONSIBILITIES ARE UNDER THE
UNITED STATES CONSTITUTION.
>> Shepard: WHAT ALLY DO YOU
EXPECT TO SEE INVOLVED NOW?
>> I WOULD HOPE WE HAVE ALL OF
OUR ALLIES IN THE GULF REGION,
BECAUSE AS INDICATED IN THE PAST
BY SECRETARY POWELL, ONCE YOU
BREAK SOMETHING, YOU OWN IT.
SO I WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT ALL
OF OUR ALLIES IN THE GULF STATES
ARE THERE AS WELL AS OUR
EUROPEAN ALLIES AND ALLIES
AROUND THE WORLD.
WHAT HAS HAPPENED AND WHEN YOU
TALK ABOUT THE VIOLATION OF THE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS PARTICULARLY,
IT IS A VIOLATION OF
INTERNATIONAL LAW.
I THINK THAT IS CLEAR.
WE ALL NEED TO STOP AND TRY TO
FIGHT TOGETHER TO PREVENT THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS THAT SYRIA
HAS BEGUN.
WHICH INCLUDES MAKING SURE THAT
THOSE THAT ARE PROPERLY VETTED
AND THOSE THAT FOR SAFETY, KIDS
AND WOMEN AND ET CETERA, THOSE
PROPERLY VETTED AS THEY'RE GOING
TO GERMANY, WE SHOULD ALLOW THEM
TO COME TO THE UNITED STATES OF
AMERICA.
>> THAT WAS PART OF YOUR SHORT
STATEMENT ON THIS MATTER.
YOU BELIEVE THAT SYRIAN REFUGEES
SHOULD BE ADMITTED TO THE UNITED
STATES AS THEY ARE IN SO MANY
OTHER COUNTRIES.
IS THE VETTING IN PLACE, A
TWO-YEAR VETTING PROCESS FOR
REFUGEES, WAS THAT NOT STRONG
ENOUGH IN YOUR MIND FOR THE
COUNTRIES THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
DESIGNATED?
>> THE VETTING PROCESS AND HAS
BEEN SUCCESSFUL.
ARBITRARILY, DETERMINE THAT
WE'RE GOING TO STOP THOSE THAT
HAD BEEN VETTEDED FOR TWO YEARS
AND MAKE THE DETERMINATION AND
MANY OF THOSE INDIVIDUALS WERE
INDIVIDUALS THAT HAVE HELPED US
IN THE WAR.
SOME OF THEM HAD BEEN MEMBERS
OF -- HAD FAMILY MEMBERS HERE
BUT THEY HAD BEEN VETTED FOR TWO
YEARS.
FOR US TO ARBITRARILY SAY THAT
WE'RE NOT GO ALLOW THEM IN I
THINK IS A MISTAKE.
IT HURTS OTHER INDIVIDUALS WHO
WOULD HELP US WITH INTELLIGENCE
ON THE GROUND FROM GIVING US
THAT INTELLIGENCE.
>> CONGRESSMAN, GREAT FOR YOU TO
BE HERE.
THANK YOU.
>> MY PLEASURE.
>> Shepard: AND NOW TO RON JOHN
ON OF WISCONSIN.
HE'S A MEMBER OF THE FOREIGN
RELATIONS COMMITTEE AND THE
CHAIRMAN OF HOMELAND SECURITY
COMMITTEE.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>> Shepard: THE PRESIDENT MADE
THIS DECISION AFTER SEEING THE
PICTURES OF THE BABIES
SLAUGHTERED.
YOU KNOW THAT THIS SLAUGHTER HAS
BEEN GOING ON FOR SEVEN YEARS.
THE ACTION OF THIS BRUTAL
DICTATOR DIDN'T CHANGE.
OUR ACTIONS CHANGED.
WAS IT WARRANTED AND IF SO WHAT
THE IS WARRANTED GOING FORWARD?
>> I DEFINITELY THINK THIS IS AN
APPROPRIATE RESPONSE.
IT'S WHAT PRESIDENT OBAMA SHOULD
HAVE DONE AFTER THE FIRST USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS OF THE SYRIAN
PEOPLE.
SHOULD HAVE BEEN SWIFT AND
DECISIVE AND WOULD HAVE PROBABLY
MADE A DIFFERENCE.
THE PRESIDENT DITHERED.
HE DIDN'T ASK FOR AN
AUTHORIZATION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP DID NOT ALLOW
THE MOMENT TO PASS, SO I SUPPORT
HIS VERY MEASURED RESPONSE TO
THIS ATROCITY.
>> SHOULD THE SYRIAN DICTATOR
STRIKE AGAIN ON HIS OWN PEOPLE
WITH CHEMICAL WEAPONS, SHOULD
THE PRESIDENT TAKE OUT HIS AIR
FORCE?
>> WE SHOULD RESPOND IN KIND
PROPORTIONATE WITH WHATEVER
MEASURES THAT THE ADMINISTRATION
WOULD DEEM APPROPRIATE.
I THINK OBVIOUSLY IT WOULD BE A
STEPPED UP RESPONSE.
>> HE'S BEEN USING BARREL BOMBS
FOR THE BETTER PART OF THE LAST
FIVE YEARS AS FAR AS I CAN TELL.
VERY CRUDE BOMBS THAT ARE TOSSED
FROM HELICOPTERS OR FIXED-WING
PLANES.
THEY KILL EVERY ONE IN THE
VICINITY THE SAME WAY THESE DO.
IF WE RESPOND TO THIS SARIN GAS
ATTACK, SHOULD WE RESPOND TO   N
CONVENTIONAL ATTACKS?
>> WE SHOULD HAVE BEEN.
THIS GENOCIDE IS CONTINUING
WITHOUT A RESPONSE.
BUT THAT WAS PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
CHOICE NOT TO RESPOND, NOT TO
COME TO CONGRESS WITH ROBUST
AUTHORIZATION.
SOMETHING THAT DID NOT TIE THE
HANDS OF THE FUTURE PRESIDENT.
THAT'S WHY PRESIDENT OBAMA COULD
GET AN AUTHORIZATION FOR USE OF
MILITARY FORCE.
IT WAS TOO WEAK.
HE NEVER TOLD THE AMERICAN
PUBLIC WHY SYRIA IS IN AMERICA'S
NATIONAL INTEREST.
WE'VE SEEN THE MIGRANT FLOW AND
THE HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS
FLOWING TO EUROPE DETABLIZING
THOSE COUNTRIES AND PUTTING INTO
RISK THE VISA WAIVER PROGRAM.
IT'S ABOUT TIME WE'RE REACTING.
IT'S IN RESPONSE TO ILLEGAL WAR
CRIME TYPES OF ACTIONS.
I GUESS WE'LL TAKE WHATEVER
MEASURES WE SHOULD IN ANSWER TO
THAT PROVOCATION.
>> Shepard: WHAT SHOULD THE
LIMIT OF OUR RESPONSE BE IN THE
SYRIAN WAR?
>> FROM MY STANDPOINT, IF WE'RE
GOING TO GET EMBROILED MORE IN
THE WAR, THAT IS SOMETHING THAT
THE PRESIDENT SHOULD COME TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE AND CONGRESS TO
LOOK FOR AN AUTHORIZATION.
BY PRESENT, I DO NOT BELIEVE HE
NEEDS AUTHORIZATION IN TERMS OF
DEFEATING ISIS, WHICH IS NOW IN
SYRIA.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT TWO
SITUATIONS HERE.
THIS RESPONSE WAS A ONE-TIME
RESPONSE HOPEFULLY TO DETER
FUTURE USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
IF WE'RE GOING TO ADDRESS THE
SYRIAN SITUATION, OUR FIRST STEP
IS TO DEFEAT ISISLE NOW WE HAVE
TO ASK OUR SAYS QUESTION.
WHO WILL DEFEAT ISIS FORCES IN
RAQQA AND WHO WILL HOLD THE
GROUND.
THAT COULD MAKE A DIPLOMATIC
SOLUTION POSSIBLE.
>> BACK TO AL-ASSAD.
SHOULD THERE BE A REGIME CHANGE?
>> I DON'T SEE HOW A DICTATOR, A
LEADER OF A COUNTRY WHO HAS
SLAUGHTERED 500,000 CITIZENS
WILL LAST LONG-TERM.
THE SAD FACT, BECAUSE OF OUR
LACK OF INVOLVEMENT, WEAKNESS,
WE CREATED A VACUUM.
IRAN AND RUSSIA HAS FILLED THE
VACUUM.
THEY HAVE SOLIDIFIED THEIR
POSITION IN WESTERN SYRIA.
WE HAVE TO CHANGE THE FACTS ON
THE GROUND AND MIGHT ALLOW FOR A
DIPLOMATIC SOLUTION.
>> IRAN, RUSSIA AND HEZBOLLAH
ARE ALL BACKING THE SYRIANS.
SHOULD THE UNITED STATES ENGAGE
IN THAT FIGHT, YOU'VE SAID HERE
THAT WE SHOULD RESPOND IN KIND
IF THERE IS BARREL BOMBING AND
THE LIKE.
SHOULD THE UNITED STATES PIT
ITSELF AGAINST THOSE THREE
POWERS AT THE SAME TIME AND DO
YOU HAVE CONCERNS ABOUT IT
SPREAD SOMETHING.
>> THE USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS
IS OUTLAWED INTERNATIONALLY.
THAT ALLOW AS CERTAIN RESPONSE.
>> BARREL BOMBING IS AS WELL.
>> I UNDERSTAND.
AGAIN, I HAVE NO IDEA WHY THE
WORLD DIDN'T RESPONSE.
WE'RE RESPONDING NOW.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR RUSSIA AND
IRAN TO DEFEND THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
IT WAS RUSSIA INVOLVED IN
PRECISION BOMBING OF HOSPITALS
AND HUMANITARIAN ENVOYS.
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION DID
NOTHING OTHER THAN TALK ABOUT
SERIOUS CONSEQUENCES.
THIS PRESIDENT PRODUCED REAL
CONSEQUENCES.
A VERY MEASURED AND VERY
DIRECTED APPROACH TO TRY TO
DETER FURTHER USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
I'M NOT SURE WHERE IT GOES FROM
HERE.
MY STANDPOINT, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION SHOULD LAY OUT A
STRATEGY, SHOULD ESTABLISH SOME
GOALS.
COME TO THE AMERICAN PUBLIC,
COME TO CONGRESS FOR
AUTHORIZATION IF HE DECIDES TO
DO SOMETHING MORE ROBUST.
>> DEMOCRAT AND REPUBLICANS
AGREEING ON THAT.
SENATOR RON JOHNSON, THE
REPUBLICAN OF WISCONSIN.
GRADE TO BE HERE.
>> HAVE A GREAT DAY.
>> Shepard: ONE ANALYST SAID THE
STRIKE COULD LEAD TO A POLITICAL
SOLUTION AND THERE'S A CLEAR
PATH FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP TO GET
THERE.
WHAT MIGHT THAT BE?
I'LL SPEAK WITH THAT ANALYST
NEXT.
REMEMBER HERE AT ALLY,
NOTHING STOPS US FROM DOING
RIGHT BY OUR CUSTOMERS.
WHO'S WITH ME?
WE'RE LIKE A BASKETBALL
TEAM HERE AT ALLY.
IF A BASKETBALL
TEAM HAD OVER 7...
I'M IN.
7,000 PLAYERS.
OUR PLAYS ARE A
LITTLE UNORTHODOX.
BUT TO BEAT THE BIG BOYS,
YOU NEED SMARTER WAYS
TO SAVE PEOPLE MONEY.
WE KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
FROM A FINANCIAL COMPANY
AND WE'LL STOP AT...
NOTHING TO MAKE SURE YOU GET IT.
ONE, TWO...
AND WE MEAN NOTHING.
♪  ♪
ENERGY IS AMAZING.NG.
HOW WE USE IT IS ONLY LIMITED
BY OUR IMAGINATION.
AND AT SOUTHERN COMPANY
WE'RE BUILDING THE FUTURE
OF ENERGY,
FOR YOU.
♪
That's life.
You diet. You exercise.
And if you still need help
lowering your blood sugar...
...this is JARDIANCE.
Along with diet and exercise...
JARDIANCE lowers blood sugar
and A1C
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
JARDIANCE is also the only type
2 diabetes treatment with heart-
proven to reduce the risk
of cardiovascular death
in adults with type 2 diabetes
and cardiovascular disease.
JARDIANCE can cause serious side
effects, including dehydration.
This may cause you to feel
dizzy, faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious side
effect that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness, and
trouble breathing.
Stop taking JARDIANCE and call
your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are sudden
kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So talk to your doctor
about JARDIANCE-
the one and only type 2 diabetes
treatment with heart.
Visit JARDIANCE.com for a free
consultation with
a Certified Diabetes Educator
if you qualify.
>> Shepard: MORE NOW ON THE U.S.
MISSILE STRIKE IN SYRIA.
MICHAEL HANLAN IS HERE FROM THE
BROOKINGS INSTITUTE.
WHAT DID YOU THINK OF THAT?
>> SHEPARD, WELL, I THINK IT WAS
A GOOD STRIKE FOR THE PURPOSES
THAT WERE ANNOUNCED AND THE
PURPOSES THAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
ANNOUNCED.
LEAVES A LOT OF QUESTIONS OF
WHAT COMES NEXT.
I THINK IT WAS WELL-DONE.
>> Shepard: WHAT IS THE EFFECT
OF THAT STRIKE PRACTICALLY
SPEAKING?
>> WELL, MILITARILY SPEAKING,
MOST OF US WOULD AGREE.
NOT VERY MUCH.
I'M NOT EVEN SURE IF THERE WERE
MANY AIRCRAFT DAMAGED.
MAY HAVE BEEN A FEW.
IN TERMS OF ANY KIND OF
MUNITIONS THAT ASSAD NEEDS, AS
POINTED OUT, HE DOESN'T NEED
MUCH IN THE WAY OF TECHNOLOGY
FOR THE TACTICS HE'S EMPLOYING.
IT WAS DESIGNED AGAINST ONE AIR
BASE OUT OF A DOZEN IN THE
COUNTRY.
IT IS MOSTLY TO SEND A MESSAGE.
MORE OF A RE-ESTABLISHMENT OF
DETERRENCE.
IT DOESN'T TELL US WHAT
MR. TRUMP MIGHT DO NEXT.
HE HAS TO THINK HARD ABOUT THAT.
THERE'S GOOD OPTIONS.
SOME INVOLVE COOPERATION WITH
RUSSIA.
THEY'RE NOT OBVIOUS.
>> THIS RUSSIAN BLUSTER, HOW DO
YOU READ IT?
>> WELL, I THINK THE RUSSIANS
WILL VET NOR AWHILE.
FOR VLADIMIR PUTIN, WE'VE BEEN
BEATING HIM UP FOR VIOLATIONS OF
INTERNATIONAL LAW.
FOR EXAMPLE, HE'S USED THE
SEIZURE AND ANNEXATION OF CRIMEA
AS JUSTIFIABLE BECAUSE IT WAS
RUSSIAN FOR SO MANY CENTURIES.
BUT WE GET ON OUR HIGH HORSE AND
BLAME HIM FOR THE WORST CRISIS
IN EUROPE SINCE WORLD WAR II AND
WE DON'T GET A U.N. RESOLUTION
TO INVADE IRAQ AND WE INVADE
LIBYA.
SO HE IS GOING TO CARRY OUT
PAY-BACK RIGHT NOW.
I DON'T THINK IT HAS TO
NECESSARILY IMPEDE US GETTING
BACK TO BUSINESS NEXT WEEK WHEN
I BELIEVE MR. TILLERSON IS
SCHEDULED TO VISIT MOSCOW.
I HOPE WE CAN START THE
COOPERATI
COOPERATION.
IT WILL TAKE SOME WORK.
BUT THERE'S WAYS TO EACH OF US
GETTING MOST OF WHAT WE WANT.
>> FROM YOUR KNOWLEDGE OF
AL-ASSAD, HOW MUCH DANGER IS
THERE THAT HE WOULD PUSH THIS
TOWARD ESCALATION?
>> I THINK SO FAR VERY LITTLE.
BECAUSE HE HAS TO KNOW THAT THE
PUNISHMENT THAT HE RECEIVED
YESTERDAY WAS VERY MINOR
COMPARED TO WHAT WE COULD DO.
THERE'S NO REASON FOR HIM THERE
TO WANT TO RUN THE RISK OF
PICKING A FIGHT WITH A SUPER
POWER.
AT THE MOMENT, ALL WE'VE SAID
FOR SURE IS WE WANT TO DEFEAT
ISIS AND WE WON'T LET HIM USE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
OTHERWISE, IT'S FREE GAME FOR
HIM WHAT HE WILL LIKELY DO IS
KEEP FIGHTING THE WAR WITHOUT
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
AFTER ALL, 99% OF THE KILLING
HE'S DONE IS WITH BARREL BOMBS
AS THE MAJOR PROBLEM IN THIS
CONFLICT SO FAR.
SO MY EXPECTATION IS HE WILL SEE
IF HE CAN RIDE OUT YESTERDAY'S
STRIKE AND HAVE THAT BE THE END
OF IT.
WE'LL HAVE TO FIND OUT.
>> Shepard: WE WILL.
MICHAEL O'HAN LAN FROM
BROOKINGS.
NICE TO SEE YOU.
ANOTHER DEVELOPING STORY AND
ANOTHER DEADLY ATTACK WITH A
TRUCK.
NOW WORD OF AN ARREST.
THE LATEST STRIKE WAS TODAY AND
THE UPDATE IS NEXT.
Yeah, my dad says our
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Various: (Shouting) Heigh!
Ho!
( ♪ )
It's off to work we go!
Woman:
On the Gulf Coast,
new ExxonMobil projects
are expected to create
over 45,000 jobs.
And each job created
by the energy industry
supports two others
in the community.
Altogether,
the industry supports over
9 million jobs nationwide.
These are jobs that natural
gas is helping make happen,
all while reducing
America's emissions.
Energy lives here.
>> Shepard: POLICE SAY THEY HAVE
ARRESTED ONE PERSON AFTER THE
DEADLY ATTACK IN SWEDEN.
THEY SAY SOMEONE STOLE A BEER
TRUCK AND KILLED FOUR AND
INJURED 15 MORE AFTER RUNNING IT
IN A DEPARTMENT STORE.
WE HAVE SECURITY CAMERA VIDEO.
WATCH HERE.
SHOWS THE MOMENT THAT PEOPLE
TAKE COVER AS THE TRUCK SPEEDS
BY THEM.
A FRANTIC SCENE.
THE SWEDISH MINISTER CALLING IT
AN ATTACK OF TERROR.
IT HAPPENED IN STOCKHOLM.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY STOPPED ALL
THE TRAINS OUT OF THE STATION.
TWO LARGE SHOPPING MALLS ALSO
SHUT DOWN.
POLICE SAY THIS IS AN IMAGE OF
MAN THEY ARRESTED.
THEY RELEASED A PHOTO EARLIER
TODAY.
NO WORD ON WHETHER THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR OTHER SUSPECTS.
THIS IS RIGHT AFTER THE CRASH.
SEAR HERE IN THE BACK?
THAT IS THE VEHICLE THAT BEER
TRUCK THAT RAMMED INTO THE
DEPARTMENT STORE.
PEOPLE LOOKING FOR A PLACE TO
RUN THERE.
THE TRUCK STICKING OUT OF THE
BUILDING.
FLAMES BURNING IN THE SPOT WHERE
IT HIT.
HERE'S PEOPLE BEING TREATED ON
THE PAVEMENT, THE COBBLESTONE.
THE TRUCK ATTACKS ARE ALL TOO
FAMILIAR.
POLICE ARE TAKING EXTRA
PRECAUTION.
AFGHANISTAN IS THE SITE OF
AMERICA'S LARGEST WAR.
IF ANYBODY KNOWS WHAT IT'S LIKE
TO BE MIRED IN FIGHTING THERE,
IT'S THE RUSSIANS.
BUT THE RUSSIANS CALLED IT QUITS
ON THIS DAY IN HISTORY.
Hey, ready for the big meeting?
Yeah.
Uh, hello!?
A meeting?
It's a big one.
Too bad.
We are double booked:
diarrhea and
abdominal pain.
Why don't you start
without me?
Oh. Yeah.
If you're living with frequent,
unpredictable diarrhea
and abdominal pain,
you may have...
...Irritable Bowel Syndrome
with Diarrhea,
or IBS-D.
A condition that can
be really frustrating.
Talk to your doctor
about VIBERZI,
a different way to treat IBS-D.
VIBERZI is a
prescription medication
you take every day
that helps proactively manage
both diarrhea and abdominal pain
at the same time.
So you stay ahead of
your symptoms.
VIBERZI can cause new or
worsening abdominal pain.
Do not take VIBERZI if you have
or may have had:
pancreas or
severe liver problems,
problems with alcohol abuse,
long-lasting or
severe constipation,
or a blockage of your bowel
or gallbladder.
If you are taking VIBERZI,
you should not take medicines
that cause constipation.
The most common side effects of
VIBERZI include
constipation, nausea, and
abdominal pain.
Stay ahead of IBS-D...
...with VIBERZI.
>> Shepard: ON THIS DAY IN 1988,
THE SOVIETS DECIDED IT WAS TIME
TO PULL TROOPS OUT OF AFGH
AFGHANIST
AFGHANISTAN.
THE SOVIET UNION WAS STUCK IN A
STALEMATE.
THEY WITH DREW FROM THE COUNTRY
AFTER EIGHT YEARS OF BLOODY
FIGHTING AGAINST THE INSURGENTS
THAT WANTED TO TOPPLE THE PRO
SOVIET COMMUNIST GOVERNMENT
THERE.
THE REBELS HAD THE SUPPORT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
IT WOULD TAKE NEARLY A YEAR
UNTIL THE LAST SOVIET SOLDIERS
LEFT THE COUNTRY AND HEADED OUT
THE KIBER PASS AFTER THE RUSSIAN
DEFENSE MINISTER SIGNED OFF ON
GETTING OUT OF AFGHANISTAN 29
YEARS AGO TODAY.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
BREAKING NEWS CHANGES EVERYTHING
ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
THE DOW HAS BEEN ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
LOOKS LIKE AN EKG.
DOWN 272.
NEIL CAVUTO IS UP NEXT, THIS IS
AMERICA'S CHOICE FOR NEWS AND
INFORMATION ON CABLE.
GLAD YOU'RE WITH US ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT.
AFTER THE AIR STRIKES ON THAT
SYRIAN AIR BASE FOLLOWING THE
ATTACK, THE BATTLE IS ON BETWEEN
THE U.S. AND RUSH SHE AND THE
U.N.
IT GOT UGLY TODAY.
OFF THE COAST OF SYRIA WHERE A
RUSSIAN WARSHIP IS STEAMING
TOWARDS TWO U.S. DESTROYERS.
THEN LOOK AT THE DOW FUTURES.
TANKING ON NEWS OF THE STRIKES
BEFORE BOUNCING BACK AS MORE AND
MORE U.S. ALLIES AND WESTERN
EUROPEAN GOVERNMENT EXPRESSED
STRONG SUPPORT FOR THOSE
ACTIONS.
AND WATER ON THIS.
A DEADLY TERROR A