>>> FOX URGENT.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
ON SEVERE WEATHER WATCH NOW AND
IT IS HITTING MUCH OF THE MID
SECTION OF THE COUNTRY.
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS TORNADO
CONDITIONS THERE.
WITH TOUCHDOWNS ALREADY
HAPPENING.
ON THE GROUND NEAR WICHITA.
IN OKLAHOMA, NEAR OKLAHOMA
CITY.
THE TWISTERS PART OF A VERY HE
STRONG AND AS YOU CAN SEE WIDE
SYSTEM MAKING ITS WAY THROUGH
THE NORTHERN AND CENTRAL PLAINS
RIGHT NOW.
THIS HAS BEEN COOKING UP FOR
THREE HOURS NOW AND WE ARE AT
THE PINNACLE OF THAT AND THE
THREAT ONLY EXPECTED TOEN
CREASE FROM THIS POINT OUT.
WE ARE AT THE TOP OF THE
HEATING OF THEIR DAY AND IT
GETS TOUGHER FROM HERE INTO THE
NIGHT UNTIL THINGS COOL DOWN.
AND THE SYSTEM EXPECTED TO
STRETCH INTO TOMORROW.
METEOROLOGIST JANICE DEAN IS IN
THE FOX WEATHER CENTER.
WE HE HAVE ONE THAT THEY ARE
WATCHING RIGHT NOW OUTSIDE OF
NORMAN OKLAHOMA.
WE BELIEVE A TOUCHDOWN
HAPPENING AS WE SPEAK.
>> YES, AND DAMAGE REPORTS
UNFORTUNATELY, HARRIS.
I CHECKED THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE AND NORMAN OKLAHOMA IS
WHERE THE STORM PREDICTION
CENTER IS.
THEY KNOW TORNADOES.
UNFORTUNATELY, WE ARE SEEING
DAMAGE IN AND AROUND OKLAHOMA
CITY NORMAN, OKLAHOMA UP
THROUGH KANSAS AND WICHITA AND
THEN COULD HAVE STRAIGHTLINE
DAMAGING WINDS MOVING THROUGH
THE KANSAS CITY AREA.
JUST WANT TO POINT OUT WHERE WE
HAVE TORNADO WATCHES EXTENDING
THROUGH OKLAHOMA AND KANSAS UP
TOWARDS IOWA AND MINNESOTA FOR
THE NEXT SEVERAL HOURS AND
UNFORTUNATELY THIS KIND OF
SCENARIO IS GOING TO KIN INTO
THE OVERNIGHT -- CONTINUE INTO
THE OVERNIGHT AND INTO
TOMORROW.
NORMAN OKLAHOMA.
SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA CITY WHERE WE
HAVE REPORTS OF DEBRIS AND SOME
DAMAGE AS WELL A TORNADO
WARNING JUST NORTH AND EAST OF
CHANDLER OKLAHOMA.
UP TOWARDS KANSAS.
SOUTH AND EAST OF WICHITA HERE,
WEST OF INDEPENDENCE KANSAS IS
WHERE WE HAVE THE TORNADO
WARNING THERE.
THEN MOVING INTO IOWA.
FORT DODGE.
GETTING INTO HEAVILY POPULATED
AREAS HERE.
CITIES.
A TORNADO WARNING EAST OF
MINNEAPOLIS THAT HAS IS SINCE
BE LIFTED WHICH IS GREAT NEWS.
YOU WILL,UNFORTUNATELY, WE ARE GETTING
INTO HEAVILY POPULATED AREAS.
DAMAGE COULD BE QUITE SEVERE
AND EXTREME IN SOME OF THE
AREAS AS THE STORMS PUSH
EASTWARD AND THEY ARE NOT
LETTING UP UNFORTUNATELY.
TAKING A LOOK AT THE SEVERE
THREAT FROM TEXAS ALL THE WEIGH
UP TO THE MIDWEST THE GREAT
LAKES WITH THE CONCENTRATED
RISK OVER THE CENTRAL PLAINS.
OKLAHOMA CITY JOPLIN,
KANSAS CITY, A YOU WILL OF THE
INGREDIENTS FAVORABLE FOR
LONGING LASTING LARGE
DESTRUCTIVE TORNADOES.
INTO MONDAY AND INTO THE
OVERNIGHT, PEOPLE NEED TO HAVE
THE NOAA WEATHER RADIOS ON IF
YOU LIVE IN THE AREAS BECAUSE
THE STORMS ARE COMING AND YOU
ARE NOT GOING TO BE ABLE TO SEE
THEM.
MONDAY STILL OKLAHOMA CITY UP
TOWARDS JOPLIN AND ALL OF THE
AREAS IN YELLOW HERE, YOU ARE
NOT OUT OF THE RISK ZONE.
COULD SEE LARGE HAIL, DAMAGING
WINDS.
HEAVY RAIN AND THE RISK FOR
TORNADOES.
HEADING INTO TUESDAY ACROSS THE
GREAT LAKES THE TENNESSEE
RIVER VALLEY AND THE
MISSISSIPPI RIVER VALLEY.
ONE OF THE MAIN INGREDIENTS WE
NEED FOR THE STORMS IS THE WARM
AIR AHEAD OF THE COLD FRONT AND
LOOK AT THIS HARRIS TALKING
ABOUT UPPER 80s AND LOW 90s
AND 50s AND 60s BEHIND THE
FRONT.
UNFORTUNATELY, A PROLONGED
EVENT FOR THE NEXT 48 EVEN 72
HOURS.
>> AS THOSE SYSTEMS COLLIDE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THERE ARE WEATHER SPOTTERS,
PEOPLE WHO DRIVE AROUND LOOKING
AT THESE THINGS WHEN THEY
HAPPEN.
I KNOW MANY OF YOU ARE TRYING
TO GET YOUR EVEN PICTURES OF
THIS.
PLEASE BE CAREFUL.
ON THE PHONE WITH US IS SOMEONE
WHO IS BEING CAREFUL.
EMILY IS DRIVING IN OKLAHOMA
CITY RIGHT NOW THE AREA AND SAW
YOU SEVERAL FUNNEL CLOUDS.
EMILY, ARE YOU WITH US?
>> YES MA'AM.
THANK YOU.
>> TELL ME WHAT YOU WITNESSED?
>> I'M ON THE EAST SIDE OF
OKLAHOMA CITY NORTH OF EDMOND.
I'M DRIVING RIGHT NOW AND I CAN
LOOK SOUTH INTO THE NORMAN AREA
AND SEE JUST BLACKNESS AND AT
5:00 SOMETHING IN THE AFTERNOON
THAT IS AN ODD SIGHT TO SEE AND
LOOK DIRECTLY NORTH WHERE THERE
WERE SEVERAL TOUCHDOWNS AND I
WITNESSED PERSONALLY IN LUCE
RAM THEN HAIL AND A SPLASH OF
SUN LIGHT HERE.
THE WEIRDEST THING I HAVE SEEN.
I HAVE TO SAY.
>> YOU ARE FROM THAT PART OF
THE COUNTRY ORIGINALLY?
>> I GREW UP IN THE THE
MIDWEST.
>> SO YOU HAVE SEEN THIS
BEFORE.
HOW DOES THE DAY COMPARE.
WHAT WE ARE HEARING ABOUT THE
SEVERAL DAY EVENT IS THE HUGE
BUILDING.
WHAT IS THE TEMPERATURE LIKE?
WHAT ARE THE CONDITIONS LIKE
COMPARATIVELY TO WHAT YOU
EXPERIENCED?
>> IT IS WEIRD.
I LIVE IN THE CITY AND YOU HEAR
THIS STUFF ALL THE TIME YOU CAN
GO OUT ON THE FRONT PORCHES AND
UNLESS YOU SEE A TORNADO FROM
THERE, THAT IS KIND OF OUR
MANTRA.
BEING IN THE CITY AND KNOWING
THERE IS A TORNADO MILES AWAY,
THERE WAS A TORNADO THAT
TOUCHED DOWN NEAR MY
NEIGHBORHOOD.
THIS IS IN THE CITY AND WHERE
WE WENT TO SCHOOL AND THIS IS
WHERE STUFF HAPPENS.
>> RIGHT NOW.
I WILL CUT IN IN JUST A SECOND.
THIS IS BRAND NEW VIDEO COMING
IN TO FOX NEWS.
THIS IS SHOWING THE DEBRIS
FIELD AND THIS REALLY
COMMUNICATES TO THE FORECASTING
EXPERTS AND I KNOW JANICE DEAN
IS WATCHING THIS, THIS
COMMUNICATES THE SIZE AND POWER
OF THIS TYPE OF MONSTER HITTING
THE GROUND.
EMILY, YOU WITNESSED SOME OF
THIS BECAUSE THIS VIDEO IS
TAKEN FROM EDMOND.
WHAT IT WAS LIKE EARLIER WITH
THOSE WINDS WHIPPING AND NOW WE
CAN SEE STUFF JUST BLOWING IN
THE AIR.
>> IT IS TERRIFYING.
IT IS TERRIFYING.
GOSH THE HOT AIR AND THEN YOU
GET IT IS REAL COOL AND YOU
HAVE SHIVERS UP YOUR SPINE.
THE ODDEST THING IS SEEING
THINGS ACTUALLY FLOATING IN THE
AIR.
NOT BLOWING ONE DIRECTION OR
ANOTHER.
LOOK UP AND ONE CLOUD HEADING
ONE DIRECTION AND ANOTHER ARE
CLOUD HEADING THE OTHER.
IT IS SURREAL.
>> YOU MENTIONED THE HEAVILY
POPULATED AREAS.
WE SAID THIS ON FOX REPORT LAST
NIGHT.
KANSAS CITY, OKLAHOMA CITY.
UNTIL YOU SEE IT, IT REALLY
DOESN'T SEEM REAL TO YOU AND
HAVING LIVED IN KANSAS CITY FOR
MANY YEARS AND I HAVE SEEN THE
TORNADOIC SYSTEMS MOVE ACROSS
THE PLAINS, YOU CAN PICK THEM
UP AND WATCH THEM MOVE INTO
YOUR TOWN.
WHEN YOU SEE THIS, IT RARELY
HITS THE AREAS WHERE THERE ARE
TALL BUILDINGS AND SO MANY
STRUCTURES.
YOU MENTIONED THE UNIVERSITY
THERE, CHRISTIAN HOW ARE
PEOPLE DEALING WITH THE
WARNINGS THERE?
ARE THEY HEEDING SIRENS?
>> I WISH I COULD SAY THAT THEY
WERE.
THAT IS THE WEIRD THING IS WE
ARE USED TO SEEING IT ON THE TV
AND NO BIG DEAL FOR WHERE WE
ARE, WE KNOW IT IS WAY OUT
THERE.
WHEN IT DOES COME TO OUR AREA,
YOU JUST GET IN THE CAR AND YOU
HAVE TO CHECK IT OUT.
I HOPE PEOPLE ARE BEING
RESPONSIBLE BUT DRIVING AROUND
IT IS HARD.
PEOPLE ARE SPEEDING.
I RAN ACROSS SOMEBODY WHO
WASN'T LOOKING WHERE THEY WERE
GOING AND THERE WAS A TERRIBLE
WRECK.
I MEAN THERE IS GOING TO BE
OTHER INJURIES AND ACCIDENTS
THAT HAPPEN BECAUSE OF TORNADO
BUT NOT THE TORNADO ITSELF AND
THAT IS THE IMPORTANT THING
TOO.
>> YOU ARE IN YOUR CAR.
PARKED, OF COURSE.
YOU ARE TALKING WITH US.
STAY SAFE, EMILY OUR FIRST
PERSON EYES TONIGHT ON FOX
REPORT.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AND OUR PRAYERS FOR THOSE
PEOPLE THAT THEY STAY SAFE
TONIGHT.
WE HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO TALK
WITH JENNIFER MONROE THE PUBLIC
INFORMATION SPECIALIST FOR THE
TOWN OF EDMOND, OKLAHOMA JUST
OUTSIDE OF OKLAHOMA CITY WHERE
THEY HAVE SEEN SO MUCH
TREMENDOUS DAMAGE AND DANGEROUS
CONDITIONS AND EVEN SOME
INJURIES.
JENNIFER, ARE YOU ON THE PHONE
WITH ME NOW?
>> I AM.
>> I WANT TO START WITH THE
FACT THAT YOU ARE THE TYPICAL
PERSON I WOULD CALL AND ASK FOR
INFORMATION IN AN EMERGENCY
SITUATION AS A REPORTER AND YOU
WOULD GIVE ME THE INFORMATION.
TODAY YOU WERE DOING SUCH
ONSIDE OF A TORNADO SHELTER.
WHAT WAS GOING ON?
>> I LIVE JUST NORTH OF TOWN SO
MY FAMILY AND I WE ACTUALLY DID
HAVE TO TAKE SHELTER OURSELVES.
SO THE STORM PASSED AND THEN
CAME ON INDOORS TO HELP ASSESS
THE DAMAGE AND WORK WITH THE
MEDIA.
>> EDMOND, OKLAHOMA, WE ARE
SEEING IT NOW.
THE PICTURES THAT HAVE COME IN
TO FOX NEWS IN THE PAST FEW
MINUTES.
THE WINDS WHIPPING AS FUNNEL
CLOUD IS TRYING TO HOLD ITSELF
TOGETHER AND DOING SO RATHER
IMPRESSIVELY.
TALK TO ME ABOUT PEOPLE
TONIGHT.
HOW ARE THEY IN YOUR AREA?
>> RIGHT NOW WE -- THE
EMERGENCY CREWS ARE STARTING
GOING NEIGHBORHOOD BY
NEIGHBORHOOD.
SO FAR THE DAMAGE IS LIMITED TO
A LOT OF TREES ARE DAMAGED.
WIND DAMAGE AND TORNADO DAMAGE
AS WELL.
SO FAR LUCKILY WE DON'T HAVE
ANY REPORTS OF INJURIES IN OUR
CITY WHICH IS WONDERFUL.
OUR METEOROLOGISTS IN THIS
COMMUNITY DID A GREAT JOB OF
WARNING EVERYBODY FOR SEVERAL
DAYS LEADING UP TO THIS EVENT.
EVERYBODY KNEW TODAY WAS A DAY
TO BE WEATHER AWARE AND SO FAR
FOR US PEOPLE IN OUR TOWN HEEDD
THAT WARNING.
>> THIS WILL BE A MULTI-DAY
EVENT.
SO YOU ARE IN CHARGE OF KEEPING
PEOPLE SAFE.
YOUR OFFICE, YOUR DIVISION.
WHAT ARE YOU TELLING THEM ABOUT
THE NEXT 24-36 HOURS?
>> WE ARE TELLING EVERYBODY TO
KEEP THEIR PHONES POWERED
FULLY CHARGED.
HAVE AN EMERGENCY STORM PLAN,
SHELTER, WHERE THEY WILL GO TO
TAKE COVER AND QUICKLY HAVE
THEIR INFORMATION GATHERED.
WE THOUGHT WE MIGHT HAVE A JUMP
BACK STORMBACK IN THE AREA.
KNOW WHERE YOUR FAMILY MEMBERS
ARE AND HAVE A PLAN BEFORE THE
STORM HITS BECAUSE YOU ONLY
HAVE A MATTER OF MINUTES REALLY
TO SPRING INTO ACTION.
>> HAS IT HELPED AT ALL TODAY
THAT THIS HAPPENED DURING THE
DAY TIME HOURS?
>> IT HELPS THAT EVERYONE IS
JUST VERY PREPARED AND IT HAS
BEEN TOP OF MIND.
EVERYBODY KNEW IT WAS COMING
TODAY SO EVERYBODY IS GLUED TO
THE TELEVISION AND THE RADIO.
>> SURE.
AND, OF COURSE, THE REASON I
ASK THAT AND MANY OF OUR
VIEWERS WILL KNOW BECAUSE WE
COVERED THIS THIS WEEK ON
WEDNESDAY AND I'M SURE YOU KNOW
THIS BE JENNIFER WHEN THE
SYSTEM WAS BEING TALKED ABOUT
WE SAW ANOTHER SYSTEM DROP
TWISTERS OVER GRANBURY TEXAS
THAT WAS HIT SO HARD, SIX
PEOPLE DEAD THERE.
AND IT HAPPENED AS THE SUN WAS
SETTING.
I ASK THAT QUESTION ABOUT
DAYLIGHT.
IT IS MORE FRIGHTENING AT NIGHT
TO PUT THE EMERGENCY PLANS INTO
PLACE BECAUSE PEOPLE TEND TO
KIND OF SLACK OFF ON THAT.
IT IS DARK OUTSIDE.
I WAS HOPING THE DAYLIGHT HOURS
MAY HAVE HELPED PEOPLE STAY
SAFE TODAY.
>> IT DOES HELP.
YOU CAN SEE IT COMING AND IN
THE SKY.
OKLAHOMANS ARE USED TO GET OUT
AND WATCH IT IS COMING
SOMETIMES.
YOU COULD SEE HE IT COMING AND
THAT WAS HELPFUL YES.
>> JENNIFER MONROE WITH THE
EDMOND OKLAHOMA OFFICE OF
EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT THERE.
THE PUBLIC INFORMATION
SPECIALIST THERE FOR THE LOW HE
CAL AUTHORITIES THAT WILL
ASSESS THE DAMAGE AS YOU HEARD
HER SAY AND HELP AS MANY PEOPLE
AS THEY CAN, THOSE WHO NEED IT.
STAY SAFE.
THIS IS NOT OVER.
ANOTHER DAY OR SO TO GO OF
THIS.
ONE OF THE WAYS WE HAVE BEEN
KEEPING TRACK OF THIS IS WITH
THE LOCAL COVERAGE FROM THE
AREA.
FOX 25 IN OKLAHOMA CITY KOKH.
MANY OF THE PICTURES WE ARE
GETTING IS VIA THEIR FANTASTIC
STAFF OF JOURNALISTS AND WE ARE
HOPING THEY STAY SAFE.
TUNE IN AND JUST LISTEN RIGHT
NOW.
>> OVER EAST OF LAKE
THUNDERBIRD.
THE TORNADO WARNING CONTINUE
THERE'S AS WELL.
THESE ARE TWO REALLY
SIGNIFICANT STORMS RIGHT NOW.
ONE OVER AND JUST EAST OF LAKE
THUNDERBIRD WITH A TORNADO.
ANOTHER ONE JUST NORTH OF
CHANDLER.
YOU CAN SEAT HOOK THERE CLEARLY
AND THEN THE OTHER IS REALLY
MOVING OUT OF THE AREA IN
NORTHWESTERN CREEK COUNTY.
THE NORTHWEST SIDE OF THE TULSA
AREA.
REALLY TWO BIG STORMS, JEFF,
THAT ARE PRODUCING POSSIBLE
TORNADOES HERE RIGHT HERE IN
AND AROUND CENTRAL OKLAHOMA.
>> THANKS, JOHN.
HEADING BACK DOWN TOWARDS PINK
AND LITTLE AXE THERE FOR YOU IN
NORTHEASTERN MCLEAN COUNTY.
THE DOUGHNUT HOLE THAT YOU SAW
RIGHT THERE.
WE SHOULD BE ON DOPPLER 3
MILLENNIUM QUICKLY PLEASE.
LET'S GO AHEAD AND THE DOUGHNUT
HOLE THAT YOU SEE RIGHT THERE
THIS IS THE ACTUAL RADAR SITE.
YOU HAVE SEEN IT AROUND TOWN OR
BEEN AROUND NORMAN THE BIG
DOPPLER BALL IS RIGHT HERE AND
LOOKING OUT.
WHAT HAPPENS IS WE ARE SCANNING
THE ATMOSPHERE AROUND HERE AND
THAT IS WHY EVERYTHING LOOKS SO
FUNNY AND USUALLY SOMETHING SO
CLOSE TO THE RADAR IT IS HARD
TO DIFFERENTIATE EXACTLY WHAT
IS GOING ON.
WHAT WE WILL DO RIGHT NOW IS
ZOOM DOWN.
ZOOM DOWN RIGHT THERE AND THEN
TAKE A PEEK AT THAT WITH THE
VELOCITY SHOTS BECAUSE THIS
HAPPENS TO BE ACTUALLY SHOWING
THE STRONG ROTATION.
USUALLY IT IS HARD TO COULD
THAT BUT JUST NORTH OF LITTLE
AXE.
AND ALSO HAVING TO TAKE THE
SPOTTERS AND CHASERS OUT THERE
HAVING TO TAKE WHAT THEY ARE
SAYING ALSO TO HEART BECAUSE
THE RADAR MAY BE SAYING ONE
THING AND WHAT IS ON THE GROUND
MAY BE SAYING ANOTHER THING.
ARE IT IS SO IMPORTANT TO HAVE
THE CHASERS ON THE GROUND LIKE
THE VIDEO YOU ARE SEEING RIGHT
THERE.
IMPORTANT TO HAVE THAT OUT
THERE EYE EX-LY WHEN YOU
HAVE -- ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
HAVE SOMETHING SO CLOSE TO THE
RADAR.
TAKE CHASER NET TWO FULL,
PLEASE.
WHERE IS THAT AT, MICHELLE OR
BARRY?
>> THAT IS ON THE CHANDLER
STORM RIGHT THERE.
>> WE ARE LISTENING IN NOW TO
OUR FOX 25 IN OKLAHOMA CITY AND
YOU ARE LISTENING TO THEM TALK
WITH SOME OF THE STORM SPOTTERS
THAT THEY HAVE OUT THERE
GATHERING VIDEO.
WE HAD OUR VERY OWN TASTE OF
THAT WITH EMILY EARLIER.
SHE WAS WITH US ON FOX REPORT
FROM EDMOND, OKLAHOMA, SHARING
PICTURES AND STORIES TONIGHT.
A FANTASTIC WAY TO GET AN EYE
INTO THE STORM AND GENERALLY WE
LEAN ON THEM A LITTLE BIT BUT
HOPING EVERYBODY STAYS SAFE.
MAKE YOU AWARE OF A COUPLE OF
DEVELOPMENTS BEFORE WE TAKE A
QUICK COMMERCIAL BREAK.
WICHITA, KANSAS AND A SUBURB
THERE HAVE BEEN KIT PRETTY
HARD.
WE WILL TALK WITH THE MAYOR OF
WICHITA RIGHT AFTER THIS.
STAY CLOSE.
[ Male Announcer ]    RUNNING OUT
OF STEAM?  ♪ ♪    NOW YOU CAN GIVE
YOURSELF    A KICK IN THE REAR!
V8 V-FUSION PLUS ENERGY.    NATURAL
ENERGY FROM GREEN TEA    PLUS FRUITS
AND VEGGIES.    NEED A LITTLE KICK?
OOH!    COULD'VE HAD A V8.    IN THE
JUICE AISLE.
[ Giada ] WHY DID I SWITCH  TO NATURAL
INSTINCTS?  IT'S HEALTHIER, AMMONIA-FREE.
AND WITH ALOE, VITAMIN E  AND COCONUT
OIL,  MY HAIR LOOKS HEALTHIER  THAN
BEFORE I COLORED.  I SWITCHED.  YOU
SHOULD TOO,  TO NATURAL INSTINCTS.
[ man ]  ON DECEMBER 17, 1903  THE
WRIGHT BROTHERS BECAME  THE FIRST
IN FLIGHT.  [ Goodall ] I THINK  THE
MOST AMAZING THING  IS HOW LIKE US
THESE CHIMPANZEES ARE.  [ LAUGHING
]  [ woman ]  CAN YOU HEAR ME?  AND
YOU HEAR YOUR VOICE?  OH, IT'S EXCITING!
[ man ] TOUCHDOWN CONFIRMED.  WE'RE
SAFE ON MARS.  [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
]  ♪ ♪  HI.  [ BABY FUSSING ]  ♪ ♪
Why are twice as many people  choosing
Verizon  over any other carrier?
Many choose us because we have  the
largest 4GLTE network.
Others, because of our  reputation
for reliability.
Or maybe it's because  we've received
JD Power
and Associates' customer service
award 4X in a row.
In the end  there are countless reasons.
But one choi.
SHE'S STILL  THE ONE FOR YOU -  YOU
KNOW IT EVEN  AFTER ALL THESE YEARS.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE  DYSFUNCTION -
YOU KNOW,THAT COULD BE A  QUESTION
OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL  FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME  THE MOMENT'S
RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT IN  YOUR
ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS THE  ONLY DAILY
ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED  AND SYMPTOMS
OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDINGO GO  FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS  AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU  TAKE NITRATES
FOR CHEST PAIN
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE DROP
IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL  IN EXCESS WITH
CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE  HEADACHE,
UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,  SEEK IMMEDIATE
MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING  MORE THAN
FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE  OR
LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY  ALLERGIC REACTIONS
SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,  SWELLING OF
THE LIPS
TONGUE OR THROAT
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING  OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET  MEDICAL
HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS  FOR
DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
>>> JOINING US KARL BREWER, THE
MAYOR OF WICHITA KANSAS.
AND WHILE HE TALKS WITH US WE
ARE LOOKING AT BRAND NEW YOU
VIDEO IN OF THIS MONSTER
TWISTER SYSTEM THAT IS MOVING
ACROSS THE MID SECTION OF OUR
COUNTRY.
IT IS CONTINUING COVERAGE OF
THE BREAKING NEWS.
OKLAHOMA AND KANSAS HIT VERY
HARD OF FUNNEL
CLOUDS, HARSH HAIL THE SIZE OF
GRAPEFRUITS, HIGH WINDS DAMAGE
TO HOMES AND VEHICLES.
MAYOR BREW ARE ARE YOU WITH
US?
>> YES, I AM.
>> I KNEE WICHITA TOOK A PUNCH
TODAY.
TELL ME HOW THINGS ARE GOING IN
YOUR CITY.
>> AS IT STANDS RIGHT NOW
EVERYONE IS TRYING TO RECOVER.
WE HAD SOME SIGHTINGS.
WE HAD TWO OR THREE SIGHTINGS
OF TORNADOES BUT SO FAR WE ARE
NOT SEEING THAT WE SEE ANYTHING
OF ANY REAL TORNADO DAMAGE.
IT WAS JUST THE HIGH WINDS THE
LARGE SIZED GOLF BALL SIZED
HAIL AND THAT ALONE AND THE
RAIN REALLY DID A NUMBER ON THE
CITY, YOU WOULD THINK THAT A
TORNADO GAME THROUGH.
THE HAIL CAME AT SUCH A
VELOCITY, RIPPED HOLES THROUGH
THE HOUSES AND TORE UP SIDING
AND BROKEN WINDOWS AND THINGS
OF THAT NATURE.
EVEN I HAD BROKEN WINDOWS AND
ALL OF MY VEHICLES THAT WERE
SITTING OUT THEY ALL ENDED UP
BEING DAMAGED AND SO TREES THAT
HAVE FELL ON TOP OF HOMES AND
JUST IT JUST THE LIST GOES ON
AND A ON AND ON.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF YOU HAVE
GOTTEN OUT A CHANCE TO LOOK AT
BEYOND DAMAGE THAT YOU ARE
SUFFERING BUT I'M CURIOUS TO
KNOW WITH US PEOPLE   BECAUSE PEOPLE
WATCH WILLING
SAY WICHITA IS A BIG CITY AND
IT IS FAIRLY RARE FOR POPULATED
AREAS TO GET HIT LIKE THIS.
WE FORECAST THAT WICHITA AND
KANSAS CITY MIGHT BE TOUCHED BY
THIS AND IN FACT THAT HAS
HAPPENED TODAY WITH YOUR CITY.
TALK TO ME ABOUT THE EMERGENCY
MANAGEMENT PREPARATION THAT YOU
TOOK AND WHAT PEOPLE WERE
PLANNING TO DO TODAY.
TODAY.
>> OUR EMERGENCY LEVEL WAS
ELEVATED TO A LEVEL TWO IN
PREPARATION FOR THE STORM TO
COME THROUGH.
AND WE HAVE CONTINUED TO
MAINTAIN THAT.
WE HAVE ALL OF OUR CREWS AND
EVERYONE HAS BEEN DISPATCHED
AND THEY WERE AT THE EMERGENCY
SERVICE CENTER IN PREPARATION.
YOU KNOW, WE DID HAVE SOME
ELECTRICAL LINES BLOWN DOWN
BECAUSE OF THE WIND BUT FOR THE
MOST PART EVERYONE WAS
FOREWARNED.
WE HAD LOTS OF WARNING AND
PREPARATION TO PREPARE
OURSELVES.
A LOT OF ADVANCE NOTICE TO GO
TO YOUR SHELTERS AND YOU COULD
ALMOST TRACK IT FOR MILES AND
MILES JUST BY LISTENING TO OUR
MEDIA.
THEY DID A FANTASTIC JOB THIS
LETTING EVERYBODY KNOW EXACTLY
WHERE EVERYTHING WAS AT AND
WHERE IT WAS APPROACHING THE
COMMUNITYS.
>> WE HE HAVE BEEN DIPPING IN
TO FOX 25 IN OKLAHOMA CITY.
I WANT TO MAKE EVERYBODY AWARE
THEY ARE SEEING A COUPLE OF
DIFF'RENT THINGS ON THE SCREEN.
TO THE RIGHT IS THE SYSTEM ON
THE MAP.
ING TOLING BETWEEN OKLAHOMA
CITY VIDEO AND NOW LOOKING TEN
MILES OUTSIDE WICHITA KANSAS.
I DON'T KNOW IF YOU CAN SEE
THIS MAYOR BREWER.
THIS IS A MONSTER SYSTEM THAT
HAS TOUCHED DOWN A FEW MILES
WEST OF WICHITA.
ARE YOU HEARING ANY REPORTS OF
ANYTHING DAMAGED IN THAT AREA?
>> NO, I HAVE NOT HEARD OF ANY
REPORTS OF ANYTHING DAMAGED IN
THAT AREA AND MY FIRE CHIEF AND
POLICE CHIEF AND THE PEOPLE
THAT WE HAVE IN OUR EMERGENCY
CENTER HAVE NOT REPORTED
ANYTHING.
CURRENTLY I'M OUTSIDE KIND OF
LOOKING AT THE DAMAGES.
>> I CAN HEAR THE WIND!
I CAN HEAR IT.
>> LOOKING AT THE DAMAGE IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD AND THE NEIGHBORS
ARE WALKING BACK AND FORTH DOWN
THE STREET TRYING TO SEE HOW
MUCH DAMAGE WAS DONE TO VARIOUS
DIFFERENT HOMES.
IT IS JUST WE ARE NOT HEARING
THAT THERE HAS BEEN ANY DAMAGE
WITH THE EXCEPTION OF WE HAD
SOME STRUCTURE TREES THAT FELL
ON HOMES AND POWER LINES THAT
ARE DOWN.
I THINK I HEARD OVER THE
SCANNER THAT ONE POWER LINE HAD
FELL ON TOP OF A CAR WITH A
FAMILY INSIDE OF IT BUT THE
FAMILY IS SAFE.
>> MAYOR BREWER, WE ARE ABOUT
TO RUN INTO A COMMERCIAL BREAK.
STAY TIGHT.
WE'LL BE HE RIGHT BACK.
THANK YOU.
[ Male Announcer ]    THIS IS BETSY.
HER LONG DAY OF PICK UPS    AND DROP
OFFS    BEGINS WITH ARTHRITIS PAIN...
AND A CHOICE.    TAKE UP TO 6 TYLENOL
IN A DAY    OR JUST 2 Aleve    FOR
ALL DAY RELIEF.    ALL ABOARD.  ♪
♪
MINE WAS EARNED        IN DJIBOUTI
AFRICA. 2004.  VIETNAM IN 1972.
[ All ]            FORT BENNING, GEORGIA
IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]      USAA AUTO
INSURANCE     IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN
FROM GENERATION TO GENERATION.
BECAUSE IT OFFERS           A SUPERIOR
LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE MILITARY MEMBERS,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY,         GET AN
AUTO INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA. WE KNOW         WHAT IT MEANS
TO SERVE.
WITH MY FRIENDS,  WE'LL DO ALMOST
ANYTHING.  OUT FOR DRINKS, EATS.
I HAVE  VERY WELL FITTING DENTURES.
I LIKE TO EAT A LOT OF FRUITS.  LOVE
THEM ALL.
THE SEAL I GET  WITH THE SUPER POLIGRIP
FREE
KEEPS THE SEEDS  FROM GETTING UP UNDERNEATH.
EVEN WELL-FITTING DENTURES  LET IN
FOOD PARTICLES.
SUPER POLIGRIP IS ZINC FREE.
WITH JUST A FEW DABS
IT'S CLINICALLY PROVEN  TO SEAL OUT
MORE FOOD PARTICLES
SO YOU'RE MORE COMFORTABLE  AND CONFIDENT
WHILE YOU EAT.
A LOT OF THINGS  GOING ON IN MY LIFE
AND THE LAST THING  I WANT TO BE THINKING
ABOUT
IS MY DENTURES.
[ Charlie ]  TRY ZINC FREE SUPER POLIGRIP.
>>> FOX URGENT CONTINUING LIVE
COVERAGE OF WHAT YOU SEE IN THE
THE MIDDLE OF YOUR SCREEN THERE
IN OKLAHOMA TONIGHT.
IT HAS JUST BEEN A VICIOUS
THUNDERSTORM SYSTEM MOVING
ACROSS THERE DROPPING TWISTERS
FROM THE SKY AND THIS IS LIVE
SO EVERY NOW AND THEN YOU MAY
SEE THE SATELLITE PHOTO DROP
OUT AS WE TRY TO CAPTURE THIS.
BUT ALSO EVERY NOW AND THEN AS
I PUT MY EYES TO THE IS CENTER
OF THE SCREEN NOW YOU WILL SEE
A FUNNEL CLOUD COME OUT OF THE
SKY.
WE HAVE SEEN THAT MORE THAN A
FEW TIMES THIS AFTERNOON AND
NOW MOVING INTO THE EVENING
HOURS.
THAT IS A WALL CLOUD OKLAHOMA
IS VERY ACTIVE.
THERE IS RED ALL OVER THE MAP
AND THAT MEAN THERE'S IS
DANGER.
METEOROLOGIST JANICE DEAN IS IN
THE FOX EXTREME WEATHER CENTER
WHERE IT IS EXTREME RIGHT NOW
JANICE.
>> OKLAHOMA IS THE AREA I WANT
TO FOCUS IN WITH THE VISUALS OF
THE FUNNEL CLOUDS DROPPING FROM
THE SKY.
TORNADO WARNINGS SEVERAL IN AND
AROUND OKLAHOMA CITY.
TORNADO WATCHES EXTENDING UP
TOWARDS THE MIDWEST.
SO TORNADOES ARE CONDUCIVE HERE
ACROSS THE CENTRAL U.S. UP
TOWARDS THE MIDWEST.
THROUGHOUT THE EVENING AND INTO
THE OVERNIGHT HOURS.
HERE IS OKLAHOMA.
THERE IS OKLAHOMA CITY SOUTH
AND EAST OF THE AREA.
WE HAVE A CONFIRMED TORNADO ON
THE GROUND SPOTTED BY FOLKS ON
THE GROUND AND TRAINED WEATHER
SPOTTERS AND WE ARE SEEING
DEBRIS IN THE AREA.
SOUTH AND EAST OF OKLAHOMA CITY
THIS IS MOVING TOWARDS PINK,
OKLAHOMA.
THEN NORTH AND EAST OF OKLAHOMA
A CITY NORTH OF CHANDLER
ANOTHER SUPERCELL DEVELOPING
AND WITH THAT PERHAPS THE
POTENTIAL FOR ARE A TORNADO AND
THEN NORTH AND EAST OF THAT
SOUTH OF CLEVELAND WEST OF
TULSA, ANOTHER TORNADO WARNED
STORM.
OKLAHOMA REALLY RIGHT NOW FOR
TORNADO ACTIVITY THIS AREA NO
STRANGE TO TORNADOES BUT THEY
KNOW WHAT TO DO WHEN THE SIREN
COMBOSS   GO UP.
TOWARDS THE NORTH AND EAST IN
IOWA A TORNADO WARNING.
NOT ONLY CONFINED TO OKLAHOMA
AND KANSAS BUT STEP UP TOWARDS
THE UPPER MIDWEST THROUGH THE
EVENING HOURS.
RIGHT NOW LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE A
TORNADO OUTBREAK UNDERWAY IN
AND AROUND THE OKLAHOMA CITY
AREA.
WORD IS THERE IS DEBRIS, THERE
IS DAMAGE ON THE GROUND.
UNFORTUNATELY, AS THIS STORM
MOVES EASTWARD AND ONE OF THE
INGREDIENTS THAT WE NEED IT THE
VERY WARM UNSTABLE AIR MASS.
LOOKING AT OKLAHOMA, 77.
BUT SOUTH OF THAT WE ARE IN THE
90s.
EAST OF THAT WE ARE INTO THE
80s AND BEHIND THAT WE HAVE
THE COLDER DRYER AIR.
HARRIS IT IS THE PERFECT
TEXTBOOK SETUP FOR TORNADOES.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THIS AREA OF
THE COUNTRY THEY ARE USED TO IT
AND HOPEFULLY THEY ARE HEEDING
THE WARNINGS AS WE BRING THEM
TO THEM.
BACK TO YOU.
>> I WANT TO ASK WHY IS IT JUST
IN THE LAST LITTLE WHILE THIS
HAS GOTTEN WORSE.
EARLIER TODAY IT WAS COOKING
AND THEN IN JUST THE LAST 15-20
MINUTES WE ARE SEEING
TOUCHDOWNS.
I'M WATCHING THE ASSOCIATED
PRESS WIRES AND LOOKING WE HAVE
ON A BIG SCREEN FOX 25 IN
OKLAHOMA CITY.
I AM KEEPING MY EYES ON THAT
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN THIS IS
POPPING.
WE ARE ARE PUTING THAT UP NOW.
WHY IS THAT, JANICE?
>> IT IS THE DAY TIME HEATING.
THE DYERNAL HEATING.
EARLIER ON TODAY THE
THUNDERSTORMS CLEARED AND THEN
THE SUN COMES OUT AND HEATS UP
THE ATMOSPHERE AGAIN.
THEN WE HAVE ALL OF THAT
MOISTURE I MEAN THE DEW POINTS
IN THE AREA, THE MOISTURE
CONTENT IN OKLAHOMA AND TEXAS
IS OPPRESSIVE.
SO YOU HAVE GOT THE VERY WARM
HUMID AIR MASS AND WARM
MOISTURE COMING IN FROM THE
GULF OF MEXICO.
THE DAY TIME HEATING SETTING IN
AND THEN THESE STORMS START TO
FIRE WITH THAT FRONT AS IT
APPROACHES WITH THE COOLER
DRYER AIR BEHIND IT.
>> ALL RIGHT.
JANICE STAY WITH ME FOR JUST A
SECOND.
RIGHT NOW, FOX 25 IS TALKING TO
THE GUY DRIVING THIS CAR THE
STORM SPOTTER.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> THERE IS A TORNADO AND SHAWN
IS COMING ON I-40 UP IN HERE.
HE IS IN THE RAIN AND HAIL UP
HERE NOT TOO FAR FROM GAIL
OKAY.
IF YOU ARE STILL ON, LISTEN TO
US.
THE TORNADO IS ACTUALLY TO THE
SOUTHWEST.
I DIDN'T KNOW YOU WERE ON I-40.
I THOUGHT YOU WERE ON ANOTHER
ROAD COMING INTO SHAWNEE.
WE ARE GETTING THE DEBRIS
SIGNATURE ON RADAR.
THE RADAR IS PICKING UP DEBRIS
FLYING AROUND THE RADAR.
WE ARE PICKING THAT UP ON THE
RADAR AND SHOWS UP AS BIG HOLES
AND STUFF LIKE THAT BECAUSE YOU
HAVE TREE HES OR DEBRIS FLYING
AROUND.
BE CAREFUL THERE, SHAWN BECAUSE
YOU HAVE A SERIOUS SITUATION
WHEN YOU TRY TO DRIVE SOUTH THE
TORNADO IS GOING TO COME RIGHT
UP ON YOU THERE.
IT IS JUST WEST OF BETHEL ACRES
AND IT IS JUST A COUPLE OF
MILES SOUTH OF THE INTERSTATE.
>> APPRECIATE IT.
I'LL SEE IF I CAN GET YOU
ANOTHER VIEW OF IT.
>> MIGHT WANT TO HEAD BACK
TOWARDS SHAWNEE AND HEAD SOUTH.
>> DID YOU HEAR WHAT HE JUST
SAID JANICE?
HE TOLD THAT GUY DRIVING THIS
CAR.
SAID YOU GOT TO BE CAREFUL THAT
DEBRIS IS GOING TO COME IN YOUR
DIRECTION.
WHICH WAY ARE YOU DRIVING YOU
GOT TO GO THE OTHER WAY.
WE HAVE VIDEO FROM EARLIER
WHERE THE DEBRIS FIELD WAS
SPINNING AROUND AND POPPED UP
ON THE SCREEN.
A LOT O THE GROUND OF STUFF CAN
HIT THE SKY.
>> IT IS INCREDIBLE VIDEO.
YOU CAN SEE THE ROTATION SO
CLEARLY ON THE SCREEN AND THE
DEBRIS FIELD COMING UP.
AND THE SKY IS SO CLOSE.
I MEAN HARRIS, OBVIOUSLY WE ARE
THIS THIS WORLD OF CELL PHONES
AND WANNABE STORM CHASERS AND
THIS IS WHAT REALLY SCARES ME
IS THIS IS WHERE WE WILL SEE
THE DEATHS UNFORTUNATELY.
EVEN THOUGH WE NEED THE VIDEO
TO SHOW YOU HOW DANGEROUS IT IS
IT IS UNFOR THE THAT THE THAT
WE HAVE ALL A THESE PEOPLE OUT
THERE IN DANGER ZONES.
>> THIS GUY IS A TRAINED STORM
SPOTTER IS WHAT I'M HEAR FT.
WORTH AFFILIATE THERE.
EVEN SO YOU CAN HEAR THE
METEOROLOGIST TELLING HIM
DUDE, STUFF COULD HIT YOU.
YOU COT TO FACE IN THE OTHER
DIRECTION.
THEN LOOK AT THIS.
DID YOU SEE BLUE SKY THERE'S ON
THE BACK END OF THIS.
GO BACK TO THAT LIVE LOOK IF
YOU CAN BECAUSE WE A LOT OF
CAMERAS ON THIS RIGHT NOW.
SO MUCH STUFF COMING IN TO FOX
NEWS AND PUT AS MUCH ON THE
SCREEN FOR YOU AS POSSIBLE.
IF WE TAKE A LOOK AT THIS IN
OKLAHOMA CITY, AS IT FACES OUT
IN THE OTHER DIRECTION THE BLUE
SKIES ALTHOUGH THEY STILL LOOK
RATHER I DON'T KNOW PROBLEMATIC
POTENTIALLY BUT AT LEAST IT IS
NOT AS ACTIVE AS WHAT WE JUST
SAW.
>> WELL OKLAHOMA RIGHT NOW
SOUTH AND EAST OF OKLAHOMA CITY
IS WHERE WE ARE SORT OF
CONCERNED WITH THE WORST OF THE
TORNADOIC CELLS.
THE SYSTEM IS SLOWLY MOVING
EASTWARD.
SO AS WE GET INTO THE OVERNIGHT
HOURS, OKLAHOMA CITY YOU ARE
GOING TO BE THIS THE CLEAR.
THEN HARRIS TOMORROW THE STORM
CLOUDS CLEAR HEATS UP AGAIN
AND THE THREAT FOR SEVERE
WEATHER YET AGAIN.
THESE FOLKS REALLY NOT OUT OF
THE WOODS FOR THE NEXT 2-24    12-24
HOURS.
>> WE ARE COVERING COVERING THIS
BREAKING NEWS HAPPENING IN THE
MID SECTION OF THE COUNTRY.
THIS AFFECTS MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
TONIGHT.
WE HAVE HEARD REPORTS OF
DAMAGE.
WICHITA GETTING HIT WHICH IS A
MAJOR POPULATED AREA BUT NO
INJURIES REPORTED AS WE ALREADY
TALKED WITH THE MAYOR OF
WICHITA.
WE ARE MOVING FORWARD WITH THE
STORY TALKING WITH STORM
CHASERS AND BRINGING YOU AS
MUCH VIDEO COMING IN TO FOX
NEWS.
I WILL HAVE UREPORT INFORMATION
TO SEND YOUR PICTURES DIRECTLY
TO US.
AND OTHER DEVELOPING TORE    STORIES
WE
WANT TO TELL YOU ABOUT ASIDE
FROM THE WEATHER.
THIS RIGHT NOW IS FOX URGENT
AND WE ARE BRINGING IT TO YOU
LIVE.
STAY CLOSE.
FROM STOUFFER'S    STARTS WITH GROUND
BEEF    ONIONS AND PEPPERS    BAKED
IN A KETCHUP GLAZE    WITH SAVORY
GRAVY    AND MASHED RUSSET POTATOES.
WHAT MAKES STOUFFER'S MEATLOAF
BEST OF ALL?    THAT MOMENT YOU ENJOY
IT    AT HOME.    STOUFFER'S.    MADE
WITH CARE,    FOR YOU OR YOUR FAMILY.
♪ ♪  [ lighter flicking ]    [ Male
Announcer ]    YOU'VE REACHED THE
AGE    WHERE GIVING UP    ISN'T WHO
YOU ARE.  ♪ ♪    THIS IS THE AGE
OF KNOWING HOW    TO MAKE THINGS HAPPEN.
SO, WHY LET ERECTILE    DYSFUNCTION
GET IN YOUR WAY?    TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT VIAGRA.    20 MILLION MEN ALREADY
HAVE.    ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF YOUR HEART
IS HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.    DO NOT
TAKE VIAGRA IF YOU TAKE    NITRATES
FOR CHEST PAIN;    IT MAY CAUSE AN
UNSAFE DROP    IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE    HEADACHE,
FLUSHING    UPSET STOMACH,    AND
ABNORMAL VISION.    TO AVOID LONG-TERM
INJURY,    SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL
HELP    FOR AN ERECTION    LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.    STOP TAKING
VIAGRA    AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT
AWAY    IF YOU EXPERIENCE    A SUDDEN
DECREASE OR LOSS    IN VISION OR HEARING.
THIS IS THE AGE    OF TAKING ACTION.
VIAGRA.    TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR.
[ HUMAN LEAGUE PLAYS  "I'M ONLY HUMAN"
]
HUMANS.
EVEN WHEN WE CROSS OUR t's    AND
DOT OUR i's,
WE STILL RUN INTO PROBLEMS.
NAMELY, OTHER HUMANS.
WHICH IS WHY    AT LIBERTY MUTUAL
INSURANCE,
TO POLICIES COME    WITH NEW CAR REPLACEMENT
AND ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS    IF YOU
QUALIFY.
SEE WHAT EE COMES STANDARD
AT LIBERTYMUTUAL.COM.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT'S YOUR POLICY?
ALL STATIONS COME OVER TO  MISSION
A FOR A FINAL GO.  THIS IS FOR REAL
THIS TIME.
STEP SEVEN POINT  TWO ONE TWO.
RIFY AND LOCK.
COMMAND IS LOCKED.
FIVE SECONDS.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
STANDING BY FOR CAPTURE.
THE MOST INNOVATIVE  SOFTWARE ON THE
PLANET...
DRAGON IS CAPTURED.
IS CONNECTING TODAY'S LEADING  COMPANIES
TO PLACES BEYOND IT.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
AS WE STAY ON THE STORY FOR YOU
RIGHT NOW.
TORNADOES TOUCHING DOWN IN
KANSAS AND OKLAHOMA AND THE
SYSTEM NOW COOKING UP.
YOU SEE ON THE BACK EDGE OF IT
THERE IN OKLAHOMA CITY A LITTLE
PEEK OF DAYLIGHT AND PEOPLE
THERE ARE TOLD T
HEED THE WARNINGS WITH BECAUSE WE
HAVE SEEN BREAKS LIKE THIS IN
THE SKIES AND THEN SUDDENLY A
WALL CLOUD AND SUDDENLY A LARGE
FUNNEL.
AND I MEAN LARGE.
WE ARE SENDING CORRESPONDENTS
INTO THE HEART OF THIS.
WE ARE TALKING WITH STORM
CHASERS PEOPLE WHO DO THIS FOR
A LIVING.
CASEY STEGALL IS ON INTERSTATE
35 IN OKLAHOMA GOING NORTH.
CASEY, YOU ARE WITH US.
TELL US ABOUT IT.
>> HARRIS WE ARE ON THE PHONE
OBVIOUSLY HEADING UP I-35.
THAT IS THE MAIN SORT OF
INTERSTATE THAT BLENDS THROUGH
OKLAHOMA EVEN RUNS UP NORTH
THROUGH KANSAS AND WE ARE ABOUT
50 MILES OR SO SOUTH OF NORMAN,
OKLAHOMA THAT IS UNDER THE GUN
THE LAST 30 MINUTES OR SO AND
JUST AS YOU HAVE BEEN SAYING
WITH JANUARY MISS DEAN THERE JANICE
DEAN I HAVE BEEN
MONITORING WHAT YOU GUYS ARE
SAYING.
A DANGEROUS FLUID SITUATION
THROUGHOUT MUCH OF THE STATE OF
OKLAHOMA.
OKLAHOMA CITY AND THEN SOUTH OF
OKLAHOMA CITY, THE VERY FIRST
REPORT [BREAK IN AUDIO] AND
THAT IS ABOUT 17 MILES NORTH OF
OKLAHOMA CITY, DEBRIS BUT NO
INJURIES WE ARE TOLD.
THEN THE STORM SORT OF TRACKED
TO THE EAST OF OKLAHOMA.
>> CASEY CASEY CAN YOU HEAR
ME.
IN YOUR LINE IS BREAKING UP A
LITTLE BIT.
I WANT TO CLEAR THIS UP BECAUSE
I THINK PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED
ABOUT YOU.
I'M WATCHING AND PEOPLE ARE
TWEETING ABOUT YOU RIGHT NOW
THEY WANT TO KNOW EXACTLY WHERE
YOU ARE AND I WANT TO GIVE THE
LINE A CHANCE TO CLEAR UP
BECAUSE YOU ARE IN A MOVING
VEHICLE AND SOMETIMES AS YOU
ARE MOVING ACROSS YOU WILL FIND
A STRONGER TOWER TO HOOK UP TO
SO I WANT TO GIVE IT A FEW
SECONDS TO DO THAT.
GOING NORTH ARE ON INTERSTATE
35 THE MAIN CORRIDOR FROM SOUTH
SOUTH
TO NORTH THROUGH THE MIDWESTERN
PORTION OF THE COUNTRY HE UP
THROUGH OKLAHOMA.
TELL ME WHERE YOU ARE AND WHAT
YOU ARE SEEING?
>> WE ARE ABOUT 55 MILES OR SO
SOUTH OF NORMAN, OKLAHOMA.
AN AREA THAT IS STILL UNDER A
TORNADO WATCH RIGHT NOW.
CONFIRMED REPORTS OF TORNADOES
ON THE GROUND IN THE NORMAN,
OKLAHOMA AREA.
WHICH, BY THE WAY TO A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT KNOW THIS, NORMAN
IS HOME TO THE UNIVERSITY OF
OKLAHOMA A UNIVERSITY OF MORE
THAN 30,000 STUDENTS AND THE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE IN
FACT EVEN HAS AN OFFICE IN
NORMAN.
I SPOKE TO A REPRESENTATIVE
THERE NOT VERY LONG AGO AND
THEY HE SAID THAT THEY WERE
STARTING TO SEE SOME CLIMATIC
ACTIVITY LITERALLY OUT OF THE
BACK OF THEIR OFFICE DOOR.
THAT IS PART OF THAT CELL AS I
MENTIONED THAT IS ACTUALLY
SOUTHEAST OF OKLAHOMA CITY
BECAUSE WE HAVE GOT THESE TWO
MAJOR CELLS IF YOU LOOK AT THE
RADAR THAT ARE SPAWNING THE
TORNADOES.
NORTHEAST OF OKLAHOMA CITY AND
THEN SOUTHEAST OF OKLAHOMA
CITY.
AND RIGHT NOW ALL EYES ARE ON
THE AREA AS JANICE DEAN WAS
SAYING PINK, OKLAHOMA, THAT IS
SOUTHEAST OF NORMAN.
SO WE HAVE THESE TWO GUIDANCE
TICK CELLS.
IN FACT SOME OF THE EARLY
REPORTS FROM THE WEATHER
SPOTTERS ON THE GROUND IS THAT
IN THE STATE OF OKLAHOMA ALONE
14 DIFFERENT TORNADOES HAVE
BEEN GENERATED IN THE LAST FOUR
HOURS OR SO.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
FORECASTERS HAD TALKED ABOUT
FOR SEVERAL DAYS.
I CAN TELL YOU WE WERE DOWN IN
NORTH TEXAS ON THE GROUND LAST
WEEK RIGHT AFTER THOSE STORMS
BLEW THROUGH AND DECIMATED SOME
PART TION OF TEXAS.
EVER SINCE THE SYSTEM MOVE
THROUGH IT HAS BEEN AN EERY
HUMID UNNATURAL FEELING THE
LAST FEW DAYS.
IT IS NOT NORMALLY HUMID IN
NORTH TEXAS AND THE SOUTHERN
PART OF OKLAHOMA.
THE AIR JUST KIND OF FELT
WEIRD.
IT WAS MUGGY AND STIFLING.
THAT WAS OF GREAT CONCERN TO A
LOT OF THE FORECASTERS AND
METEOROLOGISTS BECAUSE AS
JANICE DEAN WAS SAYING EARLIER
THIS HAS REALLY SORT OF BEEN
TEXTBOOK EXAMPLE OF WEATHER
THAT SETS UP FOR THE SUPERCELLS
AND CELLS THAT PRODUCE THE
TORNADOES.
AT THIS POINT WE ARE SAFE.
I MEAN WE ARE ABOUT 55 MILES AS
I SAID SOUTH OF NORMAN AND IT
IS SUNNY.
THAT IS THE WEIRD THING ABOUT
THIS AS YOU WERE TALKING ABOUT
THE VIDEO HE OF THE BLUE SKY
THERE OUT TO THE DISTANCE IN
OKLAHOMA CITY.
SHE ARE ARE SO SPORADIC AND SO
ISOLATED WITH TORNADOES.
SO DIFFERENT THAN A HURRICANE.
THE HURRICANE IS WIDESPREAD FOR
MILES AND MILES AND MILES AND
MILES YOU ARE HAVING THE STRONG
WINDS AND THE POURINGTHE
DOWNPOURS IN THE RAIN.
WITH THE TORNADOES IT CAN BE
SUNNY IN ONE AREA AND TEN MILES
TO THE EAST OF YOU TORNADOES ON
THE GROUND DOING LOTS AND LOTS
OF DAMAGE.
THAT IS WHAT IS REALLY ALARMING
WITH THESE.
EVEN THOUGH FORECASTERS WERE
PREDICTING THIS, THESE DROP
DOWN OUT OF THE SKY.
THEY ARE ON THE GROUND FOR A
FEW MINUTES.
DO A TON OF DAMAGE AND THEN
ASCEND BACK UP INTO THE CLOUDS
AND THAT IS WHAT WE ARE SEEING
THROUGHOUT THE PORTIONS OF
OKLAHOMA THAT HAVE BEEN UNDER
THE GUN THE LAST FOUR HOURS OR
SO HARRIS.
>> WHILE YOU WERE TALKING
VIEWERS SAW A VERY LARGE
TORNADO TOUCHING DOWN AND I
WANT TO MAKE IT CLEAR WHAT WE
ARE LOOKING AT HERE IS BRAND
NEW VIDEO.
RE-RACK THAT, PLEASE.
CASEY, THIS IS A MONSTER ON THE
GROUND AND JUST COMING IN TO
FOX NEWS NOW.
TORNADOES HITTING IN OKLAHOMA.
WE KNEW THAT.
WE KNEW THAT THEY HAD HIT
OUTSIDE OKLAHOMA CITY.
AND NOW WE ARE LEARNING MORE
ABOUT THIS.
TORNADOHUNTER .COM I UNDERSTAND
HAS SENT THIS TO US.
IT IS VIDEO NOW OUTSIDE OF
OKLAHOMA CITY.
AND IFKY GET SOME DIRECTION
FROM THE PRODUCERS IN THE BOOTH
PLEASE TO TELL ME EXACTLY WHERE
THIS IS.
BECAUSE YOU CAN SEE HOW LONG
THIS SITS ON THE GROUND AND
THEN JUST -- THIS IS WHAT CASEY
WAS TALKING ABOUT THERE.
SOMEBODY WAS JUST TALKING WITH
ME SO I PUSSED FOR PAUSED FOR A SECOND
THERE.
ABOUT HOW THEY WILL SIT AND
LOOK HUGE AND GO RIGHT BACK UP
IN THE SKY AND IT IS REALLY
DIFFICULT TO SEE THEM COMING
SOMETIMES BECAUSE MANY OF THEM
HAVE BEEN RAIN-SOAKED.
FOX 25 OKLAHOMA CITY.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> RIGHT ALONG RIGHT ON THE
HIGHWAY RIGHT THERE.
I-40 AND THEN AFTER THAT MOVE
TO THE EAST AND PULL UP CITIES
THERE FOR YOU.
AS IT STAYS LOOKS LIKE WELL
NORTH OF MACK MCARTHUR BOULEVARD
THAT IS.
MOVING OUT RIGHT NOW.
WE KNOW EXACTLY WHERE THAT
TORNADO IS AT.
WE KNOW IT IS ON THE GROUND AND
WE WILL STAY WITH IT OBVIOUSLY
AND WE HAVE TWO CHASERS ON THAT
RIGHT NOW AND TRYING TO GET
PHONERS AND VERIFY WHAT THEY
ARE SEEING.
BUT WE KNOW FOR A FACT THAT IT
IS ON THE GROUND RIGHT NOW.
THAT WAS LIVE VIDEO HE THAT YOU
SAW THERE.
WHILE MICHELLE IS DOING THAT
YOU CAN SEE ON THE CHASE NET
TWO RIGHT THERE ON THE
RIGHT-HAND SIDE OF THE SCREEN
THE TORNADO IS RIGHT BEHIND THE
BILL BILLION BOARD RIGHT BEHIND
THE SIGN RIGHT THERE.
AND THAT IS, ONCE AGAIN, I WANT
TO POINT OUT EXACTLY WHERE IT
IS AT ON THE RADAR.
MICHELLE AFTER YOU GET THE
TRACK UP THERE LET ME KNOW.
OKAY.
13 MINUTES IN ADELOT.
20 MINUTES JOHNSON.
HELLO.
DID YOU HEAR THE NAME OF THAT
IS CITY, JOHN?
>> I HAVE NOT.
>> YOU CAN SEE IT RIGHT THERE.
NOT EVEN GOING TO TRY TO
PRONOUNCE THAT.
MICHELLE PUT SOME STREETS ON
THERE AGAIN FOR US, PLEASE.
THERE YOU GO.
THANK YOU.
AND THEN THERE IS I-40 AND THEN
AGAIN SPLIT SCREENING ACTUALLY
NOW WE ARE ON FULL SCREEN HERE
AND THERE IS THE HIGHWAY SIGN
WILL AND EMERGENCY VEHICLES
THERE.
CHASERS ALL LINED UP AND
TRACKING THIS TORNADO RIGHT
ABOUT HERE.
AGAIN, JUST EAST AND NORTHEAST
OF DALE.
ALREADY SEE SOME GUSTY WINDS
EVEN AS FAR AWAY FROM THAT
TORNADO.
STILL SOME GUSTY WINDS MORE
THAN LIKELY.
>> WHAT YOU ARE WATCHING RIGHT
NOW IS AMAZING COVERAGE BY OUR
FOX 25 THERE KOKH IN OKLAHOMA
CITY.
YOU SEE THEM GATHERING THE
VEHICLES AND THEIR INSTRUMENTS
AS TOUCHDOWNS ARE HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW IN THAT AREAIA.
TWISTERS ON THE GROUND AND
THEIR REACTION AS THE HUGE
BOLTS OF LIGHTNING STRIKE FROM
THAT CLOUD COVER.
ON DOWN TO WHATEVER THE HECK
THEY ARE HITTING ON THE GROUND.
DANGEROUS SITUATION WE ARE
WATCHING AND WE ARE JUST
STARTING HERE.
STAY CLOSE.
TO YOUR TABLE    OUR SEAFOOD DINNER
FOR TWO    FOR JUST 25 DOLLARS!
FIRST GET SALAD    AND CHEDDAR BAY
BISCUITS.    THEN CHOOSE FROM A VARIETY
OF SEAFOOD ENTRéES.    PLUS CHOOSE
EITHER AN APPEZER    OR A DESSERT
TO SHARE.    OFFER ENDS SOON AT RED
LOBSTER!    WHERE WE SEA FOOD DIFFERENTLY.
I'M PHYLLIS  AND I HAVE DIABETIC NERVE
PAIN.  WHEN I FIRST FELT  THE DIABETIC
NERVE PAIN,  OF COURSE  I HAD NO IDEA
WHAT IT WAS.  I FELT LIKE  MY FEET
WERE GOING TO SLEEP.  IT PROGRESSED
FROM THERE  TO BURNING  LIKE I WAS
WALKING  ON HOT COALS...  TO LIKE
1,000 BEES  THAT WERE JUST STINGING
MY FEET.  I HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DOCTOR...  HE FOUND LYRICA
FOR ME.    [ Female Announcer ] IT'S
KNOWN    THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED    TO TREAT
DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.    LYRICA IS
NOT FOR EVERYONE.    IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIO    OR SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS    OR ACTIONS.    TELL YOUR
DOCTOR T AWAY    IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRON    OR UNUSUAL
CHAES    IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.    OR
SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,    RASH,
HIVES, BLISTERS,    CHANGES IN EYESIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,    MUSCLE
PAIN WITH FEVER    TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.    COMMON
SIDE EFFES ARE    DIZZINESS, SLEESS,
WEIGHT GAIN AND SWELLING    OF HANDS,
LEGS AND FEET.    DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKI LYRICA.    DON'T DRIVE
OR USE MACHINERY    UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.    THOSE WHO
HAVE HAD A DRUG    OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY    TO MISUSE LYRICA.
HAVING LESS PAIN --  IT'S A WONDERFUL
FEELING.    [ Female Announcer ] ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT    FOR DIABETIC
NERVE PAIN.    TO HEAR MORE OF PHYLLIS'S
STORY, VISIT LYRICA.COM.
There's a reason no one says  "Easy
like Monday morning."  Sundays are
the warrior's day  to unplug and recharge.
What if this feeling could  last all
week?  With CenturyLink as your  trusted
partner, it can.  Our visionary cloud
infrastructure  and global broadband
network  free you to focus  on what
matters.  With custom communications
solutions and dedicated support,
your business can shine  all week
long.
♪ ♪  ♪ WONDER IF I GAVE AN OREO ♪
♪ TO SOMEBODY OUT THERE  WHO I DIDN'T
KNOW ♪  ♪ WOULD THEY LAUGH  AFTER
I'D GONE? ♪  ♪ OR WOULD THEY PASS
THAT WONDER ON? ♪  ♪ I WONDER HOW
IT'D CHANGE  YOUR POINT OF VIEW ♪
♪ IF I GAVE ONE TO YOU? ♪  ♪ ♪
♪   (Annoucer) New Beneful Medley's,
in Tuscan, Romana,
and Mediterranean style  varieties.
♪
Just mix it in, and take play to
new places.
Three cans in every pack.
New Beneful Medley's.
WELCOME TO THE NEW BUFFALO...  WHERE
NEW YORK STATE IS  INVESTING ONE BILLION
DOLLARS TO ATTRACT  AND GROW BUSINESS.
WHERE COMPANIES LIKE  GEICO ARE INVESTING
IN TECHNOLOGY & FINANCE.
WELCOME TO THE STATE WHERE  CUTTING
TAXES FOR BUSINESS...
IS OUR BUSINESS.
WELCOME TO THE NEW BUFFALO.
NEW YORK STATE IS THROWING  OUT THE
OLD RULE BOOK
TO GIVE YOUR  BUSINESS A NEW EDGE,
THE EDGE YOU CAN ONLY  GET IN NEW
YORK STATE.
TO GROW OUR START YOUR  BUSINESS,
VISIT THENEWNY.COM
FOX URGENT.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
WE ARE WATCHING A DANGEROUS
SITUATION UNFOLD AND IT HAS
BEEN SINCE NOON TODAY.
IT HAS BEEN BETTER OF SIX HOURS
OR MORE WHERE THEY HAVE GONE
FROM WATCHES TO WARNINGS.
FROM OKLAHOMA TO KANSAS.
AND IN JUST THE LAST HOUR OR SO
WE HAVE SEEN MOST OF THOSE GET
INTO THE WARNING CATEGORY WHICH
MEANS IT IS HIGHLY POSSIBLE FOR
TWISTERS TO DROP OUT OF THE
SKY.
PROBABLE FOR THEM TO DO SOME
DAMAGE WHEN THEY DO AND IN FACT
SOME OF THE AREAS ARE NOW IN
TORNADO WARNING BEYOND JUST THE
THUNDERSTORM WARNING MEANING
THERE HAVE BEEN TOUCHDOWNS ON
THE GROUND.
SO FAR TODAY JUST OUR COVERAGE
ALONE WE COUNTED IS SEVERAL OF
THEM.
AND NOW WE ARE STARTING TO SEE
THE VIDEO COME IN FROM
STRINGERS.
I'M TOLD SOME OF THE LIGHTS YOU
WILL SEE THAT ARE HITTING
TRANSFORMERS GOING OUT AS THE
SYSTEMS MOVE THROUGH WITH ALL
THEIR POWER.
THIS IS EDMOND, OKLAHOMA WHERE
WE KNOW THERE WAS A LARGE
TOUCHDOWN.
WE TALKED WITH A STORM SPOTTER
THIS.
I GOOLSBEE WITH THE VIDEO
WATCHING WITH YOU AS IT
HAPPENS.
DEBRIS METAL ALL SORTS OF
MESS IN THE THE SKY.
AND IF YOU ARE HIT BY THAT, CAN
CUT YOU UP AND DO A WHOLE LOT
OF DAMAGE.
FORTUNATELY, THOUGH, THE DAMAGE
THAT WE ARE HEARING ABOUT IS TO
THINGS AND NOT PEOPLE AND THAT
IS THE BLESSING IN ALL OF THIS
BECAUSE IT DID HAPPEN EARLY IN
THE DAY.
PEOPLE HAD THEIR PLANS.
A LITTLE EASIER TO GET YOUR ACT
TOGETHER IF YOU CAN SEE IT
COMING.
NOW, IT IS GETTING LATER IN THE
EVENING AND THINGS GETTING MORE
DANGEROUS BECAUSE OF HEATING
INDEX THAT HAPPENS IN THE
LATERITE PART OF THE DAY.
KOKH HAS DONE A FABULOUS JOB OF
COORDINATING FOR THEIR OWN
PEOPLE TO KEEP THEM SAFE.
WICHITA'S MAYOR SAID THEY ARE
DOING A FABULOUS JOB.
THE LOCAL AUTHORITIES ARE
DEPENDING ON THEIR WEATHER
PEOPLE TO WARN THEM AND KEEP
THEM OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
AS WE TAKE YOU TO THE NEXT
BREAK LET'S WATCH AND LISTEN.
FOX 25 OKLAHOMA CITY.
>> AGAIN, IF YOU ARE IN THE
ADELOT AREA IT IS HEADED
TOWARDS YOU.
THAT IS THE TORNADO RIGHT
THERE.
CONTINUES TO BE ON THE GROUND
AND THIS TORNADO MEANS BUSINESS
AND IT IS COMING RIGHT TO YOUR
HOMETOWN IF YOU LIVE IN ADELOT.
THERE IS THE SIGNATURE RIGHT
THERE AND SO IF YOU LIVE IN
THAT AREA YOU NEED TO BE TAKING
PREHE CAUTIONS RIGHT NOW.
THERE IS SHAWNEE.
Do we have a mower?  No.
A Trimmer?
No.
We got nothing.
We just bought our first house  we're
on a budget.
We're not ready for spring.
Well let's get you ready.
Very nice.
You see these various colors.
Got workshops every Saturday.
Yes, maybe a little bit over  here.
Summer's here.  So are the savings.
Not bad.
More saving. More doing.
That's the power of  The Home Depot.
Get special buys on select  Toro products,
like this self propelled  mower just
$274.
♪ ♪ ♪
SO YOU CAN MAKE EASY, NO-FEE RELOADS
WITH CASH AND CHECKS...
AND KNOW YOU'RE NOT ON YOUR OWN.
SO YOU CAN GET THE RELOADABLE CARD
THAT KEEPS UP WITH YOU.
CHASE LIQUID.
SO YOU CAN.
>>> FOX URGENT.
LIVE COVERAGE OF THE TORNADO
OUTBREAK.
WE KNEW IT WAS COMING, WE
DIDN'T KNOW IT WOULD BE QUITE
THIS ACTIVE THOUGH AS EARLY IN
THE DAY AS IT HAS BEEN ON THIS
SUNDAY AND NOW IT IS STILL
COOKING.
DANGEROUS SITUATIONS IN AND OUT
FROM OKLAHOMA AND NOW ADD IOWA
TO THE LIST OF PEOPLE NOW
MILLIONS OF THEM WHO NEED TO BE
ON THE LOOKOUT.
WHAT IS FALLING FROM THE SKY
AND DOING ALL OF THE DAMAGE
THAT WE ARE SEEING?
HOW ABOUT FOUR INCH OF FROST
SIZED HAIL.
I SAW FROM THE TWITTER ARE PAGE
SOMEVE THAT
IS POSSIBLE.
MEET KAREN PETERSON ON THE
GROUND IN EDMOND, OKLAHOMA.
WE HE KNOW THAT A MONSTER STORM
TOUCHED DOWN THERE TWISTER
OUTSIDE OF OKLAHOMA CITY.
YOU ARE WITH US BY PHONE.
>> I'M HERE, THANK YOU.
>> I KNOW YOU TOOK SOME
PICTURES OF THIS.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE AS IT WAS
COMING ACROSS YOUR TOWN?
>> WELL, WE WERE JUST NORTH OF
WHERE SOME OF THE TORNADOES HIT
BUT AS YOU CAN SEE BY THE
PICTURE THE HAIL WAS VERY HE
LOUD AND VERY STRONG.
>> AND I KNOW YOU TOOK SOME
PICTURES AND TELL ME WHAT I'M
SEEING?
>> WELL, AS THE HAIL WAS COMING
DOWN AT FIRST IT STARTED OUT
YOU KNOW, LIKE PEA SIZED AND
THEN GOT TO MORE BIG MARBLES
AND THEN GOLF BALL WE CAME IN
THE HOUSE.
AFTERWARDS WE WENT OUTSIDE TO
LOOK AROUND AND MY HUSBAND DUG
A COUPLE OF LARGE HAIL STONES
THAT HAD ACTUALLY GONE DOWN
INTO THE GROUND AND I WANTED TO
FIND SOMETHING TO COMPARE IT TO
AND THAT IS A GRAPEFRUIT NEXT
TO THE HAIL PIECES DALLAS.
>> THAT CAN DO SOME PRETTY BAD
MEDICAL ATTENTION RELATED
DAMAGE I WOULD IMAGINE.
ANYBODY YOU KNOW GET HIT BY
THAT OR WERE PEOPLE PRETTY MUCH
TUCKED INSIDE?
>> WHEN THAT STARTS FALLING
WHEN IT FIRST STARTS PEOPLE
LIKE TO GO OUT AND TAKE
PICTURES BUT ONCE YOU GET INTO
THE GOLF BALL AND LARGER PEOPLE
GO INSIDE AND STAY AWAY FROM
THE WINDOWS.
WITH THE WIND THAT BLOWS IN
OKLAHOMA IT CAN CERTAINLY BLOW
HE A PIECE OF HAIL THAT BIG
INTO A WINDOW SO YOU DON'T WANT
TO BE NEAR THE WINDOWS WHEN
THAT IS FALLING EITHER.
>> THE CONDITIONS WHERE YOU
WERE TODAY, IS THAT WITH YOU
WERE ANTICIPATING,  WHAT THE
LOCAL AUTHORITIES TOLD YOU
ABOUT?
DID YOU HEAR SIRENS.
>> WE DID HEAR SIRENS BUT MORE
IMPORTANTLY THAN THAT ALL OF
THE LOCAL NEWS STATIONS HAVE
BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS FOR THE
LAST COUPLE OF DAYS ACTUALLY
AND AS IT GETS CLOSER TO THE
TIME THEY GET MORE AND MORE
ACCURATE WITH THE BROADCASTS.
THEY HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT
THIS SENSE THURSDAY OR FRIDAY
SO PEOPLE HAVE BEEN PREPARING.
WE MAIDED SURE OUR STORM
SHELTER WAS CLEANED OUT AND WE
HAVE BOTTLED WATER.
CELL PHONES ARE CHARGED UP.
I HAVE KIDS UP IN STILLWATER IN
COLLEGE.
I MADE SURE THEY HAD THEIR CELL
PHONES CHARGE AND KNEW WHERE
THEY ARE GOING TO GO IF IT
HITS.
>> I'M SURE THAT DID SOME
DAMAGE BUT I'M GLAD YOU ARE
OKAY TONIGHT.
KAREN PETERSON EDMOND, OKLAHOMA
WITH THE PICTURES OF THE
GRAPEFRUIT SIZED HAIL TONIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR SHARING
THAT FOR THE COVERAGE TONIGHT.
STAY SAFE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> CONTINUING COVERAGE AFTER
THE BREAK BECAUSE AGAIN
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE ARE STILL IN
THE THE PATH OF THIS THIS
EVENING AND WITH THE HEATING
INDEX LATE IN THE DAY IT IS
STILL VERY DANGEROUS.
WE WILL BE TON FOR YOU.
PLUS "HUCKABEE."
STAY WITH US.
WE'RE NOT IN LONDON,  ARE WE?  NO.
WHY?  APPARENTLY  MY DEBIT CARD IS.
WHAT?  I KNOW.  DON'T WORRY,  WE HAVE
CANCELLED YOUR OLD CARD.  GREAT. THANK
YOU.  IN ADDITION TO US  MONITORING
YOUR ACCOUNTS  FOR UNUSUAL ACTIVITY,
YOU COULD ALSO SET UP  FREE ACCOUNT
ALERTS.  OKAY.    [ Female Announcer
]    AT WELLS FARGO WE'RE WORKING
AROUND THE CLOCK    TO HELP PROTECT
YOUR MONEY    AND FINANCIAL    INFORMATION.
HERE'S YOUR  TEMPORARY CARD.  WELCOME
BACK.  HOW WAS LONDON?    [ Female
Announcer ]    WHEN PEOPLE TALK,
GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.
This day calls you.
To fight chronic  osteoarthritis pain.
To fight chronic low  back pain.
To take action.  To take the next
step.
Today, y will know you did  something
for your pain.
Cymbalta can help.  Cymbalta is a
pain reliever
FDA-approved to manage chronic  musculoskeletal
pain.
One non-narcotic pill  a day, every
day
can helpeduce this pain.
Tell your doctor right away if  your
mood worsens,
you have unusual changes  in mood
or behavior
or thoughts of suicide.
Anti-depressants can increase  these
in children,
teens, and young adults.
Cymbalta inot for children  under
18.
People taking MAOIs, linezolid  or
thioridazine or with
uncontrolled glaucoma should  not
take Cymbalta.
Taking it with NSAID pain  relievers,
aspirin
or blood thinners may increase  bleeding
risk.
Severe liver problems, some  fatal,
were reported.
Signs include abdominal pain  and
yellowing skin or eyes.
Tell your doctor about all your  medicines,
including those for
migraine and while on Cymbalta  call
right away if you have
high fever, confusion and stiff  muscles
or serious allergic
skin reactions like blisters  peeling
rash, hives, or
mouth sores to address possible  life-threatening
conditions.
Talk about your alcohol use,  lir
disease and before you
reduce or stop Cymbalta.
Dizziness or fainting may occur  upon
standing.
Take the next step.  Talk to your
doctor.
Cymbalta can help.
Man: The charcoal went out  already?
... Forget it.
VO: There's more barbeque time  in
every bag of
Kingsford Original Charcoal.
Kingsford.
Slow down and grill.
♪ ♪  [ Agent Smith ]  I'VE FOUND SOFTWARE
THAT INTRIGUES ME.  IT APPEARS  IT'S
AN AGENT OF GOOD.  ♪ ♪  [ Agent Smith
]  GE SOFTWARE CONNECTS PATIENTS
TO NURSES  TO THE RIGHT MACHINES
WHILE DRAMATICALLY  REDUCING WAITING
TIME.  [ telephone ringing ]  NOW
A WAITING ROOM  IS JUST A ROOM.  [
static warbles ]
MINE WAS EARNED        IN DJIBOUTI
AFRICA. 2004.  VIETNAM IN 1972.
[ All ]            FORT BENNING, GEORGIA
IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]      USAA AUTO
INSURANCE     IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN
FROM GENERATION TO GENERATION.
BECAUSE IT OFFERS           A SUPERIOR
LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE MILITARY MEMBERS,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY,         GET AN
AUTO INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA. WE KNOW         WHAT IT MEANS
TO SERVE.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
HUCKABEE IN JUST MOMENTS.
FIRST, WE ARE WATCHING THE
SEVERE ARE STORM SYSTEM
BRINGING DANGEROUS TORNADOES
ACROSS THE CENTRAL UNITED
STATES.
WE WANT TO CHECK IN WITH THE
LATEST WITH METEOROLOGIST
JANICE DEAN IN THE FOX WEATHER
CENTER.
MOMENTS AGO WE HAD ENORMOUS
TOUCHDOWN AND I'M SEEING
REPORTS OF DAMAGE.
TELL US WHERE?
>> SOUTH AND EAST OF OKLAHOMA
CITY.
TORNADO WATCHES IN EFFECT FROM
OKLAHOMA ALL THE WAY UP TOWARDS
THE WESTERN GREAT LAKES
HARRIS.
THE WORST OF THE DAMAGE RIGHT
NOW OCCURRING IN OKLAHOMA AS
THE CELLS JUST ERUPT AHEAD OF
THE COLD FRONT.
THESE ROGUE SUPERCELLS AND WHEN
YOU ARE AHEAD OF THE COLD FRONT
THAT IS WHEN WE PARTICULARLY
SEE THINGS START TO