SHR IT'S NOON ON THE WEST COAST,
3:30A.M. SATURDAY IN THE NORTH
KOREAN CAPITAL.
KIM JUDGE UN HAS CALLED
PRESIDENT TRUMP MENTALLY
DERANGED.
THE PRESIDENT REACHING BACK,
CALLING HIM A MADMAN.
NOW THE NORTH COULD REANSWER
THREATENING THE BIGGEST EVER
HYDROGEN BOMB TEST IN THE
PACIFIC OCEAN.
JEFF HORIGIAN A MILITARY
COMMANDER WHO RUNS THE AIR FAR
AGAINST THE ISLAMIC STATE.
RUNS MISSES IN AN F-22 RAPTOR.
COMMANDS TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
TROOPS.
DIRECTED MOSUL, THE FIGHT FOR
RAKKA AND OVERSAW THE TOMORROW
HAWK MISSILE STRIKE AGAINST
SYRIA.
WHEN THINGS GET TENSE WITH
RUSSIAN FORCES, THE GENERAL USES
THIS PHONE TO KEEP PROBLEMS FROM
SPREADING.
WITH RUSSIA RECENTLY BOMBING
U.S. FORCES IN SYRIA OR NEAR
THEM, AND THREATENING NEW
RETALIATION, I'LL ASK THE
GENERAL WHAT HE EXPECTS NEXT.
HE'LL JOIN US LIVE.
AND THE REPUBLICAN SENATOR JOHN
McCAIN DEALING A HUGE SETBACK TO
THE PRESIDENT'S EFFORT TO CHANGE
OBAMACARE.
McCAIN, NO ON GRAHAM-CASSIDY.
HIS REASONS AHEAD.
LET'S GET TO IT.
>> Announcer: SHEPARD SMITH
REPORTING LIVE FROM THE FOX
NEWSDESK.
>> Shepard: FROM THE FOX
NEWSDESK, THE LATEST G.O.P.
HEALTHCARE PLAN IS NOW ONE VOTE
AWAY FROM COLLAPSE.
AFTER THE REPUBLICAN SENATOR
JOHN McCAIN ANNOUNCED HE CANNOT
SUPPORT THE BILL.
THE EDITION SO SIGS DESPITE THE
FACT ONE OF ITS CO-SPONSORS IS
HIS CLOSEST FRIEND IN THE
SENATE, LINDSAY GRAHAM.
SENATOR McCAIN BROKE THE NEWS
HOURS AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP
WARNED HIS FELLOW REPUBLICANS TO
VOTE YES.
THE PRESIDENT TWEETING, RAND
PAUL OR WHOEVER VOTES AGAINST
THE HEALTHCARE BILL WILL FOREVER
FUTURE POLITICAL CAMPAIGN BE
KNOWN AS THE REPUBLICAN WHO
SAVED OBAMACARE.
KENTUCKY SENATOR RAND PAUL WAS
THE FIRST REPUBLICAN TO COME OUT
AGAINST THE BILL.
HIS REASONING, IT DOESN'T GO FAR
ENOUGH TO REPEAL THE AFFORDABLE
CARE ACT.
NOW WE'RE WAITING TO HEAR FROM
THE OTHER TWO REPUBLICANS WHO
HELPED KILL THE LAST XW O.P.
HEALTHCARE HILL.
CHIEF CONGRESSIONAL REPORTER
MIKE OMANUAL.
>> WITH SENATOR JOHN McCAIN BEAK
A NO ON THE GRAHAM-CASSIDY PLAN
THERE'S INTENSE PRESSURE TO LOCK
DOWN ALL OTHER REPUBLICAN
SENATORS.
MAINE SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS SAID
HE'S LEANING AGAINST SUPPORTING
THIS GRAHAM-CASSIDY LEGISLATION.
COLLINS IS ONE OF THE NO VOTES
ON HEALTHCARE REFORM IN JULY.
THERE WAS PRESIDENT TO SUPPORT
WITH IT HER GOVERNOR AND
VICE PRESIDENT PENCE URGING HER
TO GET ONBOARD.
>> WE'RE ENCOURAGING SENATOR
CAIN, BUT ESPECIALLY ENCOURAGING
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS.
TO JOIN US IN THIS EFFORT.
TO GIVE THE PEOPLE OF MAINE, THE
GOVERNMENT OF MAVINE THE
FLEXIBILITY TO IMPROVE THE LIVES
AND THE HEALTH OF PEOPLE OF
MAINE.
>> IF COLLINS OR ALASKA'S LISA
MURKOWSKI SAY THEY'RE AGAINST
GRAY WHOM-CASSIDY LEADERSHIP DUS
VENLT VOTES TO PASS IT.
MURKOWSKI WAS NO ON THE SKINNY
REPEAL BILL IN JULY, SO-CALLED.
PRESIDENT REPUBLICAN SOURCES
HOPE THIS TEAM WOULD BE
DIFFERENT IF FOR NO OTHER REASON
THAN JOHN McCAIN'S BEST FRIEND
IN THE WORLD IS LINDSAY GRAHAM,
AUTHOR OF THE BILL.
>> Shepard: WHAT ARE YOU HEARING
FROM DEMOCRATS?
>> THEY'RE VOI VOWING TO
CONTINUE THE FIGHT, PRAISING
SENATOR McCAIN FOR STANDING UP
AND STOPPING THIS BILL.
BOTTOM LINE, A NUMBER OF
DEMOCRATS SAY THEY PISH THE
BIPARTISAN TALKS TO TRY TO FIX
OBAMACARE WERE CONTINUING.
>> I FELT LIKE WE WERE MAKING
STEADY PROS TOWARD A BIPARTISAN
COMPROMISE TO ADDRESS THE
CHALLENGES AND PROBLEMS WITH
OBAMACARE REPEAL.
THERE'S AN AN ABRUPT HALT BY THE
REPUBLICAN LEADERSHIP, WE WILL
HAVE A VOTE THIS COMING WEEK ON
THIS BILL.
I HAVE CONCERNS HOW IT WILL
AFFECT DELAWARE AND THE COUNTRY
AND I PLAN TO VOTE AGAINST IT.
>> MITCH McCONNELL INTENDS TO
BRING UP GRAHAM-CASSIDY NEXT
WEEK BUT THAT WAS BEFORE HE HAD
TWO HARD NO VOTES AGAINST THE
BILL.
>> MIKE EMMANUEL, THANKS.
>> Shepard: CHRIS WALLACE,
MODERATOR OF "FOX NEWS SUNDAY."
JOHN McCAIN GAVE HIS REASONS.
LAST TIME AROUND, HE MADE A
PRETTY CLEAR STATEMENT WHEN HE
WAS THAT DRAMATIC VOTE FOR NO.
WE HAVE A FULL SCREEN OF THAT
I'D LIKE TO SHOW THE VIEWING
AUDIENCE.
HERE IT IS.
THIS IS WHAT HE SAID LAST TIME.
THE CONGRESS MUST NOW RETURN TO
REGULAR ORDER.
HOLD HEARINGS.
RECEIVE INPUT FROM MEMBERS OF
BOTH PARTIES.
AND HEED THE RECOMMENDATIONS OF
OUR NATION'S GOVERNORS SO THAT
WE CAN PRODUCE A BILL THAT
FINALLY PROVIDES AMERICANS WITH
ACCESS TO QUALITY AND AFFORDABLE
HEALTHCARE.
THAT PART OF IT HADN'T CHANGED,
THOUGH THIS IS TECHNICALLY
REGULAR ORDER IT WASN'T.
COMMITTEES HAD MET ON IT, AND
THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET OFFICE
HADN'T MARKED IT UP.
>> EXACTLY RIGHT.
THE COMMITTEES HAVE NOT MET ON
IT.
THEY'LL HOLD ONE OR TWO HEARINGS
THIS NEXT WEEK.
SIMPLY, I THINK, TRYING TO
SATISFY JOHN McCAIN,nd SOME
OTHERS WHO SAID THIS IS A HECK
OF A WAY TO COMPLETELY REFORM
THE HEALTH SYSTEM, ONE-SIXTH OF
THE ECONOMY.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET A CBL
SCORE, CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
OFFICE.
THE IMPACT ON PREMIUMS OR THE
IMPACT IT WOULD HAVE ON MILLIONS
OF PEOPLE POTENTIALLY LOSING
THEIR COVERAGE.
JOHN McCAIN DECIDED TO PULL THE
PLUG EARLY.
MAYBE HE DIDN'T WANT TO BE THE
ONE, THE FINAL VOTE AS HE WAS
LAST TIME, WHEN HE LITERALLY PUT
HIS THUMB DOWN.
BUT HE MADE IT CLEAR HE'S A NO
VOTE.
RAND PAUL HAS MADE IT CLEAR HE'S
A NO VOTE.
THIS REMINDS ME OF THE LINE
ABOUT THE KNIGHT AND THE PRINCE,
IN THE PRINCESS BRIDE, IT'S
MOSTLY DEAD, THIS IS MOSTLY DEAD
RIGHT NOW.
I SUPPOSE SUSAN COLLINS COULD
CHANGE BUT SHE'S BEEN AGAINST
ALL OF THESE REPEAL AND REPLACE
PLANS.
I'D BE SHOCKED IF SHE WERE TO
CHANGE.
LISA MURKOWSKI HAS BEEN AGAINST
ALMOST ALL OF THEM.
I'D BE A LITTLE LESS SHOCKED IF
SHE CHANGED.
SHELLEY MOORE OF WEST VIRGINIA,
ROB PORTMAN OF OHIO, GRASSLEY
AND EARNS THE FROM IOWA.
THERE'S A LOT OF OPPOSITION.
IT'S ON- SUPPORT, WOULD BE AN
OVERSTATEMENT.
ON LIFE SUPPORT.
>> Shepard: LISA MURKOWSKI OF
ALASKA, THERE'S A LARGE GIFT
BASKET WAITING IN THE WINGS,
IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING FOR THE
PEOPLE OF ALASKA IF SHE CHANGES
HER MIND.
>> YES, THERE'S A PROVISION FOR
SPARSELY POPULATED STATES,
ALASKA CERTAINLY QUALIFIES AS A
SPARSELY POPULATED STATE, THAT
THEY WOULD NOT FALL UNDER ALL OF
THE PROVISIONS AND IT WOULD MAKE
SURE THAT THEY GOT MORE FUNDING
RATHER THAN LESS FUNDING WHICH
THEY WOULD OTHERWISE IF THEY
WERE TREATED LIKE EVERY OTHER
STATE.
THIS IS, IT'S INTERESTING TO
SEE, SHEP, WE ALL REMEMBER
OBAMACARE, ALL OF THE COMPLAINTS
THAT REPUBLICANS HAD AT THE TIME
ABOUT THE MESSY WAY THAT WAS
PASSED.
WE HAVE A PASS IT IN ORDER TO
FIND OUT WHAT'S IN IT.
THINGS ARE JAMMED DOWN.
THERE WAS THE CORNHUSKER
KICKBACK, ALL OF THE SPECIAL
DEALS TO BUY THE VOTES OF
SENATORS.
YOU'RE SEEING ALL OF THAT IF NOT
MORE ON THE PART OF REPUBLICANS
THIS TIME.
IT'S PERFECT HYPOCRISY, WHAT YOU
SEE ON CAPITOL HILL.
>> Shepard: I WANTED TO SPEAK
SPECIAL ABOUT SUSAN COLLINS OF
MAINE.
FOR HER, SHE SAID REPEATEDLY, I
THINK, CHRIS, THIS IS ABOUT
MEDICAID.
HER CONCERNS ABOUT IT.
>> WELL, THAT'S RIGHT.
IN FACT ACCORDING TO THE
FORMULA, MAINE WOULD DO BETTER,
THERE ARE SOME STATES, ABOUT 31
STATES THAT ARE LOSERS IN THIS
BILL.
THERE ARE SOME THAT ARE WINNERS.
MAINE WOULD BE A WINNER.
BUT SHE'S VERY CONCERNED ABOUT
THE MEDICAID.
IT TURNS IT FROM A BASICALLY
OPEN-ENDED ENTITLEMENT INTO A
BLOCK GRANT AND EVENTUALLY A
FORMULA WITH DIMINISHING
FINANCING PER CAPITA, PER
PERSON.
IN THE LONG RUN, CERTAINLY AFTER
2026, PEOPLE ON MEDICAID GET
LESS FUNDING THAN IN THE PAST.
SUSAN COLLINS IS MAD ABOUT THAT.
YOU SAW THE GOVERNOR, THE
INDEPENDENT GOFF OF MAINE
JOIN -- GOVERNOR OF MAINE TO
JOIN WITH THE VICE PRESIDENT TO
URGE HER TO DO IT.
SHE'S REPORTING A LOT OF FOLKS
IN MAINE LIKE HER STAND AGAINST
PASSING THIS BILL.
>> Shepard: IT SEEMS THAT LAST
TIME THE REPUBLICANS CAME UP
WITH A PLAN, IT ONLY HAD 17%
APPROVAL ACROSS THE NATION.
THIS TIME THE CONCERN SEEMS TO
BE IF NOT PRIMARILY, LARGELY,
ABOUT A CAP ON LIFETIME BENEFITS
FOR PEOPLE WITH PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS.
AND THEY'RE DISCUSSING THIS IN
THE JIMMY KIMMEL WAY, IF YOU
HAVE A CHILD WHO NEEDS MULTIPLE
IN HIS CASE HEART SURGERIES AND
YOU HAVE A MILLION DOLLAR CAP
AND YOUR CHILD DICE AS A RESULT
OF THE FACT YOU DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH MONEY THAT SEEMS TO BE A
CONCERN FOR A LOT OF VOTERS.
>> LOOK, THE PROBLEM IS THAT
WHAT THIS DOES IS BASICALLY
KEEPS ALL OF THE TAXES FROM
OBAMACARE AND DOES AWAY WITH THE
MANDATES, DOES AWAY WITH THE
MEDICAL DEVICE TAX.
IT TAKES THE OTHER BIG TAXES AND
SIMPLY GIVES IT BACK TO THE
STATE AND SAYS FEDERALISM, YOU
DO IT.
THE PROBLEM IS THAT EVERY STATE
WOULD HAVE A DIFFERENT PLAN AND
THEY WOULD HAVE TO GET WAIVERS
FROM THE DEPARTMENT, FROM
WASHINGTON, FROM THE DEPARTMENT
OF HEALTH AND HUMAN SERVICES OF
APPROPRIATE AND AFFORDABLE
COVERAGE.
NOBODY KNOWS WHAT THAT MEANS.
NOW, THERE'S A LIKELIHOOD THAT
SOME STATES, LIBERAL STATES,
BLUE STATES, WOULD HAVE VERY
LENIENT BENEFITS AND WOULD, FOR
INSTANCE, PEOPLE WITH
PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS ARE WELL
COVERED.
OTHER STATES WE AREN'T SURE.
WHO KNOWS WHAT A WAIVER FOR
APPROPRIATE AND AFFORDABLE
COVERAGE MEANS.
THERE IS A CONCERN.
WE DON'T KNOW, IN FACT, BUT
THERE IS A CONCERN THAT SOME SAY
WITH PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS MAY
SAY ON PAPER THEY CAN GET
COVERAGE BUT IN TERMS OF THE
FINANCING, COST OF THE PREMIUMS
OR DEDUCTIBLES, THEY CAN'T.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOT DEAD BUT
IT'S EXTREMELY COLD AND
EXTREMELY WHITE.
>> IT'S MOSTLY DEAD.
>> Shepard: THE LEADERS OF NORTH
KOREA AND UNITED STATES ARE
PERSON
ALLY INSULTING EACH OTHER
AND BRINGING THE NUCLEAR
STANDOFF TO A NEW LEVEL.
THE DICTATOR KIM JUDGE UN HAS
CALLED PRESIDENT TRUMP MENTALLY
DERANGED N A PERSONAL STATEMENT,
IT COMES AFTER PRESIDENT PLUMP
THREATENED TO TOTALLY DESTROY
NORTH KOREA IF THAT IS WHAT IT
TAKES TO DEFEND THE UNITED
STATES.
THAT WAS DURING HIS SPEECH TO
THE UNITED NATIONS GENERAL
ASSEMBLY.
ACCORDING TO NORTH KOREAN STATE
TELEVISION, KIM JUNG UN SAID
WHATEVER TRUMP MIGHT HAVE
EXPECTED HE WILL FACE RESULTS
BEYOND HIS EXPECTATION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETED THIS
MORNING, KIM JUN-UN OF NORTH
KOREA, OBVIOUS LAY MADMAN,
DOESN'T MIND STARVING AND
KILLING HIS PEOPLE, WILL BE
TESTED LIKE NEVER BEFORE.
NOW, NORTH KOREA'S FOREIGN MIN
CITY SAID THEY MIGHT CONSIDER
TESTING A HYDROGEN BOMB IN THE
PACIFIC OCEAN.
HERE'S HOW THE SECRETARY OF
STATE, REX TILLERSON, RESPONDED
TO THAT.
>> ALL OF OUR MILITARY OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE AS THE
PRESIDENT SAID.
THERE WILL BE ASSEMBLED AND
THERE IS ASSEMBLED A NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNCIL THAT MEETS ON
EACH OF THESE ISSUES TO ADVISE
THE PRESIDENT.
IT WILL BE HIS DECISION
ULTIMATELY.
>> Shepard: SECRETARY TILLERSON
SAID THE U.S. WILL CONTINUE
EFFORTS IN THE DIPLOMATIC ARENA
A BACK TO CHRIS WALLACE.
GOING AT IT LIKE CHILDREN IN A
PLAYGROUND, DOES THIS LEAD TO
WAR?
YESTERDAY THE STOCK MARKET
SEEMED TO SUGGEST SO, 10 DEFENSE
STOCKS HIT THE ALL-TIME HIGH.
>> WE'RE A WAYS AWAY FROM THAT.
GENERAL McMASTER, H.R. McMASTER,
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR, SAID
WE'RE RUNNING OUT OF ROAD.
THERE IS MORE ROAD.
YOU CAN SEE THAT YESTERDAY WHEN
THE PRESIDENT ANNOUNCED THAT HE
SIGNED AN EXECUTIVE ORDER GIVING
THE TREASURY SECRETARY THE
POWERS TO CUT OFF ANY TRADE, ANY
DEALINGS WITH ANY COMPANY, ANY
BANK, THAT HAS TRADE OR DEALINGS
WITH NORTH KOREA.
PRESIDENT ALSO ANNOUNCED THAT
CHINESE, THE CHINESE CENTRAL
BANK, IN ACCOUNT THEIR FEDERAL
RESERVE, IS ORDERING ALL OF
THEIR BANKS TO CUT OFF ANY
FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS WITH
PYONGYANG, WITH THE KIM REGIME.
WE'LL WAIT TO SEE HOW IT WORKS,
WHETHER SQUEEZING NORTH KOREA IN
THAT FINANCIAL AND TRADE SENSE
SHAKES ANY SENSE INTO THE KIM
REGIME AND GETS THEM TO STAND
DOWN.
THE QUESTION, SHEP, IS WHETHER
KIM HAS MADE IN EFFECT AN
EXISTENTIAL CHOICE, BELIEVES
THAT HAVING A LONG-RANGE
BALLISTIC MISSILE WITH A NUCLEAR
WAR HEAD ON IT IS NOT THE PATH
TO DISASTER BUT THE PATH TO
SURVIVAL FOR HIS REGIME.
YOU KNOW, HE LOOKS AROUND THE
WORLD, SEES SADDAM HUSSEIN, NO
WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION,
ENDED UP DEAD.
SAME WITHCA DAFIE AND MAY
HAVE -- KHADAFFI.
THE THING THAT ENSURES HIS
SURVIVAL HE BELIEVES IS TO HAVE
A NUCLEAR WEAPON.
>> Shepard: WONDER WHAT KIND OF
REACTION HE'D GET TO AN H-BOMB
TEST IN THE PACIFIC.
>> WE HAVE HAD H-BOMB TESTS
BEFORE, A COUPLE OF WEEKS AGO,
WE THINK, IT WAS UNDERGROUND.
THIS WOULD OBVIOUSLY BE MORE
STUNNING BECAUSE IT WOULD BE
OVER GROUND.
IT WOULD BE OVER THE WATER.
WE WOULD SEE THE MUSHROOM CLOUD
THAT WOULD BRING HOME WHAT THE
THREAT IS.
DO I THINK WE'LL GO TO WAR OVER
A NUCLEAR TEST, PROBABLY NOT.
PARTICULARLY NOT WITH ALL OF
THESE SANCTIONS JUST GETTING
STARTED.
>> Shepard: CHRIS WALLACE, FROM
WASHINGTON, LOOKING FORWARD TO
YOUR PROGRAM ON FOX NEWS SUNDAY.
HE'LL TALK WITH MICROSOFT
CO-FOUNDER BILL GATES ABOUT THE
GATES FOUNDATION, THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST PRIVATE CHARITY AMONG
OTHER THINGS, ON FOX NEWS SUNDAY
ON YOUR LOCAL FOX STATION.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS GETTING SET
TO TAKE ANOTHER TRY AT A TRAVEL
BAN.
THE FIRST BAN CAUSED A BIT OF
CHAOS.
SO WHAT IS DIFFERENT THIS TIME?
JUST RELEASED DETAILS COMING UP
FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK ON THIS
FRIDAY AFTERNOON.
Dynamic performance,
Track tuned handling,
and aggressive styling.
The bold Lexus IS.
Lease the 2017 IS Turbo for
$299 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing at
your Lexus dealer.
WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE TO
THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE,
DOES PSORIASIS EVER GET IN
THE WAY OF A TOUCHING MOMENT?
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE TO SEVERE
PSORIASIS, YOU CAN EMBRACE
THE CHANCE OF COMPLETELY
CLEAR SKIN WITH TALTZ.
TALTZ IS PROVEN TO GIVE YOU A
CHANCE AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
WITH TALTZ, UP TO
90% OF PATIENTS
HAD A SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT
OF THEIR PSORIASIS PLAQUES.
IN FACT, 4 OUT OF 10 EVEN
ACHIEVED COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DO NOT USE IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING YOU
SHOULD BE CHECKED
FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE YOUR
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU ARE BEING TREATED
FOR AN INFECTION
OR HAVE SYMPTOMS.
OR IF YOU HAVE RECEIVED
A VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ.
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
JUST ASK YOUR
DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
you get time for more life.
This family wanted to
keep the game going.
SON: Hey mom, one more game?
TECH: With Safelite, you get a
text when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
MOM: Sure.
Bring it!
TECH: I'm Micah with Safelite.
MOM: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care!
FAMILY: Bye!
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
S.
>> Shepard: THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION PREPARING A NEW
ORDER TO REPLACE THE
CONTROVERSIAL TRAVEL BAND.
DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND SECURITY
HAS TAILORED RESTRICTIONS TO
EACH COUNTRY.
BASED ON WHAT THEY CALL MULTIPLE
FACTORS INCLUDING THE THREAT
EACH COUNTRY POSES AND WHETHER
IT COOPERATES WITH U.S.
REGULATIONS.
THE NEW RULES WOULD REPLACE
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S EARLIER
EXECUTIVE ORDER THAT BANNED
TRAVELERS FROM SIX MUSLIM
MAJORITY COUNTRIES.
BUT WE'RE STILL WAITING TO HEAR
WHICH COUNTRIES THE NEW TRAVEL
RULES WILL AFFECT.
KEVIN CORK, LIVE IN SOMERSET,
NEW JERSEY NOT FAR FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S GOLF CLUB WHERE HE'S
SPENDING THE WEEKEND.
KEVIN?
>> RIGHT ON THE MONEY, SHEPARD.
WE TALKED ABOUT THE PREVIOUS SIX
COUNTRY, WE DON'T KNOW HOW MANY
COUNTRIES WILL BE INVOLVED IN
THE NEW TRAVEL RESTRICTIONS.
WE DO HAVE IT ON GOOD AUTHORITY
BASED ON WHAT WE'VE BEEN
LEARNING FROM ADMINISTRATION
SOURCES AND BASE ON WHAT WE
LEARNED FROM A RECENTLY
CONCLUDED CALL THE NUMBER OF
COUNTRIES INVOLVED WILL LIKELY
EXPAND TO INCLUDE MORE THAN THE
ORIGINAL SIX COUNTRIES THAT WE
TALKED ABOUT.
LET ME SHARE PART OF AN
ADMINISTRATION STATEMENT THEY'VE
BEEN TALKING ABOUT THIS IDEA OF
SECURING THE HOMELAND AND MOST
IMPORTANTLY PROTECTING THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION WILL ENSURE
WE ONLY ADMIT THOSE PROPERLY
VOTED AND WILL NOT POSE A THREAT
TO NATIONAL SECURITY OR PUBLIC
SAFETY.
SO IN EXPANDING THE NUMBER OF
COUNTRIES ON THE LIST THE
ADMINISTRATION PROPOSES AS YOU
SAID, TO CREATE MORE
RESTRICTIONS BUT ON A
CASE-BY-CASE BASIS.
THIS IS ALSO RELEVANT FOR ONE
MAJOR IMPORTANT REASON, THAT IS
BY EXPANDING IT AND MAKING IT
COUNTRY-TO-COUNTRY, SHEPARD,
WHAT THEY'RE EFFECTIVELY TRYING
TO DO IS BLUNT PERHAPS SOME OF
THE LEGAL PUSHBACK THAT THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS PREVIOUSLY
GOTTEN.
YOU MAY RECALL THE STATE
DEPARTMENT SAID THERE WERE LIKE
17 COUNTRIES NOT UP TO U.S.
STANDARDS AND FAILED TO FALL
INTO COMPLIANCE B HALF HAVE.
WE'LL SEE WHAT THAT NUMBER LOOKS
LIKE.
I WANT TO SHARE A TWEET THAT THE
PRESIDENT SENT OUT AFTER AN
ATTACK ON LONDON.
I THINK IT'S INSTRUCTIVE, WILL
GIVE YOU A SENSE OF WHAT HE'S
BEEN THINKING.
THIS IS BACK IN SEPTEMBER 15.
A TRAVEL BAN INTO THE U.S.
SHOULD BE FOR LARGER, TOUGHER,
AND MORE SPECIFIC.
INDEED THAT APPEARS TO BE THE
CASE.
>> Shepard: KEVIN CORK, LIVE FOR
US, THANK YOU.
THERE'S BREAKING NEWS FROM
PUERTO RICO, WORD OF A DAM THAT
HAS FAILED AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA.
PEOPLE ARE RACING TO ESCAPE.
WE'LL TAKE YOU THERE.
MEXICO CITY FACES OF AGONY,
VIDEO SHOWS RELATIVES OF SOME OF
THOSE STILL MISSING DAYS AFTER
THE EARTHQUAKE LEVELED
BUILDINGS.
WAITING FOR WORD.
COMING UP.
Endless Shrimp is back
at Red Lobster.
And we went all out
to bring you even more
incredible shrimp
and new flavors.
Like new
Nashville Hot Shrimp,
drizzled with
sweet amber honey,
and new grilled
Mediterranean Shrimp
finished with a savory blend
of green onions,
tomatoes, and herbs.
Feeling hungry yet?
Good, 'cause there's plenty
more where these came from.
Like Garlic Shrimp Scampi,
and other classics you love.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
But hurry, Endless Shrimp
won't be here long.
Track your pack.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
Set a curfew,
or two.
Make dinner-time
device free.
[ music stops ]
[ music plays again ]
A smarter way to wifi
is awesome.
Introducing XFINITY xFi.
Amazing speed,
coverage and control.
Change the way you wifi.
XFINITY. The future
of awesome.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS IN
PUERTO RICO, HURRICANE MARIA
CAUSED MAJOR DESTRUCTION AFTER
MAKING LANDFALL AS A CATEGORY 4
STORM EARLIER THIS WEEK.
THIS IS THE BREAKING NEWS, NOW.
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE JUST
ANNOUNCED A DAM IN THE WESTERN
PART OF THE ISLAND ABOUT AN HOUR
AND A HALF DRIVE WEST OF THE
CAPITAL IS FAILING.
A DAM IS FAILING AND TWO TOWNS
ARE HURRIEDLY EVACUATED, THEY
HAVE SENT IN BUSS TO GET PEOPLE
OUT MACHLT REA WAS THE MOST
POWERFUL STORM TO HIT PUERTO
RICO IN 80 YEARS.
STEVE IS LIVE IN SAN JUAN, ABOUT
AN HOUR AND A HALF DRIVE EAST OF
THE DAM.
WHAT HAVE YOU HEARD, STEVE?
>> SHEPARD, PEOPLE ARE JUST
AFRAID OF WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
SO MUCH UNCERTAINTY AROUND ABOUT
WHAT IS HAPPENING IN THE OUTER
REGIONS.
IT WAS EXPECTED, ANTICIPATED,
AND FEARED THAT THIS AGING
INFRASTRUCTURE OF THE BANKRUPT
ISLAND WOULD BE TESTED BY
HURRICANE MARIA.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED.
DETAILS COMING IN BIT BY BIT.
THIS DAM IN NORTHWESTERN PART OF
THE ISLAND IS FAILING RIGHT NOW.
THEY'RE USING SCHOOL BUSES TO
EVACUATE PEOPLE AS QUICKLY AS
POSSIBLE FROM TWO TOWNS.
ALREADY FLASH FLOODING IN THE
RIVER AROUND THERE.
THIS HIGHLIGHTS A COUPLE OF
THINGS.
NOT ONLY THE INFRASTRUCTURE ISCA
LAPSING AND DEALT A DEATH FLOW
BUT THE PROBLEM WITH
INFORMATION.
CELL PHONE COVERAGE DOWN.
ROADS BLOCKED.
IN THESE OUTER REGIONS OF THE
ISLAND WHERE TRAGEDIES ARE
HAPPENING IN THE WAKE OF THE
STORM, VERY DIFFICULT.
INFORMATION COMING IN JUST IN
BITS AND PIECES.
THREE DEAD HERE, EIGHT DEAD
THERE AS THE CASUALLY FIGURE
CONTINUES TO RISE.
WE'LL MONITOR THE DAM COLLAPSE.
>> Shepard: SEARCH TEAMS PULLING
SURVIVORS FROM UNEARTHED CRUSHED
BUILDINGS THREE DAYS AFTER AN
EARTHQUAKES DECIMATED AREAS
AROUND MEXICO CITY.
MUCH OF THAT AREA WAS DESTROYED.
CITY GOVERNMENT REPORTING 60
RESCUES SINCE THAT QUAKE HIT ON
TUESDAY.
NEARLY 300 CONFIRMED DEAD.
THE MEXICAN NAVY OFFICIAL SAYS
THAT RUMORS OF A CHILD ALIVE
UNDERNEATH A COLLAPSED SCHOOL
WERE ALL WRONG.
BUT HE SAID THERE ARE STILL
COULD BE SOMEBODY UNDERNEATH
THERE, AS LONG AS THERE'S A
CHANCE HE SAID THE TEAMS WILL
KEEP DIGGING.
SIMILAR SCENES PLAYING OUT IN
AND AROUND MEXICO CITY, RESCUERS
REFUSING TO GIVE UP, RELATIVES
HOLDING OUT HOPE THAT MISSING
LOVED ONES WILL COME HOME.
OUR CHIEF CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN
HUNT IS IN MEXICO CITY AT A
TEXTILE FACTORY, CREWS SEARCHING
FOR SURVIVORS.
>> THIS HAS BEEN THE SCENE OF AN
INTENSE SEARCH AND RESCUE
OPERATION.
OVERNIGHT, ONE MAN WAS PULLED
ALIVE FROM WHAT WAS A FOUR-STORY
TEXTILE FACTORY.
YOU'RE LOOKING AT RIGHT NOW.
AS YOU CAN ALSO SEE RIGHT NOW,
THE HUNDREDS OF RESCUE WORKERS
AND VOLUNTEERS HERE HAVE PAUSED
FOR THE MOMENT.
THAT APPEARS TO TELL ITS OWN
STORY.
WE ARE AWAITING A VISIT BY THE
MAYOR OF MEXICO CITY.
AND THE VERY FACT THAT THEY HAVE
JUST, IN THE LAST FEW MINUTES,
PAUSED ALL THEIR WORK MAY
INDICATE THAT THIS IS ABOUT TO
MOVE FROM A SEARCH AND RESCUE
OPERATION TO A RECOVERY
OPERATION ONLY.
ALL DAY THEY'VE BEEN TELLING US
POSSIBLY EIGHT WOMEN WORKERS
WERE STILL MISSING IN THIS
FACTORY, SHEPARD.
IT APPEARS THAT WE ARE MOVING
TOWARDS THE POINT WHEN THEY MAY
WELL ANNOUNCE THAT THEY HAVE
DECIDED THERE ARE NO MORE
SURVIVORS.
THEY'VE GONE DOWN TO THE
BASEMENT HERE, THEY HAVE HAD THE
RESCUE DOGS SNIFFING THERE.
BUT EVERYBODY WILL TELL
WEDNESDAY YOU GET TO THE 72-HOUR
MARK HERE, IT'S VERY, VERY
UNLIKELY THAT THEY WILL FIND
MORE SURVIVORS.
AND THE FAMILIES ARE BRACING
THEMSELVES FOR THE MOVEMENT THAT
THE GOVERNMENT DECLARES THIS IS
NO LONG AREA RESCUE OPERATION,
BUT A RECOVERY OPERATION.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: JONATHAN, THANK YOU.
AMERICAN AND RUSSIAN GENERALS
MEETING FACE-TO-FACE AS THEY
FIGHT A PROXY WAR IN SIRIA.
THE PENTAGON ACCUSES MOSCOW OF
DROPPING BOMBS DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
TO U.S. SPECIAL OPERATIONS
GROUPS.
RUSSIANS SAYING THEY WILL
RETALIATE IF ANYBODY FIRES ON
THEIR SOURCES.
WE'LL SPEAK WITH THE GENERAL HO
HAS A HOTLINE TO RUSSIA,
COMMANDER OF AIR WAR AGAINST THE
ISLAMIC STATE, A FIRE PILOT
HIMSELF STILL FLYING COMBAT
MISSES OF THE GENERAL JOINS US
LIFE ON THE FOX NEWSDESK NEXT.
y,
Huh!
We gotta go.
Come on.
♪
"Grandma! Grandpa!"
Thanks mom.
Here we are. Look, right up
to here.
Principal. We can help
you plan for that.
But he's got work to do.
with a sore back.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
I wantI did my AncestryDNA
and where I came from.
and I couldn't wait
to get my pie chart.
The most shocking result was
that I'm 26% Native American.
I had no idea.
Just to know this
is what I'm made of,
this is where
my ancestors came from.
And I absolutely want to know
more about my
Native American heritage.
It's opened up
a whole new world for me.
Discover the story
only your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now at
AncestryDNA.com.
I need my blood
sugar to stay
in control.
Weekends
are my time.
I need an insulin
that fits
my schedule.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
(announcer)
Tresiba® is used
to control high blood sugar
in adults with diabetes.
Don't use Tresiba® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during
episodes of low blood sugar,
or if you are allergic
to any of its ingredients.
Don't share needles
or insulin pens.
Don't reuse needles.
The most common side effect
is low blood sugar,
which may cause dizziness,
sweating, confusion,
and headac..
Check your blood sugar.
Low blood sugar can be serious
and may be life-threatening.
Injection site reactions
may occur.
Tell your prescriber
about all medicines you take
and all your medical conditions.
Taking TZDs with insinins
like Tresiba®
may cause serious side
effects like heart failure.
Your insulin dose shouldn't
be changed
without
asking your prescriber.
Get medical help right away
if you have trouble breathing,
fast heartbeat,
extreme drowsiness,
swelling of your face,
toueue, or throat,
dizziness, or confusion.
Ask your health care provider
if you're Tresiba® ready.
Covered by most insurance
and Medicare plans.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
>> Shepard: CONTINUING KOMPL.
LINDSAY GRAHAM RESPONDING TO THE
ANNOUNCEMENT FROM SENATOR JOHN
McCAIN THAT HE WILL VOTE NO ON
THE LATEST REPUBLICAN HEALTHCARE
MAN.
SENATOR GRAHAM IS A CO-SPONSOR
OF THE BILL.
HE WROTE IN A STATEMENT, HIGH
FRIENDSHIP WITH JOHN McCAIN IS
NOT BASED ON HOW HE VOTES BUT
RESPECT FOR HOW HE'S LIVED HIS
LIFE AND THE PERSON HE IS.
I RESPECTFULLY DISAGREE WITH HIS
POSITION NOT TO PROCEED FORWARD.
THE BILL IS ONE VOTE AWAY FROM
FAILING.
WE'RE STIT WAITING TO HEAR WHEN
THE SENATE MAJORITY LEADER,
MITCH McCONNELL, WILL BRING TO
IT FLOOR FOR A VOTE.
U.S. AND RUSSIAN GENERALS COMING
FACE-TO-FACE THIS WEEK,
SOMEWHERE, UNDISCLOSED LOCATION
IN THE MIDDLE EAST FOR
DISCUSSIONS.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM A U.S.
MILITARY SPOKESMAN.
THIS MEETING JUST DAYS AFTER THE
PENTAGON ACCUSED RUSH YAF OF
WOMING U.S.-BACKED FIGHTERS IN
EASTERN SYRIA WITH AMERICAN
SPECIAL FORCES DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
TO THE ACTION.
RUSSIA THREATENED TO RETALIATE
IF ITS TROOPS COME UNDER FIRE
WHILE FIGHTING ALONG SIDE SYRIAN
FORCES.
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS SAY THEY WILL
TARGET AREAS THAT AMERICAN UNITS
OCCUPY IF NECESSARY.
THAT'S A THREAT.
IT'S BRINGING TO THE FOREFRONT
THE REAL POSSIBILITY OF DIRECT
CONFRONTATION BETWEEN THE UNITED
STATES AND RUSSIAN FORCES INSIDE
SYRIA.
WHERE A CIVIL WAR HAS BEEN GOING
ON FOR MORE THAN SIX YEARS.
A PROXY WAR BETWEEN THE UNITED
STATES AND RUSSIA.
JENNIFER GRIFF WIN THE NEWS AT
THE PENTAGON, WHAT THE LATEST ON
THE GROUND SYRIA?
>> THE RUSSIAN MILITARY
ANNOUNCED IT FIRED CRUISE
MISSILES FROM ITS SUBMARINE IN
THE IMMEDIATE TRAINION SEA ON
MILITANT POSITIONS IN WESTERN
SYRIA.
U.S. TROOPS WEREN'T NEARBY.
TENSIONS ARE RUNNING HIGH IN
EASTERN SYRIA AFTER THAT RUSSIAN
GENERAL THREATENED TO ATTACK
AMERICAN TROOPS AND THE MILITIA.
THEY'RE ADVISING RIGHT NOW,
THERE'S A STANDOFF ON THE BANKS
OF THE YOU A FRAY TEASE RIVER
BETWEEN RUSSIAN AND AMERICAN
BACKED FORCES.
BOTH SIDES ARE ESSENTIALLY
EYEBALL-TO-EYEBALL.
THE U.S. MILITARY ACCUSED
RUSSIAN JETS OF BOMBING
U.S.-BACKED FIGHTERS LAST
WEEKEND AS YOU MENTION.
NO U.S. TROOPS WERE HURT.
BUT YESTERDAY, A RUSSIAN GENERAL
WARNLD THE UNITED STATES RUSSIA
WOULD ATTACK IF THE FORCES CAME
UNDER FIRE.
THIS IS A PHOTOGRAPH OF THE
HOTLINE TELEPHONE USED BY THE
U.S. MILITARY TO CALL THEIR
RUSSIAN COUNTERPARTS AND DEACON
FLIKT, IF YOU WILL, IN THE
CROWDED SKIES OVER SYRIA.
IT IS LOCATED THE AIR BASE IN
QATAR WHERE THE U.S. RUNS THE
AIR WAR AGAINST ISIS.
IT IS USED WE'RE TOLD ABOUT A
DOZEN TIMES EACH DAY.
AT THE PENTAGON, HOSTING HIS
POLISH COUNTERPART, DEFENSE
SECRETARY JIM MALTIS WAS ASKED
IF HE WAS WORRIED ABOUT MORE
RUSSIAN AIR STRIKES AGAINST
U.S.-BACKED FIGHTERS AND THEIR
AMERICAN ADVISORS IN SYRIA.
>> NO, I'M NOT WORRIED, WE DEAL
WITH THE RUSSIANS IN A
COLLABORATIVE WAY AND WE'LL SORT
IT OUT.
>> THE U.S. AND RUSSIA ARE
BARRED BY LAW FROM COOPERATING
TOGETHER.
CONGRESS PASSED A LAW AFTER
RUSSIA'S INVASION OF UKRAINE IN
2014.
THAT DIDN'T STOP AMERICAN AND
RUSSIAN GENERALS FROM MEETING
FACE-TO-FACE IN RECENT DAYS, ON
THE GROUND, TO DEFUSE THE
ESCALATING SITUATION.
>> Shepard: WHAT ABOUT THE FIGHT
AGAINST ISIS?
>> ALL EYES ARE ON THE KURDISH
AREAS OF NORTHERN IRAQ WHERE A
CONTROVERSIAL REFERENDUM ON
INDEPENDENT EVENS IS TAKING
PLACE ON MONDAY.
U.S.-BACKED FORCES FIGHTING TO
CLEAR ISIS FROM ITS
SELF-PROCLAIMED CAPITAL IN SYRIA
HAVE CLEARED WE'RE TOLD 70% OF
RA" A.
UP TO 900 ISIS FIGHTERS IN
RACKIA.
IN IRAQ THE OPERATION TO PLIB
RATE ONE OF THE LAST POCKETS
THAT ISIS CONTROLS IN IRAQ.
AS IF THE PENTAGON DOESN'T HAVE
ENOUGH TO KEEP IT'SES ON, RUSSIA
TEST FIRED AN INTERCONTINENTAL
BALLISTIC MISS WILL A 7,500 MILE
RANGE CAPABLE OF HITTING ANY
CITY IN THE UNITED STATES.
PENTAGON OFFICIALS SAY THE U.S.
WAS WARNED ABOUT THE TEST LAUNCH
IN ACCORDANCE A WITH
LONG-STANDING TREATMENTIES.
RUSSIA HAS BEEN USING SYRIA FOR
TESTING.
THAT HAS THE PENTAGON CONCERNED.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
OUR NEXT GUEST IS THE COMMANDER
OF THE AIR WAR AGAINST THE
ISLAMIC STATE, LIEUTENANT
JEFFREY COBRA HARIGIAN HAS
DIRECTED SOME OF THE BIGGEST
EVENTS IN THE FIGHTING INCLUDING
THE NINE-MONTH FIGHT FOR THE
CITY OF MOSUL.
THIS PHOTO FROM MOSUL YESTERDAY.
MUCH OF THAT CITY IS DEVASTATED
FROM THE FIGHTING.
THE GENERAL IS AN AIR FORCE
FIGHTER PILOT WITH MORE THAN 30
YEARS EXPERIENCE.
HE FLIES OVER IRAQ AND SYRIA
NOW, THIS SHOT FROM JUNE AS HE
REFUELED DURING A RISHGS.
THE GENERAL IS ALSO A PURPLE
HEART RECIPIENT N1996 HE WAS
STATIONED IN SAUDI ARABIA WHEN
HE WAS INJURED IN THE BOMBING OF
THE KOBAR TOWERS.
19 AIRMEN DIED IN THAT ATTACK,
SOME 300 OTHERS HURT.
LT. GENERAL JEFFREY COBRA
HARIGIAN, CENTRAL COMMAND, HAN
HONOR TO HAVE YOU.
>> IT'S GREAT TO BE HERE.
>> DOES ANYTHING CHANGE IN
REGARDS TO THE RUSSIANS?
>> STEP ONE IS MANAGE THE DEACON
FLICKS, GET BACK TO THE FIGHT
AGAINST ISIS.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO WORK WITH AND
IN COORDINATION WITH THE TEAM TO
MAKE SURE WE HAVE DEACON FLIKTED
TO GET OF ONE IN THE SIGS FIGHT.
WE'LL GET THE TEAM IN POSITION
TO ENSURE THERE'S NOT A
STRATEGIC MISCOMMUNICATION THAT
CAN OCCUR.
>> Shepard: THE RUSSIANS WERE
FIRING ON OTHERS, OUR SPECIAL OP
FORCES NEARBY.
IT WAS TOO CLOSE.
AND WE SAID, BASICALLY, DON'T DO
IT AND THEY SAID WE'LL FIRE ON
YOU.
DOES THAT CHANGE ANYTHING ON THE
GROUND?
>> WELL, I THINK THE IMPORTANT
PART TO REMEMBER HERE IS WE WILL
PROTECT OUR FORCE.
IT SHOULD BE CRYSTAL CLEAR IN
EVERY AMERICAN'S MIND THAT WE'RE
FOG TO PROTECT OUR FORCE.
WE WORK THROUGH THIS, I THINK
THE PRODUCTIVE CONVERSATION THAT
NEEDS TO OCCUR IS GETTING BACK
TO FIGHTING ISIS, DE-CONFLICTING
OUR FORCES, ENSURING THE
MECHANISM TO DO THAT, WHAT IS
REQUIRED IS A CONTINUED
COVERINGS WITH THE RUSSIANS TO
MAKE THAT HAPPEN.
>> Shepard: WE HAD A MEETING
THAT HAPPENS AT UNDISCLOSED, ALL
THE REST, A MEETING YOU WOULD
HAVE ATTENDED HAD YOU NOT BEEN
HERE.
>> I HAD A REPRESENTATIVE THERE.
AND THAT REPRESENTATIVE GAVE ME
FULL FEEDBACK ON HOW THAT PLAYED
OUT.
AND THERE'S WORK TO BE DONE.
>> I KNOW WE CAN'T KNOW DETAILS,
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW DETAILS.
I WOULD LIKE TO KNOW, IF YOU CAN
TELL US, ARE THINGS GETTING
BETTER.
>> THERE WAS PROGRESS MADE.
IT WILL BE PIECEMEAL AND IT WILL
TAKE TIME.
THE KEY IS AS WE MOVE FORWARD WE
WORK THROUGH DE-CON FLICKS THAT
ALLOWS US TO CONTINUE OUR FIGHT.
AT THE END OF THE DAY WE WANT TO
ENCIRCLE AND ANNIHILATE ISIS
PARTICULARLY IN THE MIDDLE
EUPHRATES RIVER VALLEY.
>> IS THAT WHAT THE RUSSIANS
WANT?
ARE WE ABLE TO COMMUNICATE?
WE'RE NOT ABLE TO COMMUNICATE
TEAM-TO-TEAM, RUSSIANS AND
AMERICANS.
>> THAT'S WHAT THEY HAVE
COMMUNICATED TO US.
PUT AT THE END OF THE DAY AS YOU
KNOW, ACTIONS SPEECH LOUDER THAN
WORDS.
WE HAVE TO WORK OUR WAY THROUGH
THAT, FROM OUR PERSPECTIVE MAKE
SURE THAT OUR AIRMEN, OUR
TEAMMATES ON THE GROUND, OUR
SOLDIERS AND OUR PARTNERS ARE IN
A POSITION TO CONTINUE THAT
FIGHT AGAINST ISIS.
>> Shepard: OUR UNDERSTANDING OF
THINGS IS THAT WE'RE BOMBING
MORE TARGETS IN SYRIA, ISIS
RELATED, THAN IN THE PAST.
IS THAT BECAUSE THERE ARE MORE
TARGETS OR IS IT SOMETHING ELSE?
>> WELL I THINK IT'S COMBINATION
OF WHAT WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO DO TO
DEVELOP TARGETS.
OVER TIME, AS WE'VE SPENT TIME
USING OUR INTELLIGENCE,
SURVEILLANCE, AND RECON SAYS
ASSETS WE HAVE A BETTER
UNDERSTANDING OF THE
ENVIRONMENT.
THE SECOND BIG PIECE IS THE
SIRRIAL DEMOCRATIC FORCES ARE ON
THE MOVE.
IN RA" A, THE GREAT SUCCESS,
ALONG WITH THE MIDDLE EUPHRATES
RIVER VALLEY THAT, DRIVES
ACTIVITY.
>> Shepard: SYRIAN DEMOCRATIC
FORCES.
THAT'S THE ONES WE FIGHT WITH
AGAINST THE GOVERNMENT?
>> YES, SIR.
THAT'S IT.
>> Shepard: ARE THEY GETTING
BETTER AT WHAT THEY DO, AND ARE
THEY -- CAN THEY STAND UP?
>> WOULD I TELL YOU, THEIR
ASYMMETRIC ADVANTAGE IS AIR
POWER.
WE PROVIDE THE CAPABILITY TO
REMAIN ON THE OFFENSIVE.
AND PUT THEMSELVES IN A POSITION
TO SUCCEED.
THAT'S WHAT YOU SEE TODAY.
>> Shepard: THE CRITICS SAID
REPEATEDLY THAT OUR AIR FORCE IS
WORKING FOR IRAN IN THAT MATTER.
>> I WOULD DENY THAT.
>> Shepard: I WOULDN'T SUGGEST
ANYTHING ELSE.
BUT WE CAN SEE WHERE THEY'RE
COMING FROM.
>> I UNDERSTAND THAT.
BUT I THINK IMPORTANTLY, WE ARE
SUPPORTING THE SBS IN THEIR
OPERATION, THE SYRIAN DEMOCRATIC
FORCES, TO DELIBERATE THESE
CITIES IN SYRIA.
THEY HAVE PROVEN EFFECTIVE AT
DOING THAT AND WE'RE SUPPORTING
THEM EVERY DAY AND CONTINUE TO
DO THAT.
>> Shepard: WHEN YOU TAKE OUT
ISIS WHAT HAPPENS THEN?
>> WHAT WE HAVE TO DO IS
FACILITATE THE ABILITY FOR THE
POLITICAL PROCESS TO TAKE PLACE
SO THAT GOVERNANCE CAN OCCUR
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND ALLOW THE
PEOPLE TO GET BACK TO WORK.
THE KIDS TO GET BACK TO SCHOOL.
>> Shepard: THAT SOUNDS GREAT.
FROM EVERYTHING WE SEE IT LOOKS
LIKE SYRIA IS PRETTY WELL
DESTROYED.
>> THAT WILL BE A HEAVY LIFT.
BUT THE SYRIAN DEMOCRATIC FORCES
COMBINED WITH OUR PRECISION
TARGETING HAVE DONE AS MUCH AS
THEY CAN DO TO ENSURE THAT
INFRASTRUCTURE REMAINS STANDING.
GO AHEAD.
>> Shepard: I DIDN'T MEAN TO
INTERRUPT.
I WAS GOING TO ASK YOU ABOUT
IRAQ.
IT APPEARS THAT THERE'S VERY
GOOD PROGRESS THERE.
IN FACT, FROM A LOT OF READING
OVER THE LAST 24 HOURS, IT
SOUNDS LIKE THEY'RE COLLAPSING
MORE QUICKLY THAN HAD BEEN
ANTICIPATED.
>> I COMPLETELY AGREE WITH YOU.
THE WORD I'M USING IS MOMENTUM.
THEY HAVE MOMENTUM.
IT'S BECAUSE THE IRAQIE SKRT
FORCES PROVE THEMSELVES TO BE
VERY CONFIDENT IN WHAT THEY'RE
DOING.
THE SECURITY FORCES.
THEY LEMPLED THE SKILLS THAT WE
BRING TO SUPPORT THEM.
WHAT YOU SEE IS A GROWING
NATIONALISM INSIDE OF IRAQ.
THEY OWN THIS.
THE OTHER PIECE THAT I WOULD
THROW OUT IS WHAT I'VE SEEN ON
THE GROUND IS THEY'VE BEEN
COURAGEOUS, THEY'VE BEEN HEROIC
IN THE FIGHT AND THE PEOPLE
APPRECIATE WHAT THEY'VE DONE TO
LIBERATE THEM.
>> Shepard: I HAVEN'T HEARD THAT
BEFORE, THE OTHER TIMES THAT WE
HAVE ENGAGED OURSELVES WITH
GENERALS OF YOUR ILK HAVE SAID
OTHER THINGS.
THE POINT IS, AS YOU'VE WATCHED
THIS MATURE OVER TIME THE
IRAQIES HAVE BEEN UP FRONT.
WE ARE IN AN ADVISE AND ASSIST
OPERATION.
THAT'S HOW WE SUPPORT THEM.
WHEN YOU COMBINE THE OPERATIONS
WITH THE ASYMMETRIC FORCES OF
THEIR POWER, THEY ARE SUCCEEDING
AND BRINGING IN FORCES THAT
MAINTAIN THE STABILITY TO ALLOW
GOVERNANCE TO OCCUR.
>> Shepard: YOU TALK ABOUT IRAQI
NATIONALISM, THAT'S HARD TO
FIND.
THE KURDS MORE THAN EVER WANT
OUT.
THEY'RE ORGANIZING AND THEY
DON'T WANT TO BE IRAQ, THEY WANT
TO BE KURDISTAN.
>> THE KURDISH REFERENDUM IS
SOMETHING WE'RE ALL CONCERNED
ABOUT.
POLITICALLY THAT WILL BE
SOMETHING THAT WILL NEED TO BE
SORTED OUT.
FROM THE MILITARY PERSPECTIVE WE
WANT TO ENSURE THEIR STABILITY
AND SECURITY THAT FACILITATES
POLITICAL PROGRESS TO BE MADE.
>> Shepard: WILL THERE COME A
TIME WHEN THEY CAN TAKE CARE OF
THEMSELVES?
HOW WILL WE KNOW WHEN THAT IS?
>> THAT'S THE PLAN.
BUT WE HAVE TO ALLOW THAT TO
TAKE TIME.
THAT'S GOING TO TAKE A WHILE FOR
THAT TO OCCUR.
WE WILL LAY OUT METRICS AS WE
MOVE INTO THE NEXT PHASE OF THE
CAMPAIGN, THAT WOULD LAY OUT
WHAT WOULD BE THE APPROPRIATE
TIME FOR US STARTING TO HAND
OVER THE RESPONSIBILITIES
PARTICULARLY FROM A SUPPORT ON
THE MILITARY SIDE PERSPECTIVE.
>> Shepard: WE READ REPORTS THAT
THE AIR FORCE DOESN'T HAVE
ENOUGH BOMBS.
AND WHATEVER YOU READ SOMETHING
LIKE THAT AS A JOURNALIST, YOU
THINK THEY WANT MORE FUNDING.
WE ALSO WANT MORE FUNDING,
EVERYONE DOES.
OR DO WE HAVE A CRITICAL BOMB
SHORTAGE?
>> I'VE BEEN MANAGING THIS FROM
THE DAY I TOOK COMMAND 15 MONTHS
AGO.
IT'S AN ISSUE WE HAVE WORKED
THROUGH CLOSELY WITH THE AIR
FORCE AND DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE.
AND THERE'S A CONCERN OUT THERE,
CLEARLY, AS YOU LOOK AT THE
BUDGET AND ABILITY TO FORECAST
LONG TERM, CONTINUING
RESOLUTIONS DO NOT HELP OUR
ABILITY TO PROCURE THE WEAPONS
IN THE LONG TERM THAT WE NEED.
>> Shepard: YOU NEED A BUDGET.
>> THAT WOULD BE HELP.
>> Shepard: HOW IS WASHINGTON
RESPONDING?
>> I THINK THEY HEAR US BUT I'LL
COME BACK TO THERE IS TALKING
BUT WE NEED TO SEE ACTION TO GET
THE BUDGET RESOLVED.
>> Shepard: DOES THE LACK OF A
BUDGET, JUST CONTINUING
RESOLUTION, MAKE YOUR JOB AND
THE MILITARY JOB HARDER?
>> IT CONCERNS ME.
THE ANSWER TO THAT IN THE SHORT
TERM IS YES.
IT DRIVES US TO HAVE CHALLENGES
THAT WE WOULD BE ABLE TO NOT
HAVE TO DEAL WITH HAD THERE BEEN
A BUDGET.
>> Shepard: YOU HAVE HAD
PROBLEMS WITH SOME PLANES.
THERE'S BEEN TALK OF TAKING THEM
OUT OF THE THE MIX.
WHERE IS THAT?
>> I THINK AT THIS POINT, WE'VE
BEEN ABLE TO WORK THROUGH THAT
AND AS YOU LOOK AT THE RESOURCES
THAT I HAVE, AVAILABLE TO ME,
I'VE BEEN ABLE TO EXECUTE THE
FIGHT EVERY DAY WITHOUT HAVING
TO WORRY ABOUT THOSE ASSETS
BEING PULLED BACK.
>> Shepard: WHEN YOU LOOK AT
WHAT'S GOING ON WITH NORTH
KOREA, THE BACK AND FORTH
RHETORICALLY AND OTHERWISE,
WHAT'S YOURS GREATEST CONCERN?
>> WELL, I THINK AT THE END OF
THE DAY ALL OF US ARE CONCERNED
ABOUT THIS ESCALATING INTO
SOMETHING THAT NO WOULD WANTS TO
HAPPEN.
THAT IS OUT OF MY AREA OF
RESPONSIBILITY.
BUT AS AN AMERICAN, THERE IS A
CONCERN THERE THAT I THINK WE
ALL SHOULD BE WARY OF.
AND HOPE THAT WE CAN FIND A
DIPLOMATIC SOLUTION TO THIS
PROBLEM.
>> Shepard: WHAT KEEPS YOU UP AT
NIGHT?
>> WELL AT THE END OF THE DAY IN
MY AREA OF RESPONSIBILITY, IS
THE POSSIBILITY OF A STRATEGIC
MISCALCULATION.
WE ARE NOT THERE TO FIGHT
RUSSIA.
WE ARE NOT THERE TO FIGHT SYRIA.
OUR JOB IS TO CRUSH ISIS AND
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING EVERY
DAY.
I WORRY THAT WE PUT OUR AIRMEN,
OUR COALITION TEAM, IN A
POSITION WHERE STRATEGIC
MISCALCULATION COULD OCCUR.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE WORKING THIS
DE-CONFLICT.
>> Shepard: YOU USE THAT PHONE
WITH THE RUSSIANS?
>> I DON'T USE INTEREST BUT MY
GUYS DO EVERY DAY.
>> WHAT HAPPENS ON THAT PHONE?
>> THE INTERESTING PART IS I
HAVE SOME YOUNG AIRMEN THAT WE
BRING IN, THAT ARE INTERPRETERS.
SO WE'LL TALK, THEY'LL RESPOND
AND OUR INTERPRETERS, THESE
YOUNG AIRMEN, TRANSLATE FOR US.
IT'S INCREDIBLE THE CONTEXT THAT
THEY GIVE US WITH THEIR
UNDERSTANDING OF THE RUSSIAN
LAYMEN.
IT'S FASCINATING, IT'S BEEN A
LESSON IN LEADERSHIP AS WE WORK
THROUGH NEGOTIATING WITH THE
RUSSIANS ON HOW WE DE-CONFLICT
OUR OPERATIONS.
>> Sandra: IS IT WE'RE HERE,
DON'T GO THERE, OR IS IT BIGGER
PICTURE THAN THAT.
>> ALL OF THE ABOVE.
EVERY DAY, YOU KNOW, IF WE SEE
SOMETHING WE DON'T LIKE WE CALL
THEM.
WE WILL TRY TO MANAGE THE
DE-CONFLICTION, BUT IT'S A
CONVERSATION THAT ENSURES WE'RE
BEING CRYSTAL CLEAR WHAT WE DO.
GENERALLY WE COULD WHAT WE NEED
TO DO TO PROTECT OUR FORCE.
>> Shepard: YOU COMING IN HOT ON
THAT PHONE?
>> OCCASIONALLY, YES, SIR.
>> Shepard: GENERAL, I CAN'T
THANK YOU ENOUGH.
ALL OF THE BEST AND THANK YOU
FOR WHAT YOU DO FOR OUR NATION.
>> IT'S A PLEASURE TO BE HERE.
WHAT YOUR YOUNG AMERICANS ARE
DOING AND WHAT THE COALITION
TEAM IS DOING IS SOMETHING FOR
US ALL TO BE PROUD OF.
>> Shepard: HERE, HERE.
THANK YOU, TO ALL OF YOUR
COLLEAGUES, APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP
DOWNPLAYING THAT RUSSIANS BOUGHT
ARIZONA DURING THE ELECTION.
WHAT ABOUT THE TOTALLY BIASED
AND DISHONEST MEDIA COVERAGE IN
FAVOR OF COOKED HILLARY?
FACEBOOK REVEALED THIS WEEK THAT
FAKE ACCOUNTS BASED IN RUSSIA
BOUGHT AROUND 3,000 POLITICAL
ADS OVER THE PAST COUPLE OF
YEARS.
THE COMPANY ANNOUNCED YESTERDAY
IT WILL TURN OVER THE ADS TO
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATORS
LOOKING INTO RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN THE ELECTION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS ACCUSED
DEMOCRATS OF USING RUSSIA AS AN
EXCUSE FOR LOSING THE ELECTION.
THE KREMLIN SPOKESMAN DECLINED
THAT MOSCOW PLACED ADS ON
FACEBOOK AT ALL AND CLAIMED HIS
PEOPLE DON'T EVEN KNOW HOW TO DO
THAT.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THE
BACKSTORY.
TELL US MORE ABOUT WHAT FACEBOOK
IS DOING.
>> DURING THE FACEBOOK LIVE
STREAM, THE CEO SAID HE CARES
DEEPLY ABOUT THE DEMOCRATIC
PROCESS AND PROTECTING ITS
INTEGRITY.
BECAUSE OF THAT HE IS
IMPLEMENTING A SERIES OF STEPS
THE COMPANY PLANS ON TAKING TO
ENSURE THAT THIS DOES NOT HAPPEN
AGAIN.
HE ALSO GAVE AN EXPLANATION FOR
HOW IT MIGHT HAVE HAPPENED IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
WATCH.
>> MOST ADS ARE BOUGHT
PROGRAMMATICALLY THROUGH THE
APPS WITHOUT AN ADVERTISER
SPEAKING TO SOME ONE AT
FACEBOOK.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
EVEN WITHOUT OUR EMPLOYEES
DIRECTLY INVOLVED IN THE SALES,
WE CAN DO BETTER.
BY DOING BETTER HE MEANS
FACEBOOK WILL IMPROVE ITS REVIEW
PROCESS, ADD MORE PEOPLE TO THE
SECURITY TEAM, AND START
PARTNERING WITH ELECTION
COMMISSIONS THAT WILL ALSO
INCREASE TRANSPARENCY, REQUIRING
POLITICAL ADVERTISERS TO DECLARE
EXACTLY WHO IS PAYING FOR THE
AD.
ZUCKER BERG SAID THERE WILL
ALWAYS BE BAD PEOPLE IN THE
WORLD AND ENDING ALL
INTERFERENCE ISN'T REALISTIC.
SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT DO THESE ADS
LOOK LIKE?
WHAT WERE THEY ADVERTISING?
>> FACE BECOME SAID THE ADS IN
QUESTION CAME FROM ABOUT 470
PHONY ACCOUNTS.
THE ADS THEMSELVES DID NOT
REFERENCE THE U.S. ELECTIONS,
VOTING, OR ANY CANDIDATE IN
PARTICULAR.
INSTEAD THEY SPREAD, QUOTE,
DIVISIVE SOCIAL AND POLITICAL
MESSAGES AYOS THE IDEOLOGICAL
SPECTRUM, TOPICS OF LGBT
MATTERS, TO RACE, TO GUN RIGHTS.
FACEBOOK SAID THEY TARGETED
CERTAIN PARTS OF THE COUNTRY AND
MAJORITY RAN IN 2015.
AND NOW, THE SENATE INTEL
COMMITTEE WANTS FACEBOOK AND
OTHER SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANIES TO
TESTIFY ABOUT RUSSIA'S
INVOLVEMENT IN THE 2016
ELECTION.
YOU CAN BET THESE ADS WILL
CERTAINLY BE A PART OF THAT
HEARING.
THE COMMITTEE CHAIR SAYS HE'S
VERY INTERESTED IN JUST HOW MUCH
SOCIAL MEDIA COMPANIES ACTUALLY
KNOW ABOUT RUSSIAN ACTIVITIES ON
THEIR VARIOUS SITES.
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER
LIVE, THANK YOU.
VIOLENCE BREAKING OUT IN
NEW YORK CITY DURING A SPEECH BY
THE TURKISH PRESIDENT.
PEOPLE IN THE CROWD PUNCHING A
PROTESTER.
THIS IS NOT THE FIRST TIME THE
TURKISH PRESIDENT SUPPORTERS
HAVE GOTTEN VIOLENT IN THE
UNITED STATES.
THAT'S NEXT.
I count on my
Dell Small Business Advisor
for tech advice.
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪
NEW YORK CITY DURING A SPEECH BY
>> Shepard: OTHER PEOPLE IN THE
CROWD PUNCHES HIM.
WITH THE TURKISH.
.
THAT WAS IN NEW YORK CITY AND
THERE'S VIDEO.
[CROWD NOISE]
STATE DEPARTMENT OFFICIALS SAY
IT DID NOT APPEAR THAT TURKISH
OFFICIALS INVOLVED IN THE FIGHT.
BUT THEY HAVE GOTTEN VIOLENT
WITH PROTESTERS BEFORE.
LAURA ENGLE IS LIVE WITH US.
>> HEY, SHEP.
IT'S NOT ALWAYS CALM WHEN THE
TURKISH PRESIDENT VISITS THE
U.S.
WE KNOW.
AND THAT WAS NO DIFFERENT LAST
NIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT IS IN NEW YORK FOR
THE UNITED NATIONS GENERAL
ASSEMBLY, IN THE MIDDLE OF HILLS
ADDRESS TO THE TURKISH AMERICAN
NATIONAL STEERING COMMITTEE AT A
HOTEL WHEN PROTESTERS ATTEMPTED
TO SHOUT HIM DOWN.
THAT IS WHEN THINGS GOT OUT OF
CONTROL.
VERY QUICKLY.
THE TURKISH PRESIDENT'S ADDRESS
TURNED INTO THIS MELEE WHEN THE
PROTESTER SCREAMED WHY THE
YOU'RE A TERRORIST GET OUT OF MY
COUNTRY."
NOW, AS THE SECURITY DETAIL
START READ MOVING PROTESTERS,
AUDIENCE MEMBERS BEGAN PUNCHING
AND SLAPPING THE PROTESTER AS
SECURITY MOVED IN AND STARTED
TAKING PEOPLE OUT FROM THE ROOM.
A SECURITY ALSO REPORTEDLY
KICKED OUT ONE PERSON WHO
ALLEGEDLY ASSAULTED A PROTESTER.
THOSE INVOLVED SAY THEIR ACTIONS
ARE IN RESPONSE TO VIOLENCE.
TURKEY HAS INFLIKTED ON KURDISH
MUSLIMS INSIDE TURKEY.
PROTESTS HAVE BEEN BREAKING OUT
DURING HIS APPEARANCE AROUND THE
WORLD.
THIS IS HIS VISIT TO ECUADOR IN
THE LAST YEAR.
THEN IN MAY, MEMBERS OF HIS
SECURITY TEAM WERE CAUGHT ON
VIDEO ATTACKING A GROUP OF
PEACEFUL PROTESTERS OUTSIDE THE
TURKISH AMBASSADORS RESIDENCE IN
WASHINGTON.
NINE PEOPLE WERE HOSPITALIZED.
THIS SCENE PROMPTED SECURITY
OFFICIALS WERE INDICTED.
AS FOR YESTERDAY NOBODY WAS
INJURED, IN ARRESTS.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
THE TURKISH PRESIDENT HAS JAILED
THOUSANDS OF POLITICAL OPPONENTS
AND 120 JOURNALISTS, WHO HE
CALLS TERRORISTS.
YOUR WORLD WITH NEIL CAVUTO
BEGINS AFTER THIS.
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
Every year we take
a girl's trip.
Remember Nashville?
Kimchi BBQ.
Amazing Honky Tonk??
I can't believe
you got us tickets.
I did.
I didn't pay for anything.
You never do.
Send me what I owe.
I've got it.
I mean, You did find money
to buy those boots.
Are you serious?
Is that why
you don't like them?
Those boots could
make a unicorn cry.
Yeah, tears of joy.
The Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
The fast, secure and
simple way to send money.
with some big news
about type 2 diabetes.
You have type 2 diabetes,
right?
Yes.
So let me ask
you this...
How does diabetes
affect your heart?
It doesn't, does it?
Actually, it does.
Type 2 diabetes
can make you twice
as likely to die
from a cardiovascular event,
like a heart attack or stroke.
And with heart disease,
your risk is even higher.
You didn't know that.
No.
Yeah.
But, wait, there's good news
for adults who have
type 2 diabetes
and heart disease.
JARDIANCE is the only
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit.
JARDIANCE is proven to both
significantly reduce
the chance of dying from a
cardiovascular event
in adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease
and lower your A1C.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration.
This may cause you
to feel dizzy,
faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious
side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting,
stomach pain, tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
Stop taking JARDIANCE
and call your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic reaction
include rash, swelling,
and difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects
are sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE
with a sulfonylurea
or insulin may cause
low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So now that you know all that,
what do you think?
That it's time to think
about JARDIANCE.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE.
And get to the heart
of what matters.
♪
It's not just a car,
it's your daily treat.
♪
Go ahead, spoil yourself.
The ES and ES Hybrid.
Experience amazing.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT, THIS GUY
COULD CAUSE A PROBLEM.
WE'RE NOW GETTING WORD THAT KIM
JONG-UN, DESPITE THE FACT WE ARE
CLOSING THE CIRCLE AND THE
CHINESE ARE CLOSING ALL
FINANCIAL LENDING TO HIM, HE
FIRED BACK WITH A PROMISE TO
TEST HYDROGEN BOMB OVER THE
PACIFIC OCEAN.
THAT SHOULD GO WELL.
THE LAST TIME ANY COUNTRY ON
THIS PLANET ATTEMPTED TO DO
ANYTHING IN THE ATMOSPHERE WITH
SUCH WEAPONRY WAS 1980.
THAT WAS THEN.
WHAT THE HECK IS GOING TO HAPPEN
NOW?
KEVIN CORK TRAVELLING WITH THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES,
IN SOMERSET, NEW JERSEY.
HOLY TOLEDO.
>> WELL, LET ME TELL YOU, THIS
IS ONE OF THOSE CIRCUMSTANCES