SUNDAY.
>> Harris: I'M HARRIS
FAULKNER, AN AMERICAN HAS
COME OUT SHADOWS TO TELL
THE WORLD HE IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR LEAKING THAT GOVERNMENT
IS SNOOPING ON US.
ADMITTED LEAKER IS ON
RECORD ON AND ON CAMERA
INTERVIEW TELLING THE
GUARDIAN NEWSPAPER HE WAS
PART OF FED'S POWERFUL GRAB
OF CELLPHONE RECORDS FROM
EVERYDAY AMERICAN CITIZENS,
HIS NAME IS EDWARD SNOWDEN
AND HE TALKS ABOUT THE
SNOOPING IN DETAIL.
HE WAS ALARMED AT THE RATE
IT'S GROWN AND EVENTUALLY
HARM EVEN INNOCENT
AMERICANS.
THE FOLLOWING VIDEOS IS
COURTESY OF THE GUARDIAN.
GLENN GREENWALD AND ANOTHER
REPORTER.
>> EVEN IF YOU DO AREN'T
DOING ANYTHING WRONG YOU
ARE BEING WATCHED AND THE
STORAGE CAP BILLS INCREASE
OVER YEAR BY ORDER OF THE
MAGNITUDE TO GETTING TO THE
POINT YOU DON'T HAVE TO
HAVE DONE ANYTHING WRONG.
YOU SIMPLY TO HAVE
EVENTUALLY FALL UNDER
SUSPICION EVEN BY A WRONG
CALL.
THEN THEY CAN USE THE
SYSTEM TO GO BACK IN TIME
AND SCRUTINIZE EVERY
DECISION YOU EVER MADE.
>> Harris: HE SAYS HE HAS
BEEN THE SOURCE FOR THE
"WASHINGTON POST" AND
GUARDIAN NEWSPAPERS AS THE
HEADLINES HAVE BEEN FILLING
UP WITH JARRING DETAILS
ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT MINING
PHONE LORDS FOR INFORMATION
ABOUT CUSTOMERS.
WHITE HOUSE HAS VOWED WHO
IS LEAKING CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION ABOUT THE
PROGRAM WHICH IS RUN BY THE
NSA.
SNOWDEN IS A CONTRACTOR
WORK FOR THE NSA.
AND KATHERINE, IN JUST LAST
FEW MINUTES THE STORY HAS
BEEN UNFOLDING AS BREAKING
DETAILS.
WE GOT A STATEMENT FROM THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY,
WHAT DOES IT SAY.
>> Reporter: SHORT TIME AGO
WE RECEIVED A STATEMENT
FROM THE OFFICER OF
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE, ADDING THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY IS
THE DAMAGE HAS BEEN DONE BY
RECENT DISCLOSURES.
ANYBODY THAT HAS A SECURITY
CLEARANCE HAS TO PROTECT
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION AND
ABIDE BY THE LAW.
A REPORT HAS BEEN FILED AND
THAT IS FIRST STEP TOWARD A
CRIMINAL PROSECUTION.
>> Harris: WHAT MORE ARE WE
LEARNING ABOUT SNOWDEN?
>> IT COMES FROM AN
INTERVIEW POSTED BY THE
GUARDIAN NEWSPAPER,
INFORMATION MUST BE SEEN IN
THAT CON PARTICULARS.
IN THE INTERVIEW HE CLAIMS
TO BE A FORMER SYSTEMS
ADMINISTRATOR THAT ALLOWED
HIM A BROAD EITHER VIEW OF
THE NSA PROGRAM.
>> WHEN YOU ARE IN POSITION
OF PRIVILEGED ACCESS LIKE
OUR SYSTEM'S ADMINISTRATOR
FOR THE INTELLIGENCE
AGENCIES YOU ARE EXPOSED TO
A LOT MORE INFORMATION ON A
BROADER SCALE AN THE
AVERAGE EMPLOYEE.
BECAUSE OF THAT YOU SEE
THINGS THAT MAYBE
DISTURBING, BUT OVER THE
COURSE OF A NORMAL PERSON'S
CAREER YOU WOULD SEE ONE OR
TWO INSTANCES.
WHEN YOU SEE EVERYTHING,
YOU SEE THEM ON A MORE
FREQUENT BASIS.
YOU RECOGNIZE SOME OF THESE
THINGS ARE ABUSES.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO
THE BRITISH NEWSPAPER THE
FINAL PHASE THREE WEEKS AGO
AND NSA OFFICE IN HAWAII HE
COPIED DOCUMENTS AND WENT
TO HIS SUPERVISOR SAID HE
NEEDED TIME OFF BECAUSE HE
SUFFERED SEIZURES AND GOT
ON THE PLANE TO HONG KONG.
>> Harris: WHAT IS THE
RESPONSE TONIGHT?
>> FORMER EMPLOYEES SAY THE
FLIGHT TO HONG KONG APPEARS
TO BE AN EFFORT TO PUT HIM
AS FAR OUT OF REACH OF THE
U.S. GOVERNMENT BECAUSE HE
UNDERSTANDS THE DEPTH OF
THE LEAK.
HE ADDRESSES THE LIKELIHOOD
HE WILL BE EXTRADITED OR
HANDED OVER FOR TRIAL AT
SOME POINT.
>> I COULD BE RENDERED BY
THE C.I.A.
PEOPLE COME AFTER ME OR
THIRD PARTY PARTNERS OF
THEM WORK CLOSELY WITH
NUMBER OF OTHER NATIONS.
>> Reporter: HE FEARS FOR
HIS FAMILY ADDING THAT SOME
STILL WORK IN THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT.
HE WAS BROUGHT UP IN
ELIZABETH CITY, NORTH
CAROLINA AND LATER MOVED TO
MARYLAND BUT DESPITE AN
ACADEMIC RECORD HE WAS
GREAT WITH W COMPUTERS AND
FOUND HIS WAYS INTO JOBS AT
C.I.A. AND NSA.
>> Harris: WHAT IS THE
RESPONSE TONIGHT?
DO WE KNOW FOR HIS FORMER
EMPLOYER?
>> WHEN CONTACT BY FOX
NEWS, THERE IS NO COMMENT
BY THE C.I.A.
BRITISH NEWSPAPER REPORTS
THAT HE WORKED VARIOUS
CONTRACTORS AT NSA.
LATE TODAY ONE OF THE
LARGEST SECURITY FIRMS
CONFIRMING ON ITS WEBSITE
THAT SNOWDEN IS THE
EMPLOYEE.
THEY CAN CONFIRM HE HAS
BEEN AN EMPLOYEE LESS THAN
THREE MONTHS ASSIGNED TO A
TEAM IN HAWAII.
HE HAS CLAIMED TO HAVE
LEAKED INFORMATION IS
SHOCKING.
FORMER OFFICIALS TELL FOX
NEWS THAT IT'S NOT UNCOMMON
FOR CONTRACTORS TO HAVE THE
KIND OF SECURITY CLEARANCE,
BUT APPARENTLY GAVE HIM
ACCESS TO THESE DOCUMENTS
AND NSA AND CONGRESS HAS
SUPPORTED OUTSOURCING AS
PART OF RATIONALE TO REDUCE
COSTS.
>> Harris: IT WILL BE
INTERESTING TO SEE WHAT
ARGUMENTS SHAPE UP.
SOME WOULD SAY WE WOULDN'T
KNOW WHAT WAS GOING ON WITH
THE NSA SNOOPING IF IT
HADN'T BEEN FOR SOMEONE
LIKE THIS.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS
MOVING AHEAD.
>> WE'LL TAKE A CLOSER LOOK
AT EXACTLY WHO IS EDWARD
SNOWDEN.
ACCORDING TO THE GUARDIAN,
HE WAS BORN IN NORTH
CAROLINA BEFORE HIS FAMILY
MOVED TO MARYLAND.
NOT FAR FROM THE NSA
HEADQUARTERS.
IN 2003 HE ENLISTED IN THE
ARMY BUT WAS DISCHARGED
AFTER BREAKING BOTH LEGS IN
A TRAINING ACCIDENT.
HE FIRST WORK AS AN NS A A
AS SECURITY GUARD BEFORE
TRANSFERRING TO C.I.A..
THAT JOB GAVE HIM CLEARANCE
TO ACCESS A WIDE ARRAY OF
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
THEN IN 2009 HE TOOK HIS
FIRST LEGALLY NSA JOB
WORKING AT FACILITIES IN
JAPAN AND HAWAII.
BEFORE THIS NEWS BROKE,
THIS WEEKEND WE HAD BEEN
TELLING YOU THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION HAD PROMISED
A FULL INVESTIGATION INTO
THE NSA LEAKS.
NOW THAT SOMEONE HAS COME
FORWARD, WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
ANDREW NAPOLITANO JOINS US
BY PHONE.
JUDGE ARE YOU WITH US?
>> YES.
>> Harris: FIRST EDWARD
SNOWDEN ARE BLOWING THE
WHISTLE BUT SOME PEOPLE
WON'T CALL HIM A
WHISTLEBLOWER.
LET'S START THERE?
>> FOR HIM TO QUALIFY AS A
WHISTLEBLOWER HE WOULD NEED
TO DEMONSTRATE, HIS
BEHAVIOR ON WHICH HE BLEW A
WHISTLE WAS ILLEGAL OR
UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
ON ITS FACE I SAY THAT
BECAUSE I HAVEN'T SEEN THE
DOCUMENTS THAT THE
GOVERNMENT FILED WITH THE
COURT.
ON ITS FACE THEY FILE A
PROCEDURE.
AND COURT AUTHORIZED THIS
WARRANT OF THIS NATURE.
CONTRARY TO THAT IS THE
FOURTH AMENDMENT TO THE
CONSTITUTION WHICH WAS
WRITTEN TO PROHIBIT THE
TYPE OF FISHING EXPEDITION
THAT THE GOVERNMENT ENGAGED
IN HERE.
YOU HAVE A STATUTE STATE
SUPPORTS THE GOVERNMENT AND
LANGUAGE IN THE
CONSTITUTION ON ITS FACE
SUPPORTS THE WHISTLEBLOWER.
>> Harris: MEANWHILE, HE IS
IN HONG KONG.
WHAT HE SAID IN PART OF
THAT TELEVISION INTERVIEW
IS THAT HE IS HOPING THAT A
COUNTRY RECOGNIZES FREE
SPEECH WILL GIVE HIM
ASYLUM?
>> GOOD LORD, NOT IN CHINA.
CHINA IS ONE OF THE MOST
REPRESSIVE REGIMES ON THE
PLANET.
HONG KONG IS A UNIQUE PART
OF CHINA, BUT HONG KONG IS
GOVERNED BY CHINA AND THE
CHINA AND UNITED STATES
HAVE AN EXTRADITION TREAT.
BECAUSE IT'S CHINA IT WILL
BE A POLITICAL AS WELL AS
LEGAL -- IF THE CHINESE
GOVERNMENT WANTS TO
COOPERATE WITH THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION, SNOWDEN
WILL BE ON PLANE U.S.
MARSHALS BEFORE THE END OF
THE WEEK.
IF THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT
DOES NOT WANT TO COOPERATE
HE MAY HAVE FOUND A SAFE
HAVEN.
>> Harris: WHAT ABOUT
CHARGES AGAINST HIM?
>> VERY SERIOUS.
GOVERNMENT WILL CLAIM HE
ENGAGED IN, THAT
HE AIDED THE ENEMY AND
SERIOUSLY HARMED GOVERNMENT
PROGRAMS INTENDED TO
PROTECT THE NATIONAL
SECURITY OF THE COUNTRY.
HIS DEFENSE WILL BE THE
GOVERNMENT BEHAVED
UNCONSTITUTIONALLY AND
PEOPLE HAVE A RIGHT TO KNOW
ABOUT IT.
JURY WILL HAVE TO DECIDE ON
WHO THEY BELIEVE.
>> Harris: YOU ARE TALKING
ABOUT SOMETHING MORE
POLITICAL THAN LEGAL AS TO
WHETHER HE WILL BE
EXTRADITED.
WE KNOW THE PRESIDENT AND
LEADER OF CHINA WERE HERE.
HE SINCE LEFT.
YOU HAVE TO WONDER IF THAT
WOULD PLAY ANY PART TO
EXTRADITE THIS PERSON?
>> YES.
THE PRESIDENT OF CHINA AND
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES IN THE PAST 24 HOURS,
THE COUNTRIES HAVE IMPROVED
RELATIONSHIP FOR THE
WEEKEND THEY SPENT
TOGETHER.
PRESIDENT OF CHINA IS NOT
THE MOST POWERFUL PERSON.
MOST POWERFUL IS THE HEAD
OF THE CHINESE COMMUNIST
PARTY BUT THEY ARE
COLLEAGUES AND COLLABORATE
ON THEIR DECISION TO SEND
MR. SNOWDEN IS HERE.
ONE HAS TO WONDER IF THE
PRESIDENT OF CHINA KNEW IT
WAS COMING WHEN HE WAS
TALKING TO PRESIDENT OBAMA
THE LAST FEW DAYS.
>> Harris: A LOT OF
AMERICANS HAVE BEEN SAYING
ON BLOGS AND ONLINE TONIGHT
AS THE STORY IS BREAKING
THEY FEEL SNOWDEN IS
SOMEWHAT OF HERO THAT FEDS
HAVE BEEN MONITORING US.
IS THAT A DEFENSE POSSIBLY
FOR HIM?
>> THE FACT THAT PEOPLE
THINK HE IS A HERO WOULD
NOT BE A DEFENSE.
WHAT WOULD BE A DEFENSE
WOULD BE IF HIS LAWYERS CAN
DEMONSTRATE THAT THE
GOVERNMENT'S BEHAVIOR WAS
SO WIDE OFF THE MARK OF
AMERICAN VALUES AND SO
CONTRARY TO THE
CONSTITUTION THAT HE TOOK
AN OATH TO UPHOLD AND
BARACK OBAMA TOOK A VOTE TO
UPHOLD AND CLAPPER TOOK THE
OATH TO UPHOLD THAT HE
SHOULD BE ORDERED
PROTECTION AS WHISTLEBLOWER.
>> Harris: BEFORE I LET YOU
GO, I WANT YOU TO HEAR THAT
INTERVIEW.
BECAUSE YOU ARE ON A
CELLPHONE.
SO YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO SEE
IT.
IT REALLY SPEAKS TO THE
ISSUE HOW MUCH RISK THAT
SNOWDEN ACKNOWLEDGES THAT
HE HAS TAKEN?
>> THAT IS A FEAR I LIVE
UNDER FOR THE REST OF MY
LIFE.
YOU CAN'T COME FORWARD
AGAINST THE WORLD'S MOST
POWERFUL INTELLIGENCE
AGENCIES AND BE COMPLETELY
FLEE FROM RISK BECAUSE THEY
ARE SUCH POWERFUL
ADVERSARIES.
NO ONE CAN OPPOSE THEM.
>> Harris: ONE POINT HE
FEARS FOR HIS LIFE?
>> HE COULD BE ARRESTED AT
ANY TIME A PLACE HE LEAST
EXPECTS.
>> Harris: JUDGE NAPOLITANO,
WE APPRECIATE YOUR
PERSPECTIVE ON THIS TH.
THANK YOU.
>> MORE ON THIS STORY
STRAIGHT AHEAD INCLUDING
LAWMAKER REACTION AND WE
HAVE OTHER NEWS FOR YOU
TONIGHT AS WELL INCLUDING
THIS LITTLE GIRL'S FIGHT TO
LIVE.
RIGHT NOW, SARA BREATHING
WITH THE HELP OF A
VENTILATOR.
SHE WAS INTUBATED LAST
NIGHT.
TEN YEARS OLD, SHE NEEDS A
LUNG TRANSPLANT.
TOMORROW A MEETING THAT
COULD CHANGE EVERYTHING FOR
HER AND SIMILAR CHILDREN.
>> TWO LAWMAKERS ONE
INFLUENTIAL COMMITTEE AND
LOTS OF SNIPING OVER THE
IRS TARGETING CONSERVATIVE
GROUPS.
IN MINUTES NEW REACTION TO
CLAIMS THE ORDER TO GO
AFTER CERTAIN AMERICANS
CAME FROM WASHINGTON.
[ Male Announcer ]
RUNNING OUT OF STEAM?
♪
NOW YOU CAN GIVE YOURSELF
A KICK IN THE REAR!
V8 V-FUSION PLUS ENERGY.
NATURAL ENERGY FROM GREEN TEA
PLUS FRUITS AND VEGGIES.
NEED A LITTLE KICK?
OOH!
COULD'VE HAD A V8.
IN THE JUICE AISLE.
[ whirring ]
[ dog barks ]
I WANT TO TREAT MO DOGS.
♪
OUR BUSINESS
NEEDS MORE CASES.
[ Male Announcer ] WHERE DO YOU
WANT TO TAKE YOUR BUSINESS?
I NEED HELP SELLING ART.
[ Male Announcer ]
FROM BROADBAND TO WEB HOSTING
TO MOBILE APPS, SMALL BUSINESS
SOLUTIONS FROM AT&T
HAVE THE SECURITY YOU NEED
TO GET YOU THERE.
CALL US.
WE CAN SHOW YOU
HOW AT&T SOLUTIONS
CAN HELP YOU DO WHAT YOU DO...
EVEN BETTER.
♪
THERE YOU GO.
COME ON, LET'S PLAY!
[ Male Announcer ]
THERE'S AN EASIER WAY
TO PROTECT YOUR DOG
FROM DANGEROUS PARASITES.
GOOD BOY.
FETCH!
TRIFEXIS IS THE MONTHLY,
BEEF-FLAVORED TABLET
THAT PREVENTS
HEARTWORM DISEASE,
KILLS FLEAS
AND PREVENTS INFESTATIONS,
AND TREATS HOOK-, ROUND-,
AND WHIPWORM INFECTIONS.
TREATMENT WITH
FEWER THAN 3 MONTHLY DOSES
AFTER EXPOSURE TO MOSQUITOES
MAY NOT PROVIDE
COMPLETE HRTWORM PREVENTION.
THE MOST COMMON
ADVERSE REACTIONS
WERE VOMITING, ITCHING
AND LETHARGY.
SERIOUS ADVERSE REACTIONS
HAVE BEEN REPORTED
FOLLOWING
CONCOMITANT EXTRA-LABEL USE
OF IVERMECTIN
WITH SPINOSAD ALONE,
ONE OF THE COMPONENTS
OF TRIFEXIS.
PRIOR TO ADMINISTRATION,
DOGS SHOULD BE TESTED
FOR EXISTING
HEARTWORM INFECTION.
TO LEARN MORE ABOUT TRIFEXIS,
TALK TO YOUR VETERINARIAN,
CALL 888-545-5973
OR VISIT TRIFEXIS.COM.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO
GO TO EXTREMES
TO PROTECT YOUR DOG
FROM PARASITES.
YOU NEED TRIFEXIS.
VISIT OUR WEBSITE
TO SAVE UP TO $25.
AVAILABLE BY PRESCRIPTION
FROM YOUR VETERINARIAN.
>>.
>> Harris: IF YOU ARE JUST
JOINING US MAN THAT CLAIMS
TO BE THE SOURCE FOR
SECURITY, HE SAYS HE WAS
SOURCE FOR THE "WASHINGTON
POST" AND GUARDIAN WHEN IT
COMES TO FINDING OUT ABOUT
THE TOP SECRET SPYING
PROGRAMS THROUGH THE
NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY
THROUGH THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT.
NOW MORE ON THAT ISSUE.
LAWMAKERS ON BOTH SIDES OF
THE ISSUE ARE DISAGREEING
ABOUT WHETHER THIS WAS A
MASSIVE GOVERNMENT
OVERREACH.
STEVE CENTANNI HAS THAT
PART OF THE STORY.
WHAT REACTION ARE WE
GETTING FROM CAPITOL HILL?
>> WE HAVE A STATEMENT FROM
NEW YORK CONGRESSMAN PETER
KING WHO SAYS IF HE DID
LEAK THE INFORMATION EDWARD
SNOWDEN, HE SHOULD BE
PROSECUTED AND EXTRADITED
BACK TO THE U.S.
UNITED STATES MUST MAKE IT
CLEAR THAT NO COUNTRY
SHOULD BE GRANT GO THIS
INDIVIDUAL ASYLUM.
THIS IS MATTER OF
EXTRAORDINARY CONSEQUENCES
TO AMERICAN INTELLIGENCE.
KING IS MEMBER OF THE HOUSE
HOMELAND SECURITY
COMMITTEE.
>> Harris: WHAT ABOUT OTHER
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS, WHAT
ARE THEY SAYING ABOUT THE
SECRET SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAM?
>> THERE ARE TWO CAMPS.
MANY THINK THE GOVERNMENT
OVERSTEPPED ITS BOUNDS AND
THEY INCLUDE BOTH
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS.
>> WE'RE NOT TALKING ABOUT
GOING AFTER A TERRORIST.
I'M ALL FOR THAT.
GET A WARRANT, GO AFTER A
TERRORIST OR A MURDERER OR
RAPIST BUT DON'T TROLL
THROUGH A BILLION PHONE
RECORDS EVERY DAY.
IT INVADES OUR PRIVACY.
>> TERRORISM REMAINS A REAL
THREAT BUT I THINK WE HAVE
THE BILL OF RIGHTS.
FOURTH AMENDMENT PREVENTS
UNLAWFUL SEARCH AND
SEIZURES OUGHT TO BE
IMPORTANT TO US AND THERE
HAS TO BE A BALANCE HERE.
>> Reporter: SUPPORTERS OF
THE PROGRAMS BELIEVE
TERRORIST ATTACKS HAVE BEEN
PREVENTED BY THE
SURVEILLANCE AND THAT THE
GOVERNMENT HAS NOT
OVERSTEPPED ITS BOUNDS.
THEY INCLUDE LAWMAKERS FROM
BOTH SIDES OF THE AISLE.
>> WE FACE A VERY REAL
ASYMMETRIC THREAT IN
INTERNATIONAL TERRORISM AND
GREATEST LINE AGAINST THAT
IS INTELLIGENCE GATHERING
CAPABILITIES.
SO WE HAVE TO MAINTAIN
THAT.
IT'S A VERY DELICATE
BALANCE.
>> THESE PROGRAMS ARE
WITHIN THE LAW.
THE BUSINESS RECORDS
SECTION IS REVIEWED BY A
FEDERAL JUDGE EVERY 90
DAYS.
>> Reporter: ENTIRE HOUSE
OF REPRESENTATIVES WILL BE
OFFERED A BRIEFING ON
SURVEILLANCE ON TUESDAY.
>> Harris: STEVE, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
AND MENTIONING CONGRESSMAN
PETER KING, HE'LL JOINING
US LIVE AT THE BOTTOM OF
THE HOUR.
FIRST AN UPDATE ON THE
TEN-YEAR-OLD GIRL WHO NEEDS
A LUNG TRANSPLANT IN ORDER
TO LIVE.
HER STORY ONE THAT WE ARE
FOLLOWING CLOSELY.
DOCTORS GIVING HER A
BREATHING TUBE.
UPDATE FROM SARA'S MOTHER
IN HOW SHE IS DOING.
BEFORE TORI WAS TAKING HER KIDS
TO LUNCH IN HER NEW
VOLKSWAG...
BEFORE HER PASSAT HAD PASSED
OVER 30 DIFFERENT
INSPECTION TESTS...
AND BEFORE SEVERAL THOUSAND
TENNESSEANS
DISCOVERED NEW JOBS
ON VOLKSWAGEN DRIVE,
A CFO AND A BANKER
MET FOR LUNCH.
TOGETHER, WE WORKED WITH A TEAM
THAT HELPED FINANCE
CONSTRUCTION
OF THE WORLD'S FIRST
LEED PLATINUM
AUTO MANUFACTURING PLANT.
THAT'S THE IMPACT
OF GLOBAL CONNECTIONS.
THAT'S BANK OF AMERICA.
I'M VERY EXCITED ABOUT MAKING
THE SHRIMP AND LOBSTER POT PIE.
WE'VE NEVER COOKED
ANYTHING LIKE THIS BEFORE.
[ Male Announcer ]
INTRODUCING RED LOBSTER'S
SEASIDE MIMATCH.
COMBINE ANY 2
OF 7 EXCITING CHOICES
ON ONE PLATE FOR JUST $12.99!
LIKE NEW CHEDDAR BAY
SHRIMP LOBSTER POT PIE,
AND NEW PARMESAN CRUNCH SHRIMP.
PLUS SALAD AND UNLIMITED
CHEDDABAY BISCUITS.
COMBINE ANY 2 FOR JUST $12.99.
[ Stewart ]
FOR THE SEASIDE MIX & MATCH,
WE'RE REALLY MIXING IT UP.
THERE'S JUST SO MANY
COMBINATIONS TO TRY.
I'M STEWART HARRINGTON,
RED LOBSTER LINE COOK,
AND I SEA FOOD DIFFERENTLY.
♪
>> Harris: A TEN-YEAR-OLD
GIRL WHO NEEDS A LUNG
TRANSPLANT TO LIVE IS
SEDATED, NO LONGER
BREATHING ON HER OWN.
VENTILATOR DOING THE WOKE
FOR HER.
WE HAVE BEEN FOLLOWING
SARA'S STORY, SHE IS IN THE
END STAGES OF CYSTIC
FIBROSIS.
HER FAMILY FOUGHT TO GET
HER ON THE ADULT ORGAN
DONOR LIST.
A JUDGE ISSUED A TEMPORARY
ORDER TO SUSPEND THE AGE
RESTRICTION AND THAT MEANT
SHE COULD GET ADULT SET OF
LUNGS IF DOCTORS CAN FIND A
DONOR.
NOW SHE IS WAITING.
HER FAMILY SAYS SHE IS
RESTING.
ALL THIS AS MAJOR MEETING
IS SET TOMORROW OVER OUR
NATION'S TRANSPLANT POLICY.
LAURA, HOW IS SHE DOING
TONIGHT?
>> AS YOU MENTIONED SHE IS
SEDATING.
WE HAVE BEEN FOLLOWING
UPDATES AND THE MOTHER IS
KEEPING SUPPORTERS UP TO
DATE ON FACEBOOK PAGE.
LATEST ONE SAYING WHILE HER
DAUGHTER IS UNDER HEAVY
SEDATION, HER NUMBERS ARE
TRENDING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
SHE EXPRESSED HER AGONY AS
SHE WAS INTUBATED.
LAST NIGHT WAS HORRIBLE AND
TERRIFYING.
IN SOME RESPECTS SARA'S
BODY A HAS IMPROVED BUT
OTHER ASPECTS IT'S BEEN A
DISASTER.
WE ARE PRAYING FOR GREATER
STABILITY.
PETER JOHNSON, JR. SPENT
TIME WITH THE FAMILY AND
HOW THEY ARE ABLE TO STAY
STRONG.
>> AS PARENT YOU DO IT.
YOU ADAPT.
YOU BECOME WHATEVER YOU
NEED TO BECOME FOR YOUR
CHILDREN.
>> LOOKING FORWARD, THE DAD
SAYS IF SHE GETS THE
TRANSPLANT HE HOPES THEY
WILL HAVE IN NORMALCY.
>> Harris: WHAT ABOUT THE
MEETING TOMORROW?
>> THE BIG MEETING TOMORROW,
EXECUTIVE COMMITTEE OF
ORGAN PROCUREMENT
TRANSPLANT MEETING IN
RESPONSE TO KATHLEEN
SEBELIUS'S REQUEST.
THEY REVIEW CURRENT
GUIDELINES ON PEDIATRIC
LUNG TRANSPLANTS INCLUDING
WAITING TIME, ORGAN IS ON
OFFERS AND INFANT
MORTALITY.
IF CHANGES NEED TO BE MADE
THE COMMITTEE WOULD BE ABLE
TO APROVE AN INTERIM POLICY
AND CHANGE PLANS FOR
IMPLEMENTATION.
>> Harris: WE'VE ALREADY
SEEN ONE OTHER CHILD'S
FAMILY PUT THEIR SON WHO IS
UNDER THE AGE OF 12 ON THE
LIST FOR ADULT DONOR, AS
WELL.
>> WILL THERE ARE MANY
PEOPLE WAITING.
>> Harris: LAURA, GOOD TO
SEE YOU TONIGHT.
>>> NEWS IS BREAKING ON
NATIONAL SECURITY LEAKS.
THIS MAN CLAIMS TO BE THE
SOURCE FOR THE "WASHINGTON
POST" AND THIS IS ACCORDING
TO THE GUARDIAN NEWSPAPER
IN BRITAIN REPORTING.
HE WAS A CONTRACTOR WORKING
FOR THE NSA.
HE IS SPEAKING OUT.
NOW SO ARE LAWMAKERS ON
CAPITOL HILL.
NEXT, LIVE, WE'LL TALK WITH
PETER KING OF NEW YORK WHAT
HE THINKS SHOULD HAPPEN TO
THE MAN EDWARD SNOWDEN.
>> WHILE THEY MAY BE
INTENDING SOMEBODY FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT OR SOMEONE THEY
SUSPECT OF TERRORISM THEY
ARE COLLECTING YOUR
COMMUNICATIONS TO DO SO.
CKAGE PP
FROM THE UNITED STATES
POSTAL SERVICE
A SMALL DESIGN FIRM CAN SHIP
LIKE A BIG BUSINESS.
JUST GO ONLINE TO PAY, PRINT
AND HAVE YOUR PACKAGES
PICKED UP FOR FREE.
WE'LL DO THE REST.
♪
I DON'WITHOUT GOINGCISIONS
TO ANGIE'S LIST FIRST.
YOU'LL FIND REVIEWS
ON HOME REPAIR TO HEALTHCARE
WRITTEN BY PEOPLE
JUST LIKE YOU.
WITH ANGIE'S LIST,
I KNOW WHO TO CALL,
AND I KNOW THE RESULTS
WILL BE FANTASTIC.
ANGIE'S LIST --
REVIEWS YOU CAN TRUST.
WHEN HE SAID "EVERYONE
GETS HEALTH INSURANCE"?
BUT NOW CONGRESS SAYS
7 MILLION AMERICANS
WILL LOSE
THEIR HEALTH INSURANCE
AND YOUR INSURANCE RATES
COULD INCREASE BY 200%.
SOME HEALTH PLANS
EVEN GET HIT WITH A 40% TAX
AND OVER $700 BILLION
IN MEDICARE CUTS.
SO NOW WE'RE REALLY SAD.
BUT YOU CAN BE HAPPY AGAIN
BY GETTING
THE OBAMACARE SURVIVAL GUIDE.
IT'S ALREADY
A #1 NEW YORK TIMES BESTSELLER
AND OVER 500,000 AMERICANS
HAVE GOTTEN A COPY.
NEWSMAX SAYS IT'S "THE BEST
GUIDE" TO THE NEW LAW.
YOU CAN GET YOUR COPY
AT OBAMACARE911.COM.
IT GIVES YOU THE TIPS,
STRATEGIES AND LOOPHOLES
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
GET YOUR COPY OF
THE OBAMACARE SURVIVAL GUIDE
AT STORES EVERYWHERE
FOR $19.95.
OR GET THE INTERNET ONLY OFFER
OF JUST $4.95 AND SAVE $15.
GO TO OBAMACARE911.COM
TO CLAIM YOUR COPY NOW.
>>.
>> Harris: THIS THE FOX
REPORT.
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR TIME FOR
TOP OF THE NEWS CAN
BREAKING NEWS TONIGHT AS
BRITAIN'S GUARDIAN
NEWSPAPER NAMES THEIR
SOURCE FOR REVEALING
DETAILS ON MULTIPLE TOP
SECRET SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAMS THAT SNOOPED ON
AMERICAN CITIZENS' PHONE
RECORDS AND EVEN INTERNET
TRAFFIC.
ADMITTED LEAKER A
29-YEAR-OLD FORMER C.I.A.
EMPLOYEE AND CONTRACT
WORKER.
WE'RE TOLD HE IS IN HONG
KONG RIGHT NOW AND HOPES TO
SEEK ASYLUM.
EDWARD SNOWDEN OPENED WHY
HE LEAKED SUCH SENSITIVE
INFORMATION ABOUT OUR
GOVERNMENT.
>> I'M JUST ANOTHER GUY WHO
SITS DAY TO DAY IN THE
OFFICE AND GOES -- THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT IS NOT OUR
PLACE TO DECIDE.
THE PUBLIC NEEDS TO DECIDE
WHETHER THE POLICIES ARE
RIGHT OR WRONG.
>> Harris: PETER KING SAYS
IF HE DID LEAK THE NSA DATA
AS HE CLAIMS, THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT MUST PROSECUTE
HIM TO THE FULL EXTENT OF
THE LAW.
CONGRESSMAN KING JOINS US
BY PHONE?
>> HOW ARE YOU?
>> Harris: I'M WELL.
WHY MUST THE GOVERNMENT
PROSECUTE SNOWDEN?
>> THIS IS AN APPALLING
CRIME.
HE IS PUTTING AMERICAN
LIVES AT RISK.
HE IS JEOPARDIZING AMERICAN
INTELLIGENCE, HE HAS
SOURCES AND METHODS TO BE
KNOWN TO THE ENEMY.
THIS IS TREMENDOUS BOOST TO
AL-QAEDA.
IT WILL BE MORE DIFFICULT
TO GET PRIVATE COMPANIES TO
WORK WITH US.
HE TIPPED OFF AL-QAEDA A
WHAT WE'RE DOING.
NO INDIVIDUAL CAN DO THIS.
HE HAS VIOLATED HIS OATH.
HE HAS DISCLOSED TOP SECRET
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
WE CANNOT ALLOW TO GO
UNPUNISHED.
>> Harris: WHEN YOU HEAR
PEOPLE THAT IS SOMEWHAT OF
HERO, MAYBE ACCUSING THE
GOVERNMENT OF OVERREACH.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THOSE
PEOPLE?
>> I WOULD SAY, THEY ARE
TOTALLY MISGUIDED.
IT'S NOT UP HIMHAM WHAT IS
MORAL OR WHAT IS NOT.
IF HE WAS AWARE OF ANY
ILLEGALITY.
GO TO THE CONGRESS OR
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
GO TO INSPECTOR GENUINE THE
C.I.A. OR NSA.
FOR HIM TO DECIDE ON HIS
OWN TO COME FORWARD THIS IS
ABSOLUTE DISGRACE.
PEOPLE THAT TRY TO MAKE HIM
HERO IT'S BEYOND ME.
DO THEY REALIZE THE
CONSEQUENCES OF WHAT THEY
ARE DOING HERE?
IF THIS PROGRAM HAD NOT
BEEN IN PLACE BACK IN 2009,
THEY WOULD HAVE KILLED
HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS OF
PEOPLE IN NEW YORK IN A
SUBWAY SYSTEM THE PLAN HE
HAD TO SET OFF EXPLOSIVES
IN THE SUBWAY SYSTEM.
IF I WANT TO COMPARE THE
HERO A PERSON WHO STOPPED
THAT ATTACK AS HE WAS
TRYING TO CARRY OUT THE
UNITED STATES.
ESPECIALLY THERE IS NO
EVIDENCE OF ILLEGALITY.
THIS IS CLEARLY IN
COMPLIANCE WITH THE LAW.
IF THERE ARE SPECIFIC
OBJECTIONS, THERE IS A FISA
COURT THAT MONITORS THIS ON
A REGULAR BASIS.
THERE IS JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
AND ESPECIALLY THE FISA
COURT.
THIS IS UNDER COURT
SUPERVISION.
>> Harris: ONE OF THE
THINGS YOU WILL SEE WHEN
YOU WATCH THE TAPE, HE SAYS
HE KNEW THE RISKS BUT HE
FELT THE ABUSES HE WAS
WITNESSING AND POSSIBLY
TAKING A PART IN IN TERMS
OF MONITORING PHONE RECORDS
AND SNOOPING, HE THOUGHT
THOSE WERE SO EGREGIOUS AND
PEOPLE MIGHT NOT LISTEN?
>> WHO IS HE TO DECIDE TO
PUT AMERICAN LIVES AT RISK?
IF HE FELT THAT STRONGLY
ABOUT IT, GO TO THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL.
GO TO THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT.
THE FACT IS YOU CANNOT HAVE
EVERY EMPLOYEE IN THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT DECIDING
WHAT LAW THEY ARE GOING TO
FOLLOW AND WHAT LAW THEY
ARE NOT GOING TO FOLLOW.
AND WHY IS HE IN HONG KONG?
TO BE IN CHINA IS THE
LEADING COUNTRY IN THE
WORLD AS FAR AS HACKING
INTO US AND TRYING TO STEAL
OUR SECRETS.
IN MANY WAYS, INTELLIGENCE
WISE IS AN ENEMY COUNTRY.
WHY IS HE THERE SUBJECTING
HIMSELF TO CHINESE
INTELLIGENCE RAISES
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIM.
HE HAS DISCLOSED AN
INCREDIBLE ASSISTANCE TO
AL-QAEDA.
AL-QAEDA IS TRYING TO KILL
AMERICANS.
THAT IS THE MESSAGE WE HAVE
TO KEEP IN MIND.
HIS ACTIONS AND VERY LIKELY
COULD RESULT IN THE DEATHS
OF INNOCENT AMERICAN LIVES.
>> Harris: YOU MENTION WHY
DID HE GO TO HONG KONG.
WE KNOW HE WAS WITH A
JOURNALIST WITH THE
GUARDIAN.
WE DON'T KNOW IF THERE WAS
AN AGREEMENT TO GO WITH
THAT JOURNALIST.
WE DO KNOW THIS IS A
SPECIAL ADMINISTRATIVE
TERRITORY OF CHINA AND
THERE IS EXTRADITION
BETWEEN HONG KONG AND THE
UNITED STATES.
WE WILL SEE WHAT HAPPENS
GOING FORTH.
QUICKLY, FORECASTING INTO
TOMORROW, WHAT DO YOU
PERCEIVE WILL BE THE NEXT
FEW STEPS?
>> I WOULD HOPE THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT BEGIN
PROSECUTION AS SOON AS
POSSIBLE.
I HOPE OUR GOVERNMENT WILL
REACH OUT CHINA.
WE HAVE A TREATY WITH HONG
KONG BUT CHINA IS CALLING
THE SHOTS HERE.
HE HAS PUT US THE THE MERCY
OF CHINA WE HAVE TO USE ALL
THE LEVERAGE AND POWER WE
HAVE AND GET HIM BACK TO
THE UNITED STATES AS
QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
>> Harris: THE LEADER OF
CHINA WAS VISITING WITH OUR
PRESIDENT.
WE'LL SEE IF THAT PLAYS A
ROLE.
PETER KING, THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US.
>>> JOINING ME NOW
LIEUTENANT COLONEL TONY
SCHAFFER THE AUTHOR "THE
LAST LINE."
GOOD TO SEE YOU, COLONEL
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
WHEN YOU AND I WERE GETTING
THIS ISSUE EARLIER THE NEWS
HADN'T BROKEN.
SNOWDEN SAYS HE COULD
MONITOR ANYBODY.
LET'S WATCH.
>> I SITTING AT MY DESK HAD
THE AUTHORITY TO WIRETAP
ANYONE, FROM YOU TO YOUR
ACCOUNTANT TO EVEN THE
PRESIDENT.
>> Harris: I WANT TO GET
YOUR RESPONSE THAT HE
LEAKED CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION ABOUT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT'S
PROGRAM?
>> HE DID.
I AGREE WITH REPRESENTATIVE
KING THAT THIS IS TRAGIC.
THERE IS NO WAY THIS GUY
SHOULD GO ABOUT HIS
BUSINESS WITHOUT
CONSEQUENCES.
I DON'T AGREE WITH PETER
KING THAT JAMES
SENSENBRENNER THAT WROTE
THE PATRIOT ACT I DIDN'T
WANT IT TO BE USED THAT
WAY.
I WOULD PUT THEM ON TRACK
FOR THE JUDICIAL WATCH TO
HELP WHISTLEBLOWERS AND
KING SAID HE SHOULD BE
DISCLOSING THIS TO CERTAIN
MEMBERS OF CAPITOL HILL.
I HAD TO WHISTLE BLOW ON
ABLE DANGER REGARDING DATA
MINING PRE-9/11 SPEAKER OF
THE HOUSE DENNIS HASTERT
ASKED ME TO TESTIFY.
WE HAD OPEN AND CLOSED
HEARINGS.
THAT IS THE PROPER WAY TO
DO IT.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR MR. SNOWDEN
HAS CAUSED FAR MORE
PROBLEMS FOR HIMSELF AND HE
HAS DEFECTED.
HE IS IN ENEMY TERRITORY
RIGHT NOW.
CHINA IS NOT AN ADVERSARY
OF OURS BUT THERE IS
HACKING GOING ON.
WHATEVER INFORMATION IS IN
HIS HEAD IS NOW WITH
CHINESE IN SOME FORM.
>> Harris: WOW!
I HAD NOT HEARD ANYBODY PUT
IT EXACTLY LIKE THAT.
YOU HEARD CONGRESSMAN KING
TALKING A LITTLE BIT BUT
YOU DUG IN DEEPER.
THAT HAS A LOT OF IMPACT?
>> IT DOES.
HE HAS GIVEN THE CHINESE A
HUGE THING IN THE GAME.
HE IS A FORMER C.I.A.
OPERATIVE.
I'M TELLING YOU WITH HIS
ATTITUDE AND WAY HE HAS
TALKED ABOUT AND HE IS
DISGRUNTLED AND I SUSPECT
HE HAS INFORMATION FROM
C.I.A.
RIGHT NOW, NSA IS PANICKING
BECAUSE EVERYTHING HE TOOK
THEY KNOW.
ALL THE STUFF DOWNLOADED
THEY ARE GOING BACK AND
CHECKING AND RIGHT NOW,
REPRESENTATIVE KING, NOW
THE TIME TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
HE HAS DONE BECAUSE WE TO
DO DAMAGE CONTROL.
>> Harris: I DO WANT TO
TELL OUR VIEWERS, YOU AND I
WERE GOING TO TALK ABOUT
THE PROGRAM THAT THE NSA
WAS RUNNING AS BEING AN
OVERREACH IN YOUR OPINION?
>> RIGHT.
>> Harris: AS I UNDERSTAND
IT YOU WOULD HAVE SUPPORTED
EDWARD SNOWDEN HAD HE COME
TO YOU?
>> AS MUCH AS I THINK
SENATOR PAUL AND OTHERS
HAVE LEGITIMATE CRITICISM
AND THEY ARE GOING TO HAVE
DEBATE.
WE SHOULD ALWAYS HAVE A
DEBATE IN THE OPEN.
WITH THAT SAID,
REPRESENTATIVE KING IS
CORRECT, HE HAD NO RIGHT TO
UNILATERALLY ON HIS OWN
WITHOUT CHECKING OR ANYBODY
WITHIN HIS CHAIN OF COMMAND
TO GO PUBLIC ON THIS.
I WENT PUBLIC AFTER
CONGRESS GAVE ME PERMISSION
TO DO THAT.
THIS GUY DID NOT WANTED TO
DO DAMAGE.
HE HAS DONE DAMAGE AND DO
MORE BY THE FACT HE IS
SITTING IN CHINA.
>> YOU WATCH HIM IN THIS
INTERVIEW BY THE GUARDIAN
NEWSPAPER, IT'S JUST WHY HE
FELT THE DESPERATE NEED TO
COME FORWARD.
ONE OF THE THINGS, THE WAY
THEY WERE COLLECTING
INFORMATION ON EVERYDAY
AMERICANS, HE THOUGHT IT
COULD POSSIBLY FALL INTO
THE WRONG HANDS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ANYBODY IN THE POSITION
WITH ACCESS TECHNICAL
CAPABILITIES I HAD COULD
SUCK OUT SECRETS AND PASS
THEM ON THE OPEN MARKET TO
RUSSIA.
THEY HAVE AN OPEN DOOR AS
WE DO.
>> Harris: IS HE RIGHT?
>> NO, HE IS NOT.
HE IS ESSENTIALLY, LIKE A
MASTER AD MAN OVERSEEING
I.T. -- I THINK HE HAS
ACCESS TO BRIEFINGS.
WE NEVER LEFT BRIEFING ON A
NETWORK OR BECAUSE OF THIS
POTENTIAL HAPPENING.
HE IS NOT INVOLVED.
HE IS NOT A MEMBER OF THE
TEAM RUNNING THESE THINGS.
SO AS MUCH AS I THINK THERE
MAY BE VALID CONCERNS
REGARDING THE ASKING OF THE
PROGRAM, HE IS AN ADMIN
GUY.
HE HAD PROBLEMS IN THE ARMY,
HE BROKE HIS LEGS.
DIDN'T LIKE THE C.I.A. WAS
RUNNING OPERATIONS.
UNFORTUNATELY I THINK THE
GUY IS DISGRUNTLED.
IT'S NOT ABOUT FIXING
THINGS.
IT'S ABOUT TRYING TO POKE
SOMEONE IN THE EYE WITHOUT
ANY INTEREST TO FIX WHAT
WAS BROKEN.
>> Harris: WHEN GREENWALD
AND THE JOURNALIST FROM THE
GUARDIAN WHO BROUGHT THIS
INFORMATION TO THE WORLD
CLAIM TO HAVE MORE, IF
THERE ARE OTHER AMERICANS
IN EDWARD NODEN'S SHOES AND
THEY HAVE INFORMATION TO
GET OUT THERE, WHAT WOULD
YOU TELL THEM AT THIS
POINT?
>> I ADMIRE WHAT GLENN N
DOES.
IN THIS CASE HE IS WRONG.
UNFORTUNATELY HE DOES HAVE
MORE INFORMATION.
I DON'T THINK HE HAS OTHER
SOURCES, I THINK SNOWDEN
HAS GIVEN FAR MORE TO HIM
THAN HE IS WILLING TO
ADMIT.
THIS IS GOING TO BE
TREASURE TROVE OF STUFF
COMING OUT THE COMING
WEEKS.
NSA IS PRETTY MUCH AWARE
WHAT HE TOOK WITH HIM.
>> Harris: I TELL YOU, WHEN
YOU AND I WERE GOING TO
TALK SPEAK ABOUT OVERREACH
BUT YOU HAVE GIVEN US THE
WORD THAT THIS MAN HAS
DEFECTED TO CHINA.
THAT IS POWERFUL TERM.
LIEUTENANT COLONEL TONY
SCHAFFER, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
WE'RE GOING TO MOVE ON
STORY DOMESTICALLY.
NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN A
CALIFORNIA SHOOTING RAMPAGE
WE FOLLOWED LAST WEEK,
NAMING THE MAN THEY SAY
WENT ON THE ATTACK AND
RELEASED THIS PICTURE OF
HIM TODAY.
>> WE'RE LEARNING A FIFTH
VICTIM HAS DIED FROM WOUNDS
SUFFERED IN THAT RAMPAGE.
NEW REACTION FROM STUDENTS
ON THAT CAMPUS IN SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA AND WHAT WE NOW
KNOW ABOUT THAT SUSPECT.
MINE WAS EARNED
IN DJIBOUTI, AFRICA. 2004.
VIETNAM IN 1972.
[ All ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]
USAA AUTO INSURANCE
IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN
FROM GENERATION TO GENERATION.
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE MILITARY MEMBERS,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY,
GET AN AUTO INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA. WE KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS TO SERVE.
lets you connect
up to 25 devices
on one easy to manage plan.
That means your smartphone,
her Blackberry,
his laptop,
Mark's smartphone
But I'm still
on vacation.
Still on the plan.
Nice!
The intern
gets a tablet?
Everyone's devices.
His, hers-- Oh, sorry.
All easier to manage
on The Share Everything Plan
for Small Business.
Connecting more
so you can do more.
That's Powerful.
Verizon.
Get the Blackberry Z10
for $199.99.
SINCE I'VE BEEN USING
CREST PRO-HEALTH,
I'VE NOTICED A HUGE IMPROVEMENT.
[ Male Announcer ]
GO PRO
FOR A CLEAN THAT'S
UP TO FOUR TIMES BETTER,
TRY THESE CREST PRO-HEALTH
PRODUCTS TOGETHER.
THE TOOTHPASTE
IS REALLY AWESOME.
IT CLEANS A LOT.
[ Male Announcer ]
CREST PRO-HEALTH
PROTECTS NOT JUST SOME,
BUT ALL THESE AREAS
DENTISTS CHECK MOST.
THIS IS GONNA
BE A VERY GOOD CHECKUP.
I FEEL IT.
[ Male Announcer ]
GO PRO WITH CREST PRO-HEALTH.
MY DENTIST WAS SO PROUD
OF MY TEETH TODAY.
AFTER USING CREST PRO-HEALTH
FOR A FEW WEEKS,
I JUST FEEL BRIGHTER,
FRESHER, CLEANER.
♪
>> Harris: NEW DEVELOPMENTS
IN THE CALIFORNIA SHOOTING
RAMPAGE, POLICE HAVE NAMED
THE SUSPECT, WE'LL HAVE
MORE ON THAT IN JUST A
MOMENT.
THIS IS WE'RE LEARNING A
WOMAN CRITICALLY INJURED IN
THAT ATTACK HAS NOW DIED
BRINGING THE VICTIMS TO
FIVE.
THE PRESIDENT OF SANTA
MONICA COLLEGE SAYING A
STUDENT THAT REGISTERED TO
ATTEND CLASSES THIS MORNING,
SHE WAS 26 YEARS OLD.
AND WAS A PASSENGER IN THE
SUV THAT CRASHED INTO A
WALL AFTER THE DRIVER WAS
SHOT IN THE TORSO.
THAT DRIVER DIED AT THE
SCENE.
HIS NAME WAS CARLOS FRANCO,
HER DAD.
>> HE HAD BEEN A LONG TIME
EMPLOYEE OF THE COLLEGE AND
WAS VERY WELL-LIKED AND
RESPECTED.
>> THE POLICE CHIEF SAYING
THE FATHER WORKED ON CAMPUS
AS A GROUND KEEPER.
AS WE ARE GETTING NEW
INFORMATION ABOUT THE
SUSPECTED GUNMAN.
DOMINIC IS LIVE IN SANTA
MONICA TONIGHT.
TELL US WHAT YOU KNOW.
>> THE GUNMAN WAS
23-YEAR-OLD JOHN Z. THEY
WERE TRYING TO GET A HOLD
OF HER MOTHER IN LEBANON.
HE KILLED HIS FATHER AND
ALSO BROTHER.
THEY WERE IN THE HOUSE THAT
CAUGHT FIRE.
THEY HAD A RUN-IN WITH HIM
BACK IN 2006.
AT THE TIME HE WAS 17 AND A
MINOR.
WE DO ALSO KNOW THAT HE WAS
A ATTENDED AS STUDENT BACK
IN 2010.
HE HAS HAD A TROUBLED
HISTORY AND POLICE HAVE
BEEN LOOKING INTO THAT AND
SEE IF THERE IS ANY
INDICATION OF WHAT CAUSED
THE KILLING SPREE THAT HE
WENT ON FRIDAY.
>> Harris: I KNOW DOZENS OF
STUDENTS ARE HAVING TO GET
PSYCHOLOGICAL COUNSELING
FOR WHAT THEY HAVE ENDURED.
>> Reporter: THAT IS RIGHT.
THERE WAS A COMMUNITY
GATHERING OVER ON THE BUNDY
CAMPUS, IT WAS GATHERING OF
STUDENTS, FACULTY AND STAFF
AND SERIES OF COUNSELORS.
70 PEOPLE TURNED UP IN
TOTAL.
IT WAS VERY EMOTIONAL
EVENT.
>> ALTOGETHER, WE ARE
ALTOGETHER, ALL HUMAN.
THAT IS THE MAIN THING.
>> IT MAKES ME FEEL BETTER
REALLY FORESHADOWS THE
COMMUNITY IS GOING TO
OVERCOME THIS EVENT.
I THINK SANTA MONICA IS A
STRONG COMMUNITY AND VERY
POSITIVE.
>> Reporter: ALSO EVENTS
WHERE THE FAMILY HAVE BEEN
DEEPLY AFFECTED BY WHAT
HAPPENED TO MARCELA AND
CARLOS.
TOMORROW THERE WILL BE A
VIGIL HELD ABOUT 6:00 P.M.
AND ALSO A GRADUATION DAY
ON TUESDAY BUT IT SEEMS ONE
EVENT THAT WILL TAKE PLACE
TOMORROW EVENING.
>> Harris: DOMINIC, THANKS
VERY MUCH.
NEW REACTION TO THE
INTERNAL REVENUE SCANDAL
WHERE AGENTS WERE TALKING
CONSERVATIVE AMERICANS JUST
BECAUSE OF THEIR POLITICAL
BELIEFS.
TODAY, MORE DEBATE OVER
WHETHER THE IRS TARGETING
ORIGINATED FROM WASHINGTON.
ANYONE HAVE OCCASIONAL
CONSTIPATION,
DIARRHEA, GAS, BLOATING?
YES!
ONE Phillips' Colon Health
PROBIOTIC CAP EACH DAY
HELPS DEFEND
AGAINST THESE DIGESTIVE ISSUES
WITH THREE STRAINS
OF GOOD BACTERIA.
LIVE THE REGULAR LIFE.
Phillips'.
>>.
>> Harris: NOW TO THE IRS
SCANDAL AND GROWING DEBATE
INSIDE A KEY HOUSE
COMMITTEE INVESTIGATING THE
ADMITTED TARGETING OF
CONSERVATIVE GROUPS.
MARYLAND CONGRESSMAN IS
FIRING BACK AT CLAIMS MADE
BY CONGRESSMAN DARRELL ISSA
OF CALIFORNIA THAT THE
ORDERS TO CONDUCT THE
UNFAIR TARGETING CAME FROM
WASHINGTON.
CONGRESSMAN CUMMINGS IS
POINTING TO CONGRESSIONAL
TRANSCRIPTS OF INTERVIEWS
WITH IRS AGENTS ON THE
GROUND SAYING ONCE THOSE
ARE RELEASED THEIR
INVESTIGATION WILL BE OVER.
PETER DOOCY WITH THE NEWS
FROM WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: EVEN THOUGH
THE DETAILS OF EACH SCANDAL
ARE DIFFERENT, REPUBLICAN
SENATOR RAND PAUL THINGS
WHEN THE IRS UNFAIRLY
TARGETS CONSERVATIVES OR
WHEN THEY MONITORED
REPORTERS.
>> IT'S THE SAME.
>> IT'S AN ABUSE OF POWER.
ONE PARTY WINS THE NEXT
YEAR THE OTHER PARTY WINS.
NOBODY WANTS TO BELIEVE
THAT YOUR PARTY LOSES YOU
ARE GOING TO BE SUBJECTED
TO HUMILIATION AND AUDIT
AND FINANCIAL RUIN BY THIS
FOUR TRILLION DOLLAR
GOVERNMENT THAT BECOMES
THIS NATIONAL AT THIS
BULLY.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING
THE TOP DEMOCRAT ELIJA
CUMMINGS RELEASED AN
INTERVIEW WITH AN IRS
EMPLOYEE AND SELF-DESCRIBED
CONSERVATIVE REPUBLICAN,
QUOTE, I DO NOT BELIEVE THE
SCREENING OF THESE CASES
HAD ANYTHING OTHER THAN TO
TO IDENTIFY ISSUES THAT
NEEDED FURTHER DEVELOPMENT.
CUMMINGS SAYS ITS OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEE DARRELL ISSA
RELEASES ALL TRANSCRIPTS
THE INVESTIGATION WILL BE
DONE.
>> BASED ON ON UPON
EVERYTHING I'VE SEEN THE
CASE IS SOLVED.
I WOULD WRAP THIS CASE UP
AND MOVE ON.
>> Reporter: CONGRESSMAN
ISSA SAYS HE STRONGLY
DISAGREES THAT IT IS SOLVED.
HE CALLS IT A RECKLESS
ASSERTION THAT SHOWS
CUMMINGS HAS NO INTEREST TO
EXPOSE THE FULL TRUTH.
>> Harris: PETER DOOCY.
THANK YOU, A WILD END TO
THE FRENCH OPEN, NOT
NECESSARILY BECAUSE OF WHAT
WAS GOING ON BETWEEN THE
PLAYERS ON THE COURT.
AND
NOT CHALKY.
TEMPORARY...
24 HOUR.
LOTS OF TABLETS...
ONE PILL.
YOU DECIDE.
PREVENT ACID
WITH PREVACID 24HR.
[ Male Announcer ]
MOVING OBJECT DETECTION.
♪
BLIND SPOT WARNING.
LANE DEPARTURE WARNING.
SAFETY, DOWN TO AN ART.
THE NISSAN ALTIMA
WITH SAFETY SHIELD
TECHNOLOGIES.
NISSAN.
INNOVATION THAT EXCITES.
♪
[ whirring ]
[ dog barks ]
I WANT TO TREAT MO DOGS.
♪
OUR BUSINESS
NEEDS MORE CASES.
[ Male Announcer ] WHERE DO YOU
WANT TO TAKE YOUR BUSINESS?
I NEED HELP SELLING ART.
[ Male Announcer ]
FROM BROADBAND TO WEB HOSTING
TO MOBILE APPS, SMALL BUSINESS
SOLUTIONS FROM AT&T
HAVE THE SECURITY YOU NEED
TO GET YOU THERE.
CALL US.
WE CAN SHOW YOU
HOW AT&T SOLUTIONS
CAN HELP YOU DO WHAT YOU DO...
EVEN BETTER.
♪
YOU WILL LOSE 3 SETS OF KEYS
4 CELL PHONES
7 SOCKS
AND 6 WEEKS OF SLEEP
BUT ONE THING YOU DON'T
WANT TO LOSE IS ANY MORE TEETH.
IF YOU WEAR A PARTIAL,
YOU ARE ALMOST TWICE AS LIKELY
TO LOSE YOUR SUPPORTING TEETH.
NEW POLIGRIP
AND POLIDENT FOR PARTIALS
'SEAL AND PROTECT'
HELPS MINIMIZE STRESS, WHICH
MAY DAMAGE SUPPORTING TEETH,
BY STABILIZING YOUR PARTIAL.
AND 'CLEAN AND PROTECT'
KILLS ODOR-CAUSING BACTERIA.
CARE FOR YOUR PARTIAL.
HELP PROTECT
YOUR NATURAL TEETH.
LITTLE THINGS ANYONE CAN DO.
IT STEALS YOUR MEMORIES.
YOUR INDEPENDENCE.
ENSURES SUPPORT,
A BREAKTHROUGH.
AND SOONER THAN YOU'D LIKE.
SOONER THAN YOU'D THINK.
YOU DIE FROM
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
WE CURE ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
EVERY LITTLE CLICK, CALL
OR DONATION ADDS UP
TO SOMETHING BIG.
>>.
>> Harris: I DON'T KNOW HOW
MUCH YOU HAVE TO BE IN
TENNIS TO ENJOY THE FINALE
FOR THE FRENCH OPEN.
A LOT OF IT WASN'T TENNIS.
>> IT GOT SCARY ACTUALLY.
PROTESTOR RAN ON TO THE
COURT WITH A MASK ON AND
BIG TORCH.
HE RUNS TOWARDS NIDAL.
IT WAS A SERIOUS SITUATION.
SECURITY TACKLED THE GUY
AND BOTH PLAYERS WERE
AFFECTED.
IT'S A REALLY INTERESTING
MOMENT IN HOW THEY WERE
GOING TO RESPOND AFTERWARDS.
JUST THE PROTESTOR WANTED
TO MAKE A SPECTACLE.
THEY STOPPED THE MATCH
ABOUT 15 MINUTES AND COME
BACK AND NADAL TAKES CARE
OF BUSINESS AND WINS HIS
EIGHTH GRAND SLAM.
>> I DIDN'T SEE THIS LIVE.
I SAW THE RETAPE OF IT.
I HEARD THE COMMOTION IN MY
LIVING ROOM AND I RAN IN.
IT WAS JUST AMAZING.
I HAD ONLY SEEN THAT CUT.
I DIDN'T SEE HOW CLOSE HE
GOT.
>> AND ITS REALLY GOOD FOR
NADAL HE IS COMING OFF A
KNEE INJURY.
THEY CALLED IT A MIRACLE.
>> Harris: N.B.A., WHO
WOULD HAVE THOUGHT SPURS
BEAT MIAMI?
>> IN MIAMI.
THEY PLAY I GAME TWO OF THE
N.B.A. FINALS.
LeBRON JAMES SAYS I
SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN SO
PASSIVE IN THE FOURTH
QUARTER.
I CAN TAKE THE BIG SHOTS.
GAME TWO, THE SPURS AND
HEATED TWO GREAT TEAMS.
>> Harris: GIVE ME SOME
BOSTON BRUINS NEWS?
>> BRUINS TAKING ON THE
CHICAGO BLACKHAWKS IN THE
FINALS.
TWO OF THE ORIGINAL SIX
WILL GO AT IT IN THE
FINALS.
>> Harris: AWESOME, THANKS
SO MUCH FOR STOPPING BY.
FOX REPORT, WE LOVE HAVING
YOU.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER AND
UPDATES ON THE MAN THAT
CLAIMS TO BE NSA LEAKER.
NOW HUCKABEE.
>> TONIGHT ON HUCKABEE.
>> I'M EXTRAORDINARY PROUD,
MY NEW NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISOR.
>> COVER-UP, BLEW UP.
>> OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
REWARDING GOOD SOLDIERS
THAT TOW THE COMPANY LINE
AND CALLING THOSE THAT CALL
OUT CORRUPTION AS ENEMIES
OF THE STATE.
>> NOT ONLY ARE THEY LOSING
THEIR JOBS AND LIVELIHOOD
AND INCOME, THEY ARE
ACTUALLY FACING JAIL TIME.
>> GOVERNMENT
WHISTLEBLOWERS ON WHY THEY
RISK EVERYTHING TO REVEAL
THE TRUTH.
>> I COULD NOT STAND BY AND
SIMPLY BE AN EYEWITNESS TO
DIVERSION OF OUR OWN
CO