DEPLOYED SPIKE STRIPS TO SLOW IT
DOWN.
COPS CATCHING UP WITH AND
ARRESTING THE SUSPECT.
THE DRIVER WAS SUSPECTED TO BE
UNDER THE INFLUENCE OF DRUGS.
HERE'S BILL HEMMER FOR SHEP.
>> IT'S 3:00 P.M. ON THE EAST
COAST.
SUSAN RICE IS TALKING AFTER SHE
REQUESTED NAMES OF TRUMP
UP IN
SURVEILLANCE.
RICE SAID SHE HAD TO ASK FOR
CERTAIN NAMES TO DO HER JOB.
DEMOCRATS SAY THIS IS TO DRAW
ATTENTION OF THE REAL ISSUE
ABOUT LINKS BETWEEN THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION AND MOSCOW.
THE FACTS AHEAD IN A MOMENTS.
IT'S TIME FOR A SHOW DOWN OVER
THE U.S. SUPREME COURT.
DEMOCRATS HAVE ENOUGH SUPPORT TO
BLOCK NEIL GORSUCH.
WILL REPUBLICANS FOLLOW-THROUGH
ON THE NUCLEAR OPTION?
AND ALSO REPUBLICANS TRYING TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE.
THAT IDEA WENT DOWN IN FLAMES
TWO WEEKS AGO.
NOW A NEW PLAN IS RISING FROM
THE ASHES OF THE SWAMP.
IN MINUTES YOU'LL HEAR FROM A
CONSERVATIVE GROUP WHOSE SUPPORT
MIGHT MAKE OR BREAK THE PLAN.
THAT'S AHEAD IN A VERY BUSY 3:00
HOUR STARTING NOW.
I'M BILL HEMMER.
GOOD DAY.
IN FOR SHEPARD SMITH, WE BEGIN
WITH THE SHOW DOWN OVER
SURVEILLANCE IN THE NATION'S
CAPITOL.
SUSAN RICE IS CALLING
ACCUSATIONS SHE MISHANDLED
INTELLIGENCE INFORMATION AND
TARGETED MEMBERS OF TRUMP TEAM
FALSE.
RICE RESPONDING AFTER FOX NEWS
AND OTHER NEWS OUTLETS SAID WHO
IS THE ONE THAT ASKED OFFICIALS
FOR THE NAMES OF TRUMP
ASSOCIATES CAUGHT UP IN
SURVEILLANCE.
THAT MEANS REVEALING THE NAMES
IN INTELLIGENCE REPORTS NOT TO
THE PUBLIC.
HERE'S SUSAN RICE.
>> THERE WERE OCCASIONS WHEN I
WOULD RECEIVE A REPORT IN WHICH
A U.S. PERSON WAS REFERRED TO.
NAME NOT PROVIDED.
JUST U.S. PERSON.
SOMETIMES IN ORDER TO UNDERSTAND
THE IMPORTANCE OF THE REPORT AND
ACCESS ITS SIGNIFICANCE, IT WAS
NECESSARY TO FIND OUT AS TO WHO
THE U.S. OFFICIAL WAS.
>> MORE IN THAT INTERVIEW IN
JUST A MOMENT.
RICE SAYING SHE AND OTHER
OFFICIALS WOULD REQUEST THE
INFORMATION ONLY TO PROTECT THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
SHE SAID SHE NEVER DID IT FOR
POLITICAL PURPOSES AND SHE NEVER
LEAKED ANY INFORMATION TO
ANYBODY, HER WORDS EARLIER
TODAY.
ALL THIS COMING AFTER HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE CHAIRMAN DEVIN
NUNES TOLD REPORTERS THAT TRUMP
TRANSITION OFFICIALS AND EVEN
THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF MAY HAVE
GOTTEN SWEPT UP IN SURVEILLANCE
OF FOREIGNERS.
WE HAVE SINCE LEARNED TWO WHITE
HOUSE OFFICIALS HELPED GET NUNES
THE INFORMATION WHICH HE SHARED
WITH THE PRESIDENT BEFORE THE
REST OF HIS OWN COMMITTEE.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE SPEAKING WITH
CHAIRMAN NUNES EARLIER TODAY.
SHE'LL HAVE MORE ON THOSE
DEVELOPMENTS LATER THIS HOUR.
AFTER MEETING WITH NUNES,
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID HE FELT
SOMEWHAT VINDICATED AFTER HE'S
UNSUBSTANTIATED CLAIMS THAT
PRESIDENT OBAMA HAD TAPPED TRUMP
TOWER.
EVEN THOUGH NUNES SAID MANY
TIMES THAT DID NOT HAPPEN, NUNES
MET WITH THE PRESIDENT, SUSAN
RICE TELLING PBS SHE HAD NO IDEA
WHAT THE CHAIRMAN WAS TALKING
ABOUT.
>> I KNOW NOTHING ABOUT THIS.
I WAS SURPRISED TO SEE REPORTS
FROM CHAIRMAN NUNES ON THAT
COUNT TODAY.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW TO WHAT
CHAIRMAN NUNES WAS REFERRING.
BUT HE SAID THAT WHATEVER HE WAS
REFERRING TO WAS ILLEGAL LAWFUL
SURVEILLANCE AND IT WAS
POTENTIALLY INCIDENTAL
COLLECTION ON ACITIZENS.
>> SO THAT INTERVIEW FROM 13
DAYS AGO IS NOW GETTING A SECOND
LOOK TODAY.
TODAY SUSAN RICE SAYS SHE DOES
NOT KNOW WHAT INFORMATION NUNES
RECEIVED AND SHE WOULD NOT GET
IN SPECIFICS ON ANY REPORTING.
I SPOKE WITH SOUTH CAROLINA
SENATOR LINDSEY GRAMMARLIER
TODAY ON AMERICA'S NEWSROOM.
HE SAID THAT HE WANTS LAWMAKERS
TO LOOK INTO RICE AND THE ENTIRE
BUSINESS OF UNMASKING.
>> AND TERMS OF POLITICAL
MANIPULATION OF NATIONAL
SECURITY INFORMATION, SUSAN RICE
IN MY VIEW HAS DONE IT IN THE
PAST.
WHETHER OR NOT SHE DID IT THIS
TIME, I DON'T KNOW.
IT'S SOMETHING CONGRESS SHOULD
LOOK INTO.
IF SHE WAS INVOLVED IN UNMASKING
TRUMP TRANSITION FIGURES, WHAT
WAS THE REASON AND WAS THERE A
POLITICAL MOTIVE.
I'D LIKE TO KNOW THAT.
WE'LL GET TO THE BOTTOM OF IT.
>> YOU HEARD THAT SENATOR GRAHAM
SAID THAT RICE HAS MANIPULATED
SECURITY INFORMATION IN THE
PAST.
AFTER THE ATTACK IN BENGHAZI,
SHE WENT ON THE SUNDAY TALK
SHOWS AND SAID BASED ON THE
INTELLIGENCE AT THAT TIME, IT
LOOKED LIKE A SPONTANEOUS
RESPONSE TO PROTESTS OVER AN
ANTI MUSLIM VIDEO AND NOT A
TERROR ATTACK.
PRESIDENT TRUMP NOW HAS REFERRED
TO THE UNMASKING AS THE REAL
STORY ON RUSSIA.
DEMOCRATS SAY IT'S A DISTRACTION
FROM THE BIGGER ISSUE THEY ARGUE
ABOUT THE INVESTIGATIONS INTO
TEAM TRUMP AND POTENTIAL
COLLUSION WITH THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT.
YOU GOT THAT?
IT'S A MOUTHFUL.
JOHN ROBERTS ON FOX'S TOP STORY
LIVE AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
GOOD DAY TO YOU.
SO WHAT ELSE DID SUSAN RICE SAID
ABOUT THIS SO-CALLED UNMASKING?
>> BILL, WHEN IS IT NOT A
MOUTHFUL TO DIGEST EVERYTHING
THAT HAPPENED HERE DAILY?
INTERESTING TO LOOK AS YOU POINT
OUT, THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN WHAT
SHE SAID TODAY COMPARED TO THE
PBS INTERVIEW ON MARCH 22 WHEN
THERE WAS AN UTTER DENIAL OF
ANYTHING THAT DEVIN NUNES WAS
TALKING ABOUT.
TODAY NO DENIAL THAT SHE'S THE
PERSON THAT ASKED FOR THE NAMES
TO BE UNMASKED IN INTELLIGENCE
REPORTS BUT THAT FIRM DENIAL
THAT ANY OF THIS WAS DONE FOR
POLITICAL PURPOSES OR SHE LEAKED
ANY ONE'S NAME.
LISTEN HERE.
>> IT'S IN THAT PROCESS AND
WITHIN THE CONTEXT OF THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN, THE TRUMP TRANSITION,
DID YOU SEEK THE NAMES OF PEOPLE
INVOLVED IN -- DID YOU UNMASK
THE NAMES OF PEOPLE INVOLVED IN
THE TRUMP TRANSITION, THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN, PEOPLE SURROUNDING THE
PRESIDENT-ELECT IN ORDER TO SPY
ON THEM?
>> ABSOLUTELY -- ABSOLUTELY NOT
FOR ANY POLITICAL PURPOSES, TO
SPY, EXPOSE, ANYTHING.
>> SO THE WHITE HOUSE SUGGESTING
THAT MOST OF THE MEDIA IS NOT
GIVING THIS THE SENSE OF
IMPORTANCE THAT THE WHITE HOUSE
THINKS IT SHOULD HAVE.
WE KNOW THAT SHE IS THE ONE,
SUSAN RICE, THAT ASKED FOR SOME
NAMES TO BE UNMASKED.
WHAT WE DON'T KNOW IS WHO LEAKED
THE NAME OF LIEUTENANT GENERAL
MICHAEL FLYNN, AN ACT THAT MAY
CONSTITUTE A SERIOUS CRIME.
>> IN RUSSIA, A REPORT OF A BACK
CHANNEL.
COMMUNICATIONS BETWEEN VLADIMIR
PUTIN AND A DONALD TRUMP DONOR.
WHAT IS THE TRUTH ON THAT?
>> IT'S HARD TO DISCERN.
THE WHITE HOUSE AND THE PERSON
INVOLVED DENIED ANY KIND OF
MEETING TO CREATE A CHANNEL
BETWEEN THE TRUMP TRANSITION AND
VLADIMIR PUTIN.
THE PERSON AT THE CENTER OF THIS
IS ERIC PRINCE, THE FOUNDER OF
BLACK WATER SECURITY
ORGANIZATION.
A BIG CHECKERED PAST PUTTING
CONTRACTORS IN IRAQ.
HE'S THE BROTHER-IN-LAW OF BETSY
DeVOS.
WE'RE TOLD BY SOURCES THAT ON
JANUARY 11th ERIC PRINCE MET
WITH A RUSSIAN ENVOY AT THE FOUR
SEASONS HOTEL.
ONE OF THE REASONS FOR THE
MEETING SAID TO PE THAT THE
UNITED ARAB EMIRATES WANTED TO
CONVINCE PUTIN TO DIAL BACK ON
HIS SUPPORT FOR IRAN AND SYRIA.
AGAIN, THE WHITE HOUSE AND
PRINCE DENYING ALL OF THIS.
IT PRESENTS A POTENTIAL PROBLEM.
THIS IS THE SORT OF THING THAT
SUSAN RICE AND OTHER MEMBERS OF
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION COULD
SAY WE WERE CONCERNED ABOUT,
WHICH IS WHY WE ASKED FOR THE
UNMASKING.
SEAN SPICER DISMISSING ALL OF
THIS AS FLIMSY REPORTING SAYING
I GUESS SOMEONE MAY HAVE VISITED
AN ISLAND BUT THERE'S NO PROOF
THAT THEY MET WITH AN INDIVIDUAL
OR THAT THEY HAD ANY TIES OR THE
DATE OR THE CONSEQUENCES OF THE
MEETING.
I THINK THAT IT'S FLIMSY AT
BEST.
>> A PRO RUSSIAN CONGRESSMAN SET
TO MEET WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP
TODAY.
WHO IS THAT AND WHAT IS THE
MEETING ABOUT?
>> DANA RORBACHER WILL BE HERE.
HE'S AN ADVOCATE OF IMPROVING
THE RELATIONS BETWEEN RUSSIA AND
THE UNITED STATES.
DANA RORBACHER SAID IT'S A
BROUHAHA OVER NOTHING.
HE SAID "WHAT IS HAPPENING IS
YOU HAVE THE FAKE NEWS AVALANCHE
TRYING TO CREATE THE IMPRESSION
THAT SOMETHING SINISTER IS
HAPPENING WITH RUSSIA AND THAT
IS PREVENTING US FROM
NEGOTIATING AND GETTING INTO A
REAL RELATIONSHIP WHERE WE CAN
DO SOME GOOD BY WORKING TOGETHER
WITH RUSSIA."
THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID HE WOULD
LIKE TO WORK WITH RUSSIA ON
DEFEATING ISIS.
WHAT HAPPENED IN SYRIA WITH
AL-ASSAD COULD COMPLICATE
THINGS.
>> THANKS, JOHN.
WANT TO LOOK AT THIS NOW FROM
BOTH SIDES.
A FORMER DEMOCRATIC LEADER IS AN
EXECUTIVE RESIDENT AT THE
AMERICAN UNIVERSITY OF PUBLIC
AFFAIRS.
NED RYAN, FOUNDER AND CEO OF
AMERICAN MAJORITY, A POLITICAL
TRAINING INSTITUTE AND FORMER
WRITER FOR GEORGE BUSH.
GOOD DAY TO BOTH OF YOU.
ST. THE STORY CHANGING WITH
REGARD TO SUSAN RICE GIVEN THAT
INTERVIEW ON MSNBC?
>> YOU'LL HAVE TO PARDON ME OF
BEING SKEPTICAL OF SOMEONE THAT
LIED ABOUT THE BENGHAZI VIDEO
AND A FEW WEEKS AGO CLAIMED NO
KNOWLEDGE OF WHAT CONGRESSMAN
NUNES IS TALKING ABOUT AND NOW
LO AND BEHOLD, SHE'S CLAIMING
SHE KNOWS NOTHING.
I'M SKEPTICAL OF HOW HONEST
SUSAN RICE IS BEING.
HERE'S WHAT WE'RE STARTING TO
FIGURE OUT.
THIS APPEARS TO BE COORDINATED,
SYSTEMATIC.
THE THING THAT IS INTERESTING TO
ME, BILL, BASED OFF OF SOME OF
THESE RECORDS, ACCORDING TO FISA
COURT RULE AND NSA POLICIES, ANY
INCIDENTAL COMMUNICATIONS
COLLECTED THAT ARE NOT SPECIFIC
TO THE INVESTIGATION ARE TO BE
DISCARDED.
BASED OFF THE REPORTS THAT WE'RE
HEARING, NOT ONLY ARE THE
INCIDENTAL COMMUNICATIONS THAT
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH RUSSIA,
NOT ONLY ARE THEY NOT DISCARDED,
NAMES WERE UNMASKED AND PUT IN
THE REPORTS AND WIDELY
DISSEMINATED.
THAT'S A PROBLEM.
I HOPE AT THE END OF DAY AND
WE'RE GOING TO -- I FEEL LIKE
WE'RE PEELING BACK AN ONION
EVERY DAY.
THERE'S --
>> YOU'RE NOT FAR FROM OFF ON
THAT.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WOULD ARGUE THIS
IS REFERRED SURVEILLANCE.
QUICKLY.
>> I WOULD ARGUE, THERE'S REAL
QUESTIONS IS THIS REVERSE
SURVEILLANCE.
DID THE PARTY IN POWER WEAPONIZE
THE STATE AGAINST THE OPPOSING
PARTY?
THESE ARE SERIOUS ALLEGATIONS
AND SERIOUS QUESTIONS BEING
RAISED.
I WOULD LIKE SUSAN RICE TO GO
UNDER OATH, GO UP TO THE HILL IN
FRONT OF THE SENATE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE AND GIVE ANSWERS.
>> CAPRI, HOW BIG OF A DEAL THIS
IS NOW?
>> WHAT A MESS THIS IS FOR THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC, FOR OUR
CREDIBILITY.
I THINK CREDIBILITY HERE IS A
HUGE ISSUE.
YOU HAVE SUSAN RICE WHO AS THE
OTHER GUEST JUST MENTIONED HAD
CREDIBILITY QUESTIONS BECAUSE OF
THE HISTORY WITH BENGHAZI.
THEN YOU HAVE THE ISSUE OF DEVIN
NUNES AND HIS CLOUD OF
CONTROVERSY SURROUNDING WHETHER
OR NOT HE WAS POLITICALLY
MOTIVATED.
YOU HAVE TWO PEOPLE COOKING IN
THE KITCHEN THAT DON'T
NECESSARILY HAVE GREAT
CREDIBILITY IN ADDRESSING THIS
ISSUE.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE ANSWERS.
THEY DESERVE ANSWERS --
>> MIGHT TAKE SOME TIME.
>> FROM MARCH 22, JUDY WOODRUFF
ASKED SUSAN RICE ABOUT BEING
SWEPT UP IN THE SURVEILLANCE.
HER ANSWER IS "I KNOW NOTHING
ABOUT THIS."
I WAS SURPRISED TO SEE THE
REPORTS FROM CHAIRMAN NUNES.
>> I CAN MAKE THAT REQUEST.
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY
PROCESSED THAT REQUEST THROUGH
THEIR NORMAL PROCEDURES AND IF
THEY FEEL THEY CAN GIVE THE
ANSWER, THEY WILL GIVE THE
ANSWER.
THAT COMES BACK TO ME, NOT TO
ANYBODY BROADLY IN THE NATIONAL
SECURITY WORLD.
THAT IS NECESSARY FOR ME TO DO
MY JOB.
>> DID YOU SEEK THE NAMES OF
PEOPLE INVOLVED IN -- TO UNMASK
THE NAMES OF PEOPLE INVOLVED IN
THE TRUMP TRANSITION, THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN, PEOPLE SURROUNDING THE
PRESIDENT-ELECT IN ORDER TO SPY
ON THEM?
>> ABSOLUTELY NOT FOR ANY
POLITICAL PURPOSES, TO SPY,
EXPOSE, ANYTHING.
>> TWO WEEKS LATER, A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT ANSWER.
ANDREA MITCHELL HAD THE RIGHT
QUESTION.
DID YOU USE THIS INFORMATION TO
SPY.
>> NO.
THIS IS THE THING.
IF IT LOOKS LIKE AND APPEARS
THIS WAY THAT TRUMP AND HIS
TRANSITION TEAM WERE TARGETED,
IT HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
RUSSIA, THAT THERE WAS A
POLITICAL INTELLIGENCE GATHERING
OPERATION AND IT WAS WIDE BY
DISSEMINATED.
COMMON SENSE DICTATES THAT
THERE'S SOMETHING WRONG HERE.
WE'RE NOT JUST REALIZING IT'S
SUSAN, HER DEPUTY, BEN RHODES AS
WELL.
I THINK THERE'S MORE NAMES
COMING OUT.
HERE'S THE THING.
SUSAN RICE DID NOT ACT IN A
VACUUM.
SHE DID NOT DO THIS OF HER OWN
VOLITION.
THERE'S OTHERS INVOLVED.
THE QUESTION IS HOW HIGH --
>> NONE OF US HERE HAVE SECURITY
CLEARANCE.
WE HAVE NO WHAT HAPPENED BEHIND
CLOSED DOOR.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE DESERVE
ANSWERS.
WE NEED ANSWERS BOTH FROM SUSAN
RICE AND ON THE RUSSIAN
DEBACLE --
>> TO BOTH OF YOU, THANK YOU.
A QUICK BREAK HERE.
IF REPUBLICANS WANT TO REVIVE
THEIR PLAN TO REPEAL AND REPLACE
OBAMACARE, THEY NEED
CONSERVATIVE SUPPORT.
IN A MOMENT, MEET THE LEADER OF
A GROUP THAT MAY JUST GIVE THAT
NEXT LIVE HERE.
Fun in art class.
Come close, come close.
I like that.
[ ALL SOUNDS COME TO A
CRASHING HALT ]
Ah.
When your pain reliever
stops working,
your whole day stops.
Awww.
Try this.
For minor arthritis pain,
only Aleve is FDA
approved to work
for up to 12 straight hours
with just one pill.
Thank you.
Come on everybody.
Aleve.
Live Whole.
Not Part.
Remember when you said
men are supeYeah...ivers?
Yeah, then how'd I get this...
...Allstate Safe
Driving Bonus Check?
...only Allstate sends
you a bonus check
for every six months
you're accident free.
Silence.
It's good to be IN, Good Hands.
>> Bill: BREAKING NEWS ON WHAT
MIGHT BE REPUBLICAN HOPES FOR
REVIVING THE HEALTHCARE PLAN.
THE INITIAL EFFORT TO REPEAL
OBAMACARE FLOPPED TWO WEEKS AGO.
NOW ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS
MOVING TO GET IT ANOTHER GO.
THERE'S A LOT OF MEETINGS DAY
AND NIGHT.
MY GUEST MAY BE ABLE TO OFFER
HELP.
DAVID McINTOSH JOINS ME LIVE
FROM WASHINGTON.
SIR, GOOD DAY TO YOU.
READY TO BREAK SOME NEWS?
READY TO GET ON BOARD A NEW PLAN
TO PASS IT OR NOT?
>> WELL, BILL, VICE PRESIDENT
PENCE HAS WORKED HARD THE LAST
CONSERVATIVES AND MODERATE
REPUBLICANS TOGETHER.
AS YOU KNOW, THE FLAW IN THE
FIRST EFFORT WAS IT DIDN'T
REPEAL THE COSTLY REGULATIONS
THAT OBAMACARE PUT IN PLACE THAT
HAVE CAUSED INSURANCE PREMIUMS
TO GO THROUGH THE ROOF.
WHAT VICE PRESIDENT PENCE SAID
IS, YOU KNOW, THE MORE MODERATE
AND LIBERAL STATES WANT TO KEEP
THE REGULATIONS.
MORE CONSERVATIVES WANT TO GET
RID OF THEM.
HOW ABOUT IF WE DID AN APPROACH
WHERE THE STATES COULD ASK FOR
WAIVERS, THAT THEY COULD GET RID
OF THE COSTLY REGULATIONS AND IF
A STATE LIKE MY STATE OF INDIANA
WANTS TO DO THAT AND SAVE OUR
CITIZENS A LOT OF MONEY ON THEIR
HEALTH INSURANCE, THEY CAN DO
IT.
IF A STATE LIKE NEW YORK WANTS
TO KEEP THE EXPENSIVE
REGULATIONS, THEY CAN DO THAT.
>> THAT ANSWER TELLS ME YOU'RE
NOT ON BOARD.
YOU'RE STILL NEGOTIATING.
>> THE PROBLEM IS, SPEAKER RYAN
HAS NOT AGREED TO THE DEAL THAT
VICE PRESIDENT PROVIDENCE PUT
TOGETHER.
WE'RE READY TO SUPPORT IT, BILL
IF HE WILL AGREE TO IT.
>> Bill: ARE YOU ON THE SAME
SIDE AS MIKE PENCE AT THE
MOMENT?
>> YES, SIR, I AM.
HE'S GOOD A GOOD PROPOSAL.
>> Bill: LET ME INTERRUPT YOU.
TRYING TO SQUEEZE AS MUCH AS WE
CAN IN HERE.
HOW MANY MEMBERS OF THE FREEDOM
CAUCUS WOULD VOTE WITH YOUR PLAN
A SECOND TIME AROUND?
>> THEY WANT TO SEE WE WANT TO
SEE THE ACTUAL LANGUAGE IN THE
BILL.
THEY FEEL LIKE IT'S LUCY AND
CHARLIE BROWN.
THEY HAVE BEEN PROMISED THINGS
IN THE PAST AND HE DIDN'T
DELIVER IT.
I DON'T BLAME THEM.
SEE THE LANGUAGE, SEE THE BILL.
IF IT'S IN THERE, THE AGREEMENT
THAT WE REACHED WITH VICE
PRESIDENT PENCE IS IN THERE,
THEN IT'S A GOOD PROVISION AND
THE BILL SHOULD GO FORWARD.
>> DAVID, VERY IMPORTANT, AS YOU
KNOW.
THERE WERE 36 MEMBERS OF THE
FREEDOM CAUCUS, PERHAPS 35 AT
LAST CHECK.
YOU'RE SAYING THAT IF YOU GET
WHAT YOU WANT, ALL 35 SIGN ON TO
THIS?
>> I DON'T KNOW ABOUT ALL OF
THEM.
THERE WILL BE SOME THAT WON'T.
I CAN'T SPEAK FOR THEM ALL.
WHAT I DO THINK IS YOU'LL SEE
ALMOST ALL THE CONSERVATIVES
AGREE TO IT AND THEN THE
MODERATES, WILL THEY HOLD UP
REPEAL AND REPLACE.
THAT'S THEIR DECISION.
EARLY ON, THEY SIGNALS TO THE
VICE PRESIDENT THAT THEY COULD
LIVE WITH THIS COMPROMISE.
I THINK THE REAL QUESTION IS
WILL SPEAKER RYAN AND THE
MODERATES TAKE A YES AT THIS
POINT.
>> Bill: DO YOU BELIEVE AT THIS
POINT THAT THAT THERE HAPPEN?
>> YES, I DO.
I THINK IN THE END, THEY'RE
FAITHFUL TO THEIR CAMPAIGN
PROMISES THAT THEY WANT TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE.
THIS IS A COMPROMISED WAY TO DO
IT AND A GOOD WAY FORWARD.
>> SO WHEN WE TALK ABOUT A
REVIVAL FOR REPEAL AND REPLACE,
IT SOUNDS AS IF A LOT IS MOVING
AT THE MOMENT.
>> A LOT IS MOVING.
THE KEY IS NOT EVERYBODY IS
GOING TO GET EVERYTHING THEY
WANT.
CONSERVATIVES GOT A BIG PART OF
WHAT THEY WANT NOW.
THE INDIVIDUAL STATES CAN DECIDE
TO GET RID OF THOSE REGULATIONS.
I HOPE THE MODERATES WILL SAY
YES, WE PRESERVED IT FOR OUR
STATE IF WE DON'T WANT TO DO IT.
THAT'S A FAIR COMPROMISE.
>> Bill: FOR THE RECORD, WE
HEARD THE SAME THING ABOUT THREE
WEEKS AGO.
>> YEAH, YOU HAVE TO KEEP
MOVING.
THINGS CAN FALL APART IN
WASHINGTON.
THE CLUB FOR GROWTH WAS DEAD SET
ABOUT THE EARLIER BILL BECAUSE
IT DIDN'T DO ANYTHING ON THESE
REGULATIONS, THIS IS A BIG STEP
FORWARD TO PROVIDE RELIEF SO
INSURANCE PREMIUMS CAN COME
DOWN.
>> Bill: WE'LL SEE IF IT GOES.
DAVID, THANKS.
PRESIDENT FOR THE CLUB FOR
GROWTH.
IN A MOMENT HERE, CHILDREN AMONG
THE DEATH AFTER REPORTS OF A
CHEMICAL ATTACK INSIDE SYRIA.
NOW THE WHITE HOUSE UNDER
GROWING PRESSURE TO DEAL WITH
THE RUSSIAN BACK'S DICTATOR,
AL-ASSAD AFTER THE
ADMINISTRATION SAID THEY'RE NOT
FOCUSED ON REMOVING HIM FROM
POWER.
SO WHAT NOW?
THAT'S NEXT.
Why do we put so much effort
into engineering the
Can-Am Defender?
Because a job worth doing,
is worth doing right.
Can-Am Defender.
Tough, Capable, Clever.
Get a 3-year BRP limited
warranty plus a $1,500 cash
rebate on 2016 Defender models.
My lineage was the Vecchios and
Zuccolis. Through Ancestry,
through DNA I found out that I
was only 16% Italian.
He was 34% Eastern European.
So I went onto Ancestry,
soon learned that one of our
ancestors we thought was Italian
was Eastern European.
This is my ancestor who I
didn't know about.
He looks a little bit
like me, yes.
Ancestry has many paths to
discovering your story.
Get started for free at
Ancestry.com
>> THE WHITE HOUSE SAYING
TODAY'S APPARENT CHEMICAL ATTACK
IN SYRIA AGAINST CIVILIANS IS
REPREHENSIBLE AND CANNOT BE
IGNORED.
IT'S CALLING ACTIONS BY BASHAR
AL-ASSAD HEINOUS AND THAT IS A
SHIFT FROM WHAT TOP TRUMP
OFFICIALS WERE SAYING DAYS AGO.
ACTIVISTS CLAIM SYRIAN OR
RUSSIAN FIGHTER JETS DROPPED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON A TOWN IN
NORTHERN SYRIA.
A HUMAN RIGHTS GROUP SAID THE
ATTACKS KILLED 58 PEOPLE
INCLUDING 11 CHILDREN.
WE WANT TO WARN YOU, THE IMAGES
ARE DISTURBING AND YOU MAY WANT
TO THINK TWICE ABOUT SHARING
WITH YOUR KIDS.
WE'RE SHOWING THEM THOU BECAUSE
THEY CONVEY THE TRUE HORROR OF
THIS ATTACK AND THE VICTIMS IT
INVOLVES.
HEART-BREAKING PHOTOS POSTED ON
FACEBOOK.
SMALL CHILDREN IN DIAPERS AMONG
THE VICTIMS OF THE CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
MEDICS REPORTING THAT ROCKET
ATTACKS AND CLINICS TREATING THE
WOUNDED.
TODAY REPORTERS ASKED SEAN
SPICER IF THE UNITED STATES WILL
RESPOND.
SPICER IS SAYING OFF CAMERA THAT
HE WASN'T GOING TO GET AHEAD OF
THE PRESIDENT.
THIS COMING DAYS AFTER THE U.S.
AMBASSADOR TO THE U.N. NIKKI
HALEY SAID THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION WASN'T INTERESTED
IN REMOVING AL-ASSAD FROM POWER
AND IT SHOULD BE UP TO THE
SYRIAN PEOPLE TO DECIDE THE
FUTURE OF THEIR COUNTRY.
THIS IS THE THIRD CLAIM OF A
CHEMICAL ATTACK IN JUST OVER A
WEEK IN SYRIA.
LEA GABRIELLE WITH MORE ON THIS
TODAY.
LEA?
>> THERE'S REPORTS OF PEOPLE
FOAMING AT THE MOUTH, PEOPLE
UNRESPONSIVE.
YOU CAN SEE EMERGENCY WORKERS
DRESSED IN HAZMAT SUITS AS THEY
TAKE CHILDREN INTO THE HOSPITAL
FOR TREATMENT.
ONE DOCTOR SAID HE SAW PATIENTS
WITH PINPOINT PUPILS.
THESE ARE COMMON SYMPTOMS OF
TOXIC GAS EXPOSURES.
THEY THINK MORE THAN ONE GAS WAS
USED INCLUDING SARIN.
THIS HAPPENED IN AN AIR
CONTROLLED BY FORCES OPPOSED TO
THE ASSAD REGIME.
IT'S HOME TO 900,000 DISPLACED
SYRIANS.
THIS IS THE WORST TOXIC GAS
ATTACK ON A DAMASCUS SUBJECT
BOSCH.
AFTER THAT, PRESIDENT ASSAD
AGREED TO DESTROY CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
1,300 TONS OF MATERIALS WERE
DESTROYED.
MANY COUNTRIES WORRY WHETHER HE
GAVE UP HIS MATERIALS.
>> AND SENATOR McCAIN IS
QUESTIONING WHETHER IT'S TIME TO
TAKE ACTION AGAINST ASSAD.
>> TODAY A STATEMENT WAS
RELEASED SAYING "ASSAD BELIEVES
HE CAN COMMIT WAR CRIMES WITH
IMPUNITY.
THE QUESTION IS WHETHER WE WILL
TAKE ACTION TO DISABUSE HIM OF
THIS MURDEROUS NOTION."
HE SAID THE SYRIAN PEOPLE WOULD
HAVE A DECISION ABOUT ASSAD'S
FATE UNDER THESE CONDITIONS.
AS YOU RECALL LAST WEEK, THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION SAID THEY
WEREN'T FOCUSED ON TAKING OUT
ASSAD ANYMORE.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> THERE'S A POLITICAL REALITY
THAT WE HAVE TO ACCEPT IN TERMS
OF WHERE WE ARE RIGHT NOW.
WE LOST A LOT OF OPPORTUNITY THE
LAST ADMINISTRATION WITH RESPECT
TO ASSAD.
NOW IT'S UP TO THE SYRIAN
PEOPLE.
WE HAD AN OPPORTUNITY AND WE
NEED TO FOCUS ON NOW DEFEATING
ISIS.
>> WELL, TODAY PRESS SECRETARY
SEAN SPICER TOOK A DIFFERENT
TONE.
HE SAID THE ADMINISTRATION HAS A
LACK OF COMFORT WITH ASSAD.
VERY DIDN'T TONE THERE.
>> Bill: WE AWAIT THE NEXT
CHAPTER.
TRULY DISTURBING.
THANK YOU.
IN A MOMENT, MORE ON THE ONGOING
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIA'S
INVOLVEMENT IN THE PAST ELECTION
AND SUSAN RICE RESPONDING TO THE
CONTROVERSY OF UNMASKING TRUMP
ASSOCIATES CAUGHT UP IN
SURVEILLANCE.
A LIVE REPORT FROM CATHERINE
HERRIDGE.
WE'LL TALK TO HER IN A MATTER OF
MINUTES.
Over here! Over here!
No!
(Dog barking)
Whoever threw it
has to go get it.
Not me!
Somebody will get it...
♪
(Dog barking)
Anyone can dream.
Making it a reality
is the hard part.
From the B-2 to
the upcoming B-21,
Northrop Grumman
stealth bombers give
America an advantage
in a turbulent world.
And we're looking for a
few dreamers to join us.
>> Bill: FOX REPORT NOW.
AN UPDATE ON THE SUBWAY BOMBING
IN RUSSIA.
INVESTIGATORS SAY 22-YEAR-OLD
MAN FROM WAS THE CULPRIT FOR THE
BOMBING.
AND YESTERDAY THE STATION WAS
FILLED WITH SMOKE AND PEOPLE
TRIED TO PRY OPEN DOORS.
WITNESSES DESCRIBE A HORRIFIC
SCENE.
PEOPLE KNEELING OF BODIES AND
THEIR HAIR BURNED.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE SUSPECT
PLANTED A BOMB IN ANOTHER SUBWAY
STATION IN ST. PETERSBURG.
THE ENTIRE SUBWAY SYSTEM SHUT
DOWN FOR HOURS.
VLADIMIR PUTIN WAS VISITING THAT
TOWN AT THAT TIME, WHICH IS ALSO
HIS HOMETOWN.
HE COLD IT A POSSIBLE TERROR
ATTACK.
NO WORD ON GROUPS CLAIMING
RESPONSIBILITY JUST YET.
THE NEWS WILL CONTINUE AFTER
THIS.
AREDS 2.
My doctor said
PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
the National Eye
Institute recommends
to help reduce
the risk of progression of
moderate to advanced AMD
after 15 years
of clinical studies.
PreserVision
AREDS 2.
Because my eyes
are everything.
>> Bill: SENATE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE MEETING BEHIND CLOSED
DOOR AS THEY CONTINUE TO
INVESTIGATE RUSSIA'S INVOLVEMENT
IN THE ELECTION OF 2016.
A LIVE LOOK NOW AT THE STAKEOUT
CAM WHERE WE CAN HEAR FROM
MEMBERS OF THE COMMITTEE ONCE
THEY'RE DONE MEETING, THIS COMES
ONLY HOURS AFTER SUSAN RICE
ADDRESSED THE CONTROVERSY
SURROUNDING THE UNMASKING OF
TRUMP ASSOCIATE NAMES CAUGHT UP
IN SURVEILLANCE.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE IS ON THAT
STORY NOW LIVE IN WASHINGTON.
CATHERINE?
>> THANK YOU.
THE RICE INTERVIEW ILLUSTRATES
THE POLITICAL DIVIDE HERE IN
WASHINGTON.
SOME SAY THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION WAS DOING DUE
DILIGENCE.
THE FORMER NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISOR EMPHASIZING THAT
UNMASKING IS SEPARATE AND
DISTINCT FROM MAKING THE NAMES
PUBLIC.
>> THE NOTION THAT WHICH SOME
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO SUGGEST
THAT BY ASKING FOR THE IDENTITY
OF AN AMERICAN PERSON, THAT IS
THE SAME AS LEAKING IT IS
COMPLETELY FALSE.
THERE'S NO EQUIVALENCE BETWEEN
SO-CALLED UNMASKING AND LEAKING.
>> MEANTIME A GOVERNMENT SOURCE
CONFIRMED TO FOX NEWS THAT RICE
WITH BEN RHODES AND FORMER
C.I.A. DIRECTOR JOHN BRENNAN HAD
REGULAR ACCESS TO THE
INTELLIGENCE WHERE MEMBERS OF
THE TRUMP TRANSITION TEAM WERE
IDENTIFIED OR UNMASKED.
AS THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITSTY'S RANKING DEMOCRATS
SAID, IT MAY BE POSSIBLE TO GET
IDENTITIES TO UNDER THE
CONVERSATIONS.
>> Bill: ARE THEY DOING THAT
ALREADY, CATHERINE?
>> A SHORT TIME AGO, FOX NEWS
ASKING THE REPUBLICAN CHAIRMAN
RICHARD BURR ABOUT SUSAN RICE.
MEAN TONIGHT THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE, FOX NEWS
SAID THAT THOSE THAT WILL BE
INTERVIEWED BE INVESTIGATORS
INCLUDING CARTER PAGE, PAUL
MANAFORT AND ROGER STONE.
BASED ON OUR REPORTING, THERE'S
AN AGREEMENT IN PRINCIPLE WERE
DEMOCRATS FOR THE INTERVIEWS AND
COULD BE DONE AS EARLY AS APRIL
17th.
LIKELY AFTER THE RECESS.
>> SO THE FBI DIRECTOR IS BACK
IN THE CROSS HAIR.
WHAT GIVES WITH THAT?
>> JAMES COMEY AND THE NSA
DIRECTOR ADMIRAL MIKE ROGERS
TESTIFIED AT THE HEARING MARCH
20th.
BUT AFTER THESE REPORTS CAME TO
LIGHT, BOTH MEN WERE RECALLED.
THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO HAPPEN LAST
WEEK.
THE FBI SAID THAT THEY'RE NOT
COOPERATIVE ON THE MATTER.
MEANTIME, A GOVERNMENT OFFICIAL
SAID THE FBI DIRECTOR IN THEIR
OPINION WAS SO DAMAGED BY HIS
PUBLIC STATEMENTS IN THE CLINTON
E-MAIL PROBLEM AND THE RUSSIAN
ELECTION SCANDAL THAT SHE SHOULD
CONSIDER RECUSING HIMSELF.
HE WAS AT THE CENTER OF THE
MASKING OF MIKE FLYNN AS PART OF
THE COUNTER INTELLIGENCE
INVESTIGATION.
THESE INDIVIDUALS WOULD NOT
SPEAK ON THE RECORD BUT THEY
CLAIMED WHAT THE DIRECTOR SAID
IN THE MARCH 20th HEARING DID
NOT SYNC UP WITH HIS STATEMENTS
DURING PRIVATE CLASSIFIED
BRIEFINGS.
THE DIRECTOR'S VIEW ON THE
PRESIDENT'S WIRETAPPING TWEETS
WERE DESCRIBED AS SHOWING A
COMPLETE LACK OF DISCRETION.
I WOULD EMPHASIZE WE'VE HEARD
NOTHING IN A SIMILAR VEIN FROM
THE DEMOCRATS THAT ARE ON THESE
COMMITTEES.
NO A LOT TO FOLLOW, CATHERINE.
THANK YOU.
ALSO FROM THE HILL, THERE'S MORE
THIS HOUR.
SENATORS HAVE STARTED THEIR
FORMAL DEBATE OVER PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S SUPREME COURT NOMINEE,
NEIL GORSUCH.
A LIVE LOOK AT THE SENATE FLOOR.
IT'S LOOKING LIKE REPUBLICANS
MIGHT USE THE NUCLEAR OPTION TO
GET HIM CONFIRMED AND ON THE
BENCH.
41 DEMOCRATIC SENATORS SAY THEY
WILL PLAN TO VOTE NO ON
CONFIRMING GORSUCH.
THAT IS ENOUGH TO STOP
REPUBLICANS FROM GETTING THE 60
VOTES THEY NEED.
THE WAY AROUND THAT FOR
REPUBLICANS IS THE NUCLEAR
OPTION.
THAT WOULD SET A NEW PRECEDENT
AND LOWTER MAJORITY TO 51 VOTES.
THAT WAY REPUBLICANS COULD
CONFIRM GORSUCH WITHOUT A SINGLE
DEMOCRATIC VOTE.
THE RULE CHANGE WOULD BE FOR
FUTURE NOMINEES.
IT WOULD BE A DIFFERENT BODY.
PETER, DEMOCRATS ARE TRYING TO
AVOID USING THE NUCLEAR OPTION
IN WHAT WAY?
>> WE JUST HEARD FROM THE SENATE
MINORITY LEADER, CHUCK SCHUMER,
HIS PARTY IN THE MINORITY, THAT
IF THE NUCLEAR OPTION GETS USED
AGAINST THEM, THEY WILL BE
FURTHER MARGINALIZED WHILE
REPUBLICANS ARE IN CHARGE.
NOW SCHUMER SAYS THAT
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS SHOULD
GET TOGETHER IN A ROOM BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS TO TALK IT OUT AND
FIGURE OUT HOW TO AVOID USING
THE NUCLEAR OPTION.
THAT IS NEW FOR SCHUMER.
PREVIOUSLY HE HAD BEEN SAYING IF
GORSUCH WASN'T GOING TO GET 60
VOTES, PRESIDENT TRUMP SHOULD
NOMINATE SOMEONE THAT COULD.
SCHUMER AND HIS COLLEAGUES,
RICHARD BLUMENTHAL, ARE LAYING
OUT THE CONSEQUENCES OF HAVING
THE PRECEDENT CHANGED.
BLUMENTHAL IS USING BLEAK
ADJECTIVES.
>> THE REASON THEY CALL IT THE
NUCLEAR OPTION, THAT IS THAT
THERE'S FALL-OUT.
>> THE MINORITY LEADER SCHUMER
IS SUGGESTING THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP IS GOING TO HAVE A REALLY
HARD TIME DOING SOMETHING THAT
HE SUGGESTED THAT HE MIGHT DO
SOME DAY, REACH OUT TO DEMOCRATS
FOR SOME LEGISLATING HERE IF THE
NUCLEAR OPTION IS USED.
>> WHAT ARE REPUBLICANS TELLING
YOU ABOUT THE JUSTIFICATION, THE
CHANGE OF PRECEDENT?
HOW DID THEY BACK THAT UP AT
THIS LATE STAGE?
>> THEY'RE JUSTIFYING IT BY
SAYING THIS IS THE ONLY WAY THEY
CAN CONFIRM GORSUCH EVEN THOUGH
THEY KNOW THIS RULE COULD SOME
DAY BE USED AGAINST THEM.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE VERY
HARMFUL.
SOME DAY THE DEMOCRATS WILL BE
IN THE MAJORITY AND WE WILL LOSE
THE UNIQUE ASPECT OF THE WAY WE
SHOULD BE DOING BUSINESS.
IT WILL RESULT IN SUPREME COURT
NOMINEES THAT ARE MUCH MORE
RADICAL IN EITHER DIRECTION.
>> THE SECOND HIGHEST RANKING
SENATOR, ORRIN HATCH FROM UTAH
SAYS IT COULD BE THE NEXT
CONFIRMATION FIGHT THAT WOULD BE
LIKE ARMAGEDDON.
THAT MIGHT BE THE ONE WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP COULD HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO REPLACE ONE OF
THE COURT'S LIBERAL JUSTICES
WITH A CONSERVATIVE.
>> MAYBE SENATOR SCHUMER IS
COOKING UP A DEAL.
COULD BE THE ART OF HIS OWN
DEAL.
PETER DOOCY LIVE.
MORE ON THE SHOWDOWN IN THE
SENATE A AND THE POSSIBLE
CONSEQUENCES OF USING THE
NUCLEAR OPTION.
THAT IS NEXT AS WE CONTINUE.
Hey, ready for the big meeting?
Yeah.
Uh, hello!?
A meeting?
It's a big one.
Too bad.
We are double booked:
diarrhea and
abdominal pain.
Why don't you start
without me?
Oh. Yeah.
If you're living with frequent,
unpredictable diarrhea
and abdominal pain,
you may have...
...Irritable Bowel Syndrome
with Diarrhea,
or IBS-D.
A condition that can
be really frustrating.
Talk to your doctor
about VIBERZI,
a different way to treat IBS-D.
VIBERZI is a
prescription medication
you take every day
that helps proactively manage
both diarrhea and abdominal pain
at the same time.
So you stay ahead of
your symptoms.
VIBERZI can cause new or
worsening abdominal pain.
Do not take VIBERZI if you have
or may have had:
pancreas or
severe liver problems,
problems with alcohol abuse,
long-lasting or
severe constipation,
or a blockage of your bowel
or gallbladder.
If you are taking VIBERZI,
you should not take medicines
that cause constipation.
The most common side effects of
VIBERZI include
constipation, nausea, and
abdominal pain.
Stay ahead of IBS-D...
...with VIBERZI.
>> Bill: FOLLOW UP ON THE STORY
OUT OF SYRIA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP PUTTING A
STATEMENT OUT ON THE DEADLY
CHEMICAL ATTACK IN SYRIA.
BLAMING THE ASSAD REGIME FOR
WHAT THE PRESIDENT CALLS HEINOUS
ACTIONS.
ACTIVISTS SAY SYRIAN OR RUSSIAN
FIGHTER JETS DROPPED CHEMICALS
ON A NORTHERN TOWN IN SYRIA.
THE ATTACK KILLED AT LEAST 58
AND 11 CHILDREN.
THE PRESIDENT'S STATEMENT READS
THE FOLLOWING "TODAY'S CHEMICAL
ATTACK IN SYRIA AGAINST INNOCENT
PEOPLE, INCLUDING WOMEN AND
CHILDREN, IS REPREHENSIBLE AND
CANNOT BE IGNORED BY THE
CIVILIZED WORLD.
THESE ARE A CONSEQUENCE OF THE
PAST ADMINISTRATION'S WEAKNESS.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID HE WOULD
ESTABLISH A RED LINE AGAINST THE
USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS AND DID
NOTHING.
THE UNITED STATES STANDS WITH
OUR ALLIES ACROSS THE GLOBE TO
CONDEMN THIS INTOLERABLE ATTACK.
THAT IS THE STATEMENT FROM THE
PRESIDENT AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
MORE UPDATES ON THIS STORY AS WE
GET DEVELOPMENTS HERE AT THE FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
NOW BACK TO CONTINUING COVERAGE
OF THE SENATE DEBATE OVER
SUPREME COURT NOMINEE NEIL
GORSUCH.
IT'S ALMOST THAT TIME.
DEMOCRATS THREATENING TO BLOCK
THE CONFIRMATION.
REPUBLICANS SAY THEY WILL GET IT
DONE ANYWAY.
I WANT TO BRING IN EMILY GOOD
DEN TO TALK MORE ABOUT THIS.
GOOD AFTERNOON.
FOR REPUBLICANS, WHAT THE DO
THEY HAVE ON THE LINE FOR THIS
POTENTIAL NUCLEAR OPTION?
>> IT MAY BACKFIRE ON THEM JUST
LIKE IT DID ON DEMOCRATS WHEN
THEY DID THIS UNDER PRESIDENT
OBAMA.
THIS IS A VERY POWERFUL WEAPON
AND CAN BITE YOU.
THIS DOES MAKE THE NOMINATION
PROCESS EASIER FOR SUPREME COURT
NOMINEES.
BUT LET'S SAY IN 2020 A DEMOCRAT
GETS ELECTED TO THE WHITE HOUSE.
THEY WOULD HAVE AN EASIER TIME
PUTTING PEOPLE ON THE SUPREME
COURT.
>> WHAT ABOUT DEMOCRATS?
WHAT IS AT STAKE FOR THEM?
>> FOR DEMOCRATS, THIS IS REALLY
ABOUT RALLYING FOR THE BASE AND
LOOKING AHEAD TO THE 2018
ELECTION.
YOU HAVE TO KEEP IN MIND, THE
DEMOCRATIC BASE WAS FURIOUS
ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED TO MERRICK
GARLAND.
THEY SEE THIS AS HIS SUPREME
COURT SEAT THAT PRESIDENT OBAMA
SHOULD HAVE GOTTEN TO NOMINATE
HIS NOMINEE AND THE REPUBLICANS
STOLE THIS AND THE DEMOCRATS ARE
FURIOUS.
THEY'RE TRYING TO KEEP THE BASE
HAPPY.
THEY WANT TO TAKE THE SENATE
BACK.
>> THEY'RE RAISING MONEY OFF OF
THIS, TOO.
REPUBLICANS WOULD TAKE THAT
ARGUMENT AND SAYING YOU'RE DOING
THIS FOR REVENGE.
>> REVENGE OR PLANNING AHEAD,
PUT IT EITHER WAY.
THIS IS A RALLYING CRY FOR THEM.
THEY'RE ALREADY FUND-RAISING OFF
OF IT, THIS IS A BIG DEAL FOR
DEMOCRATS.
>> YOU NEED 60 VOTES TO END THE
DEBATE.
IF YOU HAD THE 60 VOTES, YOU
COULD GET AN UP OR DOWN VOTE OR
GOVERNOR SUM AND THEN ONLY NEED
51 VOTES.
SO THERE'S A RULE IN THE SENATE
THAT NEEDS TO BE VERIFY FOR
VIEWERS AT HOME.
THAT'S WHY WE TALK ABOUT 51
VERSUS 60.
DEMOCRATS CHANGED THIS RULE IN
THE FIRST PLACE UNDER HARRY REID
IN 2013.
SO WHAT ARE THEY COMPLAINING
ABOUT NOW?
>> WELL, EXACTLY.
WHAT HAPPENED REPUBLICANS WERE
FILIBUSTERING PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
NOMINEES AND DEMOCRATS WEREN'T
HAPPY.
SO THEY CHANGED IT SO YOU ONLY
NEED A SIMPLY MAJORITY FOR
EVERYTHING BUT SUPREME COURT
NOMINEES.
SO NOW WE MAY MAKE IT AN
ACROSS-THE-BOARD SIMPLE 51.
>> LET'S TURN THE LOGIC AROUND.
SAY YOU'RE CHUCK SCHUMER.
YOU DON'T WANT TO BREAK THIS
RULE FOR SUPREME COURT NOMINEES,
RIGHT?
SO YOU WORK OUT A WAY TO GET THE
60 VOTES.
THE REASON YOU TRY TO DO THAT IS
NOT BECAUSE YOU'RE A BIG
SUPPORTER OF NEIL GORSUCH, YOU
DON'T KNOW WHAT THE IS BEHIND
DOOR NUMBER 2.
IF PRESIDENT TRUMP GETS ANOTHER
NOMINEE, WHO KNOWS WHO LE OFFER.
HE OR SHE MAY BE LESS PALATABLE
TO DEMOCRATS IN THE SENATE THEN.
SO YOU DO A DEAL NOW SO IF THE
EVENT COMES UP.
YOU SAVE FACE FOR LATER IS.
THAT LOGIC TOO TWISTED OR IS
THAT LOGIC IMPOSSIBLE?
>> BILL, I THINK YOU'RE EXACTLY
RIGHT.
THERE'S A CONCERN AMONG SOME
THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL GET
ANOTHER NOMINATION.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE JUSTICES ON
THE COURT, THE ODDS ARE THE
PERSON LEAVING WILL BE A MORE
LIBERAL MEMBER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL APPOINT A
CONSERVATIVE.
IF HE ONLY NEEDS 51 VOTES, IT'S
A DONE DEAL.
>> WHAT IS YOUR GUESS NOW?
IS NEIL GORSUCH SWORN IN AS THE
NEXT SUPREME COURT MEMBER BY THE
END OF THE WEEKEND?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S A DONE DEAL.
>> A DONE DEAL.
>> YOU BELIEVE RIGHT NOW IT'S A
51 VOTE COUNT THAT DOES IT WITH
THE NUCLEAR OPTION OR DO YOU
THINK CHUCK SCHUMER AS PETER
DOOCY IS REPORTING IS WORKING ON
A BIG DEAL BEHIND CLOSED DOORS
NOW?
>> I THINK THAT'S THE UNKNOWN
QUESTION.
THAT'S THE UNKNOWN.
WILL IT BE THE 60 OR THE 51.
KEEP IN MIND, CHUCK SCHUMER
WANTS TO BE SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER ONE DAY.
WHATEVER RULES HE MAKES RIGHT
NOW, HE HAS TO OPERATE UNDER IN
THE FUTURE.
>> HOW WOULD THAT INFLUENCE HOW
HE MAKES THIS WORK OR NOT NOW,
EMILY?
>> HE WANTS TO THINK ABOUT HE'S
MAJORITY LEADER IN SAY 2018.
HE'S MAJORITY LEADER UNDER A
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE'S GOING TO WANT TO BE ABLE TO
HAVE TO USE THE 60 VOTES BECAUSE
THAT'S HARDER TO GET.
SO HE'S PROBABLY THINKING AHEAD
THAT WAY.
>> YOU THINK CHUCK SCHUMER IS IN
A BOX ON THIS?
>> I'M NOT SURE HE'S IN A BOX,
BUT HE HAS TO TREAD CAREFULLY.
HE'S BALANCING THE FUTURE POWER
OF THE SENATE VERSUS HIS PARTY
AND HIS DEMOCRATIC BASE, WHICH
HE NEEDS IN ORDER TO GET CONTROL
OF THE SENATE.
>> LAST QUESTION.
YOU BELIEVE PACED ON THE
JUDICIAL RECORD OF NEIL GORSUCH
THAT HE IS THAT OFFENSIVE TO
DEMOCRATS?
IS HE THAT OFFENSIVE TO LIBERALS
OR JUST THE EXTREME LIBERAL PART
OF THE DEMOCRATIC PARTY?
>> THEY HAVE SOME CONCERNS ABOUT
HIS RECORD ON WORKERS RIGHT.
THAT'S A BIG PART OF THE BASE,
WOMEN'S RIGHT.
SO THERE ARE SOME RED FLAG
ISSUES THERE.
WHETHER THAT IS USUALLY
DISQUALIFYING, I KNOW A LOT OF
SENATORS ARE THINKING ABOUT THAT
WE'RE SEEING DEMOCRATS SAY
THEY'RE GOING TO VOTE FOR HIM.
>> UP TO THREE, I DO BELIEVE.
THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME TODAY.
EMILY GOODEN, YOU'RE ON RECORD.
YOU'RE BRAVE.
THANKS.
FOR YEARS THE EGYPTIAN PRESIDENT
HAS NOT BEEN WELCOME IN
WASHINGTON D.C.
NOW TODAY THAT IS CHANGING.
THE TRUMP TEAM EXTENDING A HAND
TO THE LEADER.
WE'LL LOOK WHY THIS IS HAPPENING
AND WHAT IT SIGNALS FOR THE
MIDDLE EAST AND POLICY BETWEEN
THE UNITED STATES AND THOSE
COUNTRIES.
STAY TUNED FOR THAT.
WE CONTINUE.
>> SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON MEETING WERE THE
EGYPTIAN PRESIDENT AT THE STATE
DEPARTMENT.
THIS COMES ONLY ONE DAY AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP MET WITH THE
AUTHORITARIAN LEADERTHE
WHITE HOUSE, THIS MARKS A MAJOR
SHIFT FROM PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
ADMINISTRATION.
HE NEVER HOSTED THE PRESIDENT
AFTER A MILITARY TAKEOVER FOUR
YEARS AGO.
THE U.S. HAS CONDEMNED EGYPT FOR
HUMAN RIGHTS VIOLATIONS.
THE GOVERNMENT IS HOLDING AN
AMERICAN AIDE WORKER FOR THREE
YEARS.
WE'RE GOING TO RICH EDSON WITH
MORE.
>> WELL, BILL, THIS IS THE
SECOND STRAIGHT DAY OF MEETINGS
FOR PRESIDENT SISI RIGHT HERE IN
WASHINGTON.
HE'S ON CAPITOL HILL RIGHT NOW
MEETING WITH TOP CONGRESSIONAL
LEADERS RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS AFTER A PUBLIC DISPLAY
YESTERDAY IN THE OVAL OFFICE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE WHERE PRESIDENT
TRUMP SAID THAT THE U.S. STANDS
BEHIND SISI NOTING HE'S DONE A
FANTASTIC JOB IN A DIFFICULT
SITUATION.
THE WHITE HOUSE ALSO ADDS THAT
THE U.S. AND EGYPT WILL CONTINUE
COORDINATING ON MILITARY AND
DIPLOMATIC AND POLITICAL EFFORTS
TO DEFEAT EXTREMISM.
THAT IS SOMETHING THAT THE
SECRETARY OF STATE HAS BEEN
WORKING ON OVER THE LAST COUPLE
WEEKS.
HE JUST RETURNED FROM OVERSEAS,
MEETING WITH TURKISH OFFICIALS,
NATO OFFICIALS.
ON TOP OF THAT, AS YOU
MENTIONED, THIS IS A MUCH
GREATER EMBRACE BY THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION THAN THE
PREDECESSOR, PRESIDENT OBAMA,
BECAUSE OF THOSE HUMAN RIGHTS
ISSUES.
THE PRESIDENT HAS ACKNOWLEDGED
THERE'S SOME DIFFERENCES BUT
DIDN'T GET INTO THE SPECIFICS OF
THE HUMAN RIGHTS VIOLATIONS THAT
THOSE AROUND THE WORLD AND HUMAN
RIGHTS GROUPS HAVE SEEN, BILL.
>> Bill: AND THERE'S NEWS ON
SYRIA.
SECRETARY TILLERSON JUST PUT OUT
A STATEMENT.
WHAT DID IT SAY?
>> THE SECRETARY OF STATE HAS
JUST RELEASED THE STATEMENT.
WHAT TILLERSON IS SAYING, HE'S
CALLING UPON RUSSIA AND IRAN TO
EXERCISE THEIR INFLUENCE OVER
THE SYRIAN REGIME IN
GUARANTEEING THAT THIS SORE OF
HORRIFIC ATTACK NEVER HAPPENS
AGAIN.
THE WHITE HOUSE SHORTLY BEFORE
THEN PUT OUT A STATEMENT SAYING
THAT IT WAS THE ADMINISTRATION
OF PRESIDENT OBAMA TO BLAME FOR
THIS FOR NOT ENFORCING THAT
INFAMOUS RED LINE IF THE SYRIAN
REGIME OF BARBER AL-ASSAD HAD
USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS AGAINST
HIS OWN PEOPLE, THIS IS A WEEK
AFTER THE SECRETARY OF STATE
SAID IT'S UP TO THE SYRIAN
PEOPLE TO DECIDE AL-ASSAD'S
FUTURE.
>> Bill: MORE TO COME.
BREAK.
BACK HERE IN A MOMENT ON THIS
DAY IN HISTORY, OLD GLORY.
WHY PAUSE A
SPONTANEOUS MOMENT?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
>> Bill: ON THIS DAY IN 1818,
CONGRESS DECIDED ON NEW RULES
FOR THE AMERICAN FLAG, WHAT IT
SHOULD LOOK LIKE.
BEFORE THEN, THE NUMBER OF STARS
AND STRIPES HAD CHANGED OVER THE
YEARS.
LAWMAKERS SAID OLD GLORY SHOULD
ONLY HAVE 13 STRIPES FOR THE
ORIGINAL 13 COLONYS.
PRESIDENT JAMES MONROE SIGNED
THE MEASURE INTO LAW AND OUR NEW
FLAG WAS BORN 199 YEARS AGO
TODAY.
WELL-DONE!
WE HAVE TO RUN.
WHEN NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL BREAK
IN.
MEANTIME, DECENT DAY FOR THE
DOW.
UP 38.
42 POINTS AT THE CLOSE.
HERE'S NEIL.
SEE YOU TOMORROW IN AMERICA'S
NEWSROOM.
BYE-BYE.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU, BILL.
I KNOW, I KNOW, EVERYONE IS
WONDERING ABOUT RUSSIA AND RICE
AND WHAT SHE KNEW AND WHEN SHE
KNEW IT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TALKING JOBS AND
JOBS.
HE WAS A LASER BEAM ON THIS
FOCUS TODAY.
HIS 17th CEO MEETING OF HIS
YOUNG PRESIDENCY, 170 BUSINESS
LEADERS COLLECTIVELY, MORE THAN
BARACK OBAMA HAD IN HIS ENTIRE
EIGHT YEARS, MORE THAN GEORGE
BUSH HAD.
WHAT IS REALLY GOING ON HERE?
THERE'S SOME POSITIVE
DEVELOPMENTS WE CANNOT MISS.
WHILE WE'RE NOT GOING TO MISS
SOME OF THESE OTHER DEVELOPMENTS
NETWORKS ARE POUNCING ON, WE
THOUGHT WE WOULD BALANCE IT OUT
WITH GOOD NEWS THE MARKETS ARE
POUNCING