>> PRESIDENT TRUMP DEALS WITH
THE FALL OUT FROM HIS DECISION
TO FIRE JAMES COMEY AND THE
WAR OF WORDS THAT FOLLOW.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE, I'M
JULIE AND THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT.
JULIE: THE PRESIDENT
DELIVERING HIS FIRST
COMMENCEMENT SPEECH SINCE
TAKING OFFICE.
TO GRADUATES AT LIBERTY
UNIVERSITY HE REFLECTED ON THE
FIRST FEW MONTHS OF HIS
PRESIDENCY AND SHARED LESSONS
THAT HE HAS LEARNED AND
OFFERED ADVICE TO THE
GRADUATES, CALLING THEM THE
NEXT GENERATION OF AMERICAN
LEADERS.
MEANWHILE BACK IN DC, AT LEAST
EIGHT CANDIDATES TO LEAD THE
FBI VISITED THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT FOR INTERVIEWS
TODAY IN THE SEARCH TO REPLACE
FIRED DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY,
WHO PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE
WILL RERE: PLACE BY NEXT
FRIDAY.
NOW, THE NEW YORK TIMES IS
REPORTING THIS WEEK PRESIDENT
TRUMP DEMANDED A PLEDGE OF
LOYALTY FROM COMEY SHORTLY
AFTER TAKING OFFICE.
SOMETHING THE WHITE HOUSE
DENIES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN THE
MEANTIME SAID SUCH A QUESTION
WOULDN'T BE INAPPROPRIATE IN A
CONVERSATION WITH JUDGE, WHICH
CAN BE SEEN LATER TONIGHT.
BUT WE'VE GOT A PREVIEW.
WATCH.
>> PEOPLE SUGGEST THAT THE
QUESTION THAT APPARENTLY THE
NEW YORK ASKED COMEY WHETHER
OR NOT YOU HAD HIS LOYALTY WAS
POSSIBLY INAPPROPRIATE.
COULD YOU SEE HOW THEY WOULD
THINK THAT?
>> NO.  I READ THAT ARTICLE.
I DON'T THINK IT'S
INAPPROPRIATE, NUMBER ONE.
>> DID YOU ASK THAT QUESTION?
>> NO.
NO, I DIDN'T.
BUT I DON'T THINK IT WILL BE A
BAD QUESTION TO ASK.
I THINK LOYALTY TO THE
COUNTRY.
LOYALTY TO THE UNITED STATES
IS IMPORTANT.  YOU KNOW, I
MEAN, IT DEPENDS ON HOW YOU
DEFINE LOYALTY.
NUMBER ONE.
NUMBER TWO, I DON'T KNOW HOW
THAT GOT THERE BECAUSE I
DIDN'T ASK THAT QUESTION.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE IDEA THAT IN
A TWEET YOU SAID THAT THERE
MIGHT BE TAPE-RECORDINGS?
TRUMP: THAT, I CAN'T TALK
ABOUT.
I WON'T TALK ABOUT THAT.
ALL I WANT IS FOR COMEY TO BE
HONEST, AND I HOPE HE WILL BE,
AND I'M SURE HE WILL BE.
I HOPE.
JULIE: ALL OF THIS IN THE
SHADOW OF A REPORT NOW
BREAKING THAT NORTH KOREA HAS
TEST FIRED YET ANOTHER
BALLISTIC MISSILE, AND WE HAVE
FOX NEWS TEAM COVERAGE FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
ELLISON BARBER WATCHING THE
SEARCH FOR FBI DIRECTOR, BUT
WE BEGIN WITH CAROLINE WHO
JOINS US NOW LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE WITH THE LATEST ON THE
PRESIDENT'S DECISION TO
DISMISS JAMES COMEY.
WHAT IS THE FALLOUT TODAY?
>> I THINK THE CALLS FOR THE
INDEPENDENT COMMISSIONER
GETTING LOUDER THIS WEEKEND.
THAT COULD POTENTIALLY
INVESTIGATE IF THERE WERE ANY
TIES BETWEEN THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN OR TRUMP SURROGATES
AND RUSSIA.
THE FBI WAS LEADING ONE OF THE
MAIN INVESTIGATIONS ALREADY IN
PLACE IN WASHINGTON WHEN
MR. TRUMP FIRED COMEY THIS
WEEK.
THAT INVESTIGATION CONTINUES
STRONGLY THIS WEEKEND.
HERE'S WHAT MR. TRUMP TOLD
JENIN PIRO.
>> I DON'T WANT TO BE IN A
POSITION WHERE IT'S NOT DONE
CORRECTLY.
SO LET THEM DO IT CORRECTLY.
LET THEM TAKE THEIR TIME.
LET THEM DO IT CORRECTLY.
I'M TALKING ABOUT THE HOUSE,
THE SENATE, THE FBI.
>> SO, NO, INDEPENDENT
COMMISSION?
TRUMP: I DON'T THINK YOU NEED
IT.
I MEAN, HONESTLY, WHATEVER'S
GOING TO DO THE BEST.
>> BUT IT'S CONGRESS THAT
WOULD MAKE THE DECISION ON
WHETHER OR NOT AN INDEPENDENT
COUNSEL IS NEEDED IN THIS
CASE.
MR. TRUMP ALSO CAUSED
CONTROVERSY THIS WEEK WHEN HE
TWEETED, AND MR. COMEY TWEETED
TO THE PRESS HE BETTER HOPE
THERE ARE NO TAPES OF THE
CONVERSATIONS.
THE WHITE HOUSE HAS FAILED TO
ELABORATE ON THAT THIS
WEEKEND.
BUT WE ARE TOLD BY SENATOR
MARK WARNER IF THOSE TAPES DO
INDEED EXIST, CONGRESS WANTS
THEM.
JULIE.
JULIE: VERY INTERESTING.
WHAT MORE DO WE KNOW ABOUT
NORTH KOREA'S MISSILE LAUNCH?
WAS IT SUCCESSFUL?
IT APPEARS TO HAVE BEEN.
SOUTH KOREA'S REPORTING THAT
THIS LAUNCH WENT ABOUT
435 MILES.
IF THAT'S TRUE, IT WOULD BE
CONSIDERED A SUCCESS.
A PENTAGON OFFICIAL CONFIRMS
THE FOX NEWS THAT NORTH KOREA
LAUNCHED SOME TYPE OF
BALLISTIC MISSILE THAT
OFFICIAL SAYS THE U.S. PACIFIC
COMMAND AND STRATEGIC COMMAND
ARE STILL SATISFYING.
IF THIS INITIAL REPORTING
BEARS OUT, THIS WOULD BE
KIM JONG-UN'S FIFTH ATTEMPT AT
THE BALLISTIC LAUNCH THIS PAST
MONTH AND HIS SUCCESSFUL ONE.
A NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM HAS
BEGIN OVER THE DETAILS WITH
MR. TRUMP HERE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THE TIMING, THOUGH, JULIE, IS
VERY CURIOUS ON THIS.
THIS COMES ON THE SAME DAY
THAT A NORTH KOREAN SENIOR
DIPLOMAT SAID THAT THE NORTH
WOULD BE INTERESTED IN SITTING
DOWN WITH U.S. OFFICIALS IF
CONDITIONS WERE SET RIGHT.
JULIE.
.
JULIE: ALL RIGHT, CAROLINE,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
AND FOR MORE ON ALL OF THIS,
TUNE IN LATER TONIGHT TO JUDGE
JENIN PIRO'S CONVERSATION WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP WHERE HE ALSO
ADDRESSES HIS REMARKS ABOUT
ENDING LIVE WHITE HOUSE PRESS
BRIEFINGS.
TRUMP: WHEN WE HAVE THOSE
PRESS CONFERENCES, I ACTUALLY
SAID WE SHOULDN'T HAVE THEM
BECAUSE SARAH HUCKABEE --
>> 100 YEARS WE'VE BEEN
DOING.
YOU CAN'T PUT AN END TO THAT.
>> THERE'S NEVER BEEN ACTION
LIKE THIS.
THIS IS CRAZY.
I MEAN, WE'RE GETTING HIGHER
RATINGS -- THEY'RE GETTING
HIGHER RATINGS ON THIS PRESS
CONFERENCES.
>> WOULD YOU SERIOUSLY
CONSIDER STOPPING THESE PRESS
SESSIONS?
>> NO, WE WOULD DO IT IN A
DIFFERENT WAY.
JULIE: YOU CAN SEE THE REST OF
THAT CONVERSATION TONIGHT ON
JUSTICE WITH JUDGE JENIN, IT
AIRS 9:00 P.M. EASTERN RIGHT
HERE ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
SO THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT IS
INTERVIEWING CANDIDATES.
THAT'S GOING ON ALL DAY TODAY
TO TAKE OVER THE REIGNS OF THE
FBI.
AND THERE ARE NOW AT LEAST
EIGHT NAMES TOSSED IN THE
MIX.
THIS AFTER THE FIRING OF JAMES
COMEY, THE FBI DIRECTOR.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYING THE
WHITE HOUSE COULD NAME COMEY'S
REPLACEMENT AS EARLY AS
FRIDAY.
ALLISON BARBER JOINS US LIVE
FROM WASHINGTON OUTSIDE OF THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE.
ALLISON, EIGHT INTERVIEWEES.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT IS IT.
THERE WILL BE NONE TOMORROW.
ANYONE TALKING AS THEY LEAVE?
>> NO.
MOST OF THEM AREN'T EVEN
STOPPING THEIR CARS.
AT BEST, THEY ARE SAYING NO
COMMENT IN THE LAST HOUR,
THOUGH, WE HAVE HAD TWO LAST
MINUTE INTERVIEW ADDITIONS.
ONE IS A FORMER HOMELAND
SECURITY ADVISER TO GEORGE W.
BUSH AND THE OTHER IS A FORMER
MICHIGAN CONGRESSMAN MIKE
RODGERS, WE BELIEVE THAT'S THE
CAP FOR TODAY.
AS YOU SAID, THAT WOULD PUT US
AT EIGHT.
SOURCES ARE DESCRIBING THESE
MEETINGS AS SUBSTANTIVE
DISCUSSIONS.
GREAT CANDIDATES, SUPREMELY
WELL-QUALIFIED.
NOW, THE ADMINISTRATION IS
REPORTEDLY CONSIDERING ABOUT A
DOZEN CANDIDATES FOR THIS
JOB.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL AND A
DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
ALREADY INTERVIEWED A HANDFUL
OF THEM TODAY, INCLUDING
ACTING FBI DIRECTOR ANDREW
MCCABE, MICHAEL GARCIA, WHO
WAS A JUDGE FROM NEW YORK,
SITTING TEXAS GOVERNOR, ALEX
FISHER, HENRY HUDSON, A
VIRGINIA JUDGE, AND SPECIAL
AGENT ADAM LEE.
NOW, THE LAST INTERVIEW WE'RE
EXPECTING TO SEE TODAY IS MIKE
RODGERS.
HE SHOULD BE HERE WITHIN THE
HOUR.
HE RECEIVED A VERY BIG
ENDORSEMENT TODAY FROM THE FBI
AGENTS ASSOCIATION.
THEY REPRESENT A LOT OF ACTIVE
AND A FORMER FBI AGENT MIKE
RODGERS WAS IN THE FBI HIMSELF
BEFORE HE LEFT TO GO INTO
POLITICS.
JULIE.
.
JULIE: ALL RIGHT.  AND WHAT IS
THE TIMETABLE FOR ALL OF
THIS?
COULD THE ADMINISTRATION MAKE
A DECISION SOON?
>> WELL, PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
THAT IT'S POSSIBLE THERE COULD
BE A DECISION AS EARLY AS THIS
WEEK.
TAKE A LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID
ON AIR FORCE ONE.
>> ALMOST ALL OF THEM ARE VERY
WELL KNOWN.  YOU KNOW, THEY'VE
BEEN VETTED OVER THEIR
LIFETIME, ESSENTIALLY.
BUT VERY WELL KNOWN.
HIGHLY RESPECTED.
REALLY TALENTED PEOPLE.
AND THAT'S WHAT WE WANT OF THE
FBI.
>> THE FBI DIRECTOR IS A
POSITION THAT TYPICALLY LASTS
FOR TEN YEARS AND BEFORE THAT
TENURE CAN BEGIN, THE
CANDIDATE WOULD NEED SENATE
CONFIRMATION.
JULIE, BACK TO YOU.
JULIE: ALL RIGHT, ELLISON,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
A FOX NEWS ALERT WITH THE
PENTAGON CONFIRMING RIGHT NOW
NORTH KOREA HAS LAUNCHED SOME
KIND OF BALLISTIC MISSILE.
THEY APPARENTLY TEST FIRED IT
EARLY SUNDAY MORNING FROM A
PROVINCE IN THE WESTERN PART
OF THE COUNTRY.
WE ARE AWAITING THE PENTAGON'S
RESPONSE AND ASSESSMENT.
WE ARE ALSO AWAITING A
RESPONSE FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
ON ALL OF THIS.
THIS LATEST LAUNCH COMES AMID
HEIGHTENED TENSIONS BETWEEN
THE U.S. AND KIM JONG-UN AFTER
A SERIES OF FAILED LAUNCH
ATTEMPTS.
AND PRESIDENT TRUMP'S, IN
ESSENCEPRESIDENTPRESIDENT
TRUMP'S INSISTENCE ALL OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE.
WOULD BE WILLING TO ENGAGE IN
DIALOGUE WITH THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IF THE
CONDITIONS WERE RIGHT.
JOINING ME NOW WITH ANALYSIS
ON ALL OF THIS, JORDAN, AN
EXPERT ON ASIA, AUTHOR OF
NUCLEAR SHOWDOWN, NORTH KOREA
TAKES ON THE WORLD.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR
TALKING TO US.
NOT THE FIRST TIME WE'VE HAD
TO TALK HERE UNDER THESE SORT
OF CONDITIONS IN THAT NORTH,
ONCE AGAIN, HAS TEST FIRED
ANOTHER MISSILE IN THE PAST
AND, IN FACT, IN THE LAST
MONTH, YOU THOUGHT PERHAPS IT
WAS A FAILED LAUNCH THAT WAS
BEING REPORTED BUT YOU, IN
FACT, THOUGHT IT WAS
INTENTIONAL FOR IT TO LAND ON
NORTH KOREA'S SOIL SO THAT THE
EVIDENCE WOULDN'T BE
ACCESSIBLE TO OTHERS.
WHAT DO YOU THINK HAPPENED
HERE?
>> WELL, 435 MILES IS A
SUCCESSFUL TEST, AND I THINK
WHAT THE NORTH KOREAN'S ARE
DOING IS BY THE TIMING OF THIS
LAUNCH, THEY ARE THINKING THAT
THAT IS GOING TO HELP THEM GET
THESE NEGOTIATIONS STARTED.
THE ONE THING NORTH KOREA
SEEMS TO WANT, BECAUSE WE'VE
SEEN IN THE LAST TWO OR THREE
DAYS A NUMBER OF INITIATIVES
IN THIS REGARD, THEY SEEM TO
WANT RELIEF FROM SANCTIONS.
AND OF COURSE, PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS GOING THE OTHER WAY WANTING
TO PUT ON TOUGHER SANCTIONS ON
NORTH KOREA, SO THIS IS COMING
TO A HEAD.
AND I THINK THE MISSILE LAUNCH
WAS AN ATTEMPT AGAINST THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION AND MOON,
THE NEW PRESIDENT OF
SOUTH KOREA TO THE BARGAINING
TABLE.
JULIE: SO YOU THINK THIS WAS
AN INTENTIONAL MESSAGE?
THIS TEST LAUNCH TODAY WAS AN
INTENTIONAL MESSAGE TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP?
>> YES.  BECAUSE, YOU KNOW, WE
DIDN'T SEE A MISSILE LAUNCH IN
THE RUN-UP TO THE SOUTH KOREAN
ELECTIONS.
AND THE REASON IS THAT THE
CANDIDATE THAT NORTH KOREA
WANTED WHO EVENTUALLY WON WAS
LEADING.
AND I THINK THEY WANTED TO
PREVENT ANYTHING FROM
HAPPENING THAT WOULD DERAIL
HIS CANDIDACY.
NOW THAT MOON IS ACTUALLY
PRESIDENT OF SOUTH KOREA, WE
KNOW THAT MOON WANTS TO START
TALKS WITH NORTH KOREA.
HE ALSO WANTS TO PROVIDE AIDE
TO THE NORTH KOREAN'S.
SO I THINK THE NORTH KOREAN'S
RIGHT NOW THINK THAT THIS IS A
PERFECT TIME FOR THEM TO
REALLY CORRAL THE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY,
INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES.
GET THEM TO SIT DOWN AND DO
WHAT NORTH KOREA WANTS.
JULIE: IN LATE APRIL, THE
PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP HAD
WARNED IN AN INTERVIEW TO
REUTERS THAT A QUOTE MAJOR,
MAJOR CONFLICT WITH THE NORTH
WAS POSSIBLE, BUT THAT HE
WOULD PREFER A DIPLOMATIC
OUTCOME TO THE DISPUTE OVER
ITS NUCLEAR MISSILE PROGRAMS.
AND THEN WE HEAR ABOUT THIS
PERSON FROM THE REGION FROM
THAT REGION SAYING THEY WOULD
CONSIDER SITTING DOWN WITH THE
U.S.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID HE WOULD
IF THE CONDITIONS WERE RIGHT.
WHAT IS ALL OF THIS?
>> WELL, I THINK ALL OF THIS
RIGHT NOW IS REALLY CONFUSION
ON EVERYONE'S PART.
YOU HAVE THE ADMINISTRATION
RIGHT NOW CONSUMED BY THE
COMEY CRISIS.
THE NORTH KOREAN'S SEE THAT,
AND I THINK THAT THEY BELIEVE
THAT THEY CAN GIVE PRESIDENT
TRUMP AN OUT TO SORT OF GIVE
HIM HEADLINES THAT HE WOULD
PREFER TO HAVE.
NOW, I THINK THE
NORTH KOREAN'S ARE TIMING THIS
WRONG.
BUT NONETHELESS, THAT'S THE
WAY THEY THINK.
THEY THINK IN WAYS WHICH ARE
VERY DIFFERENT THAN THE WAYS
WE DO, AND SO I THINK
SOMETIMES THEY GET THEMSELVES
INTO TROUBLE.
BUT NONETHELESS, IN THEIR WAY
OF THINKING, THEY BELIEVE THIS
IS A GOOD TIME RIGHT NOW TO
PUT THE U.S. ON THE BACK FEET.
JULIE: YOU HAVE SAID TO ME IN
THE PAST THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS TRIED TO COAX THE CHINESE
TO HELP ON NORTH KOREA.
TRIED TO FLATTER THE CHINESE,
PRESIDENT PING, AND HE'S
IGNORED BLATANT CHINESE
SUPPORT.
WHAT DO WE DO WITH CHINA?
WHAT MESSAGE DO WE SEND TO
THEM?
AND WAS OUR MESSAGE THAT WE
SENT TO SYRIA STRONG ENOUGH TO
SEND A MESSAGE TO NORTH KOREA
THAT WE MEAN BUSINESS?
>> YEAH.  I THINK PRESIDENT
TRUMP NEEDS TO GIVE THE
CHINESE A DEADLINE.
AS YOU POINT OUT, THEY
FLATTERED THE CHINESE RULER
AND ALSO HAS FLATTERED
KIM JONG-UN LAST WEEK SAYING
THAT KIM IS A SMART COOKIE,
THAT TRUMP WOULD BE HONORED TO
TALK TO THE NORTH KOREAN
LEADER.
SO CLEARLY, THIS IS AN ATTEMPT
I THINK TO AT LEAST ESTABLISH
A DIALOGUE PATH.
BUT, YOU KNOW, PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS SAID VERY CLEARLY THAT IF
THE CHINESE DON'T HELP THAT IF
THE NORTH KOREAN'S DON'T
DISARM, THAT HE WILL DO THIS
ON HIS OWN AND THAT THE UNITED
STATES HAS THE ABILITY TO DO
THAT.
THAT'S A THREAT, OF COURSE,
AND THAT'S HANGING OVER THE
HEADS OF THE NORTH KOREAN'S
WHO OBVIOUSLY WANT TO PREVENT
THAT EVENTUALITY.
SO I THINK THEY'RE TRYING TO
SEE RIGHT NOW IF THEY CAN
ACTUALLY SIT DOWN AND TALK.
YOU KNOW, THE CHINESE HAVE
ALWAYS WANTED TO TALK.
NOW THE SOUTH KOREANS WANT TO
TALK.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS OPEN TO THE
IDEA OF TALKING.
SO IT SEEMS AT THIS POINT FOR
NEGOTIATIONS.
I THINK NEGOTIATIONS ARE
PREMATURE.
YOU WON'T TALK TO THE
NORTH KOREANS UNTIL THEY KNOW
THEY'RE DEFEATED.
WE'RE A LONG WAY FROM THAT.
JULIE: IT'S INTERESTING YOU
MENTION SOUTH KOREA WITH THE
FIRST LIBERAL PRESIDENT TO BE
ELECTED RECENTLY AND THAT
PRESIDENT WANTING TO TALK TO
NORTH KOREA, WE HAVEN'T SEEN
THAT.
SO YOU HAVE THESE THREE
NATIONS, POTENTIALLY, IN FOR
TALKS.
OF COURSE, THAT WILL TAKE A
LOT OF TIME AND NOT HAVING TO
SEE THESE SORT OF BLATANT
DISRESPECT SLAP IN THE FACE TO
THE WEST EACH TIME TEST FIRES
A MISSILE.
JORDAN, GREAT TO HAVE YOU ON,
AND WE LOOK FORWARD TO THE
NEXT TIME.
NOT TO A LAUNCH BUT TO OUR
INTERVIEW.
>> THANK YOU.
JULIE: THANK YOU.
RIGHT NOW HOSPITALS IN THE UK
STRUGGLING TO RESTORE THEIR
COMPUTER SYSTEMS AFTER A
MASSIVE CYBER ATTACK.
HOW HEALTH CARE FACILITIES AND
THOUSANDS OF OTHER COMPANIES
FELL VICTIM ACROSS THE GLOBE.
PLUS, SOME BIG NAMES AT
COMMENCEMENTS NATIONWIDE.
BUT ONE FORCED TO DROP OUT
AFTER OPPOSITION FROM STUDENTS
AND PROTESTS AGAINST ANOTHER
SPEAKER.
Dear Predictable,
There's no other
way to say this.
It's over.
I've found a permanent
escape from monotony.
Together, we are
perfectly balanced,
our senses awake,
our hearts racing as one.
I know this is sudden,
but they say: If you
love something...
set it free.
See you around, Giulia
♪
Anyone ever have occasional
constipation,diarrhea,
gas or bloating?
She does.
Help defend against
those digestive issues.
Take Phillips' Colon Health
Probiotic Caps daily
with three types of
good bacteria.
400 likes? Wow!
Try Phillips'
Colon Health.
AtMore than one flavor, oruch
texture, or color.ing.
A good clean salad is so much
more than green.
And with Panera catering, more
for your event.
Panera. Food as it should be.
More "Doing Chores For Dad"
per roll
More "Earning Something
You Love" per roll
Bounty is more absorbent,
so the roll can last 50% longer
than the leading ordinary brand.
So you get more "Life" per roll.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker Upper
I have age-related maculare
degeneration, AMD,
he told me to look at this
grid every day.
And we came up with a plan
to help reduce
my risk
of progression,
including PreserVision
AREDS 2.
My doctor said
PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
the National Eye
Institute recommends
to help reduce
the risk of progression of
moderate to advanced AMD
after 15 years
of clinical studies.
PreserVision
AREDS 2.
Because my eyes
are everything.
You wTo progress.move.
To not just accept what you see,
but imagine something new.
At Invisalign®,
we use the most advanced teeth
straightening technology
to help you find the next
amazing version of yourself.
It's time to unleash
your secret weapon.
It's there, right
under your nose.
Get to your best smile
up to 50% faster.
Visit Invisalign.com to
get started today.
.
JULIE: FOR THE SECOND TIME
THIS WEEK, U.S. OFFICIALS SAY
A RUSSIAN FIGHTER JET FLEW
CLOSE TO A NAVY PLANE.
THEY SAY IT HAPPENED FRIDAY
MORNING ABOUT 30 MILES FROM
THE RUSSIAN BORDER OVER THE
BLACK SEA.
A RUSSIAN JET FLEW ABOUT
40 FEET FROM A U.S. NAVY PLANE
JUST LIKE THE ONE YOU SEE
HERE.
NOW, IT OCCURRED IN
INTERNATIONAL AIRSPACE AND A
PENTAGON OFFICIAL CALLS THIS
SECOND INCIDENT QUOTE SAFE AND
PROFESSIONAL.
THE U.S. HAS STEPPED UP RECON
FLIGHTS SINCE 2014.  WELL,
COMPANIES ACROSS THE GLOBE
RIGHT NOW RACING TO RECOVER
AFTER A MASSIVE CYBER ATTACK.
BRITAIN PUBLIC HEALTH SYSTEM
WAS ONE OF THE VERY HARDEST
HIT.
BUT THE ATTACK ALSO TARGETED
GOVERNMENT AGENCIES AND
BUSINESSES IN NEARLY 100
COUNTRIES.
HACKERS USING MALICIOUS
SOFTWARE STOLEN FROM THE NSA
TO CONDUCT WHAT IS BELIEVED TO
BE THE LARGEST RANSOMWARE
ATTACK ON RECORD.
>> WHAT WE'VE NOW GOT IS A
BUNCH OF 21ST CENTURY HIGHWAY
ROBBERS THAT HAVE HACKED INTO
OUR NHS AND BASICALLY OFFERING
PROTECTION MONEY TO GET THE
INFORMATION BACK IN ORDER TO
TREAT CANCER PATIENTS OR
ANYBODY ELSE.
IT'S UNBELIEVABLY DISGUSTING.
JULIE: LIVE FROM OUR NEW YORK
STUDIO HERE AND LET'S JUST
TALK ABOUT WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT
THIS ATTACK BECAUSE IT WAS
VERY FAR REACHING.
>> I MEAN, THIS IS AN
UNPRECEDENTED ATTACK, JULIE,
UNLIKE ANYTHING WE'VE EVER
SEEN.
IT IS THE LARGEST ATTACK OF
THIS TYPE AND HACKERS USED
MESSAGES THAT WERE FIRST
DEPLOYED BY THE NATIONAL
SECURITY AGENCY IN SECRET BUT
OF COURSE THESE MESSAGES WERE
LEAKED ON THE INTERNET WHICH
ALLOWED HACKERS TO THEN USE
IT.
AND AMONG THE TOOLS USED WAS A
MICROSOFT WINDOWS FLAW THE NSA
KNEW ABOUT.
HACKERS EXPLOITED THIS FLAW TO
INFECT COMPUTERS WITH
RANSOMWARE.
IT GETS INTO SPAM E-MAIL OR
ATTACHMENTS, IT LOCKS YOUR
COMPUTER HOLDING IT AND ITS
DATA HOSTAGE UNTIL USER HAS TO
PAY RANSOM.
THIS IS A SCREENSHOT OF WHAT
THE VIRUS DUBBED WANT TO CRY.
IN THIS CASE USERS HAD TO PAY
UP TO $600 TO GET ACCESS
AGAIN.
THE SIDE AND SPEED HITTING
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF COMPUTERS
INCLUDING IN HUNDREDS OF
COMPANIES INCLUDING THE U.S.,
UK, CHINA.
IT AFFECTED FEDEX HERE IN THE
U.S. AND BRITISH HOSPITALS AND
MEDICAL CENTERS.
MANY WERE FORCED TO CANCEL OR
DELAY ROUTINE PROCEDURES LIKE
X-RAYS, VITAL PROCEDURES LIKE
CANCER TREATMENTS AND NO ONE
HAS CLAIMED RESPONSIBILITY.
BUT AS FOR, SAY, IT'S NOT
LIKELY TO BE A GOVERNMENT.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS WE HAVE
TO OFTEN GROUND OURSELVES IN
AS SECURITY PROFESSIONALS IS
ALTHOUGH WE OFTEN HEAR ABOUT
THE NATION STATE ATTACKS
BECAUSE THEY HAVE BECOME
SENSATIONALIZED IN THE NEWS,
THE REALITY IS 80% OF WHAT
WE'RE DEALING WITH ON A
DAY-TO-DAY BASIS IS ORGANIZED
CRIMINAL GANGS.
THIS IS, IN FACT, ONE OF THE
LARGEST ILLEGAL ECONOMIES IN
THE WORLD.
>> IBM IS SATISFYING THE
DAMAGE, JULIE.
JULIE: ALL RIGHT.  SO HOW IS
THIS ATTACK STOPPED?
AND WHAT CAN PEOPLE DO TO
PROTECT THEMSELVES?
>> BOTTOM LINE AMAZING IS THIS
ATTACK WAS STOPPED BY A SAVVY
22-YEAR-OLD BASED RESEARCHER
WHO STOPPED THIS ATTACK USING
A $11 DOMAIN.
THIS ANONYMOUS RESEARCHER
TWEETING I WILL CONFESS THAT I
WAS UNAWARE REGISTERING THE
DOMAIN WILL STOP THE MALWARE
UNTIL AFTER I REGISTERED IT SO
INITIALLY, IT WAS ACCIDENTAL.
THE ADVICE FOR YOU.
DOWNLOAD THE LATEST MICROSOFT
WINDOWS SECURITY UPDATE.
BACK UP YOUR DATA.
DO NOT OPEN SPAM.
STAY SAFE OUT THERE.
THERE ARE LIKELY GOING TO BE
MORE ATTACKS.
JULIE: BRIAN, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
>> OF COURSE.
JULIE: NORTH KOREA FIRST
PROVOCATIVE MOVE SINCE
SOUTH KOREA'S NEWS AND THEIR
NEW PRESIDENT TOOK OVER.
WE ARE CLOSELY MONITORING
THIS.
WE WILL BRING YOU THE VERY
LATEST, AND WE ARE WAITING FOR
THE WHITE HOUSE TO RESPOND.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN BRIEFED
ON THE SITUATION.
WE'LL HAVE MORE AS WE GET IT.
PLUS, WHAT THE POPE IS SAYING
ABOUT PRESIDENT TRUMP AHEAD OF
HIS VISIT AHEAD.
♪
I'm Dr. Kelsey McNeely and some
day you might be
calling me an energy farmer.
♪
Energy lives here.
Z286NZ ZWTZ
Y286NY YWTY
If you have postmenopausal
osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture...
I can tell you
Prolia® is proven to help
protect bones from fracture.
But the real proof?
My doctor said Prolia® helped my
bones get stronger.
Are your bones getting stronger?
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions, like
low blood pressure;
trouble breathing; throat
tightness; face, lip,
or tongue swelling; rash;
itching or hives have happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems,
as severe jaw bone problems may
happen,
or new or unusual pain in your
hip, groin or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
Speak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®,
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects, like low blood calcium;
serious infections, which could
need hospitalization skin
problems;
and severe bone, joint or muscle
pain.
Only Prolia® helps strengthen
and protect bones
with 2 shots a year.
I have proof Prolia® works for
me.
Ask your doctor about Prolia®
today.
.
JULIE: POPE FRANCIS ANSWERING
QUESTIONS ON HIS UP COMING
MEETING WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP
THIS AFTER A TRIP TO PORTUGAL
WHERE HE WAS GREETED BY
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS AS THE
POPE MARKS THE 100TH
ANNIVERSARY OF THE REPORTED
HOLY VISIONS.
JOHN IS LIVE IN OUR MIDDLE
EAST BUREAU WITH MORE.
>> JULIE, HALF A MILLION
PEOPLE ATTENDED POPE FRANCIS'
OPEN AIR MASS CELEBRATION
TODAY IN PORTUGAL.
THIS IS A TOWN, BY THE WAY, OF
ABOUT 11,600 PEOPLE, SO YOU
CAN IMAGINE HOW ABSOLUTELY
PACKED IT WAS.
BUT FOR GOOD REASON.
♪
>> THE POPE WAS THERE TO
CANONIZE THE TWO SHEPPARD
CHILDREN WHO SAID THEY SAW
VISIONS OF THE VIRGIN MARY 100
YEARS AGO AND FRANCISCO.
7 AND 9 AT THE TIME, THEY SAY
THEY SAW THE APPARITION SIX
TIMES BETWEEN MAY 16, 1917 AND
OCTOBER 1ST, 1917, ALONG WITH
THEIR OLDER COUSIN WHO IS ALSO
ON THE WAY.
FRANCISCO DIED IN THE 1918
FLUE PANDEMIC BUT WERE
CANONIZED FOR A TRADITION TO
THEM.
A LITTLE BOY LUCAS WHO FELL
OUT OF A WINDOW IN 2013 IN
BRAZIL WAS NOT EXPECTED TO
SURVIVE OR AT LEAST HAVE BRAIN
DAMAGE, THE MOTHER PRAYED TO
FRANCISCO.
SIX DAYS LATER, LUCAS WOKE UP,
BEGAN TALKING, AND WAS
RELEASED FROM THE HOSPITAL.
THE FAMILY HAD AN EMOTIONAL
MEETING WITH THE POPE TODAY.
POPE FRANCIS ALSO SPENT TIME
WITH A PALESTINIAN IRAQI
FAMILY.
THE SECOND TIME THAT FAMILY IS
MET WITH THE POPE AND THE
FAMILY'S GRANDMOTHER TOLD POPE
FRANCIS THEY HOPE TO SEE HIM
AGAIN AT SOME POINT HERE IN
JERUSALEM.
LAST TIME POPE FRANCIS WAS IN
JERUSALEM WAS BACK IN 2014.
BUT YOU MAY RECALL HE MET WITH
PALESTINIAN AUTHORITY
PRESIDENT AT THE VATICAN THIS
PAST JANUARY.  WELL, PRESIDENT
TRUMP WILL BE HERE IN
JERUSALEM AND ALSO ISRAEL
LATER THIS MONTH.
AND AFTER HERE, HE'LL MEET
WITH POPE FRANCIS ON MAY 24TH
AT THE VATICAN.
BOTH LEADERS HAVE HAD A
RELATIONSHIP CONTRASTING
VIEWS.
BUT POPE FRANCIS TOLD REUTERS
HE WON'T TRY TO SOFTEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S VIEWS ON --
POLICIES ON IMMIGRATION OR THE
ENVIRONMENT.
BUT INSTEAD, LOOK FOR THINGS
IN COMMON.
AND WHEN ASKED WHAT THE WORLD
CAN EXPECT FROM THE MEETING,
THE POPE HAD ONE WORD.
PEACE.
JULIE.
JULIE: JOHN, THANK YOU.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS NOW
ORDERED TO PURSUE THE MOST
SERIOUS CHARGES AGAINST ALL
SUSPECTS.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM ATTORNEY
GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS.
BUT CRITICS OF THE POLICIES
SAY IT IS UNFAIR TO LOWER
LEVEL OFFENDERS.
WE'RE GOING TO EXPLAIN WHAT
THAT MEANS.
NEXT.
PLUS, PRESIDENT TRUMP GOES
BACK TO SCHOOL, OFFERING HIS
ADVICE TO THE CLASS OF 2017.
TRUMP: FOLLOWING YOUR
CONVICTIONS MEANS YOU MUST BE
WILLING TO FACE CRITICISM FROM
THOSE WHO LACK THE SAME
COURAGE TO DO WHAT IS RIGHT.
80 percent of recurrent
ischemic strokes
could be prevented
with the right steps.
And take it from me,
every step counts.
A Bayer aspirin regimen
is one of those steps
in helping prevent
another stroke.
Be sure to talk
to your doctor
before you begin
an aspirin regimen.
in New Herbal Essences
It's Bio:Renew
A blend of sea kelp, aloe
and antioxidants that help
bring your hair back to life.
New Herbal Essences.
Let Life In.
♪
SFX: Engine revving
(Silence)
♪
ARE MAKING THE MOVE TO NISSAN.
BECAUSE OF ROGUE,
THE BEST SELLING SUV IN AMERICA.
TITAN, WITH AMERICA'S BEST
TRUCK WARRANTY.
AND THE MOST ADVANCED
SAFETY FEATURES ON ALITMA
AND OUR BEST SELLING MODELS.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE AMERICA'S
FASTEST-GROWING AUTO BRAND.
GET 0% FINANCING
FOR UP TO 72 MONTHS
ON 11 MODELS.
♪
Scalpel.
I have no idea
what I'm doing.
I'm just a TV doctor.
I never went
to college.
(Scream)
I don't do blood.
But now, thanks to Cigna,
I can do more than
just look the part.
Is that a foot?
We are the TV
Doctors of America.
And we're partnering with
Cigna to help save lives.
By getting you
to a real doctor
for an annual check-up.
So go, know, and take
control of your health.
Doctor poses.
CignTogether, all the way.
Termites,
We're on the move.24/7.
Roger.
Hey Rick, all good?
Oh yeah, we're good.
We're good.
Termites never stop trying to
get in,
we never stop working to keep
them out.
Terminix.
Defenders of Home.
Essential for him,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate did not
work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections,
lymphoma and other cancers have
happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR if you
have an infection.
Tears in the stomach or
intestines,
low blood cell counts and higher
liver tests and
cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ
XR, and monitor
certain liver tests. Tell your
doctor if you were
in a region where fungal
infections are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
Fine for some.
But for you, one pill a day may
provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor about XELJANZ
XR. An "Unjection™".
.
JULIE: THE FOX REPORT, IT IS
THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR.
TIME NOW FOR THE TOP OF THE
NEWS.
THE PENTAGON CONFIRMING TO FOX
NEWS TONIGHT NORTH KOREA HAS
INDEED LAUNCHED A BALLISTIC
MISSILE.
IT HAPPENED JUST BEFORE DAWN
EARLY SUNDAY MORNING.
NORTH KOREA TIME.
SOUTH KOREA REPORTS IT
TRAVELED ABOUT 435 MILES,
WHICH WOULD CASE A SUCCESSFUL
LAUNCH.
THE NATIONAL SECURITY COUNCIL
SAYS PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS BEEN
BRIEFED.
WE ARE AWAITING A RESPONSE
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
MEANWHILE, THE PRESIDENT GAVE
HIS FIRST COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS
SINCE TAKING THE PRESIDENCY,
IN VIRGINIA TODAY HE CALLED
THE GRADUATES QUOTE THE NEXT
GENERATION OF AMERICAN LEADERS
AND SHARED LESSONS HE HAS
LEARNED SINCE BECOMING
PRESIDENT.
AND BACK IN WASHINGTON.
IT'S BEEN BUSY.
THE ADMINISTRATION WASTING NO
TIME IN THE SEARCH FOR A NEW
CHIEF OF THE COUNTRY'S TOP LAW
ENFORCEMENT AGENCY.
AT LEAST SIX CANDIDATES TO
LEAD THE FBI VISITED THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT TODAY FOR
INTERVIEWS AS THE
ADMINISTRATION LOOKS TO
REPLACE JAMES COMEY, FIRED
SUDDENLY BY THE PRESIDENT THIS
WEEK.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS THE WHITE
HOUSE COULD NAME COMEY'S
SUCCESSOR AS EARLY AS FRIDAY.
SPEAKING OF JAMES COMEY, IT
WAS A ONE-TOPIC OF A WIDE
RANGING DISCUSSION BETWEEN
JUDGE JENIN PIRO AND PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
THEY SAT DOWN AT THE WHITE
HOUSE FOR A CONVERSATION THAT
YOU CAN SEE IN JUST ABOUT 90
MINUTES HERE ONLY ON THE FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
THE PAIR DISCUSSED THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION, THE SEARCH FOR
A NEW FBI DIRECTOR, AND THE
PRESIDENT'S FRUSTRATIONS WITH
THE NEWS MEDIA.
LISTEN.
>> YOUR AGENDA IS NOT GETTING
OUT BECAUSE PEOPLE ARE CAUGHT
UP ON THE COMEY ISSUE AND
RIDICULOUS --
TRUMP: I AGREE.
I AGREE.
>> HOW DO YOU GET RID OF
COMEY --
TRUMP: I THINK.
>> WHO IN THE PRESS OFFICE
SAYS ONE THING, THE VICE
PRESIDENT SAYS ANOTHER THING.
HOW DO WE RESOLVE THAT?
TRUMP: WELL, THAT'S AN
INTERESTING SITUATION.
I ACTUALLY SAID TODAY, LET'S
NOT DO ANY MORE PRESS
BRIEFINGS.  YOU KNOW, THEY'RE
GETTING TREMENDOUS RATINGS AND
ESPECIALLY THE FAKE MEDIA.
THEY'RE GOING CRAZY.
THEY ARE GOING CRAZY.
AND THEY'LL BE IN THE ROOM,
AND YOU HAVE TO SEE THE WAY
THEY ASK QUESTIONS, I WANT.
I WANT.
SCREAMING AND THERE'S NEVER
BEEN ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
IN ALL FAIRNESS TO SEAN AND
SARAH HUCKABEE AND ANYBODY WHO
STOOD UP THERE.
THEY DON'T KNOW ME.
I'M A VERY ACTIVE PRESIDENT.
I'M DEALING WITH CHINA.  I'M
DEALING WITH JAPAN.
I'M DEALING WITH NORTH KOREA.
I'M DEALING WITH ALL OF THESE
DIFFERENT THINGS.
RUSSIA CAME TO SEE ME, THE
FOREIGN MINISTER THE OTHER DAY
AND RIGHT AFTER THAT, THEY
DIDN'T SAY THIS BUT RIGHT
AFTER THAT, THE FOREIGN
MINISTER FROM UKRAINE CAME
IN.
I SAID FELLAS, YOU'VE GOT TO
MAKE PEACE.
YOU'VE GOT TO GET PEACE.
THEY ONLY TALKED ABOUT RUSSIA
COMING IN.  OKAY?  AND WE TOOK
PICTURES, THEY TOOK PICTURES.
WE RELEASED THE PICTURES.
THEY MADE A BIG DEAL ABOUT
IT.
EVERYBODY KNEW HE WAS COMING,
AND HE WAS SCHEDULED TO COME.
BUT THEY DIDN'T TALK ABOUT
UKRAINE.
THE POINT IS THIS:  WHEN WE
HAVE THOSE PRESS CONFERENCES,
I ACTUALLY SAY WE SHOULDN'T
HAVE THEM BECAUSE SARAH
HUCKABEE.
>> 100 YEARS WE'VE BEEN
DOING.
TRUMP: NO.  NO.
BUT THERE'S NEVER BEEN ACTION
LIKE THIS.
THIS IS CRAZY.
I MEAN, WE'RE GETTING HIGHER
RATINGS -- THEY'RE GETTING
HIRE RATINGS ON THOSE PRESS
CONFERENCES --
>> WOULD YOU SERIOUSLY
CONSIDER STOPPING THESE PRESS
SESSIONS?
TRUMP: NO, WE DO IT IN A
DIFFERENT WAY.
>> HOW?
TRUMP: WE DO IT THROUGH A
PIECE OF PAPER WITH A
PERFECTLY, ACCURATE, BEAUTIFUL
ANSWER.
I'LL GIVE YOU AN ANSWER.
>> IN WRITING?
TRUMP: THEY ASK 100 QUESTIONS
OR 50 QUESTIONS OR 20
QUESTIONS.
IF THEY GET ONE OUT OF 50,
JUST A LITTLE BIT OFF, 5%,
10%, 20%, IT'S THE NEXT DAY
IT'S A FRONT-PAGE STORY IN
EVERY NEWSPAPER.
>> RIGHT.
SO?
TRUMP: PRESS CONFERENCES
WEREN'T EVEN COVERED FOR
OBAMA, PRACTICAL.
THEY WERE ON C-SPAN AND
C-SPAN2 AND, YOU KNOW, THERE
WAS NOTHING GOING ON.
>> BUT WILL YOU PUT AN END TO
THEM?
TRUMP: THESE PRESS CONFERENCES
ARE, LIKE, THE BIGGEST THING
ON DAYTIME TELEVISION.
>> THEY ARE.
TRUMP: OKAY?  YOU SEE THE
RATINGS.
THEY'RE BLOWING AWAY
EVERYTHING ON JUST ABOUT I
THINK EVERYTHING ON DAYTIME
TELEVISION.
WHAT I LOVE TO DO IS STOP
THEM.
IT'S NOT FAIR TO THE PEOPLE.
I'LL GIVE YOU -- LOOK, I AM A
VERY ACTIVE PERSON.
I HAVE A LOT OF VERY POSITIVE
THINGS GOING ON RIGHT UP HERE
FOR THIS COUNTRY.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE FOR A PERSON
OR TWO PEOPLE OR THREE PEOPLE
WHO ARE PRESS PEOPLE TO COVER
EVERY ASPECT OF WHAT I'M
THINKING AND WHAT I'M DOING.
AND I THINK IT'S UNFAIR.
AND IF THEY GET JUST A LITTLE
BIT WRONG, THEY DON'T MEAN TO,
THEY'RE LIARS.
THEY'RE HORRIBLE PEOPLE.
THEY'RE LIARS, THE PRESS
GOES.
AND IT BECOMES A BIG STORY FOR
TWO OR THREE DAYS.
AND IT'S VERY, VERY UNFAIR TO
A PERSON IN THAT JOB.
I THINK THAT'S REALLY A TOUGH
JOB, TO BE HONEST.
ESPECIALLY FOR ME BECAUSE I'M
HAVING MEETING AFTER MEETING.
I'M CUTTING THE PRICE OF THE
AIRPLANES WITH LOCKHEED.
I'M CUTTING THE PRICE OF
AIRPLANES WITH BOEING.
I'M DOING ALL OF THESE
THINGS.
I'M MAKING DEALS WITH CHINA.
I'M TRYING TO SOLVE A PROBLEM
IN NORTH KOREA, WHICH IS A
REALLY BIG PROBLEM.
>> ARE YOU MOVING SO QUICKLY
THAT YOUR COMMUNICATIONS
DEPARTMENT CANNOT KEEP UP WITH
YOU?
TRUMP: YES.
THAT'S TRUE.
>> SO WHAT DO WE DO ABOUT
THAT?
TRUMP: WE DON'T HAVE PRESS
CONFERENCES, AND WE DO.
>> YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
TRUMP: WELL, JUST DON'T HAVE
THEM UNLESS I HAVE THEM EVERY
TWO WEEKS, AND I DO THEM
MYSELF.
WE DON'T HAVE THEM.
I THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU HAVE A LEVEL
OF HOSTILITY THAT'S
INCREDIBLE, AND IT'S VERY
UNFAIR.
SARAH HUCKABEE IS A LOVELY
YOUNG WOMAN.
YOU KNOW SEAN SPICER.
HE IS A LOVELY HUMAN BEING.
HE'S A NICE MAN.
>> IS HE YOUR PRESS SECRETARY
TODAY AND TOMORROW?
TRUMP: YEAH, HE IS.
>> WILL HE BE HERE TOMORROW?
TRUMP: WELL, HE'S DOING A GOOD
JOB, BUT HE'S GETTING BEAT
UP.
>> WILL HE BE THERE TOMORROW?
TRUMP: HE'S BEEN THERE FROM
THE BEGINNING.
>> IS HE --
TRUMP: HE JUST GETS BEAT UP BY
THESE PEOPLE.
JULIE: REMEMBER TO WATCH JUDGE
JENIN'S INTERVIEW WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP RIGHT HERE ON
FOX NEWS CHANNEL TONIGHT AT
9:00 P.M. EASTERN.
I HAVE A FEELING IT WILL BE A
LITTLE BIT DIFFERENT THAN MOST
INTERVIEWS YOU'VE SEEN HIM
DO.
PRETTY ENTERTAINING.
THAT WAS GOOD STUFF.
THANK YOU.  WELL, PRESIDENT
TRUMP GIVING HIS FIRST
COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS AS
PRESIDENT IN FRONT OF A RECORD
CROWD.
IN FRONT OF ABOUT 50,000
PEOPLE TELLING GRADUATES NEVER
GIVE UP TO THEIR DREAMS AND TO
CHALLENGE THE STATUS QUO.
KEVIN HAS MORE FROM LYNCHBURG,
VIRGINIA.
>> JULIE, GREAT TO BE WITH YOU
HERE IN THE PICTURESQUE
PENNSYLVANIA.
THE PRESIDENT'S VERY FIRST
COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS AS
COMMANDER-IN-CHIEF.
IT'S ACTUALLY, BY THE WAY, HIS
THIRD VISIT HERE TO THIS
CAMPUS.
YOU MAY RECALL HE WAS HERE NOT
THAT MANY MONTHS AGO AS A
CANDIDATE FOR THE HIGHEST
OFFICE IN THE LAND.
AND TODAY, HE DREW FROM THAT
PERSONAL EXPERIENCE TO
ENCOURAGE THE STUDENTS TO BE
THEMSELVES, TO BE BOLD.
DON'T LISTEN TO THE CRITICS
AND THE NAYSAYERS, ESPECIALLY
NOW AS THEY LOOK FORWARD TO
WRITING THEIR OWN NARRATIVE AS
YOUNG ADULTS.
>> NOTHING IS EASIER OR MORE
PATHETIC THAN BEING A CRITIC.
BECAUSE THERE ARE PEOPLE THAT
CAN'T GET THE JOB DONE.
BUT THE FUTURE BELONGS TO THE
DREAMERS.
NOT TO THE CRITICS.
>> WE MENTION THE OVERWHELMING
SUPPORT THE PRESIDENT RECEIVED
HERE AMONG THE CROWD.
ABOUT 50,000 PEOPLE IN ALL IN
THE STADIUM AND AROUND IT
TAKING IN THE PRESIDENT'S
REMARKS THIS AFTERNOON.
HE ALSO TOLD THE STUDENTS
HERE, AND I THOUGHT THIS WAS
AN IMPORTANT NOTE.
DON'T BE AFRAID TO BE THE
OUTSIDER BECAUSE PEOPLE WILL
ALWAYS TELL YOU WHAT YOU CAN'T
DO.
BUT DON'T LET THAT SLOW YOU
DOWN.
>> CARRY YOURSELF WITH DIGNITY
AND PRIDE.
DEMAND THE BEST FROM YOURSELF
AND BE TOTALLY UNAFRAID TO
CHALLENGE ENTRENCHED INTEREST
IN FAILED POWER STRUCTURES.
DOES THAT SOUND FAMILIAR, BY
THE WAY?
THE MORE PEOPLE TELL YOU IT'S
NOT POSSIBLE, THAT IT CAN'T BE
DONE, THE MORE YOU SHOULD BE
ABSOLUTELY DETERMINED TO PROVE
THEM WRONG.
>> AMONG THE SHOUTOUTS, THE
PRESIDENT OFFERED TODAY, HE
THANKED VETERANS FOR THEIR
SUPPORT.
AND, BY THE WAY, THERE WERE
THOUSANDS OF THEM GRADUATING
TODAY HERE AS WELL.
HE ALSO SAID, HEY, DON'T
FORGET.
IT'S SUNDAY COMING UP.
THAT'S MOTHER'S DAY.
THANK YOU TO THE MOMS FOR
BEING SO SUPPORTIVE AND
GETTING THOSE STUDENTS TO THIS
POINT.
BUT IN PARTICULAR, THERE WAS A
HEARTFELT CONGRATULATIONS TO
JIM KELLY.
YOU MAY REMEMBER HE WAS A
QUARTERBACK OF THE BUFFALO
BILLS.
OH, THOSE MANY YEARS AGO
MAKING IT TO SUPER BOWL AFTER
SUPER BOWL.
HE'S BEATEN CANCER TWICE.
HIS DAUGHTER AMONG THE
GRADUATING CLASS OF 2017.
A DAY SHE WON'T SOON FORGET,
AND I THINK THAT WILL
CERTAINLY BE THE CASE FOR THE
MANY THOUSANDS WHO WERE HERE
IN ATTENDANCE.
JULIE.
JULIE: KEVIN, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.  WELL, FEDERAL
PROSECUTORS ARE NOW UNDER
ORDERS TO GO AFTER THE MOST
SERIOUS CHARGES POSSIBLE FOR
MOST ACCUSED CRIMINALS.
NOW, THE MOVE REVERSES SOME
POLICIES FROM THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION, WHICH WERE
MEANT TO FIGHT PRISON
OVERCROWDING.
EXPERTS SAY IT WILL LIKELY PUT
MORE PEOPLE BEHIND BARS FOR
LONGER.
ATTORNEY GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS
PROMISED TO MAKE CRACKING DOWN
ON DRUGS AND VIOLENCE A TOP
PRIORITY AT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT.
HE SAYS THE NEW POLICY WILL
PRODUCE MORE QUOTE CONSISTENCY
IN SENTENCING.
BUT CRITICS SAY LOWER LEVEL
CRIMINALS WILL INSTEAD NOW
FACE UNFAIR MANDATORY MINIMUM
SENTENCES.
PETER DUCEY HAS MORE.
>> YOU DRUG DEALERS ARE GOING
TO PRISON.
>> AND WITH THAT, A TRUMP
CAMPAIGN PROMISE OF LAW AND
ORDER BECAME AN INSTRUCTION
FOR AMERICA'S LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
A TWO-PAGE MEMO FROM THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL TO U.S.
ATTORNEYS WARNS CRIMINALS.
PROSECUTORS WILL NOW ALMOST
ALWAYS PURSUE CHARGES WITH THE
LONGEST POSSIBLE SENTENCES.
AND IT'S MANDATORY MINIMUM
SENTENCES WILL EVEN APPLY TO
DRUG OFFENSES WITH WHICH THE
LAST ADMINISTRATION TRIED TO
BE LEANT AND CONSIDERED
NONVIOLENT.
>> WE'RE RETURNING TO THE
ENFORCEMENT OF THE LAW AS
PASSED BY CONGRESS, PLANE AND
SIMPLE.
IF YOU ARE A DRUG TRAFFICKER,
WE WILL NOT LOOK THE OTHER
WAY.
>> THAT'S A MAJOR CHANGE FROM
A OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
APPROACH DESIGNED TO REDUCE
PRISON POPULATIONS.
>> A PRIMARY DRIVER OF THIS
MASS INCARCERATION PHENOMENON
IS -- OUR DRUG LAWS ARE
MANDATORY MINIMUM SENTENCING
AROUND DRUG LAWS.
>> ONE OF OBAMA'S ATTORNEY
GENERALS ERIC HOLDER NOW SAYS
QUOTE THE POLICY ANNOUNCED
TODAY IS NOT TOUGH ON CRIME,
IT IS DUMB ON CRIME.
BUT THE TRUMP WHITE HOUSE SAYS
THE CHANGE WAS CAREFULLY
CRAFTED.
>> THIS POLICY WAS FORMULATED
AFTER EXTENSIVE CONSULTATION
WITH THE PROSECUTORS THAT
HANDLE THESE CASES EACH AND
EVERY DAY AROUND THE COUNTRY.
>> PRISON REFORM ADVOCATES ARE
ALARMED BY THE PROSPECT OF A
RETURN TO THE WAR ON DRUGS.
>> THE PROBLEM WITH THE WAR ON
DRUGS WAS THAT IT SWEPT UP NOT
JUST PEOPLE ENGAGED IN HIGH
LEVEL DRUG OFFENDING BUT LOTS
OF PEOPLE IN THE LOWER LEVELS
OF THE DRUG TRADE.
THAT HAD VERY LITTLE IMPACT ON
DRUG USE AND ABUSE.
>> ON CAPITOL HILL, DEMOCRATS
AND AT LEAST ONE REPUBLICAN
ARE SCOFFING AT THIS NEW
POLICY TOO.
SENATOR RAND PAUL SAYS QUOTE
MANDATORY MINIMUM SENTENCES
HAVE UNFAIRLY AND
DISPROPORTIONALLY INCARCERATED
TOO MANY MINORITIES FOR TOO
LONG.
A FORMER FEDERAL DRUG SEES
THINGS DIFFERENTLY.
>> WHEN THEY SAY A HOLDER IN
THE CROWD AND PRESIDENT OBAMA
SAY GO EASY ON THIS STUFF,
THEY WANT YOU TO THINK WHAT
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT IS SOME
GUY SITTING IN HIS ROOM TOKING
UP ON A JOINT.
THAT'S NOT THE KIND OF CASES
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT.
THEY DIDN'T PROSECUTE MAJOR
DRUG DEALING CASES.
AND THIS HAS CREATED MORE OF A
PROBLEM.
>> I WAS WITH THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL IN WEST VIRGINIA
YESTERDAY WHEN HE ANNOUNCED A
MORE AGGRESSIVE APPROACH TO
ROUNDING UP DRUG DEALERS.
AND NOW HE'S SAYING WHAT HE
WANTS TO DO ONCE THEY ARE IN
CUSTODY.
SESSIONS IS NOT PROPOSING ANY
NEW LAWS, JUST SAYING THAT
THIS DEPARTMENT WILL NO LONGER
PICK AND CHOOSE WHICH ONES TO
ENFORCE.
>> .
JULIE: PETER DUCEY, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
REPORTING FROM WASHINGTON.
NEW DETAILS JUST IN ABOUT
NORTH KOREA'S LATEST MISSILE
LAUNCH COMING IN FROM U.S.
PACIFIC COMMAND.
WE WILL HAVE THE VERY LATEST
ON THIS BREAKING NEWS STORY
COMING UP RIGHT AFTER THIS
BREAK.
STAY WITH US
Thank you!
Imagine if the things you
bought every day
earned you miles to
get to the places
you really want to go.
With the United MileagePlus
Explorer Card,
you'll get a free checked bag,
2 United Club passes...
Priority boarding...
and 50,000 bonus miles.
Everything you need
for an unforgettable vacation.
The United MileagePlus
Explorer Card.
Imagine where it will take you.
But with my back pain I couldn't
sleep or get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
And now. I'm back!
Aleve PM for a better AM.
Whether it's connecting one of
Or bringing WiFi to 65,000 fans.
campuses.
Businesses count on
communication, and communication
counts on CenturyLink.
gave us the power to turn this
enemy into an ally?
Microsoft and its partners are
using smart traps to capture
mosquitoes and sequence their
DNA to fight disease.
There are over 100 million
pieces of DNA in every sample.
With the Microsoft Cloud,
we can analyze the data
faster than ever before.
If we can detect new viruses
before they spread,
we may someday prevent outbreaks
before they begin.
.
JULIE: THIS IS A FOX NEWS
ALERT AND BREAKING NEWS WITH
AN UPDATE ON THE LAUNCH OF A
MISSILE BY NORTH KOREA.
THE U.S. PACIFIC COMMAND
SAYING IT DID DETECT AND TRACK
THIS MISSILE THIS MORNING.
LAUNCHED FROM THE WESTERN PART
OF THE NATION AND LANDING IN
THE SEA OF JAPAN.
THE MILITARY SAYS IT IS
SATISFYIN ASSESSING THE
MISSILE LAUNCH, AND ITS FLIGHT
WAS NOT CONSISTENT OF THAT OF
A INTERCONTINENTAL BALLISTIC
MISSILE.
THE CENTER OF COMMAND SAYS IT
IS WORKING CLOSELY WITH
SOUTH KOREA AND JAPAN TO
MAINTAIN SECURITY.
NOW, THE U.S. GOVERNMENT DOES
SAY THE LAUNCH POSED NO THREAT
TO NORTH AMERICA.
THIS LATEST LAUNCH COMES AMID
HEIGHTENED ATTENTION WITH THE
U.S. AND KIM JONG-UN AFTER A
SERIES OF FAILED LAUNCH
ATTEMPTS THIS PAST MONTH.
IN FACT, PRESIDENT TRUMP'S, IN
ESSENCE, THAT ALL OPTIONS ARE
ON THE TABLE, WE ARE WAITING
FOR THE WHITE HOUSE TO RELEASE
A STATEMENT.
WE HAVE BEEN TOLD THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS BEEN BRIEFED ON
THE SITUATION.
THE POCKET HAS ALSO CONFIRMED
ALL OF THIS.
WHAT IT MEANS NEXT.
WE SOON FIND OUT MORE AS WE
GET IT.
IN THE MEANTIME, ONE OF THE
COUNTRY'S BUSIEST AIRPORTS IS
GETTING A MAKEOVER.
LAX IS SHUFFLING AROUND A
THIRD OF ITS TERMINALS THIS
WEEKEND.
NOW PASSENGERS ARE EXPECTING
POSSIBLE DELAYS.
THIS SOUNDS LIKE A MESS IN THE
WAITING.
WILL.
>> YEAH.  JULIE, THIS IS A
MAJOR TRANSITION AT THE SECOND
BUSIEST AIRPORT IN THE
COUNTRY.
IT OPERATES 24/7, SO THEY
REALLY WANTED TO START THIS
DURING THE DOWN HOURS
OVERNIGHT, SO THEY STARTED THE
MOVE JUST AFTER MIDNIGHT.
THEY BROUGHT IN BIG BOXES AND
MOVING TRUCKS AND OVER THE
NEXT FIVE TO SIX DAYS, 21
AIRLINES WILL BE OPEN FOR
BUSINESS IN NEW TERMINALS, AND
IF YOU'VE EVER THROWN INTO
LAX, YOU KNOW IT CAN BE BUSY.
THEY HAVE PUT IN A FULL COURT
COMMUNICATIONS PRESS
CONTACTING PASSENGERS VIA
E-MAIL, TEMECULA, AND SOCIAL
MEDIA, AND PASSENGERS TELL US
IT'S WORKING.
>> WELL, EVERYBODY WARNED US,
AND THEY TEXT THE US EVEN THIS
MORNING SAYING YOU SHOULD GET
AHERE THREE OR FOUR HOURS IN
ADVANCE, DEPENDING ON THE
FLIGHT, SO WE EXPECTED IT TO
BE THREE HOURS, AND IT REALLY
WASN'T A PROBLEM.
>> TO HELP, DELTA, WHICH IS
FINANCING THE RELOCATION, HAS
MORE THAN 200 STAFF MEMBERS ON
THE PREMISES.
THEY'RE ANSWERING QUESTIONS
AND HELPING WITH ANY
CONFUSION.
SO FAR THERE ARE NO PLANE
DELAYS, BUT EVERYONE IS STILL
URGING PASSENGERS TO SHOW UP
AS EARLY AS POSSIBLE.
>> WE ARE TRYING TO BE AS
PROACTIVE AS WE CAN, WHETHER
IT'S RADIO SPOTS WORKING WITH
UBER AND LYFT, ALL SORTS OF
WAYS TO COMMUNICATE.
IS AND SO FAR, IT SEEMS TO BE
WORKING.
PEOPLE ARE SHOWING UP IN THE
RIGHT PLACE.
>> AND THE REASON FOR THE
RELOCATION IS THAT DELTA
WANTED TO GET INTO TWO
TERMINALS SET FOR EXPANSION IN
THE COMING YEARS.
IF THERE'S ANY INCONVENIENCE
IN THE COMING DAYS, JULIE, IT
WILL BE WELL WORTH IT.
JULIE: WILL CARR, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
A WORLD WAR II VETERAN IS
STILL LOOKING FOR A WAY TO
GIVE BACK DECADES AFTER
LEAVING THE BATTLEFIELD.
HOW HE'S USING HIS RETIREMENT
TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE IN THE
LIVES OF OTHERS.
PLUS PUTTING A TAX ON YOUR
NETFLIX ACCOUNT.
WHY SOME LOCAL GOVERNMENTS ARE
CONSIDERING A PLAN TO DO JUST
THAT AS MORE CABLE SUBSCRIBERS
CUT THE CORD.
Dear Predictable,
There's no other
way to say this.
It's over.
I've found a permanent
escape from monotony.
Together, we are
perfectly balanced,
our senses awake,
our hearts racing as one.
I know this is sudden,
but they say: If you
love something...
set it free.
See you around, Giulia
♪
You know how painful heartburn
can be.
For fast-acting, long-lasting
relief,
try doctor recommended Gaviscon.
It quickly neutralizes stomach
acid
and helps keep acid down for
hours.
Relieve heartburn with fast-
acting, long-lasting Gaviscon.
when a fire destroyed
everything in our living room.
We replaced it all
without touching our savings.
Yeah, our insurance
won't do that.
No.
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance
.
JULIE: A WORLD WAR II VETERAN
IN MICHIGAN ISN'T ON THE FRONT
LINES ANYMORE, BUT HE IS STILL
FINDING A WAY TO SERVE HIS
COUNTRY.
DAVID IS ALMOST 90 YEARS OLD.
HE JOINED THE NAVY IN 1945.
GOD BLESS HIM.
FOR THE LAST 14 YEARS, HE HAS
SPENT HIS DAYS COLLECTING
DONATIONS FOR A VETERANS
RELIEF FUND.
>> THERE'S MANY VETERANS THAT
NEED HELP.
AND THIS MONEY GOES TO THE --
OUR RELIEF FUND.
IF A VETERAN GETS IN TROUBLE,
HIS CAR BREAKS DOWN OR
SOMETHING, WE CAN HELP HIM OU O.
JULIE: SO ELDRIDGE GIVES AWAY
SMALL FLOWERS TO ANYONE WHO
DONATES TO HIS ARMED FORCES
FUND.
THE POPPIES HONOR THE SOLDIERS
WHO LOST THEIR LIVES FIGHTING
IN WORLD WAR I.
THAT IS A GREAT STORY.
SO MORE CABLE SUBSCRIBERS ARE
MAKING THE DECISION TO CUT THE
CORD AND PAYING TO STREAM
VIDEO THROUGH SERVICES LIKE
NETFLIX AND HULU.  WELL, NOW
SOME LOCAL GOVERNMENTS ARE
TRYING TO MAKE UP SOME LOST
REVENUE BY ADDING UTILITY TAX
TO VIDEO STREAMING SITES.
CLAUDIA EXPLAINS HOW IT ALL
WORKS.
>> THE POWER TO TAX THEY
SQUEEZE OUT ONE PLACE, THEY
POP UP SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> CITIES ARGUE THEY'RE LOSING
MONEY AND NEED TO GET
CREATIVE.
CABLE PROVIDERS LOST MORE THAN
THREE-QUARTERS OF A MILLION
SUBSCRIBERS IN THE FIRST THREE
MONTHS OF THIS YEAR.
FIVE TIMES MORE THAN DURING
THE SAME PERIOD LAST YEAR.
A TREND THAT'S MEANT TO DROP
IN UTILITY TAXES ATTACHED TO
CABLE BILLS.
GLENDALE, CALIFORNIA IS AMONG
THOSE CONSIDERING INCREASING
UTILITY TAXES, WHICH COVER
GAS, ELECTRIC, AND TELECOM
SERVICES.
TO MAKE UP FOR HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS IN LOST REVENUE THAT
HELPS PAY FOR POLICE AND OTHER
CRITICAL SERVICES.
>> NOT TO TAX YOU TWICE BUT TO
ALLOW THAT THERE IS A
CONSISTENT FLOW OF REVENUE
THAT PAYS FOR THE SERVICES
THAT YOU AS A RESIDENT, AS A
BUSINESS, AS A VISITOR EXPECT
FROM THAT LOCAL GOVERNMENT.
>> GLEN DAILY IS ENLIFTING THE
HELP OF PROVIDERS TO DETERMINE
HOW SUCH A STREAMING VIDEO TAX
MIGHT WORK.
BUT CRITICS FEAR A SLIPPERY
SLOPE WHEN STREAMING VIDEO
SERVICES ARE TAXED LIKE A GAS
OR WATER BILL.
>> IF YOU ALLOW A CITY TO DO
THAT, YOU'RE SETTING A
PRECEDENT WHERE ALMOST
ANYTHING ON THE INTERNET OR
MAYBE EVEN OFF THE INTERNET
COULD BE CONSIDERED A TAXABLE
UNDER A UTILITY TAX, AND
THAT'S VERY PROBLEMATIC FOR
CONSUMERS.
JULIE: LOTS OF BIG NAMES
MAKING APPEARANCES AT
COMMENCEMENT CEREMONIES THIS
WEEKEND.
OPRAH WINFREY RECEIVING AN
HONORARY DEGREE AT THE SCOTT
COLLEGE IN ATLANTA.
>> HAVING GREAT SHOES IN A
CLOSET FULL OF SHOES OR CARS
OR HOUSES OF SQUARE FOOTAGE
DOESN'T FILL UP YOUR LIFE.
IT DOESN'T.
BUT LIVING A LIFE OF SUBSTANCE
CAN.
SUBSTANCE THROUGH YOUR
SERVICE, YOUR OFFERING OF YOUR
WHOLE SELF.
AND THE BASELINE FOR HOW DO
YOU LIVE A LIFE OF SUBSTANCE
IS WHATEVER IS THE TRUTH FOR
YOU?
WHAT DO YOU STAND FOR?
.
JULIE: IN THE MEANTIME U.S.
SENATOR JOHN CORNIN'S SPEECH
WAS CANCELED AFTER A STUDENT
PETITION JUST DAYS AFTER BETSY
DEVOS WAS BOOED DURING HER
SPEECH.  WELL, ONE HIGH SCHOOL
IS CONFISCATING ALL OF ITS
YEARBOOKS, APPARENTLY.
THE SHOCKING REASON WHY.
NEXT
Intelligent technology can help
protect it.
The all-new Audi Q5 is here.
Yet up 90% fall short in getting
key nutrients from food alone.
Let's do more.
Add One A Day 50+
a complete multi-vitamin
with 100% daily value
of more than 15
key nutrients.
One A Day 50+.
. .. .
. .
♪
I'm Dr. Kelsey McNeely and some
day you might be
calling me an energy farmer.
♪
Energy lives here.
I count on my Dell Small
for tech advice.
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs and
I get back to business.
♪
you get to do the dishes.ed...
Bring 'em on. Dawn Ultra has
3 times more
grease-cleaning power.
A drop of Dawn and
grease is gone.
[VO] The grille is distinctive.
But it's usually seen from the
rear.
The all-new Audi Q5 is here.
>> A NORTH CAROLINA HIGH SCHOOL
IS CONFISCATING ITS YEARBOOKS.
WHEN YOU LIKE TO CONFISCATE ONE
OF YOUR YEARBOOKS BECAUSE OF THE
PHOTO.
IT'S BECAUSE SOME SENIOR QUOTES
ARE TOO APPROPRIATE.
INCLUDING THIS ONE, QUOTE
READING "BUILD THAT WALL"
REFERENCING TRUMPS CONTROVERSIAL
BORDER WALL.
THE SCHOOL SAYING IT DOES NOT
TOLERATE INAPPROPRIATE CONDUCT
TOWARD ANY STUDENT.
THE DISTRICT ISSUED AN APOLOGY
SAYING IT IS WORKING WITH A
PUBLISHER TO MAKE CORRECTIONS.
IT'S CALLED FREE SPEECH.
GET OVER IT.
THAT'S THE FOX REPORT.
WATERS WORLD STARTS NOW.
>> JESSE: WATERS WORLD IS ON.
WERE GOING TO A PIECE OF PAPER
WITH A PERFECTLY ACCURATE.
>> PRESS CONFERENCES WERE NOT
EVEN COVERED FOR OBAMA.
THEY WERE ON C-SPAN A C-SPAN TO.
>> TO DONALD TRUMP REALLY KILL
WHITE HOUSE PRESS CONFERENCES.
I WILL GUARANTEE YOU ONE THING.
THERE'S A CAN BE THAT KIND OF
BOWL BEFORE AND IT DONALD TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.
INSIDE THE CORNER WITH BOBBY
KNIGHT.