THE BIG PICTURE HAS TO COME
FIRST.
TO MY MIND THAT'S
>> HERE WE ARE WATCHING
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND THE FIRST
LADY EXIT AIR FORCE ONE AS THEY
COME TO MEET THE CHINESE
PRESIDENT.
I'LL HAND IT OVER TO SHEPARD
SMITH.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST.
3:00 ON THE EAST COAST.
WE'RE WATCHING THREE MAJOR
BREAKING NEWS EVENTS.
FIRST, SOUTH FLORIDA WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS JUST
ARRIVED.
MOMENTS AGO, SECRETARY OF STATE
TILLERSON SAID THE SECOND MAJOR
SIGNAL OF AN AMERICAN POLICY
CHANGE TOWARDS SYRIA.
HE SAID THE UNITED STATES IS
ORGANIZING AN INTERNATIONAL
COALITION TO RESPOND TO BASHAR
AL-ASSAD'S CHEMICAL ATTACK ON
HIS OWN PEOPLE.
DOES THIS MEAN AMERICAN MILITARY
ACTION IN SYRIA?
IT'S BREAKING NOW.
ON CAPITOL HILL, WE JUST WATCHED
HISTORY UNFOLD.
A MOVE ON THE SENATE FLOOR THAT
COULD FOREVER CHANGE CONGRESS
AND ALSO THE UNITED STATES
SUPREME COURT FOR MANY
GENERATIONS TO COME.
YOU'VE HEARD ABOUT THE NUCLEAR
OPTION.
TODAY THE SENATE REPUBLICANS
BLEW IT UP.
THE FALL-OUT COULD BE
EXTRAORDINARY.
WE'LL EXPLAIN EXACTLY WHAT IT
MEANS AND WHY IT MATTERS SO
MUCH.
AND SHAKE-UP IN THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
THE REPUBLICAN CHAIR OF THE
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
AGREES TO STEP ASIDE AS HE IS
NOW UNDER INVESTIGATION.
DEVIN NUNES BLAMING WHAT HE
CALLS ACCUSATIONS FROM LEFT-WING
GROUPS.
AHEAD YOU'LL HEAR THE MAN WHO IS
TAKING OVER.
AND WHY THE IRS TOOK MILLIONS OF
DOLLARS FROM PEOPLE THAT DID
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING WRONG.
WHO ARE THE VICTIMS?
LET'S GET TO IT.
IT IS RARE TO HAVE THIS MANY
ENORMOUS STORIES BREAKING AT ONE
TIME.
WE ARE AT THAT TIME.
WE'LL TAKE YOU TO THE FALL-OUT
FROM SECRETARY OF STATE
TILLERSON'S BLOCKBUSTER
ANNOUNCEMENT.
BUT FIRST, THE UNITED STATES
LEGISLATIVELY SPEAKING, THE
ADULTS IN THE ROOM, WHEN THE
COUNTRY GOES TOO FAR LEFT OR
RIGHT, THE SENATE WOULD COOL
THINGS OFF.
FIND SOMETHING CLOSER TO THE
MIDDLE SO THE NATION DOESN'T
SLIDE TO THE EXTREME.
THE SENATE.
THE GUARDRAILS OF DEMOCRACY.
IF THE LEGISLATIVE BUS CAREENS
OVER THE LEFT OR RIGHT, THE
GUARDRAILS BOUNCE THE BUS BACK
TO THE MIDDLE.
IT SERVED OUR REPUBLIC WELL FOR
A COUPLE CENTURIES.
ONLY A SORT OF LEGISLATIVE
NUCLEAR EXPLOSION COULD CHANGE
THAT.
FOR INSTANCE, SUSPEND THE RULES
TO CHANGE THE TRADITION SO THE
SENATE IS MORE LIKE THE HOUSE
AND ONLY NEEDS 51 VOTES INSTEAD
OF 60 TO GET BIG THINGS DONE.
IT'S ALWAYS BEEN AN OPTION.
AT LEAST SINCE 1957 AFTER A
THREAT IN 1917 AND TODAY THE
SENATE EXERCISED THAT NUCLEAR
OPTION.
AS OF LAST HOUR, WE'RE IN A NEW
LEGISLATIVE WORLD.
IT MARKS A HISTORIC CHANGE TO
SENATE NORMS THAT COULD AFFECT
OUR DEMOCRACY AND OUR REPUBLIC
BEYOND ANY OF OUR LIFETIMES.
THE MOVE LETS REPUBLICANS IN
THIS CASE ADVANCE PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S SUPREME COURT NOMINEE,
NEIL GORSUCH WITH A SIMPLY
MAJORITY OF 51 VOTES INSTEAD OF
60.
IT SET AS PRECEDENT THAT
ANALYSTS SAY THAT WILL ALLOW ANY
PARTY TO CONTROL THE SENATE TO
APPROVE SUPREME COURT NOMINEES
WITHOUT BIPARTISAN SUPPORT.
LAWMAKERS FROM BOTH PARTIES ARE
BLAMING EACH OTHER.
THE TRUTH BE TOLD, THEY'RE ALL
TO BLAME.
REPUBLICANS SAY THEY HAD TO USE
THE NUCLEAR OPTION BECAUSE
DEMOCRATS FILIBUSTERED JUST
GORSUCH'S NOMINATION.
HIS NOMINATION VOTE IS SET FOR
TOMORROW.
DEMOCRATS ARE BLAMING GOP
LEADERS BECAUSE THEY NEVER HELD
HEARINGS FOR MERRICK GARLAND.
MITCH McCONNELL SAID DEMOCRATS
OVER THE YEARS HAVE REPEATEDLY
RAISED THE STAKES IN
CONFIRMATION BATTLES.
>> THE OPPOSITION TO THIS
PARTICULAR NOMINEE IS MORE ABOUT
THE MAN THAT NOMINATED HIM AND
THE PARTY HE REPRESENTS THAN THE
NOMINEE HIMSELF.
IT'S PART OF A MUCH LARGER
STORY, ANOTHER EXTREME
ESCALATION IN THE LEFT'S
NEVER-ENDING DRIVE TO POLITICIZE
THE COURTS AND THE CONFIRMATION
PROCESS.
>> THE REPUBLICANS SAY HARRY
REID STARTED ALL OF THIS IN 2013
WHEN HE ALLOWED THE SAME NUCLEAR
OPTION FOR OBAMA'S NOMINEES FOR
EVERYONE EXCEPT THE SUPREME
COURT.
AND THEN MITCH McCONNELL CALLED
IT A DEMOCRATIC POWER GRAB AND A
SAD DAY IN THE HISTORY OF THE
SENATE.
THAT WAS 2013.
THE CURRENT SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER CHUCK SCHUMER SAID
DEMOCRATS AT THE TIME HAD TO USE
THE NUCLEAR OPTION BECAUSE
REPUBLICANS WERE USING THE
FILIBUSTER TO STONEWALL
NOMINEES.
>> THE TRUTH IS, OVER THE LONG
HISTORY OF PARTISAN COMBAT OVER
JUDICIAL NOMINATIONS, THERE'S
BLAME ON BOTH SIDES.
WE BELIEVE THE BLAME SHOULD NOT
BE SHARED EQUALLY BETWEEN
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS.
WE BELIEVE THE REPUBLICAN PARTY
HAS BEEN FAR MORE AGGRESSIVE IN
THE ESCALATION OF TACTICS AND IN
THE SELECTION OF EXTREME
JUDICIAL CANDIDATES WHILE
DEMOCRATS HAVE TENDED TO SELECT
JUDGES CLOSER TO THE MIDDLE.
>> OF COURSE HE DOES.
HE'S THE DEMOCRATIC LEADER.
THE REPUBLICANS SAY THE SAME
THING ABOUT THE DEMOCRATS.
MANY DEMOCRATS EVEN ADMITTED
LONG BEFORE TODAY THAT THEY
SHOULDN'T HAVE DONE WHAT THEY
DID IN 2013 BECAUSE IT HAS HURT
THE BODY, BUT THEY DID.
SO NOW NO MORE SUPER MAJORITY
NECESSARY IN THE SENATE.
FOR JUDGES, SUPREME COURT
JUSTICES.
IF THIS IS THE MIDDLE OF
DOMINOES FALLING, FIRST JUDGES
IN 2013, NOW SUPREME COURT
JUSTICES, THE QUESTION IS WILL
THERE COME A TIME THAT THE
SENATE MIGHT SUSPEND THE RULES
TO CHANGE THE RULES FOR ALL
LEGISLATION?
THAT IS POSSIBLE.
THAT IS SORT OF HOW FALLING
DOMINOES TEND TO WORK.
WE'RE NOT THERE YET.
MAYBE WE'LL NEVER GET THERE.
STILL YOU COULD ARGUE OUR
POLITICS HAVE BEEN SO POLARIZED
THAT THE RULES ARE JUST CATCHING
UP WITH THE STATE OF POLITICAL
AFFAIRS.
ONE JUST CHANGED AND THE PROCESS
OF RUNNING OUR NATION CHANGED
WITH IT.
MIKE EMANUEL IS LIVE ON CAPITOL
HILL.
MIKE A DAY FOR THE HISTORY
BOOKS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SHEP.
YOU'RE RIGHT ABOUT THE IMPACT.
MISSOURI SENATOR CLAIRE
McCASKILL QUESTIONED HER PARTY'S
STRATEGY.
SHE SUGGESTED IF THE NEXT
VACANCY HAPPENS TO BE JUSTICE
RUTH BADER GINSBERG, ANTHONY
KENNEDY OR STEPHEN BREYER,
DEMOCRATS WILL LIVE TO REGRET
NOT HAVING THE FILIBUSTER.
>> IT'S A BAD -- A VERY SAD DAY
FOR THE SENATE.
BECAUSE WE HAVE NOW DESTROYED
200 YEARS OF TRADITION OF
REQUIRING 60 VOTES WHICH MEANING
THAT YOU HAVE TO HAVE BIPARTISAN
APPROACH TO THESE ISSUES AND
THESE APPOINTMENTS.
I THINK WE'RE ON A SLIPPERY
SLOPE.
>> A SLIPPERY SLOPE.
OTHER REPUBLICANS WERE FURIOUS
WITH CHUCK SCHUMER.
THE SENATE CHAIRMAN ACCUSED OF
TREATING JUDGE GORSUCH UNFAIRLY.
>> THROUGHOUT THIS PROCESS, THE
MINORITY LED BY THEIR LEADER HAS
BEEN DESPERATELY SEARCHING FOR A
JUSTIFICATION FOR THEIR
PREPLANNED FILIBUSTER.
OVER THE COURSE OF THE LAST
COUPLE MONTHS, THEY'VE TROTTED
OUT ONE EXCUSE AFTER ANOTHER.
BUT NOTHING WILL STICK.
>> THAT LEAVES 30 HOURS OF
DEBATE.
ALL INDICATIONS ARE THAT JUDGE
GORSUCH WILL BE CONFIRMED BY
TOMORROW EVENING.
>> WHAT ARE DEMOCRATS SAYING
TODAY, MIKE?
>> THEY'RE FURIOUS WITH MITCH
McCONNELL.
THEY'RE SAYING THAT McCONNELL
DIDN'T TREAT NEIL GORSUCH'S
PREDECESSOR, JUDGE MERRICK
GARLAND, THE LAST NOMINEE
NOMINATED TO THE HIGH COURT.
DEMOCRATS VENTED THEIR ANGER AT
MITCH McCONNELL.
THEY WERE HELPLESS TO STOP THE
SO-CALLED NUCLEAR OPTION AND
BLASTED McCONNELL.
>> SO THE SENATOR FROM KENTUCKY
HAS MADE HISTORY.
HE COMES TO THE FLOOR AND TELLS
US HISTORY.
HE MADE HISTORY IN THE NUMBER OF
FILIBUSTERS THAT HE USED ON THIS
FLOOR.
HE MADE HISTORY AND DENYING A
PRESIDENTIAL NOMINEE THE
OPPORTUNITY FOR A HEARING AND A
VOTE, WHICH HAD NEVER, NEVER
HAPPENED BEFORE IN THE HISTORY
OF THE UNITED STATES.
TALK ABOUT PARTISANSHIP.
>> SOURCES ON BOTH SIDES SUGGEST
THERES PLENTY OF BLAME TO GO
AROUND.
WE'RE IN AN ERA OF PARTISANSHIP.
>> Shepard: NO DOUBT.
MIKE EMANUEL ON THE HILL.
THANKS.
LET'S GO TO GREGORY McGARIAN
FROM ST. LOUIS.
LOVE IT THERE.
THE BACKGROUND ON THIS IS IT'S
ALL POLITICS.
THE LEFT IS MAD AT THE RIGHT,
THE RIGHT IS MAD AT THE LEFT.
PRACTICALLY SPEAKING, WHAT DOES
THIS MEAN GOING FORWARD?
>> WELL, IT HAS IMPLICATIONS FOR
THE SENATE AND FOR THE SUPREME
COURT.
FOR THE SENATE, AS YOU SAID,
THIS IS SORT OF A STAGE IN A
PROCESS RATHER THAN MAYBE A
SINGLE DEFINING MOMENT.
THE SENATE HAS BEEN MOVING
TOWARD MORE PARTISAN DIVISION.
I THINK, AS YOU SUGGESTED,
REFLECTING THE POLITICS OF THE
NATION AND THE GREATER
DIFFICULTY OF FORGING CONSENSUS
WITHIN THE DELIBERATIVE BODY.
FOR THE SUPREME COURT, THIS MAY
WELL MEAN THAT OVER TIME BOTH
PARTIES ARE -- HAVE A GREATER
INCENTIVE TO PROMOTE JUDGES AND
JUSTICES WHO ARE MORE SHARPLY
IDEALOGICAL AND LEFT CENTRISTS.
>> Shepard: BECAUSE THEY
WOULDN'T NEED TO REACH OUT TO
THE OTHER SIDE TO GET HELP TO
PUSH THOSE THROUGH.
SO IF AS MANY PEOPLE SUSPECT,
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS ABLE TO
APPOINT ANOTHER SUPREME COURT
JUSTICE.
MIGHT TILT WILDLY RIGHT.
IF THE NEXT PRESIDENT, IF IT
TAKES UNTIL THE NEXT PRESIDENT,
HE OR SHE IS A DEMOCRAT, IT
MIGHT TILT WIDELY LEFT.
THAT INCREASES THE PARTISANSHIP
ALL OVER THE LAND.
>> I THINK THAT'S RIGHT.
ACTUALLY, OVER THE LONG-TERM.
I THINK THERE'S A GOOD
POSSIBILITY THAT THIS WILL
BENEFIT -- I WOULDN'T SAY
BENEFIT DEMOCRATS SO MUCH AS
BENEFIT THE LEFT MORE THAN THE
RIGHT.
>> Shepard: WHY IS THAT?
>> OVER THE PAST COUPLE
GENERATIONS, CONSERVATIVES HAVE
BEEN MUCH MORE ANIMATED
POLITICALLY ABOUT THE SUPREME
COURT.
AS A RESULT, CONSERVATIVE
SUPREME COURT NOMINEES HAVE
GENERALLY BEEN MORE STRONG IN
THEIR IDEALOGICAL CONVICTIONS.
THERE'S BEEN SOME EXCEPTIONS
GOING BACK TO JUSTICE KENNEDY.
IF YOU LOOK AT JUSTICE THOMAS,
JUSTICE SCALIA, CHIEF JUSTICE
ROBERTS, VERY STRONGLY COMMITTED
CONSERVATIVES.
ON THE DEMOCRATIC SIDE, YOU HAD
MORE NOMINATIONS OF JUSTICE
BREYER, JUSTICE KAGAN THAT ARE
ON THE LEFT SIDE, CERTAINLY TO
THE LEFT OF THE REPUBLICAN
APPOINTEE COLLEAGUES.
BUT NOT NEARLY AS FAR TO THE
LEFT AS WARREN COURT GENERATION,
THE LEADERS OF THAT COURT IN THE
60s THAT WERE SEEN AS LIBERAL
ACTIVISTS.
SO IF THERE IS FROM THIS LOSS OF
THE FILIBUSTER A SORT OF
LIBERATION OF IDEALOGICAL
NOMINEES, THAT LIBERATION WOULD
HAVE A STRONGER EFFECT ON THE
DEMOCRATIC SIDE THAN THE
REPUBLICAN SIDE.
>> Shepard: WHAT EFFECT DOES
THIS HAVE ON FUTURE CHANGES THAT
COULD ALLOW FOR A 51-VOTE ON
REGULAR LEGISLATION?
WE'RE NOT THERE YET.
THE LEADERS TODAY SAY THAT WON'T
HAPPEN.
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE OF THAT, IS
THERE?
>> NO.
IT'S TRADITION AND SORT OF
SELF-CONTROL OR FUNNY THINGS.
THE CONSTITUTION GIVES THE
SENATE AND THE HOUSE THE POWER
TO SET THEIR OWN RULES.
AT ANY GIVEN MOMENT, THOSE
BODIES HAVE THE POWER TO CHANGE
THEIR RULES.
SO IN ONE SENSE, THIS COULD BE A
HICCUP.
IT COULD BE A PARTISAN MOMENT.
IN THE FUTURE OF THE SENATE
COULD FULLBACK FROM THIS BRINK.
MORE THAN WHAT THIS CAUSES IS
WHAT IT REPRESENTS.
IT REPRESENTS THE GREATER
DIFFICULTY OF FORGING BIPARTISAN
CONSENSUS AND THE SENATE IS
ADJUSTING TO THE REALITY AND
HAPPENS TO BE AT A MOMENT WHEN
THE REPUBLICANS ARE IN CONTROL
AND TRYING TO GET DONE WHAT THEY
WANT DON'T.
>> Shepard: THIS HAS SEEN AS A
TRADITION BEFORE TODAY.
THE SENATE, THE ONES THAT STEP
UP AND KEEPS THE COUNTRY FROM
GOING TOO FAR ONE WAY OR TOO FOR
THE OTHER.
IS THERE REASONS FOR PEOPLE THAT
HOPE THAT THE CENTER HOLDS IN
THIS NATION IS THERE REAL REASON
FOR THEM TO BE VERY CONCERNED
TODAY OR IS THIS JUST ANOTHER
ONE OF THOSE MOMENTS THAT THE
SYSTEM CAN OVERCOME?
>> IT CERTAINLY COULD BE A
MOMENT THE SYSTEM COULD
OVERCOME.
SOME OF IT DEPENDS ON
PERSONALITIES AND POLITICS IN
THE SENATE.
ANYONE THAT IS STRONGLY IN
BIPARTISAN COOPERATION HAS HAD A
LOT OF REASONS TO BUN HAPPY OVER
THE PAST DECADE OR MORE.
I THINK TODAY IS A CONTINUATION
OF THAT.
>> GREGORY MAGARIAN FROM
WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY, I
APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
THANK YOU.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> Shepard: IF YOU WATCHED IN
THE LAST 20 MINUTES OR SO, YOU
SAW WHAT MAY HAVE BEEN A MASSIVE
SHIFT IN UNITED STATES POLICY
TOWARDS SYRIA.
THE SYRIANS HAVE BEEN IN THE
MIDDLE OF A CIVIL WAR.
THE SYRIAN LEADER, BASHAR
AL-ASSAD, BY ALL INTERNATIONAL
OBSERVATION HAS MURDERED
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF HIS OWN
PEOPLE BY USING BARREL BOMBS AND
ALL KINDS OF EXPLOSIONS THE LAST
MANY YEARS.
THE LAST COUPLE DAYS, THERE WAS
VIDEO OF A CHEMICAL ATTACK, A
SARIN GAS ATTACK, ONE
PERPETRATED BY BASHAR AL-ASSAD
HIMSELF AND IT APPEARS THE
POLICY OF THE UNITED STATES HAS
CHANGED IN AN ENORMOUS WAY.
THE SECRETARY OF STATE THAT
THEY'RE PUTTING TOGETHER AN
INTERNATIONAL COALITION TO
RESPOND.
IS MILITARY ACTION, BOOTS ON THE
GROUND AHEAD FOR THE UNITED
STATES IN SYRIA?
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
THE RUSSIANS AND THE IRANIANS
ARE ON THE OTHER SIDE.
IT'S BREAKING NEWS AND IT'S
NEXT.
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
You totaNobody's hurt, new car.
but there will still be pain.
It comes when your insurance
company says they'll only pay
three-quarters of what
it takes to replace it.
What are you supposed to do?
Drive three-quarters of a car?
Now if you had Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
you'd get your whole car back.
I guess they don't want you
driving around on three wheels.
Smart.
With Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
we'll replace the full
value of your car.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>> Shepard: THERE'S BREAKING
NEWS ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
FIRST PRESIDENT TRUMP YESTERDAY
SAYING HIS ATTITUDE TO BASHAR
AL-ASSAD HAS CHANGED.
IN THE LAST 30 MINUTES, ANOTHER
SIGN.
SECRETARY OF STATE TILLERSON
ANNOUNCING THAT "STEPS ARE
UNDERWAY TO ORGANIZE AN
INTERNATIONAL COALITION TO
REMOVE THE MURDEROUS SYRIAN
DICTATOR, BASHAR AL-ASSAD, FROM
POWER FOLLOWING THIS WEEK'S
APPARENT CHEMICAL ATTACK IN THE
WAR-TORN COUNTRY."
REGIME CHANGE.
THAT'S BRAND NEW.
THIS REPRESENTS AN ENORMOUS
DEPARTURE FROM DAYS AGAINST WHEN
THE WHITE HOUSE SAID THE SYRIANS
SHOULD DECIDE.
THEN IT WOULD NOT MAKE SENSE TO
TRY TO REMOVE BASHAR AL-ASSAD
FROM POWER AND THAT THE FOCUS
SHOULD BE ON DEFEATING ISIS.
NOW WE LEARNED THAT SYRIA'S
FOREIGN MINISTER HAS DENIED THAT
HIS GOVERNMENT USED CHEMICAL
WEAPONS
WEAPONS IN  ATTACKS.
86 PEOPLE DIED INCLUDING DOZENS
OF WOMEN AND CHILDREN.
THEY SAID THE POISON GAS ATTACK
INJURED HUNDREDS MORE.
RUSSIA IS A KEY ALLY OF
AL-ASSAD.
THE RUSSIANS ARE FIGHTING WITH
THE SYRIANS.
THE IRANIANS ARE IN THE MIX
SUPPORTING HEZBOLLAH.
A SYRIAN AIR STRIKE HIT A REBEL
FACTORY.
SO THE RUSSIANS SAY IT HAPPENED
THE OTHER WAY.
THE AMERICANS SAY IT HAPPENED
ANOTHER.
THE RUSSIANS ARE ON THIS SIDE,
THE AMERICANS ARE ON THE OTHER.
IN THE SENDER IS BASHAR
AL-ASSAD.
THE RUSSIANS HAVE PROPPED HIM
UP.
THE RUSSIANS SAY THAT BASHAR
AL-ASSAD SHOULD STAY IN POWER.
THE RUSSIANS ARE SUPPORTING HIM.
THE AMERICANS JUST SAID WE'RE
ORGANIZING A COALITION TO TAKE
HIM OUT.
THAT MEANS THE UNITED STATES
WITH SYRIAN REBELS AGAINST THE
SYRIANS, THE RUSSIANS AND THE
IRANIANS THAT SUPPORT HEZBOLLAH.
SO FAR PRESIDENT TRUMP AND MANY
OTHER WORLD LEADERS SAY THE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT IS FLATLY TO
BLAME.
THE TRUTH IS, THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT HAS BEEN MURDERING
ITS OWN PEOPLE FOR YEARS.
BY THE HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS.
THESE PICTURES ARE NEW.
THIS INCIDENT IS NEW.
THIS SITUATION IS VERY OLD.
THEY DROPPED BARREL BOMBS FROM
THE SKY AND MURDERS CHILDREN IN
THEIR BEDS ON A DAILY BASIS.
BUT THESE PICTURES AND THIS
INCIDENT IS NEW ALONG WITH THIS
PRESIDENT AND HIS ENTOURAGE.
NOW PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS THE
HORRIBLE IMAGES FROM THIS WEEK'S
ATTACK MADE HIM CHANGE HIS
ATTITUDE TOWARD SYRIA AND ASSAD.
>> IT'S A TERRIBLE THING.
YOU SEE BABIES DEAD FROM GAS AND
A VERY HEINOUS FORM OF GAS,
WHICH VERY FEW PEOPLE HAVE
ACCESS, TO IT'S BAD STUFF.
REALLY BAD.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
SAID THAT THE AL-ASSAD REGIME'S
ACTIONS CANNOT BE TOLERATED.
AND NOW VLADIMIR PUTIN IS
ACCUSING PRESIDENT TRUMP OF
RUSHING TO JUDGMENT.
THE RUSSIANS SAYING ONE THING
AND THE AMERICANS SAYING
ANOTHER.
THE AMERICANS ORGANIZING A
COALITION TO SETTLE IT ALL.
HERE'S WHAT SECRETARY OF STATE
REX TILLERSON SAID 30 MINUTES
AGO.
>> OBVIOUSLY THE EVENTS THAT
HAVE OCCURRED IN SYRIA WITH THE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK HERE IN
THE PAST DAY HAVE JUST I THINK
HORRIFIED ALL OF US AND BROUGHT
TO THE FRONT PAGES INTO OUR
TELEVISION SCREENS AS WELL.
THE TRAGEDY THAT IS PART OF THE
SYRIAN CONFLICT.
THERE'S NO DOUBT IN OUR MINDS
AND THE INFORMATION WE HAVE
SUPPORTS THAT SYRIA, THE SYRIAN
REGIME ON ORDERS OF PRESIDENT
BASHAR AL-ASSAD ARE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS ATTACK.
AND I THINK FURTHER IT IS VERY
IMPORTANT THAT THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT CONSIDER CAREFULLY
THEIR CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR THE
ASSAD REGIME.
>> Shepard: TODAY A SPOKESMAN
FOR THE RUSSIAN PRESIDENT SAID
WE WOULD WELCOME A MORE
CONSIDERED APPROACH.
IT IS A PERILOUS SET OF
CIRCUMSTANCES NOW.
THE RUSSIANS HAVE BEEN
SUPPORTING AL-ASSAD FOR A LONG
TIME.
AL-ASSAD HAS BEEN MURDERING HIS
OWN PEOPLE FOR A LONG TIME.
HEZBOLLAH AND THE IRANIANS HAVE
BEEN IN ON THAT EFFORT FOR A
LONG TIME AS THE UNITED STATES
SUPPORTS THE REBELS.
NOW THE QUESTION IS, DO WE
LAUNCH WITH A COALITION THAT HAS
BEEN SUGGESTED A MILITARY STRIKE
TO REMOVE THE MURDEROUS DICTATOR
FROM THAT COUNTRY?
IF SO, WHAT HAPPENS AFTERWARDS?
WHO FILLS THE VOID THAT BASHAR
AL-ASSAD HAS HELD.
THOSE ARE THE VERY BIG QUESTIONS
THAT HAVE JUST ARISEN ON AN
ENORMOUS NEWS DAY.
RICH EDSON WITH ANALYSIS WITH
A.B. STODDARD.
THAT'S NEXT ON A THURSDAY ON THE
FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
Crohn's disease,...
...I was always searching for
ways to manage my symptoms.
I thought I had it covered.
Then I realized managing was
all I was doing.
When I finally told my doctor,
he said HUMIRA was for people
like me
who have tried other
medications,...
but still experience the
symptoms
of moderate to severe
Crohn's disease.
In clinical studies,
the majority of patients
on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom
relief...
...and many achieved remission.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections...
...including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,...
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,...
...and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested
for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,...
...hepatitis B, are prone to
infections,
...or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
If you're still just managing
your symptoms,
ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA, remission
is possible.
>> WE'RE CONSIDERING THAT
APPROPRIATE RESPONSE FOR THIS
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK WHICH
VIOLATES ALL PREVIOUS U.N.
RESOLUTIONS, VIOLATES
INTERNATIONAL NORMS AND
LONG-HELD AGREEMENTS BETWEEN
PARTIES INCLUDING SYRIAN REGIME,
THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT AND ALL
OTHER MEMBERS OF THE U.N.
SECURITY COUNCIL.
IT'S A SERIOUS MATTER.
IT REQUIRES A SERIOUS RESPONSE.
>> Shepard: GASSING YOUR OWN
PEOPLE IS A WAR CRIME.
BY ALL ACCOUNTS, THE SYRIAN
DICTATOR, BASHAR AL-ASSAD, HAS
BEEN MURDERING HIS PEOPLE BY THE
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS FOR YEARS.
NOW 30 MINUTES AGO WE LEARNED
THE UNITED STATES IS PREPARING
TO TAKE ACTION.
IT'S BREAKING NEWS AND RICH
EDSON IS ON IT AT THE STATE
DEPARTMENT.
RICH?
>> THE SECRETARY OF STATE SAYS
THAT STEPS ARE UNDERWAY FOR THE
UNITED STATES TO LEAD AN
INTERNATIONAL COALITION TO
REMOVE BASHAR AL-ASSAD FROM
POWER.
JUST A WEEK AGO, THE SECRETARY
OF STATE ASKED ABOUT THIS IN
TURKEY.
HIS RESPONSE TO THAT WAS THAT IT
IS UP TO THE SYRIAN PEOPLE TO
DECIDE THE LONG-TERM FUTURE OF
BASHAR AL-ASSAD.
SO THIS CHEMICAL ATTACK
REPRESENTING A DRAMATIC SHIFT IN
THE POSITION, MUCH MORE DETAILED
FROM THE UNITED STATES AND
SECRETARY TILLERSON THAN HE
SPOKE ABOUT A WEEK AGO IN
TURKEY.
THIS IS AS THE SECRETARY SAYS
THERE'S NO DOUBT THE REGIME OF
BASHAR AL-ASSAD IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE CHEMICAL ATTACK THIS
WEEK ON HIS OWN CITIZENS.
THERE'S RUSSIA ANGLE AS YOU HAVE
DISCUSSED.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT SAYS THAT
RUSSIA NEEDS TO THINK ABOUT ITS
SUPPORT FOR BASHAR AL-ASSAD AND
THIS IS ONE WEEK AHEAD OF
SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON'S VISIT TO MOSCOW
WHERE HE WILL MEET WITH THE
STATE DEPARTMENT THERE.
OFFICIALS SAY THE CHEMICAL
ATTACK WILL COLOR THOSE
DISCUSSIONS.
STATE DEPARTMENT OFFICIALS SAY
THAT THE UNITED STATES WITH
SECRETARY OF STATE REX TILLERSON
STILL EXPLORE A RELATIONSHIP
WORKING TOGETHER WITH RUSSIA ON
AREAS THAT BENEFIT THE UNITED
STATES.
THIS ALL COMING ONE WEEK AHEAD
OF THAT VISIT, SHEP, AS THE
SECRETARY OF STATE SPEAKING AT
LENGTH ABOUT SYRIA PREVIOUS TO
THIS SAYING THAT THE U.S. IS
ALREADY IN DISCUSSIONS, TALKING
ABOUT A POST AL-ASSAD SYRIA AND
AS YOU PLAYED LEADING INTO OUR
DISCUSSION HERE, THAT THE U.S.
IS LEAVING A NUMBER OF OPTIONS
ON THE TABLE IN RESPONDING TO
THIS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THANKS.
A.B. STODDARD WITH
REALCLEARPOLITICS.COM.
THIS STORY JUST BREAKING.
PRESIDENT OBAMA WAS GIVEN AS A
LIST OF BAD OPTIONS.
HE CHOSE THE BAD OPTION THAT WAS
TO REMAIN OUT OF THIS CONFLICT
LARGELY.
WE'VE HAD VERY BAD RESULTS.
THERE'S NO QUESTIONING THIS.
NOW AS A PATTERN BY AL-ASSAD
CONTINUES, THIS PRESIDENT HAS
MADE ANOTHER DECISION.
WHAT ARE WE LOOKING AT HERE,
A.B.?
>> SHEP, YOU POINT OUT CORRECTLY
THIS HAS BEEN GOING ON FOR A
LONG TIME.
PRESIDENT TRUMP KNEW THERE WERE
CHEMICAL ATTACKS IN THE PAST,
THAT, AS YOU POINTED OUT, THIS
PRESIDENT HAD BEEN BUTCHERING
HIS OWN CIVILIANS TO THE TUNE OF
500,000 PEOPLE OVER SEVEN YEARS.
RE LENTLESSLY.
THIS IS A VERY BIG CHANGE OF
MIND AFTER THE ATTACK.
ALTHOUGH THE IMAGES ARE
GRUESOME, THE ATTACKS HAVE NOT
CHANGED.
SO THE QUESTION IS NOT THAT
THERE'S JUST A RUSSIAN ANGLE
HERE, THE RUSSIAN PART IS
EVERYTHING.
TILLERSON GOES TO MOSCOW TO TRY
TO KEEP AN AVENUE OPEN ON ISSUES
THAT WE CAN WORK ON WITH THE
RUSSIANS.
THEY ARE BACKING THIS BRUTAL
DICTATOR WHO IS MURDERING HIS
PEOPLE AND DON'T INTEND TO BACK
DOWN.
THEY'RE MAKING EQUIVOCATING
COMMENTS TODAY THAT IF IT WASN'T
REALLY AN ATTACK, A ACCIDENTAL
ATTACK ON A WEAPONS FACTORY RUN
BY THE REBELS, THAT WOULD BE OUT
OF THE NORMS.
THEY THINK THE U.N. SHOULD DO AN
INVESTIGATION.
WE KNOW THEY'VE BEEN BACKING
THIS REGIME, FIGHTING ITS OWN
PEOPLE, NOT ISIS.
SO AT THIS POINT, WHAT IS
PRESIDENT TRUMP EXPECTING OF THE
RUSSIANS?
ARE WE GOING TO GO TO WAR
AGAINST THEM OR ARE WE GOING TO
TRY TO COAX THE RUSSIANS INTO
DEPOSING AL-ASSAD WITH US?
THAT IS EVERYTHING IN THIS
EQUATION.
WHAT IS THE INTENTION OF THE
RUSSIANS.
WHAT DO THE ADMINISTRATION
THINKS THEY CAN GET THE RUSSIANS
TO DO?
>> WE KNOW THE RUSSIANS WANT THE
UNITED STATES AND THE REST OF
THE WEST TO BACK OFF ON THEIR
ANNEXATION, THEIR INVASION AND
ANNEXING OF CRIMEA.
WE KNOW THE RUSSIANS WANT NATO'S
FRONT NOT TO BE SO CLOSE TO THE
RUSSIANS.
THEY HAVE A BUNCH OF DESIRES.
IT'S A MATTER OF HOW MUCH YOU'RE
WILLING TO GIVE.
>> IF WE GAVE THEM ALL OF THOSE
CONCESSIONS IN EASTERN EUROPE,
THEY WOULD -- PUTIN IS ENJOYING
A SUPREMACY THAT HE'S NEVER HAD
BEFORE.
HE RESCUED PRESIDENT OBAMA IN
2013 SO THAT HE COULD RETREAT
FROM HIS THREAT OF AIR STRIKES
WITH THIS DEAL HE NEGOTIATED TO
GET ALL THE CHEMICAL WEAPONS OUT
OF SYRIA.
THAT IS A HOAX.
I DON'T THINK HE WANTS TO BACK
AWAY FROM HIS RELATIONSHIP WITH
THE IRANIAN REGIME AND THE
SYRIAN REGIME.
HE'S PLAYING AN IMPORTANT ROLE
ANT I DON'T THINK HE HAS ANY
INTENTION OF BACKING DOWN OVER
WHAT CONCESSIONS WE GIVE.
>> Shepard: WE'RE STILL IN THE
WORDS CATEGORY.
THIS IS NOTHING BUT TALK AT
LEAST AT THIS MOMENT.
IT'S VERY CLEAR THAT THE PLANS
ARE BEING DRAWN UP.
THERE'S ALWAYS BEEN PENTAGON
GAME PLANS.
HEZBOLLAH IS IN THERE AND THE
IRANIANS SUPPORT HEZBOLLAH.
WE HAVE UNITED STATES FORCES ON
THE GROUND.
HOWEVER QUIETLY.
THEY ARE THERE FIGHTING AGAINST
ISIS.
THE RUSSIANS ARE ON THE GROUND
SUPPORTING AL-ASSAD.
YOU HAVE THIS TOXIC MIX OF ALL
OF THOSE PEOPLE AND TO REMOVE
THIS MAN FROM POWER, REGIME
CHANGE, SOMETHING AGAINST WHICH
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS RAILED FOR
YEARS.
COULD REALLY UPSET THE
EQUILIBRIUM IN THAT REGION AND
AROUND THE WORLD.
WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT I RAN HERE,
HEZBOLLAH, RUSSIA, THE UNITED
STATES AND SYRIA, THAT IS ALMOST
A WORLD WAR DEFINED OR AT LEAST
YOU RISK THAT POSSIBILITY.
>> RIGHT.
THAT'S THE THING.
IF HE WANTS TO DO SOME AIR
STRIKES ON THE WEAPONS ARSENALS,
THAT'S ONE THING.
OBVIOUSLY REGIME CHANGE IS A
HUGE OCCUPATION OF SYRIA AND A
MASSIVE GROUND WAR IN WHICH YOU
MENTIONED THERE'S SO MANY SIDES
AND PROXY FIGHTS GOING ON.
AGAIN, ARE WE GOING TO DO IT
WITH THE RUSSIANS OR NOT?
THAT'S THE QUESTION.
WE'LL LEARN MORE IN WEEKS TO
COME.
>> Shepard: WE NEED TO DISCUSS
THIS FURTHER.
THERE'S A NUMBER OF OPTIONS THAT
HAVE ALREADY BEEN DISCUSSED,
DIFFERENT POSSIBILITIES.
A.B. WILL BE BACK IN A MINUTE.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A COMMERCIAL
BREAK.
IN THE MIDDLE OF THAT, WE HAVE A
MINUTE OF OTHER HEADLINES.
AND THEN WE'LL BE BACK TO THIS.
ORGANIZING A COALITION FOR
SYRIA.
But with added touches you can't
get everywhere else,
like Claim Free Rewards...
or Safe Driving Bonus Checks.
Oh Yes....
Even a Claim Satisfaction
Guaranteeeeeeeeeee!
IN means protection
plus unique extras
only from an expert
Allstate agent.
It's good to be in,
good hands.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS SAY THEY HAVE
DIFFUSED ANOTHER EXPLOSIVE
DEVICE IN ST. PETERSBURG AND
ARRESTED THREE PEOPLE IN
CONNECTION WITH THE SUBWAY
BOMBING.
THE DEVICE TURNED UP IN THE
APARTMENT WHERE THE SUSPECT
LIVED.
THEY'RE ACCUSED OF HAVING TIES
TO THE SUICIDE BOMBER THAT
KILLED 13 OTHERS ON MONDAY.
A WOMAN THAT FELL 60 FEET TO THE
GROUND WHILE TAKING A SELFIE ON
A BRIDGE IS NOT LIKELY TO FACE
CHARGES.
THAT'S THE WORDS FROM SHERIFF
DEPUTIES.
CREWED AIRLIFTED HER AND SHE'S
EXPECTED TO SURVIVE.
FAMILY AND FRIENDS OF JOHN GLENN
GATHERING IN ARLINGTON NATIONAL
CEMETERY TO SAY THEIR FINAL
GOOD-BYES.
GLENN WAS THE FIRST AMERICAN TO
ORBIT THE EARTH.
HE DIED IN DECEMBER AT AGE 95.
RELATIVES SAID THEY HAD THE
FUNERAL TODAY BECAUSE IT WOULD
HAVE BEEN HIS 75th ANNIVERSARY
WITH HIS WIFE, ANNIE.
THE NEWS WITH SHEP CONTINUES
AFTER THIS.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL AND MUCH MORE ON
SECRETARY TILLER SEASON.
THE SECRETARY OF STATE
ANNOUNCING THAT STEPS ARE
UNDERWAY TO FORM AN
INTERNATIONAL COALITION TO
REMOVE THE MURDEROUS SYRIAN
DICTATOR, BASHAR AL-ASSAD.
THIS AFTER INTERNATIONAL
INVESTIGATORS SAY HE LAUNCHED
ANOTHER CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK
KILLING DOZENS OF HIS OWN PEOPLE
AN INJURING DOZENS AND CHILDREN
AS THEY SLEPT IN THEIR BEDS.
LET'S GO BACK TO A.B. STODDARD
FROM REALCLEARPOLITICS.COM.
YOU CAN ALWAYS CARRY OUT
STRATEGIC AIR STRIKES.
IN 2015, THE RUSSIANS WENT IN
AND OWNED THE AIR BASES.
THAT I HAVE THREE DIFFERENT
BASES AND MISSILE DEFENSE
SYSTEMS THERE.
THE IDEA THAT THE RUSSIANS WOULD
ALLOW US TO STRIKE THE SIX AIR
STRIKES THAT EXIST SEEMS AT THIS
MOMENT IMPLAUSIBLE.
>> RIGHT.
THERE'S RUSSIANS EVERYWHERE
THERE.
SO THE POTENTIAL FOR AN
ACCIDENT, WHICH WE ALMOST HAD IN
2015 WITH OUR MORE LIMITED AIR
STRIKES WITH THE RUSSIANS AND
STARTING WORLD WAR III WITH THEM
IS VERY HIGH.
SO I DON'T KNOW -- IT'S
INTERESTING THAT TRUMP SAID
UNTIL YESTERDAY THAT HE DOESN'T
TELEGRAPH WHAT HE'S GOING TO DO
AND HE LIKES TO DO THINGS
SECRETLY.
HE'S TALKING ABOUT AN
INTERNATIONAL COALITION TO TAKE
OUT AL-ASSAD WITH ALL OF THESE
TERRIBLE OPTIONS.
IT'S GOING TO BE INTERESTING TO
SEE WHAT THEY'RE CONSIDERING,
WHAT OTHER COUNTRIES ARE WILLING
TO PUT GROUND FORCES ON.
WE HAVE 900 SPECIAL FORCE
THERE'S ALREADY IN HARM'S WAY.
THE CONGRESS AT SOME POINT,
SHEP, IS GOING TO HAVE TO
WEIGH-IN ON THIS.
THEY BACKED AWAY WHEN OBAMA
WANTED TO RENEW THE 2001
AUTHORIZATION FOR USE OF
MILITARY FORCE A FEW YEARS AGO.
THEY ABDICATED THE
RESPONSIBILITY.
I WAS CRITICAL AT THE TIME THEY
DID THAT.
THE PRESSURE WILL BE ON THEM TO
WEIGH-IN ON THIS.
THAT'S A WHOLE OTHER POLITICAL
DEBATE AND WHOLE OTHER HURDLE.
>> Shepard: INTERESTING YOU SAY
THAT BECAUSE PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAID THE SAME THING BACK
REGARDING THIS MATTER EARLIER.
LOOK AT THE TWEET THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP SENT BACK, BEFORE HE WAS
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THIS WAS FROM 2013.
"WHAT WILL WE GET FOR BOMBING
SYRIA BESIDES MORE DEBT AND A
POSSIBLE LONG-TERM CONFLICT?
OBAMA NEEDS CONGRESSIONAL
APPROVAL ON THAT SAME LINE."
TODAY SENATOR RAND PAUL FROM
KENTUCKY SAID IF WE WANT TO
CARRY OUT STRIKES IN SYRIA,
THERE SHOULD BE CONGRESSIONAL
APPROVAL.
THE CHANCES OF CONGRESS WEIGHING
IN ON THIS, A.B.?
>> THEY DON'T WANT TO.
I'LL TELL YOU THAT MUCH.
THEY'LL BE FORCED.
AND IF THERE'S EVIDENCE THAT
THIS WAS A SARIN ATTACK, IT
SHOULD BE PRESENTED TO THE
PUBLIC BEFORE THERE'S ANY
MILITARY INTERVENTION.
CONGRESS WILL BE ASKING AS THEY
REPRESENT THE PEOPLE IN 435
CONGRESSIONAL DISTRICTS AND THE
HOUSE, THEY'LL BE ASKING FOR
HARD EVIDENCE TO LAY OUT THE
CASE IF THEY ARE TO SUPPORT MORE
AGGRESSIVE AIR STRIKES, LET
ALONE GROUND OPERATIONS THE
TOPPLE THE REGIME, THIS SOUNDS
LIKE A LONG BATTLE.
ALTHOUGH THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION SAYS THAT THEY'RE
WORKING ON SOME PLAN TO DO
SOMETHING EXTREMELY BOLD, AS A
FEW DAYS AGO, THEY HAD NO PLAN
IN PLACE AND NO INTENTIONS LIKE
THIS.
SO I THINK THEY'RE FLYING A BIT
BY THE SEAT OF THEIR PANTS.
NOBODY IN CONGRESS KNOW WHAT'S
THEY'RE TALKING ABOUT.
AGAIN THAT MEETING IN RUSSIA
SAYS IT WILL BE SO PIVOTAL.
HOW DOES THE UNITED STATES GO IT
ALONE AGAINST THE RUSSIANS
SUPPORTING ASSAD'S REGIME?
DOESN'T SEEM POSSIBLE.
>> Shepard: A.B. STODDARD WITH
THE BREAKING NEWS.
I APPRECIATE IT.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: I JUST LEARNED THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS SPOKEN ABOUT
SYRIA AS HE HEADED ON AIR FORCE
ONE DOWN TO FLOOR.
JOHN ROBERTS IS ALREADY IN PALM
BEACH.
WHAT DID HE SAY, JOHN?
>> GOOD AFTERNOON TO YOU.
THE PRESIDENT CAME BACK TO THE
PRESS CABIN IN THE REAR RIGHT
SIDE OF AIR FORCE ONE TO TALK
ABOUT A NUMBER OF DIFFERENT
THINGS.
HE WANTED TO TALK ABOUT THE
SUMMIT HE'S HAVING WITH
XI JINPING, WHICH IS SUPPOSED TO
BE THE THEME OF THIS NEXT 24
HOURS.
IT'S CLEAR THAT WHAT IS GOING ON
WITH SYRIA AND THE POTENTIAL
THERE IS OVERSHADOWING THAT.
A ROUTINE LEADER SUMMIT BETWEEN
THE UNITED STATES AND CHINA IS
TURNING INTO SOMETHING ELSE ALL
TOGETHER.
THE PRESIDENT TALKING TO THE
PRESS ABOUT SYRIA.
HE WAS ASKING WHETHER BASHAR
AL-ASSAD SHOULD GO.
THIS IS ON CAMERA.
WE DON'T HAVE THE TYPE.
SO I'LL READ THE TRANSCRIPT.
THE PRESIDENT SAID WHAT ASSAD
DID IS TERRIBLE.
WHAT HAPPENED IN SYRIA IS ONE OF
THE TRULY EGREGIOUS CRIMES.
AND WHEN ASKED IF THE PRESIDENT
WAS GOING TO TAKE TO PRESIDENT
PUTIN, HE SAID I MAY.
THERE WILL BE A RANGE OF OPTIONS
PRESENTED TO THE PRESIDENT ON
HOW HE COULD RESPOND MILITARY.
THE FACT THAT THEY'RE DISCUSSING
THIS DOESN'T MEAN THAT IT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
IF AN AIR STRIKE OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT WERE TO HAPPEN, IT
WOULD BE A TEST OF HOW GOOD A
RELATIONSHIP THE PRESIDENT COULD
HAVE WITH THE PRESIDENT OF
RUSSIA.
WHEN ASKED IF BASHAR AL-ASSAD
SHOULD LEAVE POWER, HE SAID IT'S
A DISGRACE TO HUMANITY.
HE'S THERE AND HE'S RUNNING
THINGS BUT SOMETHING SHOULD
HAPPEN.
REX TILLERSON IN THE CAMP OF
YES, HE NEEDS TO GO.
THE UNITED STATES TRYING TO GET
A COALITION FOR A POLITICAL
FRAME WORK FOR THAT TO HAPPEN
SOME POINT DOWN THE ROAD.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION WAS LOOKING AT
WHICH CAME TO NOTHING.
>> Shepard: IT DEED.
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION WANTED
TO STOP IT.
THE WORLD WANTS TO STOP IT.
THE LEADER OF THE COUNTRY IS
MURDERING HIS PEOPLE BY THE
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS AND THE
REST OF THE WORLD IS WATCHING
BECAUSE ALL OF THE OPTIONS ARE
BAD OPTIONS.
THAT WAS THE DECISION OF
PRESIDENT OBAMA.
HE DIDN'T ACT.
NOW THIS PRESIDENT SAYS WE NEED
TO ACT.
HE'S TRYING TO FORM A COALITION.
BUT WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU
OVERTHROW BASHAR AL-ASSAD?
WHO HOLDS THE LAND THEN?
WHO IS IN CHARGE?
HOW DO YOU COME TO SOME
AGREEMENT WITH THE RUSSIANS WHO
HAVE BEEN PROPPING UP THE SYRIAN
DICTATOR?
WOULD THE RUSSIANS ALLOW A NO
FLY ZONE?
IT'S THE RUSSIAN'S AIRSPACE.
THIS IS AS COMPLICATED AS ANY
FOREIGN MATNER THE WORLD RIGHT
NOW AS HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS ARE
DYING BEFORE OUR EYES.
WE HAVE THAT AND A LOT MORE ON
FOREIGN POLICY CHALLENGES FACING
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION.
THE MEETING WITH THE CHINESE
LEADER, XI JINPING IS ABOUT TO
HAPPEN RIGHT NOW.
ON ANY NORMAL DAY, THAT WOULD BE
THE HEADLINE.
OH, BY THE WAY, THE LEADER OF
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
THAT HAS BEEN WORKING TO
INVESTIGATE THE RUSSIAN MATTER
WHO SAID WHY WOULD I STEP DOWN?
HE JUST STEPPED DOWN.
THAT WOULD ALSO BE THE LEAD ON A
GIVEN DAY.
DEVIN NUNES, WHAT IS NEXT FOR
THAT INVESTIGATIVE BODY.
STILL TO COME ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
TOMERS.
WHO'S WITH ME?
WE'RE LIKE A BASKETBALL
TEAM HERE AT ALLY.
IF A BASKETBALL
TEAM HAD OVER 7...
I'M IN.
7,000 PLAYERS.
OUR PLAYS ARE A
LITTLE UNORTHODOX.
BUT TO BEAT THE BIG BOYS,
YOU NEED SMARTER WAYS
TO SAVE PEOPLE MONEY.
WE KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
FROM A FINANCIAL COMPANY
AND WE'LL STOP AT...
NOTHING TO MAKE SURE YOU GET IT.
ONE, TWO...
AND WE MEAN NOTHING.
♪  ♪
It's about moving forward, not
AND WE back..OTHING.
It's looking up, not down.
It's being in motion.
In body, In spirit, In the now.
BOOST® High Protein
It's intelligent nutrition with
15 grams of protein
and 26 vitamins and minerals.
For when you need a little
extra.
BOOST® Be Up for It
that gives you better taste
and better nutrition
in so many varieties.
Classic.
Cage Free.
And Organic.
Only Eggland's Best.
Better taste.
Better nutrition.
Better eggs.
how to brush his teeth.
(woman VO)
In March, my husband
didn't recognize our grandson.
(woman 2 VO)
That's when moderate Alzheimer's
made me a caregiver.
(AVO)
If their Alzheimer's
is getting worse,
ask about once-a-day NAMZARIC.
NAMZARIC is approved for
moderate to severe
Alzheimer's disease
in patients who are
taking donepezil.
It may improve cognition
and overall function,
and may slow the worsening
of symptoms for a while.
NAMZARIC does not change
the underlying
disease progression.
Don't take if allergic
to memantine,
donepezil, piperidine,
or any of the ingredients
in NAMZARIC.
Tell the doctor
about any conditions;
including heart, lung, bladder,
kidney or liver problems,
seizures, stomach ulcers,
or procedures with anesthesia.
Serious side effects may occur,
including muscle
problems if given anesthesia;
slow heartbeat, fainting,
more stomach acid
which may lead to
ulcers and bleeding;
nausea, vomiting,
difficulty urinating,
seizures, and worsening
of lung problems.
Most common side effects
are headache, diarrhea,
dizziness, loss of appetite,
and bruising.
(woman 2 VO)
I don't know
what tomorrow will bring
but I'm doing what I can.
(AVO)
Ask about NAMZARIC today.
[VO] QuickBooks introduces
and her mobile wedding business.
She travels far and wide to
officiate I do's.
And QuickBooks automatically
tracks those miles.
She categorizes with a swipe and
is ready for tax time.
Find more than $4000 in tax
savings.
Visit QuickBooks-dot-com.
>> THE PROCESS BY WHICH AL-ASSAD
WOULD LEAVE IS SOMETHING THAT
REQUIRES AN INTERNATIONAL
COMMUNITY EFFORT.
BOTH TO FIRST DEFEAT ISIS WITHIN
SYRIA, TO STABILIZE THE SYRIAN
COUNTRY TO AVOID FURTHER CIVIL
WAR AND TO WORK COLLECTIVELY
WITH OUR PARTNERS AROUND THE
WORLD THROUGH A POLITICAL
PROCESS THAT WOULD LEAD TO
AL-ASSAD LEAVING.
>> Shepard: LOFTY GOALS AND A
CHANGE IN POLICY.
WITH ALL THAT IS GOING ON WITH
SYRIA, BREAKING RIGHT NOW,
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS GEARING UP
FOR HIS FIRST MEETING WITH THE
CHINESE PRESIDENT, XI JINPING
AFTER TALKING ABOUT CHINA IN A
VERY TOUGH WAY THROUGHOUT THE
CAMPAIGN.
THROUGHOUT HIS PRESIDENCY AND
EVEN TODAY.
THIS MORNING PRESIDENT TRUMP
TOLD FOX NEWS THAT THE UNITED
STATES HAS NOT BEEN TREATED
FAIRLY ON MANY -- ON TRADE FOR
MANY, MANY YEARS BY CHINA.
LAST WEEK, HE TWEETED THAT
TODAY'S MEETING WOULD BE A "VERY
DIFFICULT ONE" SAYING WE CAN NO
LONGER HAVE MASSIVE TRADE
DEFICITS AND BIG LOSSES.
ALEX IS HERE FROM POLITICO.
ALL THE TALK COMES AND NOW THE
FACE-TO-FACE.
YOU WONDER HOW THIS WILL GO.
>> YEAH, IT'S GOING TO BE
INTERESTING AND INTERESTING TO
WATCH THE CHEMISTRY OF THESE TWO
LEADERS, HOW THEY GET ALONG, HOW
THEY WORK.
WHAT THEIR BODY LANGUAGE IS LIKE
AFTER YOU REFERENCED THE TOUGH
TALK IN THE CAMPAIGN.
WE'RE LEARNING IN REAL-TIME HOW
DONALD TRUMP RESPONDS TO FOREIGN
POLICY CRISES THAT ARE HAPPENING
ON PARALLEL TRACKS.
ON ONE HAND YOU HAVE SYRIA, ON
THE OTHER HAND YOU HAVE NORTH
KOREA THAT IS THE FOCUS OF THESE
TALKS WITH CHINA.
>> Shepard: THE WORLD NEEDS
CHINA ON THAT FRONT.
IT'S CHINA THAT HAS THE SWAY
OVER NORTH KOREA.
IT'S CHINA THAT ALLOWS FOR
REALLY 90% OF EVERYTHING THAT
NORTH KOREA NEEDS TO HAPPEN.
HOW MUCH LEVERAGE DO WE HAVE ON
CHINA WITH THIS -- ON THIS
MATTER AND WHAT DOESN'T TRUMP
PLAN TO USE AS LEVERAGE?
>> THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
THERE'S SOME QUESTION MARKS
THERE.
WHAT IS CLEAR THAT THE
ADMINISTRATION IS SERIOUS ABOUT
TRYING TO EXERT SOME PRESSURE ON
CHINA TO TAKE A TOUGHER LINE ON
NORTH KOREA.
YOU SAW THE WHITE HOUSE STARTING
TO DO THAT A LITTLE BIT THIS
WEEK AHEAD OF THE MEETING.
IT'S PRETTY CLEAR THAT BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS YOU'LL SEE
PRESIDENT TRUMP TRY TO PUSH THE
CHINESE PRESIDENT TO TAKE A
HARDER TACT HERE.
SO DURING THE CAMPAIGN, A LOT OF
TALK SURROUNDED TRADE POLICIES.
THIS MEETING WILL BE LESS ABOUT
TRADE AND MORE ABOUT NORTH
KOREA.
>> Shepard: AS WE TALK ABOUT
NORTH KOREA, THERE'S A FEAR THAT
NORTH KOREA WOULD TAKE ANOTHER
AGGRESSIVE ACTION JUST AS IT DID
A COUPLE DAYS AGO.
I THINK THOSE THAT WATCH NORTH
KOREA CLOSELY ARE CONCERNED THAT
A MISTAKE ON THE PART OF THE
NORTH KOREANS COULD START A
SERIES OF EVENTS THAT COULD LEAD
ANOTHER WAR AND UPSET THE ENTIRE
WORLD.
I'M ASSUMING THAT THAT IS PART
OF THIS DISCUSSION.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
LOOK, HOVERING OVER THIS ARE
THESE QUESTIONS THAT WE DON'T
HAVE ANSWERS TO, REALLY WHAT IS
DONALD TRUMP'S RED LINE.
WHERE IS THE POINT THAT HE WOULD
BE INTERESTED IN MILITARY ACTION
OF SOME KIND.
WE DON'T HAVE AN ANSWER FOR THAT
AND WE DON'T HAVE AN ANSWER ON
THAT YET ON NORTH KOREA EITHER.
BUT THESE ARE THE SORTS OF
THINGS THAT ARE REALLY TURNING
INTO MAJOR HEADLINES AND THE
FOCAL POINT OF THIS WEEKEND AS
HE DEALS WITH THESE TWIN CRISES.
>> Shepard: THE USE OF GOING IT
ALONE AGAINST NORTH KOREA IS NOT
OFF THE TABLE.
ALEX, THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: AS THE NEWS
CONTINUES TO BREAK ON A VERY
BUSY THURSDAY, THE CHAIRMAN OF
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
SAYS HE'S REMOVING HIMSELF FROM
THE RUSSIA INVESTIGATION AFTER
THE CONTROVERSY OVER THE
INTELLIGENCE DOCUMENTS THAT HE
VIEWED AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
NOW HE'S UNDER INVESTIGATION.
THAT'S NEXT.
So much lobster, so little time.
At Red Lobster's Lobsterfest
any of these 9 lobster dishes
could be yours.
So don't resist delicious new
Lobster Mix and Match
or Lobsterfest Surf and Turf
because you won't have this
chance for long.
>> Shepard: AFTER SAYING TO
REPORTERS FOR WEEKS, WHY WOULD I
STEP DOWN?
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
CHAIRMAN DEVIN NUNES IS STEPPING
DOWN FROM HIS PANEL'S
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIA'S
MEDDLING IN THE 2016 CAMPAIGN
ELECTION.
A TEMPORARY MOVE, HE SAYS.
ALSO NEW, THE HOUSE ETHICS
COMMITTEE IS INVESTIGATING
WHETHER NUNES MISHANDLED
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
HIS RESPONSE, SOUTHWEST
LEFT-WING ACTIVISTS GROUPS HAVE
FILED ACCUSATIONS AGAINST ME
WITH THE OFFICE OF CONGRESSIONAL
ETHICS.
THE CHARGES ARE POLITICALLY
MOTIVATED AND LEVELLED JUST AS
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ARE STARTING
TO LEARN ABOUT UNMASKING OF
CITIZENS AND ABUSE OF POWER.
DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS HAVE
QUESTIONED WHETHER CONGRESSMAN
NUNES COULD BE AT FAULT.
SOME SAY HE'S A SHIELD FOR THE
WHITE HOUSE.
NUNES SHARED INFORMATION WITH
THE PRESIDENT BEFORE HIS
COMMITTEE.
WAS HE GIVING THE PRESIDENT
COVER?
CONGRESSMAN NUNES, THE WHITE
HOUSE AND THEIR SUPPORTERS HAVE
BEEN TRYING TO CHANGE THE
NARRATIVE.
OPPONENTS SAY THEY'RE TRYING TO
DISTRACT FROM THE INVESTIGATION
INTO WHETHER MEMBERS OF TEAM
TRUMP WORKED WITH THE RUSSIANS
TO TAKE DOWNHILL HILL AND GET
THEM CANDIDATE TRUMP ELECTED.
PETER DOOCY WITH THIS BACK AND
FORTH.
PETER?
>> SHEP, CONGRESSMAN NUNES HAS
SENT A LAWYER TO THE HOUSE
ETHICS COMMITTEE.
HE WANTS TO KNOW WHAT EVIDENCE
YOU HAVE ON THEM THAT SOMEBODY
UNKNOWN, HE SAYS, A LEFT-LEANING
OUTSIDE GROUP SUBMITTED THAT LED
TO THIS INVESTIGATION.
I SPOKE TO TEXAS CONGRESSMAN
MIKE CONWAY, THE REPUBLICAN FROM
THE COMMITTEE, WHO WILL TAKE
OVER THE RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
HE SAID HE GOT A CALL FROM NUNES
LAST NIGHT ASKING HIM TO TAKE
OVER, SO HE'S GOING TO DO IT.
HE STILL HAS NOT SEEN THE
DOCUMENTS THAT NUNES SAW ON THE
WHITE HOUSE GROUNDS THAT ALLEGED
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
IMPROPERLY UNMASKED THE IDENTITY
OF TRUMP TRANSITION OFFICIALS IN
U.S. INTELLIGENCE REPORTS.
HE COULDN'T CONFIRM OR DENY
WHETHER SUSAN RICE, THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL WHO IS
ALLEGEDLY INVOLVED WITH SOME OF
THAT UNMASKING, IS GOING TO COME
AND TESTIFY.
THE REASON HE WOULDN'T CONFIRM
OR DENY AN INVITATION FOR THE
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR IN THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION IS BECAUSE
HE SAYS HE DOESN'T WANT TO
CONDUCT COMMITTEE BUSINESS IN
THE PRESS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THANKS, PETER.
BUSY NEWS DAY?
LIKE FEW OTHERS.
THE UNITED STATES PUTTING
TOGETHER A COALITION FOR REGIME
CHANGE IN SYRIA.
NEIL CAVUTO PICKS UP AFTER THIS.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT.
FORGET GOING NUCLEAR.
Z AND/OR TAX REFORM.
YOU GET AN IDEA THAT NOT
EVERYONE IS ON THE SAME PAGE?
MAYBE EVEN WITHIN THE WHITE
HOUSE ITSELF?
I'M CONFUSED.
THIS LOOKS LIKE IT'S