ECIAL
EDITION OF "SPECIAL REPORT"
ONLINE.
IT'S COMING UP.
THAT'S RIGHT IT'S MONDAY,
IT'S NOT WEDNESDAY.
IT'S COMING UP RIGHT NOW.
>> THIS IS "THE FOX
REPORT."
TONIGHT, THE MAN ACCUSED OF
EXPOSING THE TOP SECRET
GOVERNMENT PHONE AND EMAIL
SPYING PROGRAM NOW ON THE
RUN FROM SOME OF THE MOST
POWERFUL GOVERNMENTS IN ALL
THE WORLD WHAT ELSE DID HE
KNOW?
WHAT ELSE WILL HE REVEAL?
>> I SITTING AT MY DESK HAD
THE AUTHORITY TO WIRETAP
ANYONE, EVEN THE PRESIDENT.
>> Shepard: EDWARD SNOWDEN
TELLS THE GUARDIAN
NEWSPAPER THE FEDS OWE THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE AN
EXPLANATION.
>> SOME OF THESE THINGS ARE
ACTUALLY ABUSES.
>> Shepard: HE SAYS HE IS
HIDING OVERSEAS AND LOOKING
FOR ASYLUM.
BUT ONE CONGRESSMAN CALLS
HIM A DEFECTOR WHO SHOULD
PAY THE PRICE FOR PUTTING
AMERICANS IN DANGER.
>> AL QAEDA AND ITS
AFFILIATES NOW KNOW EXACTLY
WHAT WE ARE DOING.
>> Shepard: NOW ONE SENATOR
IS THREATENING TO CHALLENGE
THE SPY PROGRAM AT THE
SUPREME COURT.
PLUS GEORGE ZIMMERMAN GOES
ON TRIAL FOR KILLING TRAVON
MARTIN THE NEIGHBORHOOD
WATCH VOLUNTEER SAYS HE
SHOT THE UNARMED TEENAGER
IN SELF-DEFENSE PROSECUTORS
CALL IT SECOND DEGREE
MURDER.
TONIGHT, PICKING A JURY TO
DECIDE.
AND --
>> -- TWINKLE, TWINKLE,
LITTLE STAR
>> Shepard: HER FAMILY SAYS
THE LITTLE WHO NEEDS A LIFE
SAVING LUNG TRANSPLANT HAS
TAKEN A TURN FOR THE WORSE.
JUST DAYS AFTER WINNING THE
BATTLE TO GET ON THE ADULT
WAITING LIST.
BUT FIRST FROM FOX THIS
MONDAY NIGHT HE SAYS HE
HAD THE POWER TO WIRETAP
EVEN PRESIDENT OBAMA AND HE
WANTS AMERICANS TO KNOW HOW
MUCH POWER OUR SPY AGENCIES
HAVE TO KEEP TABS ON EACH
AND EVERY ONE OF US.
29-YEAR-OLD EDWARD SNOWDEN
SAYS THAT'S EXACTLY WHY HE
EXPOSED THE GOVERNMENT'S
PHONE AND EMAIL
SURVEILLANCE PROGRAMS.
HE SAYS HE WORKED AS A
NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY
OFFICE IN HAWAII AS AN
EMPLOYEE OF A GOVERNMENT
CONTRACTOR.
HE INSISTS HE HAS DONE
NOTHING WRONG AND TELLS THE
GUARDIAN NEWSPAPER OF GREAT
BRITAIN HE WANTED TO TAKE
DOWN WHAT HE CALLS THE
ARCHITECTURE OF OPPRESSION.
>> I'M JUST ANOTHER GUY WHO
SITS THERE DAY TO DAY IN
THE OFFICE, WATCHES WHAT'S
HAPPENING AND GOES, THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT IS NOT OUR
PLACE TO DECIDE.
THE PUBLIC NEEDS TO DECIDE
WHETHER THESE PEOPLE OR
POLICIES ARE RIGHT OR
WRONG.
SNOWDEN SAYS HE LEFT HIS
GIRLFRIEND BEHIND IN HAWAII
AND TOOK OFF FOR HONG KONG
THREE WEEKS AGO AFTER
COPYING THE DOCUMENTS HE
PLANNED TO RELEASE.
THEIR HOUSE IS NOW FOR SALE
IT TURNS OUT.
GIRLFRIEND SAID TO BE BACK
ON THE MAINLAND WEST COAST.
NEIGHBORS IN HAWAII SAY THE
COUPLE MADE SURE THAT
NOBODY COULD SEE INSIDE
THAT HOME EVERYTHING WAS
COMPLETELY BLOCKED.
LIKE A WALL OF BOXES ALL
THE WAY ACROSS.
>> Shepard: SNOWDEN SAYS HE
IS HOPING TO GET POLITICAL
ASYLUM.
MAYBE IN ICELAND THE HOME
BASE OF WIKILEAKS.
ICE ATLANTIC LAWMAKER AND
FREE SPEECH ACTIVIST SAY
THEY ARE TRYING TO GET IN
TOUCH WITH SNOWDEN TO MAKE
SURE ICELAND IS THE BEST
PLACE TO GO.
HE TOLD THE GUARDIAN ALL MY
OPTIONS ARE BAD.
WE HAVE TEAM FOX COVERAGE
CATHERINE HERRIDGE IS WITH
US TONIGHT AND JONATHAN
HUNT.
DO WE KNOW WHERE HE IS NOW.
>> TO THE BEST OF OUR
KNOWLEDGE, SHEP HE IS STILL
IN HONG KONG.
THERE HAVE BEEN REPORTS
THAT HE SPENT SOME TIME AT
THE W HOTEL IN HONG KONG.
THERE WAS ANOTHER REPORT IN
THE "THE WASHINGTON POST"
TODAY THAT A RECEPTION AT
THE MIRROR HOTEL ALSO SAID
THAT SOMEBODY BY THE NAME
OF EDWARD SNOWDEN HAD BEEN
THERE AND CHECKED OUT
EARLIER TODAY ALL OF WHICH
FITS IN WHAT SNOWDEN
HIMSELF SAID HE IS LIKELY
TO SPEND THE REST OF HIS
LIFE AS A FUGITIVE.
LISTEN.
>> I CAN BE RENDERED BY THE
CIA.
I CAN HAVE PEOPLE COME
AFTER ME OR ANY OF THEIR
THIRD PARTY PARTNERS.
THEY WORK CLOSE WHETHER I A
NUMBER OF OTHER NATIONS.
THEY COULD PAY OFF THE TRY
ADDS OR ANY OF THEIR AGENTS
OR ASSETS.
WE HAVE A CIA STATION UP
THE ROAD.
THE CONSULATE HERE IN HONG
KONG, I'M SURE THEY ARE
GOING TO BE VERY BUSY FOR
THE NEXT WEEK AND THAT'S A
FEAR I WILL LIVE UNDER FOR
THE REST OF MY LIFE
HOWEVER LONG THAT HAPPENS
TO BE.
>> SNOWDEN SAID IN THAT
SAME INTERVIEW, SHEP, THAT
HE BELIEVES ABSOLUTELY THAT
HE DID NOTHING WRONG, SHEP?
>> Shepard: HE COULD BE
BROUGHT BACK TO THE UNITED
STATES.
BUT IT SOUNDS LIKE IT'S
VERY IFFY.
>> YEAH.
THERE IS AN EXTRADITION
TREATY BETWEEN THE UNITED
STATES AND HONG KONG.
BUT IT HAS NEVER BEEN
TESTED IN A CASE LIKE THIS.
AND THERE IS AN EXCEPTION.
IF THE AUTHORITIES IN HONG
KONG BELIEVE THAT AN
EXTRADITION REQUEST IS
POLITICALLY MOTIVATED ALL
OF WHICH ACCORDING TO THE
THE SUM HONG KONG BASED
LEGAL EXPERTS MAY HELP ED
SNOWDEN, LISTEN.
>> COMING TO HONG KONG IS
PROBABLY A GOOD DECISION
BECAUSE NOT ONLY DO WE HAVE
PROTECTIONS UNDER OUR
EXTRADITION LAW, THROUGH
THE COURT SYSTEM, AND THE
POLITICAL OFFENSE
EXCEPTION, BUT WE ALSO HAVE
STRONG PROTECTIONS FOR
PEOPLE MAKING ASYLUM
CLAIMS.
>> THEN, OF COURSE, SHEP
THERE IS CHINA.
IT DOES NOT COMPLETELY
CONTROL THE DECISION THAT
THE HONG KONG AUTHORITIES
MIGHT MAKE IN THIS CASE BUT
IT DOES HAVE INFLUENCE AND
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT MAY
HAVE THEIR OWN REASONS FOR
WANTING TO KEEP EDWARD
SNOWDEN PRETTY CLOSE BY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: YEAH, THAT
MAKES SENSE.
THANKS.
SNOWDEN ALSO TOLD THE
GUARDIAN NEWSPAPER CHINA IS
NOT AN ENEMY OF THE UNITED
STATES.
TEAM FOX COVERAGE
CONTINUES.
OUR CHIEF INTELLIGENCE
CORRESPONDENT CATHERINE
HERRIDGE FROM WASHINGTON
TONIGHT.
CAT.
>> SHEP, THAT PART OF THE
INTERVIEW TRY TO DEBUNK THE
WELL DOCUMENTED STRAINS
BETWEEN WASHINGTON AND
BEIJING IS INTRIGUING.
>> CHINA IS AN ENEMY OF THE
UNITED STATES.
IT'S NOT THERE ARE
CONFLICTS BETWEEN THE
UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT
AND THE CHINESE PRC
GOVERNMENT BUT THE PEOPLES
INHERENTLY, WE DON'T CARE.
WE TRADE WITH EACH OTHER
FREELY.
YOU KNOW, WE ARE NOT AT
WAR.
>> A FORMER ATTORNEY
GENERAL SAYING THE LEAK
CASE COULD BE HANDLED BY A
JUNIOR JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
LAWYER BECAUSE SNOWDEN IS
APPARENTLY IMPLICATING
HIMSELF.
THE KEY IS GETTING TO
SNOWDEN BEFORE HE LEAKS
AGAIN AND BEIJING
INTERROGATES HIM.
>> WHEN YOU ARE ON CHINESE
TERRITORY YOU DON'T BARGAIN
WITH THE CHINESE.
YOU EITHER GIVE THEM WHAT
THEY WANT OR CONCEIVABLY
ACCIDENTS HAPPEN.
THEY ARE NOT REAL
SENTIMENTAL ABOUT STUFF
LIKE THAT.
>> A FORMER SENIOR NSA
OFFICIAL SAYING THE
INVESTIGATION WILL LIKELY
TAKE THE BIG DATA NSA
PROGRAM SNOWDEN COMPLAINS
OF AND TURN THEM ON HIM.
>> EVERYTHING WILL BE
AVAILABLE.
EVERY PLACE HE TOUCHED THE
SYSTEM ELECTRONICALLY,
TERMINALS, ACCOUNTS.
EMAILS BOTH IN THE SYSTEM
AND OUTSIDE THE SYSTEM.
ANY AND ALL INFORMATION
RELATED TO ANY CONTACT HE
MAY HAVE HAD WITH REPORTERS
AND JOURNALISTS AND OTHERS
THEY WILL TURN HIS LIFE
INSIDE OUT AS THEY DID WITH
ME.
>> DRAKE SAYS THE CHOICE OF
HONG KONG MAKES A LOT OF
SENSE BECAUSE IT SHOWS
SNOWDEN WANTED TO BE AS FAR
OUT OF REACH OF THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT AS POSSIBLE,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: AS FOR SPYING
PROGRAMS, CATHERINE IT
SOUNDS LIKE LAWMAKERS ARE
ABOUT TO LEARN MORE ABOUT
THEM.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
FOX NEWS CONFIRMING THAT
TUESDAY AFTERNOON THE FULL
HOUSE WILL BE BRIEFED BY
DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
JAMES KOHL, DEPUTY FBI
DIRECTOR SEAN JOYCE AND
DEPUTY DIRECTOR OF THE NSA
CHRIS INGLIS ON THE
PROGRAMS.
>> WE HAVE OUR INTEL
COMMITTEE THAT GETS BRIEFED
BUT THE FULL CONGRESS DOES
NOT.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE
REQUESTED TO BE BRIEFED
TOMORROW.
WE ARE GOING TO HAVE A
NUMBER OF INDIVIDUALS
COMING DOWN FROM NSA,
ATTORNEY GENERAL'S OFFICE
FBI TO WALK THROUGH THE
ENTIRE CONGRESS MEMBERS
WHAT IS GOING ON.
>> AND LATE TODAY THE
POWERFUL CHAIR OF THE
SENATE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE DIANE DIANNE
FEINSTEIN CONFIRMING HER
COMMITTEE IS GETTING A
SIMILAR BRIEFING ALSO CLOSE
TO THE PUBLIC ON THURSDAY.
ASKED WHY THE BRIEFINGS ARE
NECESSARY GIVEN THE
PRESIDENT'S CLAIM ON FRIDAY
THAT EVERYONE IN CONGRESS
KNEW ABOUT THE PROGRAM.
THE WHITE HOUSE SPOKESMAN
DID NOT DIRECTLY ANSWER
THAT QUESTION SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE
THANKS VERY MUCH.
WALL STREET ALSO REACTED TO
THIS CONTROVERSY.
CONTROLLED THE LEAKER
TANKED IN THE EARLY DAYS.
ALLEN HAMILTON STOCK
DROPPED.
IT DROPPED SOME A% AT THE
START OF TRADING AND ENDED
THE DAY DOWN.
COMPANY RELEASED A
STATEMENT SAYING SHOCKING
AND VIOLATION OF THE CORE VALUES.
SOME ARE CALLING SNOWDEN A
TRADER BUT ANDREW
NAPOLITANO HAD A VERY
DIFFERENT TAKE.
>> I WOULD DESCRIBE THIS
MAN AS AN AMERICAN HERO, AS
A PERSON REALLY TO RISK
LIFE, LIMB AND LIBERTY IN
ORDER TO EXPOSE TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE ONE OF THE
MOST EXTRAORDINARY
VIOLATIONS OF AMERICAN
PRINCIPLE VALUE JUDGMENTS
AND CONSTITUTION ITSELF IN
ALL OF OUR HISTORY.
>> Shepard: NOW, ANOTHER
LIBERTARIAN IS THREATENING
A LEGAL FIGHT AT THE
HIGHEST COURT IN OUR LAND.
THAT'S COMING UP INSIDE FOX
REPORT.
NOW, THOUGH, THE START OF
THE TRIAL OF GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN.
A CASE THAT IS SHAPING UP
TO BE THE TRIAL OF THE
SUMMER.
ATTORNEYS HAVE STARTED
QUESTIONING THE POTENTIAL
JURORS WHO ARE TO DECIDE
ZIMMERMAN'S FATE.
OF COURSE, HE IS THE
ONE-TIME NEIGHBORHOOD
WATCHMAN IN CENTRAL FLORIDA
WHO SAYS HE SHOT AND KILLED
THE TEENAGER TRAVON MARTIN
IN SELF-DEFENSE.
PROSECUTORS CHARGE HIM WITH
MURDER IN THE SECOND
DEGREE.
THOSE CHARGES DID NOT COME
UNTIL WEEKS AFTER THE
SHOOTING.
IN FACT, POLICE INITIALLY
DIDN'T ARREST THE SHOOTER,
AT LEAST UNTIL THE CASE
SPARKED PROTESTS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
BEFORE JURY SELECTION
BEGAN, TODAY FAMILY
MEMBERS OF BOTH THE SHOOTER
AND THE DEAD TEENAGER
TALKED ABOUT THE TENSION
THIS CASE HAS CREATED.
>> WE LIVE AT SECLUDED
PLACE.
NOBODY KNOWS WHERE WE LIVE.
WE HAVE DEATH THREATS
DIRECTED AT US FOR BEING
GEORGE'S FAMILY.
>> WE ASK THAT THE
COMMUNITY CONTINUE TO STAY
PEACEFUL AS WE PLACE OUR
FAITH IN THE JUSTICE
SYSTEM.
WE ASK THAT THE COMMUNITY
DO THE SAME.
>> NOW ALL THAT ATTENTION
COULD MAKE IT HARD TO FIND
JURORS WHO HAVE NOT ALREADY
MADE UP THEIR MINDS.
DEFENSE ATTORNEYS AND
PROSECUTORS ARE WORKING TO
PICK JUST SIX JURORS AND
FOUR ALTERNATES FROM A POOL
OF 500 PEOPLE.
PHIL KEATING WITH THE NEWS
AT THE COURTHOUSE IN
CENTRAL FLORIDA.
THE TOWN OF SANFORD.
PHIL, HOW MANY POTENTIAL
JURORS DID THEY GET THROUGH
SO FAR?
>> SHEP, A BIT OF A SLOW
START TODAY.
FOUR PEOPLE TOTAL.
THREE WOMEN ONE MAN BY THE
END OF DAY ONE NOT A SINGLE
JUROR YET SELECTED FOR IN
THIS TRIAL.
ABOUT 100 PEOPLE SHOWED UP
THIS MORNING.
MANY STILL HOLDING THEIR
COURT SUMMONSES TO PERFORM
THEIR CIVIC DUTY IN THE
COURTROOM.
THE JUDGE HAS BARRED THE
MEDIA FROM IDENTIFYING
THESE PEOPLE.
TOP CONCERNS FOR ATTORNEYS
PRE-TRIAL PUBLICITY AND
ACHIEVABLE IMPARTIALITY.
>> MY GIRLFRIEND HAD HER
OPINION ABOUT IT AND SHE
THINKS THAT -- SHE TOLD ME
SHE THOUGHT THAT
MR. ZIMMERMAN SHOULD HAVE
STAYED IN HIS CAR AND THAT
COULD HAVE ALLEVIATED THE
WHOLE THING.
>> BOTTOM LINE IS YOU ARE
LIKE A BLANK SLATE.
>> YEAH.
>> YOU ARE JUST GOING TO
LISTEN TO THE EVIDENCE AND
MAKE YOUR DECISION ON WHAT
HAPPENS IN THIS COURTROOM
IF YOU ARE PICKED AS A
JUROR OBVIOUSLY?
>> YES.
>> ON HAND TODAY WATCHING
IT ALL, TRAVON MARTIN'S
PARENTS SITTING IN THE
FRONT ROW AND RIGHT ACROSS
THE ROOM, SHELLY ZIMMERMAN,
THE DEFENDANT'S WIFE
SERVICING AFTER A YEAR OF
HIDING.
JUDGE DEBRA NELSON HAS YET
TO DECIDE OR AT LEAST
ANNOUNCE HER DECISION
WHETHER THE JURY WILL BE
SEQUESTERED ONCE ARGUMENTS
AND TESTIMONY BEGINS AS WAS
THE CASE, OF COURSE AT
FLORIDA'S OTHER BIG TRIAL
OF THE SUMMER TWO YEARS AGO
CASEY ANTHONY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: PHIL, THANKS.
THERE HASN'T BEEN ANY
INDICATION YET ON WHETHER
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN WILL
TESTIFY IN HIS OWN DEFENSE.
HE HAS ALREADY TAKEN THE
STAND DURING EARLIER BOND
HEARINGS.
THE GUNMAN IN FRIDAY'S
SHOOTING RAMPAGE TILLED
FIVE PEOPLE.
POLICE SAY HE HAD THE
POTENTIAL TO KILL SO MANY
MORE BECAUSE HE HAD STOCKED
UP WITH MORE THAN A
THOUSAND ROUNDS OF
AMMUNITION.
DETAILS ON THE SHOOTER AND
HIS PARENTS WHO HAD A LONG
HISTORY FIGHTS.
OFFICIALS SAY A SOLDIER
OPENED FIRE INSIDE A MAJOR
ARMY POST HOURS AGO.
POLICE SAY THE SHOOTER KNEW
HIS VICTIM.
THE DETAILS FROM THE
JOURNALISTS OF FOX NEWS ON
THIS MONDAY FOX REPORT.
I WANT TO MAKE THINGS  MORE SECURE.
[ whirring ]  [ dog barks ]  I WANT
TO TREAT MO DOGS.  ♪ ♪  OUR BUSINESS
NEEDS MORE CASES.    [ Male Announcer
] WHERE DO YOU    WANT TO TAKE YOUR
BUSINESS?  I NEED HELP SELLING ART.
[ Male Announcer ]    FROM BROADBAND
TO WEB HOSTING    TO MOBILE APPS,
SMALL BUSINESS    SOLUTIONS FROM AT&T
HAVE THE SECURITY YOU NEED    TO GET
YOU THERE.    CALL US.    WE CAN SHOW
YOU    HOW AT&T SOLUTIONS    CAN HELP
YOU DO WHAT YOU DO...    EVEN BETTER.
♪ ♪
[ Male Announcer ]    AT HIS CURRENT
PACE,    BOB WILL RETIRE WHEN HE'S
153    WHICH WOULD BE FINE    IF BOB
WERE A VAMPIRE.    BUT HE'S NOT.
♪ ♪    HE'S AN ARCHITECT    WITH TWO
KIDS AND A MORTGAGE.    LUCKILY, HE
FOUND SOMEONE    WHO GAVE HIM A FRESH
PERSPECTIVE ON HIS PORTFOLIO.    AND
WITH SOME PLANNING    AND EFFORT,
HOPEFULLY BOB CAN RETIRE    AT A MORE
APPROPRIATE AGE.    IT'S NOT ROCKET
SCIENCE.    IT'S JUST COMMON SENSE.
FROM TD AMERITRADE.
>> Shepard: WE HAVE LEARNED
MORE AT FOX REPORT TONIGHT
ABOUT THE SUSPECT IN
FRIDAY'S DEADLY CRIME SPREE
THAT ENDED IN A COMMUNITY
CLEANING IN SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA.
WE COVERED THIS STORY LIVE
AS IT HAPPENED AND NOW ONE
WOMAN WHO SUFFERED NOT ONE
BUT FOUR GUNSHOT WOUNDS
TELLS FOX NEWS THE GUNMAN
WAS FEROCIOUS AND QUICK
LIKE HE WAS ON A MISSION.
>> HE LOOKED LIKE HE WAS
LITERALLY IN THE MIDDLE OF
A MILITARY OPERATION WHERE
ALL FOCUS AND ATTENTION WAS
ON EXACTLY WHAT HE IS
DOING.
HE DIDN'T HESITATE FOR A
SECOND.
>> NOW WE HAVE A PICTURE OF
THE 23-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT.
HERE HE IS.
ACCORDING TO INVESTIGATORS
HE WAS HEAVILY ARMED WITH
UP TO 1300 ROUNDS OF AMMO.
THEY SAY HE FIRST KILLED
HIS OWN BROTHER AND FATHER.
THEN HE A APPARENTLY SET
THEIR HOUSE ON FIRE.
THEN COPS SAY HE WENT ON A
SHOOTING RAMPAGE UNTIL THEY
FINALLY CAUGHT HIM AT SANTA
MONICA COLLEGE WHERE THEY
SAY HE DIED IN A SHOOTOUT.
ADAM HOUSLEY IS IN SANTA
MONICA FOR US THIS
AFTERNOON.
WE NOW HAVE THE NAMES OF
ALL FIVE VICTIMS, RIGHT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT SHEPARD.
MARGARITA GOSMEDZ WAS THE
FIFTH AND FINAL NAME
RELEASED TODAY.
ELDERLY WOMAN LIVES NEARBY.
COME TO CAMPUS TO PICK UP
BOTTLES AND OTHER SEE CYCLE
LABLES.
KNOWN TO THE POLICE
OFFICERS AND SO.
STUDENTS.
SHE WAS NOT A STUDENT
HERSELF.
SHE WAS A VICTIM IDENTIFIED
TODAY.
SHE JOINS TWO OTHER
COMPLETELY RANDOM VICTIMS
AS PART OF THE FIVE.
CARLOS AND MARCELLA FRANCO.
THEY WERE A DAUGHTER AND
FATHER.
THEY WERE HERE ON FRIDAY AS
WELL.
HE WORKED AS A -- SOMEONE
WHO WORKED HERE AROUND THE
UNIVERSITY.
SHE WAS ACTUALLY A STUDENT.
HAD COME HERE TO GET BOOKS
ON FRIDAY WITH HER FATHER.
HE WAS SHOT DRIVING AN SUV
AND DIED AT THE SCENE.
SHE DIED OVER THE WEEKEND
FROM HER INJURIES AND THEIR
FAMILY SAYS THEY ARE
HEART-BROKEN BY THEIR
LOSSES.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> MY HUSBAND WAS A VERY
WONDERFUL HUSBAND.
AND A NICE DAD.
HE WAS VERY DEDICATED WITH
MARCELLA.
SHE WAS MY HUSBAND'S LITTLE
GIRL.
>> AND THEY WILL BE
REMEMBERED TONIGHT IN A
VIGIL HERE ON CAMPUS.
SECURITY WAS TIGHT AND WILL
BE SO WE'RE TOLD UNTIL
SUMMER SCHOOL STARTS WHICH
WILL BE A NUMBER OF DAYS
ABOUT THE MIDDLE OF JUNE.
THERE IS ALSO GOING TO BE
TOMORROW GRADUATION.
THERE WILL BE A MEMORIAL
THERE AS WELL.
MEANTIME WE ARE GETTING A
COUPLE OF PICTURES IN OF
THIS SUSPECT, JONATHAN
ZAWAHIRI WHO WENT AROUND
AND SHOT AT FOUR DIFFERENT
LOCATIONS KILLING FIRST HIS
BROTHER AND FATHER AND THEN
THOSE THREE RANDOM VICTIMS
HERE AT SANTA MONICA
COLLEGE.
HE WAS A STUDENT NEARBY.
AND WAS A STUDENT HERE AT
TIMES AS WELL.
OF COURSE, THE
INVESTIGATION INTO HIS
BACKGROUND, SHEPARD
CONTINUES AT THIS HOUR.
SHEPARD?
>> Shepard: ADAM, I
MENTIONED THE GUNMAN KILLED
HIS OWN BROTHER AND FATHER
FIRST.
COLLEAGUES AND A NEIGHBOR
SAY THE MOTHER HAD BEEN OUT
OF THE COUNTRY VISITING HER
OWN AILING MOTHER IN
LEBANON IS COURT DOCUMENTS
SHOW THE GUNMAN'S PARENTS
HAD FOUGHT FOR YEARS.
THEY SHOW THAT THE FATHER
TRIED TO GET A DIVORCE BACK
IN 1993 AND THE MOTHER
REQUESTED A RESTRAINING
ORDER AGAINST HIM JUST FIVE
YEARS LATER CALLING HIM
VERBALLY ABUSIVE AND
CONTROLLING.
THEY EVENTUALLY DID
SEPARATE.
THE MOTHER ALSO WORKS PART
TIME AT A RESTAURANT IN
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA.
TODAY ITS TWO OWNERS SAID
SHE IS WELL-LIKED BY HER
CO-WORKERS AND PRAY TON --
PATRONS SHE HAS BEEN
RESPONSIBLE EMPLOYEE.
WE HAD NO KNOWLEDGE OF HER
PERSONAL LIFE.
A U.S. SOLDIER SHOT AND
WOUNDED A FELLOW SERVICE
MEMBER INSIDE AN ARMY POST
TODAY.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO A
SPOKESMAN FOR FORT SAM
HOUSTON IN THE SAN ANTONIO
AREA.
THE POST WENT ON LOCKDOWN
ABOUT TWO HOURS AFTER THE
SHOOTING.
THAT SPOKESMAN SAID THAT
THE SHOOTER EVENTUALLY
TURNED HIMSELF IN AND IS
NOW IN MILITARY CUSTODY.
POLICE SAY THE SHOOTER AND
THE VICTIM WERE IN SOME
SORT OF RELATIONSHIP AND
THAT THE GUNMAN DID NOT
TARGET ANYBODY ELSE.
THE ARMY REPORTS FORT SAM
HOUSTON HAS BEEN OPERATING
SINCE THE 19TH CENTURY.
MANY ARMY MEDICS GO THROUGH
TRAINING THERE.
THE PEOPLE WHO DECIDE WHICH
PATIENTS CAN GET ORGAN
TRANSPLANTS ARE MEETING TO
DISCOVER NEW RULES FOR
CHILDREN THAT AS THE MOTHER
OF A GIRL WHO DESPERATELY
NEEDS NEW LUNGS STAY MIGHT
ALREADY BE TOO LATE.
TROUBLING UPDATE ON SARAH
NEXT.
PLUS WE ARE WATCHING THE
WEATHER AND THE THREAT OF
DANGEROUS TWISTERS IN
PLACES THAT WE DON'T OFTEN
REPORT ON HERE.
COMING UP, THE MAJOR EAST
COAST CITY WHERE FOLKS
SPOTTED THIS FRIGHTENING
SITE.
[ Female Announcer ] CALTRATE'S
DONEVEN MORE TO MOVE US.    BECAUSE
VITAMIN D3 HELPS BONES    ABSORB CALCIUM
CALTRATE HAS THE HIGHEST LEVEL
OF VITAMIN D3.     MORE THAN    ANY
OTHER BRAND,    TO HELP MAXIMIZE
CALCIUM ABSORPTION.    SO CALTRATE
WOMEN    CAN MOVE THE WORLD.
WITH OUR "NAME YOUR PRICE" TOOL, PEOPLE
PICK A PRICE AND WE HELP THEM FIND
A POLICY THAT WORKS FOR THEM. Huh?
ALSO...
WE'VE BEEN WORKING ON SOMETHING VERY
SPECIAL.
[ MINIONS GASP, CHUCKLE ]
Ohhh! Ohhh!
ONE DAY THE WORLD...
NO, THE UNIVERSE WILL HAVE THE PRICING
POWER THEY DESERVE.
MOUHAHAHA!
Mouhahaha!
Ooh-hee-hee-hee! Blaaaah!
WE'LL WORK ON IT.
WATCH UNSEEN FOOTAGE Wah-hah-hah!
ONLY AT PROGRESSIVE.COM/DM2.
>> Shepard: THE YOUNG GIRL
WHO NEEDS A LUNG TRANSPLANT
TO LIVE IS IN WORSENING
CONDITION.
HER MOTHER SAYS SHE THOUGHT
HER DAUGHTER MIGHT DIE AT
ONE POINT OVER THE WEEKEND.
A HEALTH SCARE ON SATURDAY
FORCED DOCTORS IN PHILLY TO
SEDATE THE 10-YEAR-OLD AND
INSERT A BREATHING TUBE.
SHE IS IN THE END STAGES
THEY TELL US OF CYSTIC
FIBROSIS.
GENETIC DISORDER THAT
CAUSES LUNG INFECTIONS.
LATEST ORDEAL LEFT HER
FEELING TERRIFIED AND
OVERWHELMED.
A JUDGE ORDERED LAST WEEK
THAT SHE AND AN 11-YEAR-OLD
BOY WITH THE SAME DISEASE
SHOULD BOTH GO ON THE ADULT
WAITING LIST FOR ORGAN
TRANSPLANT.
THE RULES NORMALLY KEEP
ANYBODY UNDER 12 OFF THAT
LIST.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH MORE.
TRACE, SOME TENSE MOMENTS
FROM THE FAMILY THAT'S
ALREADY ENDURED SO MUCH.
>> AND BECAUSE SHE IS ON A
BREATHING TUBE SHEP HER
LUNG ALLOCATION SCORE WHICH
IS WHAT THEY USE TO GAUGE
HOW SICK SHE IS HAS
SKYROCKETED.
A WEEK AGO IT WAS 66.
FRIDAY 78.
NOW IT'S UP TO 91.
IT JUST CANNOT GET ANY
WORSE.
NOW, SHE IS AT THE TOP OF
THE TRANSPLANT LIST BUT
THREE FACTORS PLAY INTO
WHEN SHE ACTUALLY GETS
DONOR LUNGS.
ONE IS GEOGRAPHY.
THE DONOR LUNGS CAN ONLY BE
A FEW HOURS AWAY OR THEY
SIMPLY WILL NOT LAST.
TWO, SIZE ADULT LUNGS CAN
BE MODIFIED TO FIT SARAH
BUT THEY CANNOT BE TOO BIG
OR THEY WON'T WORK AND
FINALLY, BLOOD TYPE.
IT HAS TO MATCH.
SO THE BODY WILL NOT REJECT
IT THE BOTTOM LINE HERE,
SHEP, IS THE FAMILY NEEDS
THE STARS TO ALIGN AND THEY
NEED THEM TO ALIGN VERY
QUICKLY, SHEP?
>> Shepard: TODAY, HEALTH
EXPERTS HELD A BIG MEETING
ON ORGAN TRANSPLANT RULES
FOR KIDS, TRACE.
>> IT LED TO IT A BIG
CHANGE SHEP.
YOU HAD LAWYERS ARGUING
THAT THE RULE UNDER 12
SHOULD BE CHANGED.
YOU HAD A TRANSPLANT
PATIENT SAYING THAT THE
REAL KEY IS TO GET MORE
DONORS INVOLVED, PEOPLE TO
SIGN UP.
MOST OF THE DOCTORS SAID
THE RULES SHOULD NOT BE
CHANGED BECAUSE INHERENTLY
IT WAS NOT UNFAIR.
UP ABOUT BUT THEN YOU HAD
THE CHAIRMAN OF THE ORGAN
TRANSPLANT WHO SAID KIDS
UNDER 12 SHOULD BE TAKEN
CASE BY CASE.
LISTEN TO HIM.
>> STANDARD TO ALLOW
CENTERS TO REQUEST A LUNG
ALLOCATION SCORE FOR A
PATIENT BELOW THE AGE OF 12
IN ORDER THAT IF DEEMED
APPROPRIATE BY THE LUNG
REVIEW BOARD THEY MAY
RECEIVE ADDITIONAL PRIORITY
FOR ADOLESCENT AND ADULT
LUNGS.
>> AND IN THE END, THE
CHAIRMAN WON.
KIDS WILL NOW BE EVALUATED
UNDER 12 CASE BY CASE FOR
AT LEAST THE NEXT YEAR.
IT'S A BIG VICTORY FOR KIDS
UNDER 12, SHEP.
>> Shepard: IT SOUNDS LIKE
IT IT TRACE GALLAGHER
THANKS.
FACEBOOK APPLE ALL DENY
REPORTS THAT THEY GAVE THE
GOVERNMENT DIRECT ACCESS TO
THEIR SERVERS WHO KEEP TABS
ON ALL OF US AND ALL USING
STRIKINGLY SIMILAR LANGUAGE
ABOUT THOSE NSA LEAKS.
WE'LL HAVE THAT FIRST A FOX
NEWS WEATHER ALERT.
TORNADO WATCHES IN EFFECT
FOR SEVERAL COUNTIES ACROSS
THE TENNESSEE VALLEY AND UP
AND DOWN THE EAST COAST
INCLUDING THE NATION'S
CAPITAL AND PART OF
MARYLAND.
SHEAR A FUNNEL CLOUD
FORMING BALTIMORE.
SOME FOLKS ON THE GROUND
CAPTURED THIS VIDEO OF IT
AS IT CAME OUT OF THE SKY.
CHIEF METEOROLOGIST AT OUR
FOX STATION THERE SNAPPED
THIS PHOTO OF THE THING
FROM A HIGH RISE BUILDING
NEAR THE HARBOR.
JANICE DEAN IS IN OUR
EXTREME WEATHER CENTER
TONIGHT.
JANICE?
>> YEAH PEOPLE ON EDGE,
SHEPARD.
SEVERAL TORNADO WATCHES AS
YOU MENTIONED.
SEVERAL THUNDERSTORM
WARNINGS AND TORNADO
WARNINGS RIGHT NOW AS WE
SPEAK.
LET'S ZOOM IN TO THIS ONE
FOR SOUTHEASTERN VIRGINIA.
CITY OF CHESAPEAKE AND
VIRGINIA BEACH AS THIS CELL
MOVES NORTH AND EASTWARD
AND THEN UP TOWARDS
MARYLAND.
HOWARD, BALTIMORE COUNTY
AND CARO COUNTY UNTIL 8:00
P.M. LOCAL TIME.
SO WE ARE SPOTTING SOME
SERIOUS ROTATION ON DOPPLER
RADAR.
THIS THREAT IS GOING TO
CONTINUE OVERNIGHT INTO
TOMORROW.
SHEPARD, SEE THE THREAT FOR
FLOODING.
STAY SAFE AND STAY TUNED.
MORE SHEPARD AND "THE FOX
REPORT" WHEN WE RETURN.
EVEN IN STUPID LOUD PLACES.  TO PROVE
IT, WE SET UP  OUR CALL CENTER RIGHT
HERE...  [ chirp ]  ALL GOOD?  [ chirp
]  GETTY UP.
SERIOUSLY,  THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING!
[ cellphone rings ]  HELLO?  IT'S
A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.    [ Male
Announcer ] GET IT DONE  [ chirp ]
WITH THE ULTRAUGGED    ocera Torque
ONLY FROM Sprint   Direct Conct.
BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE    FOR YOUR
BUSINESS.
For all those who sleep
too hot or too cool, and struggle
to sleep comfortably together
now there's a solution.
Introducing Sleep Number DualTemp,the
revolutionary
temperature-balancing layer
with Active Air technology that
works on any mattress, including yours.
Whether you sleep hot or cool,
Sleep Number Dual Temp allows each
of you to
select your ideal temperature.
And it's only at one of our over
400 Sleep Number stores nation wide.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
[ Male Announcer ]    ERICA HAD A
ROUGH DAY.    SHE GOT A PARKING TICKET...
♪ ♪    AND SHE FORGOT TO PAY    HER
CREDIT CARD BILL ON TIME.    GOOD
THING SHE'S GOT    THE CITI SIMPLICITY
CARD.    IT DOESN'T CHARGE LATE FEES
OR A PENALTY RATE. EVER.    AS IN
NEVER EVER.    NOW ABOUT THAT PARKING
TICKET.  [ grunting ]    [ Male Announcer
] TO APPLY    FOR THE CITI SIMPLICITY
CARD    GO TO CITI.COM/SIMPLICITY.
IT'S THE ONLY CARD THAT NEVER    HAS
LATE FEES, A PENALTY RATE,    OR AN
ANNUAL FEE, EVER.    SO APPLY TODAY.
Can vitamins melt into mouth-watering
flavor? Yes. With New Nature Made
VitaMelts.
Melt-in-your-mouth vitamin supplements.
In flavors like creamy vanilla...
...And juicy orange
Irresistibly melty
New Nature Made VitaMelts.
Get a sample on our facebook page
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR HELP RELIEVING
HEARTBURN, CAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES 24-HOUR
HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE AVAILABLE FOR JUST $18
A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE AND
LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA, CONTACT
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH CONDITIONS MAY
EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT HAND FOR JUST $18 A MONTH.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT NEXIUM.
>> Shepard: THERE IS
BREAKING NEWS NOW ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
A SOUTHWEST AIRLINES FLIGHT
FROM LOS ANGELES TO AUSTIN,
TEXAS HAS BEEN DIVERTED.
IT'S NOW IN PHOENIX.
AND LAW ENFORCEMENT THERE
IN LOS ANGELES SAY THEY ARE
CHECKING OUT A POSSIBLE
THREAT.
LET'S GET TO TRACE
GALLAGHER IN LOS ANGELES AT
THE BREAKING NEWS DESK.
WHAT'S, THIS TRACE?
>> A SECURITY THREAT
APPARENTLY MADE IN THE AIR,
SHEP.
THIS THING LANDED EMERGENCY
LANDING IN PHOENIX SKY
HARBOR AIRPORT.
AS YOU SEE THERE THE PLANE
WAS RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE TARMAC.
THEY BROUGHT OUT THE STAIRS
AND THEY EVACUATED ALL 143
PEOPLE OFF BOARD THAT
PLANE.
A PASSENGER OR SOMEONE AT
LEAST CLAIMING TO BE A
PASSENGER TWEETED OUT AND
WE CAN'T CONFIRM THIS
SAYING THAT IT WAS LED IN
BY A FIGHTER JET ESCORT.
WE HAVE CONTACTED SOUTHWEST
AIRLINES TO GET
CONFIRMATION.
SO FAR NO WORD ON EXACTLY
WHAT THAT SECURITY THREAT
IS.
BUT IT DID CLOSE DOWN AS
YOU SEE HE THERE PARTS OF
THE AIRPORT.
THEY ARE TRYING TO GET
INCOMING AND OUTGOING
PLANES GOING BACK ON
SCHEDULE HERE.
CLEARLY THEY HAVE NOW BUSED
THE PASSENGERS AWAY AND
THEY ARE GETTING THEM
INSIDE THE TERMINAL AND
THEY HAVE GOT FULL SECURITY
CREWS NOW BOARDING THE
AIRPLANE TO FIND OUT
EXACTLY WHAT, IF ANY THREAT
MAY HAVE BEEN ON BOARD.
143 PASSENGERS.
WE'LL KEEP YOU UP TO SPEED
AS WE GET MORE INFORMATION
ON EXACTLY WHAT THAT THREAT
WAS SHEP.
>> Shepard: GOOD TRACE,
THANKS.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR, TIME FOR THE TOP OF
THE NEWS.
AND EXECUTIVES OF SOME OF
AMERICA'S BIGGEST TECH
COMPANIES INSIST THEY ARE
NOT GIVING THE FEDS DIRECT
ACCESS.
TO SNOOP ON EVERYTHING WE
ARE DOING ONLINE.
ANALYSTS SAY THAT MAY NOT
BE THE WHOLE STORY.
IT'S THE TOP STORY AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR.
DOUG McKELWAY IS ON IT
LIVE FROM D.C.
DOUG?
>> SHEP GOOGLE'S CEO ERIC
SCHMIDT SAID BACK IN 2009
QUOTING NOW IF YOU HAVE
SOMETHING THAT YOU DON'T
ANYBODY TO KNOW ABOUT MAYBE
YOU SHOULDN'T BE DOING IT
IN THE FIRST PLACE.
ALL OF THE HIGH TECH
COMPANIES NAMED IN THE NSA
LEAK HAVE DENIED
INVOLVEMENT IN THE NSA
PRISM PROGRAM.
THE SIMILARITY OF THEIR
STATEMENTS ABOUT THAT IS
REMARKABLE.
MARK ZUCKERBERG OF FACEBOOK
SAID HERE FACEBOOK IS NOT
AND HAS NEVER BEEN PART OF
ANY PROGRAM TO GIVE THE
U.S. OR ANY OTHER
GOVERNMENT DIRECT ACCESS TO
OUR SERVERS.
GOOGLE'S STATEMENT READ AND
I'M QUOTING WE HAVE NOT
JOINED ANY PROGRAM THAT
WOULD GIVE THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT OR ANY OTHER
GOVERNMENT DIRECT ACCESS TO
OUR SERVERS.
AND APPLE'S STATEMENT,
QUOTE:  WE HAVE NOT PROVIDE
ANY GOVERNMENT AGENCY WITH
DIRECT ACCESS TO OUR
SERVERS.
OUR CATHERINE HERRIDGE
REPORTED ON FRIDAY IN 2012
THE OBAMA CAMPAIGN
HARNESSED GOOGLE'S
EXPERTISE TO BUILD VIRTUAL
PROFILES OF VOTERS.
THAT VERY TEAM OPERATES
CIVIS ANALYTICS GOOGLE'S
ERIC SCHMIDT INVESTED
EVIDENCE HADLY IN THAT
COMPANY.
EXPECTS THE COMPANY TO WORK
FOR DEMOCRATIC CANDIDATES
AND ONLY DEMOCRATS NEXT
YEAR.
ONE GOVERNMENT WATCHDOG
SAYS THERE IS HUGE
POTENTIAL FOR DATA MINING
OF POLITICAL OPPONENTS.
>> WE DECIDE WE WANT TO
TARGET UNION MEMBERS.
WE WANT TO TARGET TEA PARTY
MEMBERS.
WE WANT TO TARGET WHOEVER
WE WANT, THEY CAN TAKE THE
INFORMATION THEY BUY FROM
ONE DATA BROKER COMBINE IT
WITH ANOTHER.
>> GIVEN THE RECENT
REVELATIONS THAT FOX NEWS
JAMES ROSEN AND OTHERS WERE
TARGETED BY THE DOJ AND
CONSERVATIVE GROUPS WERE
TARGETED BY THE IRS, MANY
AMERICANS WANT TO KNOW MORE
ABOUT THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT AND THE SEARCH
ENGINES WE ALL USE.
SHEP BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: DOUG, THANKS.
ONE LAWMAKER SAYS HE WANTS
TO LAUNCH A CLASS ACTION
LAWSUIT AGAINST THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT OVER ITS
ELECTRONIC SNOOPING.
AND HE WANTS YOUR HELP.
SENATOR RAND PAUL TOLD "FOX
NEWS SUNDAY" HOST CHRIS
WALLACE HE WILL ASK PHONE
COMPANIES AND INTERNET
PROVIDERS TO INVITE THEIR
CUSTOMERS TO JOIN HIM IN
THE LEGAL CHALLENGE.
AND THAT IF 10 MILLION
PEOPLE SIGN ON, MAYBE
QUOTE:  SOMETHING WILL
CHANGE IN WASHINGTON.
THE KENTUCKY REPUBLICAN
ALSO SAYS HE HOPES THE CASE
EVENTUALLY REACHES THE
SUPREME COURT.
CARL CAMERON WITH HIS STORY
FROM D.C.
CARL?
>> THANKS, SHEP.
RAND PAUL IS A G.O.P.
CONSERVATIVE AND TEA PARTY
FAVORITE ALSO POSITIONING
FOR A 2016 PRESIDENTIAL
RUN.
HE DELIVERED A COMMENCEMENT
ADDRESS IN PENNSYLVANIA
TODAY.
THE CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT
AGAINST WHAT PAUL CALLS THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION'S BIG
GOVERNMENT INTRUSION MAKES
A GREAT POLITICAL
ORGANIZING TOOL OVER THE
NEXT FOUR YEARS.
OUTRAGE OVER THE NATIONAL
SECURITY AGENCY'S
COLLECTION OF CALL DATA
RECORDS FROM BILLIONS OF
PHONE CALLS IN THE U.S. HAS
ONCE AGAIN UNITED CIVIL
LIBERTARIANS ON THE RIGHT
AND THE LEFT.
>> THIS IS WHAT WE OBJECTED
TO AND WHAT OUR FOUNDING
FATHERS PARTLY FOUGHT THE
REVOLUTION OVER IS THEY DID
NOT WANT GENERALIZED
WARRANTS WHERE YOU COULD GO
HOUSE TO HOUSE WITH
SOLDIERS LOOKING FOR THINGS
OR NOW FROM COMPUTER TO
COMPUTER TO PHONE TO PHONE
WITHOUT SPECIFYING WHO YOU
ARE TAGHTING WELL PAUL
BLAMES BOTH PARTIES IN
CONGRESS TOO MUCH EXECUTIVE
POWER.
ON THE LIBERAL LEFT YOU
HAVE FOLKS LIKE FORMER OHIO
CONGRESSMAN DENNIS KUCINICH
WHO HAS RUN FOR PRESIDENT
HIMSELF TWICE.
HERE HE IS.
>> YOU HAVE AN EXPECTATION
TO PRIVACY THAT GOVERNMENT
WILL STAY OUT OF YOUR
BEDROOM THAT GOVERNMENT
WILL STAY OUT OF YOUR BANK
ACCOUNTS YOUR MEDICAL
RECORDS, YOUR EDUCATIONAL
RECORDS.
ONCE THE PATRIOT ACT WAS
PASSED, IT PIERCED THAT
SHIELD OF PROTECTION WHICH
INDIVIDUALS THOUGHT THAT
THEY HAD.
>> WELL, KUCINICH VOTED
AGAINST THE PATRIOT ACT.
RAND PAUL WASN'T IN
CONGRESS AT THE TIME.
HE HAS SINCE EMERGED AS A
REAL HARSH CRITIC AND EACH
PUSHED TO BLOCK THE PATRIOT
ACT'S REAUTHORIZATION.
BEN FRANKLIN SUMMED IT UP
TWO CENTURIES AGO PLUS
SAYING THOSE WILLING TO
GIVE UP LIBERTY TO OBTAIN A
TEMPORARY MEASURE OF SAFETY
DESERVE NEITHER.
BUT HE WAS LIVING IN THIS
MODERN AGE OF INSTANTANEOUS
GLOBAL COMMUNICATION AND
TERRORISM.
AND THAT'S WHERE THE
DILEMMA REALLY SAND BOTH
SIDES ARE TRYING TO BALANCE
IT SHEP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CARL, THERE IS NEW WORD OF
KNOW.
GOVERNMENT SCANDAL THIS
TIME AT THE AGENCY IN
CHARGE OF U.S. DIPLOMACY.
A REPORT BY THE STATE
DEPARTMENT'S OWN
INVESTIGATORS CLAIMS
OFFICIALS THERE COVERED UP
ALLEGATIONS THAT EMPLOYEES
OVERSEAS COMMITTED SEXUAL
ASSAULT, SOLICITED
PROSTITUTES AND USED DRUGS.
CBS NEWS FIRST BROKE THIS
STORY AND FOX NEWS OBTAINED
MEMO FROM THE STATE
INSPECTOR GENERAL'S OFFICE
THAT DETAILS 8 SPECIFIC
INSTANCES OF SUSPECTED
CRIMES AND FINDS OFFICIALS
DID COMPROMISE
INVESTIGATIONS INTO CHARGES
OF MISCONDUCT TO AVOID
CONTROVERSY AND PROTECT THE
ACCUSED.
JAMES ROSEN IS LIVE FOR US
AT THE STATE DEPARTMENT.
JAMES?
>> SHEP, GOOD EVENING.
THE EIGHT CASES LISTED IN
THAT OCTOBER 2012 MEMO FROM
WITHIN THE STATE
DEPARTMENT'S OFFICE OF
INSPECTOR GENERAL OR OIG
INCLUDED ALLEGATIONS THAT
THE DIPLOMATIC SECURITY OR
DS AGENTS PROTECTING THEN
SECRETARY OF STATE HILLARY
CLINTON OVERSEAS WERE
GUILTY OF AN ENDEMIC
PROSTITUTION PROBLEM.
STATE DENIED THAT TODAY
SAYING ANY PROBLEMS THAT
MAY HAVE EXISTED WERE NOT
ENDEMIC.
AIG MEMO NAMED CLINTON'S
CHIEF OF STAFF CHERYL MILLS
AS THE OFFICIAL WHO
INTERVENED TO BLOCK A FULL
INVESTIGATION INTO A U.S.
DIPLOMAT IN IRAQ DISCOVERED
TO HAVE SHARED SENSITIVE
DATA WITH HIS MISTRESS, A
REPORTER.
A DRAFT OIG REPORT WRITTEN
DECEMBER 20123 CONCLUDED
THE OIG TEAM INSTANCES
WHERE ONCE OR TWICE A YEAR
BROUGHT PRESSURE TO BEAR TO
IMPROPERLY HALT OR
INFLUENCE INVESTIGATIONS
INCLUDING INTO ALLEGATIONS
OF SERIOUS CRIMINAL
MISCONDUCT.
>> THESE ARE ALLEGATIONS IN
A MEMO.
SO, OBVIOUSLY AS I STATED
AT THE BEGINNING, THEY HAVE
BEEN -- ALL THESE CASES ARE
BEING LOOKED INTO.
THEY WERE ALREADY IN THE
PROCESS OF OF COURSE LOOKED
INTO PRIOR TO THE MEMO.
AND, AGAIN, I DON'T HAVE
ANY UPDATE ON STATUS.
BUT I CAN SAY BROADLY THE
NOTION THAT WE WOULD NOT
VIGOROUSLY PURSUE CRIMINAL
MISCONDUCT IN A CASE IN ANY
CASE IS PREPOSTEROUS.
>> THE OCTOBER OIG MEMO
ALSO CONTAINED ALLEGATIONS
ABOUT A U.S. AMBASSADOR
STILL ON THE JOB IN A
EUROPEAN COUNTRY WHO IS
SAID TO HAVE ROUTINELY
DITCHED HIS PROTECTIVE
DETAIL IN ORDER TO SOLICIT
SEX FROM PROSTITUTES AND
MINORS.
FOX NEWS IS WITHHOLDS THE
NAME OF THAT DIPLOMAT
BECAUSE THOSE    ALLEGATIONS
REMAIN UNVERIFIED.
>> Shepard: THE DSS IS THE
STATE DEPARTMENT'S OWN
SECURITY FORCE.
IT IS IN CHARGE OF
PROVIDING PROTECTION FOR
THE SECRETARY OF STATE AND
FOR U.S. AMBASSADOR SERVING
ABRODZ.
THE SERVICE ALSO
INVESTIGATES INVESTIGATION
OF MISCONDUCT ON THE PART
OF 70,000 STATE DEPARTMENT
EMPLOYEES AROUND THE GLOBE.
WELL A BREAKING NEWS
UPDATE NOW FROM PHOENIX.
NEW INFORMATION ON THAT
EMERGENCY LANDING.
POLICE SAY THEY ARE
CHECKING OUT A THREAT.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THE
NEWS INFORMATION NEXT.
You will never survive The Running
of the Bulls... ( Bull Roar )
...if you don't attend The Running
of the Bulls.
Ole!
p>nÑ@ç-ÑO/,o wt;gG7;4ho@u@çw.Ñ@m;o7Mñs└@oñsx>úópñúóóPí8hn@wñ?Ñóó@w??Ñv>ñwúbpí]spS÷lwt0éo?óú]úÑuoW
m÷ççw@>+O@Ñ
>> Shepard: CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF THE BREAKING
NEWS FROM ARIZONA AND FOR
THAT MATTER LOS ANGELES.
A SOUTHWEST AIRLINES FLIGHT
MADE AN EMERGENCY LANDING
IN PHOENIX.
IT'S FLIGHT 2675, 143
PASSENGERS ON BOARD.
LAW ENFORCEMENT SAY
BASICALLY AND NOTHING ELSE,
THEY ARE CHECKING OUT A
POSSIBLE THREAT.
BUT TRACE GALLAGHER HAS AN
UPDATE FOR US.
TRACE, WHAT KIND OF THREAT.
DO WE KNOW.
>> APPARENTLY WE DON'T KNOW
THE SHEP, SHEP.
BUT APPARENTLY IT WAS
PHONED IN LIE THE LOS
ANGELES POLICE DEPARTMENT.
WE JUST CALLED L.A.P.D. AND
THEY WON'T CONFIRM THAT
APPARENTLY THE THREAT
ORIGINATED HERE IN LOS
ANGELES AS DID THE PLANE IN
ROUTE TO AUSTIN, TEXAS.
THE PILOT SAYING OUT OF
ABUNDANCE OF CAUTION HE
LANDED IN PHOENIX.
YOU SEE THE PLANE RIGHT
THERE.
THE PLANE WAS PULLED OFF
THE SIDE OF THE TARMAC.
THEY PUT THE STAIRS UP
THERE AND EVACUATED ALL 143
PASSENGERS.
WE'RE STILL TRYING TO
CONFIRM A TWEET THAT WAS
SENT OUT BY SOMEBODY
CLAIMING TO BE A PASSENGER
SAYING THE PLANE ACTUALLY
HAD A MILITARY ESCORT, A
FIGHTER JETTERS COURT, IF
YOU WILL, IN TO PHOENIX SKY
HARBOR AIRPORT.
AND YOU SHOULD NOTE, YOU
CAN SEE OUR FOX AFFILIATE
THERE UP IN THE AIR GETTING
PICTURES OF THIS.
WE SHOULD NOTE THAT THE
WEST END OF SKY HARBOR
AIRPORT HAS BEEN SHUT DOWN.
THEY ARE TRYING TO GET
TRAFFIC REREGULATED AGAIN.
FOR THE TIME BEING PEOPLE
GOING TO AND FROM THE THE
AIRPORT ARE GOING TO HAVE
SOME DIFFICULTIES.
YOU SHOULD ALSO KNOW THAT
THE SOUTHWEST PLANE LANDED
WITHOUT INCIDENT AT ALL THE
PASSENGERS GOT OUT.
WE WERE TOLD IT WAS A VERY
CALM EXIT AND NOW WE ARE
BEING TOLD BY ONE OF THE
LOCAL AFFILIATES THERE THAT
THE PASSENGERS ARE INSIDE
THE TERMINAL SHEP, THEY
ARE HAVING TO FILL OUT
THESE FBI QUESTIONNAIRES.
WE DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
THE QUESTIONS ARE.
IT MAY BE STANDARD
OPERATING PROCEDURE BECAUSE
THEY LEFT ALL OF THEIR
BELONGINGS ON BOARD THAT
PLANE.
THE PLANE NOW HAS A
SECURITY TEAM THAT IS ON
BOARD SWEEPING IT, LOOKING
FOR ANY KIND OF SECURITY
THREAT AT ALL.
HIGHLY UNUSUAL FOR A THREAT
TO BE CALLED IN BY A LOCAL
POLICE DEPARTMENT AND THEN
TRANSFERRED UP TO THE PILOT
AND THEN HE KIND OF MAKES
THE DECISION ON WHETHER TO
LAND.
BUT THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
JUST HAPPENED IN PHOENIX.
WE'RE NOW BEING TOLD THAT
ALL THOSE PASSENGERS WILL
BE REROUTED TO AUSTIN,
TEXAS SOON AS ANOTHER PLANE
BECOMES AVAILABLE.
THAT PLANE RIGHT THERE
WON'T GO ANYWHERE FOR THE
TIMENNING BECAUSE IT IS NOW
UNDER SURVEILLANCE OR AT
LEAST SECURITY WATCH TO
MAKE SURE THAT IT IS
TOTALLY CLEAR AND THEY HAVE
TO KIND OF DO THE TRIFECTA
OF CHECKING THE THREE
POINTS, IF YOU WILL,
L.A.P.D. FBI, AND THE FAA
WILL MAKE SURE EVERYTHING
IS FINE WITH THAT PLANE
BEFORE IT GOES AIRBORNE
AGAIN SHEP.
WE WILL KEEP YOU UP TO
SPEED ON MORE DEVELOPMENTS
AS THEY COME IN WITH THIS
EMERGENCY LANDING AT SKY
HARBOR AIRPORT.
>> Shepard: I WONDERED IF
THIS WASN'T SOMETHING THAT
MIGHT INSIDE
BECAUSE THEY HAVE KEPT IT
SO FAR FROM THE TERMINAL
YOU WONDER IF THE POLICE IN
LOS ANGELES HADN'T
SUGGESTED THERE IS
SOMETHING ON HERE THAT
MIGHT BE OF DANGER TO
PEOPLE IN THAT TERMINAL.
>> IT'S A GREAT POINT.
I MEAN, IT'S A GREAT POINT.
WHY NOT JUST BRING IT UP IF
THEY THOUGHT SOMETHING WAS
DANGEROUS ENOUGH TO LEAVE
IT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
TARMAC IT'S A VERY GOOD
POINT, BECAUSE NORMALLY YOU
WOULD BRING IT CLOSER TO
THE GATES.
THEY BROUGHT THE BUS OUT TO
THE PLANE.
OF COURSE, THEY BROUGHT THE
POLICE OUT TO THE PLANE.
NONE OF THE PASSENGERS BY
THE WAY ANY SUSPICIONS
RAISED ON ANY OF THEM THEY
WERE BROUGHT OFF ORDERLY
AND BROUGHT INSIDE THE
TERMINAL.
ANOTHER PASSENGER AGAIN,
CLAIMING TO BE A PASSENGER
TWEETED THAT THERE WAS VERY
HIGH SECURITY INSIDE THE
TERMINAL.
AND NOW AS WE KNOW THOSE
PASSENGERS ARE KIND OF
BEING GROUND TOGETHER AND
QUESTIONED ABOUT WHAT IT IS
THAT THEY HAVE BEEN DOING
OVER THE PAST 12 TO 24
HOURS OR SO.
AGAIN THEY LITTLE
INFORMATION COMING FROM
EITHER THE FBI, THE F.A.A.,
OR THE LOS ANGELES POLICE
DEPARTMENT ABOUT THE
ORIGINATION OF THIS THREAT,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER
WITH US, THANKS.
WE ARE INFORMED THAT THE
POLICE ARE GOING TO HOLD A
NEWS CONFERENCE.
WHEN WE GET THE DETAILS OF
THAT NEWS CONFERENCE, WE
WILL BRING IT TO YOU RIGHT
AWAY.
FIRST THOUGH, ASTEROIDS,
THEY HAVE THE POTENTIAL TO
END LIFE AS WE KNOW IT ON
THIS PLANET OR TO MAKE SOME
PEOPLE VERY RICH.
NEXT, A PLAN TO CAPTURE
THEM AND TO MINE THE
VALUABLE RESOURCES THEY
CONTAIN.
THE GOLD RUSH IS ON IN
OUTERSPACE.
es lets you connect up to 25 devices
on one easy to manage plan.
That means your smartphone her Blackberry
his laptop Mark's smartphone...
But I'm still on vacation...
...stilln the plan. Nice!
So is his tablet, that guy's hotspot,
thentern's tablet.
The intern gets a tablet?
Everyone's devices.
His, hers, oh sorry...
all easier to manage on The Share
Everything Plan
for Small Business.
Connecting more so you can do more.
That's Powerful. Verizon.
Get the Blackberry Q10 for $199.99.
♪ ♪    [ Male Announcer ]    MOVING
OBJECT DETECTION.  ♪ ♪    BLIND SPOT
WARNING.  ♪ ♪    LANE DEPARTURE WARNING.
SAFETY, DOWN TO AN ART.    THE NISSAN
ALTIMA    WITH SAFETY SHIELD    TECHNOLOGIES.
NISSAN.    INNOVATION THAT EXCITES.
♪ ♪
>> Shepard: OFFICIALS AT
TWO AMERICAN COMPANIES SAY
THEY HAVE A PLAN TO LASSO
ASTEROIDS INTO EARTH'SOR
BIT AND THEN MINE THEM FOR
PRECIOUS METALS AND
MINERALS.
GOLD, PLATINUM AND THE LIKE
OF THE AS IT TER RODE BELT
BETWEEN MARS AND JUPITER
WOULD BE ENOUGH TO GIVE
EVERYBODY ON EARTH
$100 BILLION.
SO DO THAT.
SO FAR ONLY ONE SPACE PROBE
HAS BEEN RETURNED TO EARTH
WHEN AN AS IT TER RODE
SAMPLE.
DAN SPRINGER IS IN OUR
SEATTLE NEWSROOM.
HEY DAN.
>> YEAH, SHEP.
ONE OF THE -- BUILT TINY
SPACE CRAFT 2 FEET HIGH
DESIGNED TO LAND ON
ASTEROID AND TAKE PICTURES
AND MEASURE.
S SO PICTURES BACK ON EARTH
CAN PICK OUT THE BEST FOR
MINING.
ROSS PEROT JR.
COMPANY CALLED SPACE X IS
GIVING RIDES IN SPACE EVEN
THESE ENTREPRENEURS ADMIT
GOVERNMENT WILL PLAY A ROW.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT THAT WE
HAVE A PARTNERSHIP WITH THE
GOVERNMENT IN THESE
ENDEAVORS.
THIS REALLY IS AN
INVESTMENT IN THE FUTURE OF
THE UNITED STATES AND ALL
OF HUMANITY.
>> THE GOAL IS TO BE ABLE
TO USE THE WATER AND METALS
IN THE ASTEROIDS TO FUEL
DEEPER SPACE EXPLORATION
AND ONE DAY COLONIZATION.
BUT THERE ARE REAL
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHO CAN
STAKE A CLAIM TO THE LAND.
>> ANYTHING A PRIVATE
PERSON DOES IN OUTERSPACE
THE COUNTRY THEY COME FROM
IS RESPONSIBLE FOR WHAT
THEY DO.
SO THERE IS SOME PEOPLE WHO
SAY THAT MEANS THAT YOU
CAN'T GO OUT THERE AND OWN
ANYTHING.
>> WELL LEGAL OR NOT
THESE SPACE MINERS SAY THEY
WILL BE MAKING MONEY IN
ABOUT A DECADE.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THERE IS A LOT
OF IT DAN.
THE MINERALS AND METALS IN
AN AVERAGE SIZE ASTEROID
WOULD BE WORTH AROUND
$30 BILLION HERE ON EARTH.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO THE
SCIENTISTS AT NASA.
AT LEAST 40 PEOPLE HURT
TONIGHT ONE SERIOUSLY AS A
DOUBLE-DECKER BUS SLAMS
INTO A BRIDGE AND THAT TOPS
OUR NEWS AROUND THE WORLD
IN 80 SECONDS.
JAMAR, POLICE SAY THAT BUS
WAS CARRYING STUDENTS FROM
DENMARK WHEN IT CRASHED
INTO A RAILWAY OVERPASS IN
MUNICH.
THE IMPACT RIPPED OFF PART
OF THE UPPER DECK, TEENAGE
GIRL REPORTEDLY SUFFERED
HEAD AND SPINE INJURIES.
FIRE OFFICIALS SAY THE
DRIVER HAD APPARENTLY
OVERLOOKED A SIGN
INDICATING THE BRIDGE WAS
ONLY A BIT MORE THAN THE
11 FEET HIGH.
THAILAND, AUTHORITIES
ARRESTED A PET SHOP OWNER
AFTER FINDING HUNDREDS OFS
EXOTIC ANIMALS IN WAREHOUSE
IN THE CAPITAL CITY OF
BANGKOK.
THOSE ANIMALS INCLUDED RARE
ALBINO LIONS, WHITE
SQUIRRELS, AND SEVERAL
SPECIES OF BIRDS.
SOME OF THOSE CRITTERS ARE
PROTECTED UNDER THE LAW.
THAILAND IS REPORTED LAY
HUB FOR EXOTIC ANIMAL
TRADING ON THE BLACK
MARKET.
CZECH REPUCK BIBLICAL.
PILOTS CHASES OFF IN THE
AIR BACK PARTICULAR
FREESTYLE CHALLENGE IN
PRAAGH.
PERFORMED CUSTOM ROUTINES
IN FRONT OF SOME 20,000
SPECTATORS.
THREE FRENCH MEN TOOK TOP
HONORS.
AUSTRALIA.
IT'S CALLED VIVID SYDNEY.
ANNUAL FESTIVAL LIGHTING UP
DOZENS OF BUILDINGS AND
AKON NIC LANDMARKS.
MORE THAN 70 COMPANIES 14
COUNTRIES TOOK PART WHICH
WRAPS UP TONIGHT.
THAT'S A WRAP ON THIS FOX
TRIP AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
>> Shepard: NEW UPDATES
COMING IN THIS MINUTE ON
OUR BREAKING NEWS THAT
SOUTHWEST AIRLINES FLIGHT
MAKING EMERGENCY LANDING IN
PHOENIX REPORTEDLY WITH A
FIGHTER JET ESCORT.
WHAT WE'RE LEARNING ABOUT
THE POSSIBLE THREAT WHICH
POLICE MENTIONED.
THAT'S COMING UP NEXT.
IT STARTS WITH LITTLE THINGS.  TINY
CHANGES IN THE BRAIN.  LITTLE THINGS
ANYONE CAN DO.
IT STEALS YOUR MEMORIES.  YOUR INDEPENDENCE.
ENSURES SUPPORT  A BREAKTHROUGH.
AND SOONER THAN YOU'D LIKE.
SOONER THAN YOU'D THINK.
YOU DIE FROM  ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
WE CURE ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
EVERY LITTLE CLICK, CALL  OR DONATION
ADDS UP  TO SOMETHING BIG.
[ Lorenzo ] I'M LORENZO.  I WORK FOR
47  DIFFERENT COMPANIES.  WELL, TECHNICALLY
I WORK FOR ONE.  THAT COMPANY, THE
UNITED STATES  POSTAL SERVICE®   WORKS
FOR THOUSANDS  OF HOME BUSINESSES.
BECAUSE AT USPS.COM®  YOU CAN PAY,
PRINT  AND HAVE YOUR PACKAGES PICKED
UP  FOR FREE.  I CAN EVEN DROP OFF
FREE BOXES.  I WEAR A LOT OF HATS.
WELL, TECHNICALLY I WEAR ONE.  THE
U.S. POSTAL SERVICE®  NO BUSINESS
TOO SMALL.  ♪ ♪  [ Agent Smith ]
I'VE FOUND SOFTWARE  THAT INTRIGUES
ME.  IT APPEARS  IT'S AN AGENT OF
GOOD.  ♪ ♪  [ Agent Smith ]  GE SOFTWARE
CONNECTS PATIENTS  TO NURSES  TO THE
RIGHT MACHINES  WHILE DRAMATICALLY
REDUCING WAITING TIME.  [ telephone
ringing ]  NOW A WAITING ROOM  IS
JUST A ROOM.  [ static warbles ]
>> Shepard: TIM TEBOW FOUND
A NEW HOME WITH HIS ONE
TIME RIVALS.
FORMER NEW YORK JETS
QUARTERBACK OR BACKUP
QUARTERBACK ABOUT TO SIGN
WITH THE NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS.
IN FACT, A NATIONAL
FOOTBALL LEAGUE SOURCES
TELL ESPN THEY EXPECT TIM
TEBOW TO SHOW UP AT THE
PAT'S TRAINING TOMORROW.
THE JETS DROPPED HIM IN
APRIL AFTER VERY UNEVENTFUL
SEASON.
THIS.
JOSH TO HEISMAN TROPHY
WINNER.
NOW HE IS THE PAT'S
OFFENSIVE COORDINATOR.
UPDATING SOME OF FOX TOP
STORY TONIGHT, THE MAN
CLAIMING TO A FORMER U.S.
DEFENSE CONTRACTOR AND WHO
SAYS HE LEAKED INFORMATION
ON CLASSIFIED U.S.
SURVEILLANCE PROGRAMS
REPORTEDLY SEEKING REFUGE
IN HONG KONG STAYING OUT OF
THE HANDS OF THE UNITED
STATES GOVERNMENT.
THERE IS WORD THAT HE MAY
SEEK ASYLUM IN ICELAND.
GRAND JURY SELECTION BEGAN
TODAY OR JURY SELECTION IN
THE CASE OF GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN'S MURDER TRIAL.
THE SELECTED JURORS WILL
EVENTUALLY HAVE TO DECIDE
WHETHER ZIMMERMAN ACTED IN
SELF-DEFENSE AS HE CLAIMS
WHEN HE SHOT AND KILLED THE
UNARMED 17-YEAR-OLD NAMED
TRAVON MARTIN IN CENTRAL
FLORIDA LAST WEEK.
AND NOW AN UPDATE ON
BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
ARIZONA SOUTHWEST FLIGHT
2675 MADE THAT EMERGENCY
LANDING IN PHOENIX.
POLICE SAYING THEY ARE
CHECKING OUT A POSSIBLE
THREAT.
TRACE GALLAGHER HAS MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT THIS
THREAT.
TRACE?
>> THE "L.A. TIMES" IS NOW
REPORTING, SHEP, THAT A
VEGAS THREAT WAS CALLED IN
TO LAX POLICE REFERENCING
THE TALIBAN.
THEY WOULD NOT EXPOUND ON
THAT.
CHANNEL 11 LOCAL FOX HERE
REPORTING THAT IT WAS
ACTUALLY CALLED INTO THE LA
POLICE DEPARTMENT.
AND THEN HE T. WAS REROUTED
TO THE AIRPLANE AND PILOT
OUT OF AN ABUNDANT OF
CAUTION MADE THAT LANDING
IN PHOENIX.
OFFICIALS ARE REPORTING
WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT
EARLIER THAT NORAD SAID THE
TWO F-16 FIGHTER JETS DID
SHADOW THIS PLANE AND THEN
ESCORT IT IN TO SKY HARBOR
AIRPORT AND THAT THE
PASSENGERS HAVE NOW BEEN
ROUNDED UP ARE INSIDE THE
TERMINAL AND FILLING OUT
FBI QUESTIONNAIRES.
THE GENESIS OF THIS THREAT
IS STILL UNKNOWN.
WE ARE LOOKING INTO THIS.
WE HAVE PHONED THE FBI AS
WE GET MORE INFORMATION.
WE WILL BRING IT TO YOU,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
AND ON THIS DAY IN 1752.
BENJAMIN FRANKLIN AND HIS
SON FLEW A KITE IN A
LIGHTNING STORM TO PROVE
FRANKLIN'S THEORY ABOUT
ELECTRICITY.
CONTRARY TO POPULAR BELIEF
HE DID NOT DISCOVER
ELECTRICITY.
INSTEAD, HE SHOWED THAT
LIGHTNING WAS A STREAM OF
ELECTRIC FIND AIR.
HIS IDEAS HAVE BEEN
PUBLISHED IN 1751 BUT HE
HAD LITTLE EVIDENCE TO
SUPPORT THEM UNTIL HE TIED
A KEY TO A KITE STRING AND
LET IT SOAR DURING A NASTY
WEATHER.
LIGHTNING STRUNG AND SPARK
JUMPED BETWEEN KEY AND
KNUCKLE.
THAT STORMY NIGHT HELPED
HIM DEVELOP MANY TERMS LIKE
BATTERY AND ELECTRIC SHOCK.
HE WOULD LATER INVENT THE
LIGHTNING ROD AMONG OTHERS
THINGS.
A BOLT GAVE HIS THEORY THE
BOOST 261 YEARS AGO TODAY.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS
FOR THIS MONDAY, JUNE THE
10TH 2013.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
WE'RE BACK TOMORROW FOR
"STUDIO B" AND FOR "THE FOX
REPORT" RIGHT BEFORE THE
FACTOR IS ON.
>> Bill: THE O'REILLY
TONIGHT:
>> WITH RESPECT TO THE
INTERNET AND EMAILS THIS
DOES NOT APPLY TO U.S.
CITIZENS AND IT DOES NOT
APPLY TO PEOPLE LIVING IN
THE UNITED STATES.
>> DON'T CONTROL -- TROLL
THROUGH A BILLION PHONE
THAT IS UNCONSTITUTIONAL
AND VIOLATES OUR PRIVACY.
>> Bill: WHERE DO YOU STAND
ON THE ISSUE?
IT IS CONFUSING.
WE WILL CLARIFY IT FOR YOU
TONIGHT.
>> YOU ARE NOT ALLOWED TO
GO INTO THAT DATA UNTIL
THEY HAVE A PARTICULAR
WARRANT SIGNED OFF ON BY A
JUDGE.
>> Bill: THE SURVEILLANCE
CONTROVERSY IS DIVIDING
BOTH POLITICAL PARTIES BOTH
LIKE JOHN MCCAIN AND NEWT
GINGRICH SUPPORT
SURVEILLANCE WHILE RUSH
LIMBAUGH AND GLENN BECK
OPPOSE IT WE WILL HAVE
EXTENSIVE REPORT ON THAT.