>> Bret: HAVE YOU TRIED TO
LEAVE?
THANKS FOR INVITING US INTO
YOUR HOME TONIGHT.
THAT'S IT FOR THIS "SPECIAL
REPORT," FAIR, BALANCED AND
UNSTILL UNAFRAID.
>> Shepard: THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT.
TONIGHT, PROTESTS.
A POLICE CRACKDOWN.
MAJOR CHAOS ON THE STREETS
OF A MAJOR U.S. ALLY.
WHAT DOES PRESIDENT OBAMA
THINK OF HIS FRIENDS NOW?
PLUS THE MAN BEHIND THE
BIGGEST INTELLIGENCE LEAK
IN A GENERATION.
STILL MISSING IN ACTION.
BUT HE MAY NOT BE THROUGH
TALKING.
THERE IS WORD ED SNOWDEN
HAS MORE SECRETS TO EXPOSE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A
LOT MORE SIGNIFICANT
REVELATIONS.
>> NOW, THE RUSSIANS SAY
THEY MAY GIVE HIM ASYLUM.
AND WE'RE LEARNING MORE
ABOUT THE BALLERINA AND
ACROBATIC PERFORMER
GIRLFRIEND HE LEFT BEHIND.
PLUS, THE FEDS SAY
OVERDRAFT PROTECTION
PROGRAMS ARE COSTING US
BILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN BANK
FEES.
SO YOU MIGHT BE BETTER OFF
WITH NO PROTECTION AT ALL.
AND WHAT'S MORE STRESSFUL?
DRIVING OR SKY DIVING?
RESEARCHERS SAY THEY HAVE
THE ANSWER.
IN OTHER NEWS,.
[CHEERS]
>> THIS HAPPENED.
BUT FIRST FROM FOX THIS
TUESDAY NIGHT, A WORLDWIDE
MANHUNT FOR THE NSA LEAKER
AND THE LAWYERS ARE ALREADY
HARD AT WORK.
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT IS
NOW FACING TWO LAWSUITS FOR
MONITORING THE PHONE
RECORDS OF MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS.
THE AMERICAN CIVIL
LIBERTIES UNION REPORTS IT
HAS NOW FILED A
CONSTITUTIONAL CHALLENGE
ARGUING THE PROGRAM
VIOLATES BOTH FREEDOM OF
SPEECH AND PRIVACY RIGHTS.
ACCORDING TO THE ACLU, IT
IS THE EQUIVALENT OF
REQUIRING EVERY AMERICAN TO
FILE A DAILY REPORT WITH
THE GOVERNMENT OF EVERY
LOCATION THEY VISITED
EVERY PERSON THEY TALKED TO
ON THE PHONE, THE TIME OF
EACH CALL, AND THE LENGTH
OF EVERY CONVERSATION.
IT'S FOX TOP STORY AND
TRACE GALLAGHER IS ON IT
LIVE THIS AFTERNOON FROM
OUR WEST COAST NEWS HUB.
WHAT ARE THE OTHER
ARGUMENTS OF THIS LAWSUIT
TRACE.
>> THE ACLU LAWSUIT SHEP,
GOES EVEN A STEP FURTHER
THAN WHAT YOU SAID
ACCUSING THE GOVERNMENT OF
VIOLATING OUR VERY RIGHT OF
ASSOCIATION.
THE PEOPLE YOU KNOW WE HANG
OUT WITH, SAYING AND I'M
QUOTING HERE IT GIVES
GOVERNMENT COMPREHENSIVE
ASSOCIATION.
WEALTH OF DETAIL ABOUT OUR
FAMILIAL, POLITICAL
PROFESSIONAL RELIGIOUS AND
INTIMATE ASSOCIATIONS.
THE SECOND LAWSUIT WAS
FILED BY A FORMER DOJ
PROSECUTOR WHO HAS SUED THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
BEFORE.
BUT ALSO BY THE PARENTS OF
MICHAEL STRANGE.
HE WAS AMONG 25 NAVY SEALS
AND FIVE OTHER AMERICANS
KILLED IN A HELICOPTER
CRASH IN AFGHANISTAN BACK
IN 2011.
THE PARENTS ALLEGE THE
GOVERNMENT MAY HAVE
ACCESSED THEIR PHONE
RECORDS BECAUSE THEY HAVE
BLAMED THE GOVERNMENT FOR
THE CRASH THAT KILLED THEIR
SON.
THE ADMINISTRATION HAS YET
TO COMMENT, SHEP, ON EITHER
ONE OF THESE LAWSUITS.
>> Shepard: IN ADDITION, WE
ARE TO BELIEVE THAT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT TRACKS
EVERY SINGLE THING WE DO,
YET, THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
CANNOT LOCATE A 29-YEAR-OLD
HIGH SCHOOL DROPOUT.
>> AND THERE IS NO EVIDENCE
THAT EDWARD SNOWDEN HAS
LEFT HONG KONG.
7 MILLION PEOPLE IN THAT
CITY, 65,000 HOTEL ROOMS.
AND NOW THERE IS WORD THAT
RUSSIA MIGHT BE WILLING TO
GIVE HIM ASYLUM.
PRESIDENT PUTIN SAYS IF THE
REQUEST IS MADE IT WILL BE
CONSIDERED.
TO APPLY FOR ASYLUM, HE
WOULD SIMPLY HAVE TO GO TO
THE RUSSIAN CONSULATE IN
HONG KONG SNOWDEN WOULD
HAVE TO APPLY.
HE ONCE TOLD THE GUARDIAN
NEWSPAPER THAT HE DOES NOT
EXPECT TO BE FREE FOREVER
THOUGH, LISTEN.
>> YOU CAN'T COME FORWARD
AGAINST THE WORLD'S MOST
POWERFUL INTELLIGENCE
AGENCY AND BE COMPLETELY
FREE FROM RISK BECAUSE THEY
ARE SUCH POWERFUL
ADVERSARIES THAT NO ONE CAN
MEANINGFULLY OPPOSE THEM.
IF THEY WANT TO GET YOU
THEY WILL GET NEW TIME.
>> SNOWDEN LEFT THE HAWAII
HOME HE SHARED WITH HIS
GIRLFRIEND LINDSEY MILLS
THE SELF-PROCLAIMED POLE
DANCER.
HE LEFT THREE WEEKS AGO.
AS PART OF THIS
INVESTIGATION THAT HOME
WILL BE SEARCHED AND HIS
GIRLFRIEND WILL BE
QUESTIONED.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE, THE NSA
LEAKER HAS A LOT MORE TO
LEAK.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM ONE OF
THE COLUMNISTS WHO
PRESENTED HIS STORY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A
LOT MORE SIGNIFICANT
REVELATIONS THAT HAVE NOT
YET BEEN HEARD OVER THE
NEXT SEVERAL WEEKS, A
MONTH, HOW FAST WE GET THE
NEXT ONE OUT IS SOMETHING
WE ARE DECIDING NOW.
BUT THERE ARE DOZENS OF
STORIES GENERATED BY THE
DOCUMENTS THAT HE PROVIDED.
AND WE INTEND TO PURSUE
EVERY LAST ONE OF THEM.
>> Shepard: HE ALSO SAYS
SNOWDEN IS READY TO FACE
THE CONSEQUENCES AND
WHATEVER IS COMING HIS WAY.
GOOGLE EXECUTIVES ARE
ASKING THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT TO LET THEM
RELEASE ALL GOVERNMENT
SURVEILLANCE REQUESTS.
THEY SAY THAT WILL PROVE
THEY ARE NOT GIVING THE
FEDS UNFETTERED ACCESS TO
THEIR SERVERS GOOMG TO
REPORTERS PUT THE LETTER IN
WRITING TO THE ERIC HOLDER
AND FBI DIRECTOR ROBERT
MUELLER.
SO FAR NO RESPONSE.
THE FEDS ARE GIVING MEMBERS
OF CONGRESS MORE
INFORMATION ABOUT THE SPY
PROGRAMS.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE
CONTINUES TEAM FOX COVERAGE
THERE WERE TWO BRIEFINGS
THERE TODAY RIGHT, CAT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SHEP.
RARE BRIEFING OF THE FULL
HOUSE BY SENIOR AT THE    DEPUTIES
AT
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT FBI
AND NATIONAL SECURITY
AGENCY ABOUT THE DATA
COLLECTION PROGRAM.
ALSO ON CAPITOL HILL THE
HEAD OF THE NSA AND U.S.
CYBER COMMAND JEN KEITH
ALEXANDER WHOSE PROGRAMS
ARE AT THE CENTER OF THE
LEAKS.
LAWMAKERS PRESSING
WITNESSES ON HOW A
29-YEAR-OLD CONTRACTOR GOT
A HIGH LEVEL SECURITY
CLEARANCE.
HOW HE WALKED OUT WITH
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS AND
HOW MUCH WEB CONTENT THE
NSA IS SCOOPING UP.
AFTER ONE BRIEFING A SENSE
THERE IS MORE TO THE
PROGRAMS AND THE WAY THEY
ARE POLICED.
>> SOME OF THE MEDIA
ACCOUNTS I HAVE READ BASED
ON THE LEAKS DO NOT PAINT A
COMPLETE AND ACCURATE
PORTRAYAL HOW THE PROGRAMS
WORK AND HOW THE SAFEGUARDS
THAT EXIST FOR THE PROGRAM
WORK.
>> TONIGHT, THE DEMOCRATIC
SENATOR OF THE SENATE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
DIANNE FEINSTEIN SAYING THE
DECLASSIFYING INFORMATION
ON THE NSA PROGRAMS WOULD
SHOW SO.
BENEFITS AS WELL SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT'S THE
LATEST ON POTENTIAL
CRIMINAL CHARGES AGAINST
THE LEAKER?
>> WELL, A SOURCE FAMILIAR
WITH THE SCOPE OF THE
INVESTIGATION TELLS FOX
NEWS CHARGES MUST BE
WEIGHED CAREFULLY BECAUSE
WHATEVER CHARGES SNOWDEN IS
EXTRA DILTED ON MUST BE THE
SAME CHARGES HE IS
PROSECUTED ON IN THE U.S.
SO THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
CANNOT PULL THE EQUIVALENT
OF A BAIT AND SWITCH IN
THIS CASE.
THE WHITE HOUSE TODAY
DODGING QUESTIONS
CHARACTERIZING THE NSA
LEAKER.
>> ARE YOU WILLING TO SAY
WHETHER YOU SEE SNOWDEN AS
A WHISTLEBLOWER?
>> I AM NOT WILLING TO
COMMENT ON THE STATUS OF
THE INDIVIDUAL UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
>> CONSULTING GIANT BOOZ
ALLEN HAMILTON SAYS IT
FORMALLY TERMINATED SNOWDEN
FOR VIOLATION OF THE FIRM'S
CODE OF ETHICS AND THE
FIRM'S POLICY.
THE SPEAKER OF THE HOUSE
WENT EVEN FURTHER.
>> HE IS A TRAITOR.
THE PRESIDENT OUTLINED LAST
WEEK THAT THESE WERE
IMPORTANT NATIONAL SECURITY
PROGRAMS TO HELP KEEP
AMERICANS SAFE AND GIVE US
TOOLS TO FIGHT THE
TERRORIST THREAT THAT WE
FACE.
THE DISCLOSURE OF THIS
INFORMATION PUTS AMERICANS
AT RISK.
IT SHOWS OUR ADVERSARIES
WHAT OUR CAPABILITIES ARE.
>> FOX NEWS HAS ALSO TOLD
THE INVESTIGATION IS
CONSIDERING WHETHER SNOWDEN
HAD HELP BUT AT THIS EARLY
STAGE THE EVIDENCE DOES NOT
SUGGEST THAT, SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE THE
NEW LEAKS HAVE BOOSTED THE
ORIGINAL INTEREST IN THE
ORIGINAL BIG BROTHER NOVEL
GEORGE ORWELL 18984.
AMAZON.COM REPORT THAT
SALES OF THE PAPERBACK
VERSION OF THAT BOOK HAVE
TRIPLED OVER THE LAST 24
HOURS.
1984 WAS PUBLISHED BASS IN
194, IT TELLS OF A NEAR
FUTURE WORLD IN WHICH
NEARLY ALL OF OUR
ACTIVITIES ARE UNDER
SURVEILLANCE GOVERNMENT
SURVEILLANCE AND MIND
CONTROL.
TENSIONS HAVE BEEN BOILING
OVER ALL DAY ON THE STREETS
OF A KEY U.S. ALLY IN THE
MIDDLE EAST.
TWO WEEKS OF PROTESTS IN
TURKEY HAVE TURNED INTO
VIOLENT CONFRONTATIONS AND
NOW SPARKS ARE FLYING.
[EXPLOSIONS]
>> Shepard: PROTESTERS
SETTING OFF FIREWORKS AND
THROWS STONES AT RIOT
POLICE IN THE HEART OF
ISTANBUL AS RIOT POLICE
FIRED TEAR GAS IN RETURN.
[EXPLOSIONS]
>> Shepard: POLICE GOING
BACK AND FORTH WITH THE
CROWD ALL DAY.
REPEATEDLY CHASING PEOPLE
AWAY FROM THE SQUARE USING
WATER BULLETS AND WATER
CANONS ONLY TO SEE THE
DEMONSTRATIONS FLARE UP YET
AGAIN.
THIS IS ONE OF 78 CITIES
WHICH PROTESTS POP UP
ACROSS TURKEY.
UNHAPPY WITH A VARIETY OF
ISSUES.
INCLUDING WHAT THEY SEES A
PRIME MINISTER ATTEMPT TO
IMPOSE A RELIGIOUS
LIFESTYLE ON WHAT'S
CURRENTLY A SECULAR
SOCIETY.
TURKEY, OF COURSE, SHARES
BORDERS WITH SYRIA, IRAQ
AND IRAN AMONG OTHERS.
BUT THE VIOLENCE WE SAW
TODAY IN ISTANBUL WAS ON
THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
COUNTRY.
IT'S HAPPENING IN THE
CENTRAL PART OF THE CITY IN
AN AREA KNOWN AS SQUARE.
AND AS THE VIDEO CAMERAS
GAVE US A SENSE OF THE
CHAOS, THE STILL IMMANUELS
SHOW JUST HOW MUCH THESE
PROTESTERS ARE WILLING TO
RISK OF THE MAN YOU SEE
HERE PUT HIS HEAD UNDER THE
WHEEL OF A POLICE WATER
CANON IN AN ATTEMPT IT TO
STOP IT ANOTHER PHOTO SHOWS
A DEMONSTRATOR WHOSE
CLOTHES CAUGHT FIRE HE'S
RAN FROM POLICE.
BUT FOR MANY OBSERVERS
THIS REMAINS THE PICTURE
THAT SUMS UP THE WHOLE
ORDEAL.
THE WOMAN IN THE RED DRESS
WHOM RIOT POLICE BLASTED
WITH TEAR GAS LAST WEEK.
THESE ARE THE COUNTRY'S
BIGGEST PROTESTS IN MANY
YEARS AS WE TAKE A LIVE
LOOK NOW AT THE SCENE IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT.
WE SEE PROTESTERS HAVE
STARTED A KNEW -- NEW FIRE
AND HOLDING THEIR GROUND.
THIS CONFLICT IS FAR FROM
OVER.
>> THE BATTLE OF THE SQUARE
RAGED INTO THE THE NIGHT
WITH LARGE FIRES BURNING AS
PROTESTERS CONTINUED
FIGHTING OVER THE LITTERED
GROUND.
[EXPLOSIONS]
THIS MORNING VOLUNTARILIES
OF TEAR GAS AND WATER
CANONS WERE ANSWERED BY
ROCKS AND MOLOTOV
COCKTAILS.
RUBBER BULLETS INJURED
COUNTLESS DEMONSTRATORS.
THEIR COMPATRIOTS DESTROYED
AT LEAST ONE WATER TANKER
AND LIT A POLICE OFFICER ON
FIRE.
PROTESTERS SPENT THE
WEEKEND BREAKING APART
ISTANBUL'S MANY CITY
SQUARE.
BUILDING BARRICADES AROUND
THEIR POSITIONS THEIR HARD
WORK PROVED LARGELY IN VAIN
AFTER THE PRIME MINISTER
DECLARED THE TIME HAD COME.
>> THIS IS OVER, HE SAID.
WE WON'T PUT UP WITH THISNY
ANY LONGER.
POLICE SAY THE HEAVY
TACTICS ARE THE REASON FOR
DEMONSTRATIONS.
HE ORDERED A PARK NEAR
CLEARED OF PROTESTERS
DEMONSTRATING AGAINST
TURNING THE SQUARE INTO A
SHOPPING MALL.
IMAGES OF WATER CANONS
KNOCKING DOWN YOUNG WOMEN
BROUGHT MORE TO THE STREET.
ANGRY THAT THE THREE TIME
ELECTED PRIME MINISTER IS
MOVING THEIR SECULAR
COUNTRY TOWARDS AN ISLAMIC
STATE.
>> WE DON'T TRUST HIM THIS
PROTESTER SAID DURING A
LULL IN THE FIGHTING.
WE HAVE TAKEN THE SQUARE
WITH STRUGGLE AND FROM NOW
ON NO MATTER HOW MUCH
POLICE FORCES WILL COME, WE
WILL CONTINUE TO FIGHT.
>> Shepard: LELAND VITTERT
REPORTING.
THE VIOLENCE IN RECENT DAYS
HAS KILLED AT LEAST FOUR
PEOPLE INCLUDING A POLICE
OFFICER.
LELAND VITTERT IS LIVE IN
OUR NEWSROOM NOW.
WHAT CAN WE EXPECT
TOMORROW LELAND?
>> SHEP SUNRISE IN JUST A
COUPLE OF HOURS AND
ISTANBUL AND THAT'S WHEN WE
WILL REALLY KNOW WHETHER
POLICE HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
CLEAR OUT THE SQUARE,
WHETHER THE PROTESTERS WHO
CONTACT IN ISTANBUL TELLS
ME ARE NOW TRYING TO MOVE
BACK INTO THE SQUARE AND
REOCCUPY IT COME MORNING
HAVE SUCCEEDED.
ONLY TIME WILL TELL.
THE PRIME MINISTER FOR HIS
PART HAD BEEN BELLIGERENT
AT TIMES CERTAINLY DEFIANT
TOWARDS THESE PROTESTERS.
BUT HE IS MEETING WITH SOME
OF THEM TOMORROW.
THAT'S WHEN WE WILL GET A
SENSE IN TERMS OF WHETHER
HE IS GOING TO MOVE THIS
TOWARDS PEACE OR WHETHER
THE VIOLENCE WE SAW
OVERNIGHT IS JUST THE
BEGINNING.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: LELAND WILL BE
REPORTING FROM THAT SQUARE
FOR US TOMORROW.
IT'S NOT A PARTICULARLY
SAFE PLACE OR WELCOMING
PLACE FOR REPORTERS.
HIS MIKE WASN'T CLOSED, OUR
APOLOGIES.
ACCORDING TO THE COMMITTEE
TO PROTECT JOURNALISTS THE
PRIME MINISTER HAS CRACKED
DOWN ON FREEDOM OF THE
PRESS IMPRISONING MORE THAN
75 JOURNALISTS SINCE LAST
SUMMER.
THE ORGANIZATION REPORTS
THERE ARE MORE JOURNALISTS
IN PRISON IN TURKEY THAN IN
IRAN OR CHINA.
A UNITED STATES AMBASSADOR
ACCUSED OF LOOK FOR SEXUAL
FAVORS FROM PROSTITUTES AND
CHILDREN.
TONIGHT, THE AMBASSADOR
RESPONDS.
PLUS A PLANE STUCK ON THE
TARMAC FOR HOURS IN
100-HEAT.
NO WATER NO
AIRCONDITIONING WOULD A
LITTLE KARAOKE MAKE YOU
FEEL BETTER?
FROM THE JOURNALISTS OF FOX
NEWS, THIS IS A TUESDAY FOX
REPORT.
irring ]  [ dog barks ]  I WANT TO
TREAT MO DOGS.  ♪ ♪  OUR BUSINESS
NEEDS MORE CASES.    [ Male Announcer
] WHERE DO YOU    WANT TO TAKE YOUR
BUSINESS?  I NEED HELP SELLING ART.
[ Male Announcer ]    FROM BROADBAND
TO WEB HOSTING    TO MOBILE APPS,
SMALL BUSINESS    SOLUTIONS FROM AT&T
HAVE THE SECURITY YOU NEED    TO GET
YOU THERE.    CALL US.    WE CAN SHOW
YOU    HOW AT&T SOLUTIONS    CAN HELP
YOU DO WHAT YOU DO...    EVEN BETTER.
♪ ♪
[ Lorenzo ] I'M LORENZO.  I WORK FOR
47  DIFFERENT COMPANIES.  WELL, TECHNICALLY
I WORK FOR ONE.  THAT COMPANY, THE
UNITED STATES  POSTAL SERVICE®   WORKS
FOR THOUSANDS  OF HOME BUSINESSES.
BECAUSE AT USPS.COM®  YOU CAN PAY,
PRINT  AND HAVE YOUR PACKAGES PICKED
UP  FOR FREE.  I CAN EVEN DROP OFF
FREE BOXES.  I WEAR A LOT OF HATS.
WELL, TECHNICALLY I WEAR ONE.  THE
U.S. POSTAL SERVICE®  NO BUSINESS
TOO SMALL.
POWERFUL ENOUGH TO TAKE
DOWN A COMMERCIAL AIRPLANE.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO SECRET
DOCUMENTS.
THEY INCLUDE A MANUAL WITH
DIAGRAMS AND PHOTOGRAPHS
SHOWING HOW TO USE THE SA 7
SHOULDER FIRED MISSILE.
THE PENTAGON CALLS THIS
WEAPON THE GRAIL.
AND ANALYSTS TELL THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS THAT
MANUAL STRONGLY SUGGESTS
MILITANTS ALREADY HAVE THE
MISSILE IN THEIR
POSSESSION.
EXPERTS ALSO CALL IT A MAN
PORTABLE AIR DEFENSE SYSTEM
OR A MAN PAD.
THE ANALYSTS SAY THOSE
FIGHTERS IN MALY LIKELY
SWIPED THE MISSILE FROM
LIBYA AMID THE FALL OF THE
DICTATOR THERE MUAMMAR
QADDAFI TWO YEARS AGO.
THE U.S. AMBASSADOR TO
BELGIUM SAYS IS HE
DEVASTATED BY STATE
DEPARTMENT MEMO THAT
SUGGESTS HE SOLICITED SEX
FROM PROSECUTES AND
CHILDREN HE IS AMBASSADOR
HOWARD GUTMAN WHO RELEASED
A STATEMENT I'M ANGERED AND
SADDENED BY THE BASELESS
ALLEGATIONS.
AT NO POINT HAVE I EVER
ENGAGED IN ANY IMPROPER
ACTIVITY.
THE ALLEGATIONS ABOUT
GUTMAN'S PRIVATE LIFE CAME
TO LIFE AS PART OF AN
INTERNAL INVESTIGATION
THERE THE REPORT WE FIRST
TELLING YOU ABOUT YESTERDAY
SUGGESTED THE AGENCY TRIED
TO COVER UP THE BAD
BEHAVIOR OF SEVERAL
GOVERNMENT WORKERS.
JAMES ROSEN FOR US AT THE
STATE DEPARTMENT TONIGHT.
JAMES?
>> SHEP, GOOD EVENING, THE
STATE DEPARTMENT IS PUSHING
BACK IN CONCERTED WAY
AGAINST ALLEGATIONS TODAY
FAR MORE VIGOROUSLY THAN
YESTERDAY.
UNDER SECRETARY OF STATE
FOR MANAGEMENT PATRICK
KENNEDY IS THE SENIOR
OFFICIAL ALLEGED IN A
OCTOBER OIG MEMO TO HAVE
SHUT DOWN THE PROBE INTO
ALLEGATIONS OF SEX CRIMES
BY U.S. AMBASSADOR TO
BELGIUM HOWARD GUTMAN.
TODAY, KENNEDY SPOKE
THOUGHT A STATEMENT THAT
SAID IN PART:  IN MY
CURRENT POSITION IT IS MY
RESPONSIBILITY TO MAKE SURE
THE DEPARTMENT AND ALL OF
OUR EMPLOYEES NO MATTER
THEIR RANK ARE HELD TO THE
HIGHEST STANDARD AND I HAVE
NEVER ONCE INTERFERED NOR
WOULD I CONDONE INTERFERING
IN ANY INVESTIGATION
UNQUOTE.
SEEN HERE WITH SECRETARY OF
STATE JOHN KERRY ON HIS
VISIT TO BRUSSELS IN APRIL
AMBASSADOR GUTMAN IS A
HARVARD-TRAINED LAWYER AND
PROLIFIC DEMOCRATIC
FUNDRAISER.
ONLY AFTER HE RELEASED A
PUBLIC STATEMENT THIS
MORNING DID FOX NEWS
IDENTIFY HIM BY NAME IN OUR
COVERAGE.
>> ALL THE OCTOBER OIG MEMO
LISTED 8 CASES WHERE STATE
DEPARTMENT HIGHER UPS
SUPPOSEDLY INTERFERED WITH
INVESTIGATIONS INTO
MISCONDUCT OR CRIMES BY
DEPARTMENT EMPLOYEES.
A SPOKESPERSON TODAY SAID
THAT MEMO CONTAINED
UNSUBSTANTIATED ALLEGATIONS
AND WAS ITSELF WRITTEN
WITHOUT ACCESS TO THE
PERTINENT CASE FILES.
>> PRIOR TO THE DRAFTING OF
THIS MEMO BUREAU SECURITY
HAD ALREADY LOOKING INTO
ALL OF THESE CASES WILL BE
BROUGHT TO THEIR LOGICAL
CONCLUSIONS.
>> BUT WHEN I ASKED HER IF
KERRY HAS FULL FAITH AND
CONFIDENCE IN AMBASSADOR
GUTMAN.
SACKY DIDN'T SAY YES
INSTEAD SHE SPOKE OF THE
SECRETARY'S PRIDE OF
LEADING THIS DEPARTMENT OF
70000 MEN AND WOMEN, SHEP?
>> Shepard: JAMES, YOU
MENTIONED THE OFFICE OF THE
INSPECTOR GENERAL, THE
STATE DEPARTMENT'S INTERNAL
WATCHDOG.
WE'RE TOLD THAT IN THIS
CASE THE OIG RELIED ON
OUTSIDE INVESTIGATORS,
FORMER LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIALS WHO REVIEWED THE
ALLEGED COVERUPS.
WELL, A NEW VICTORY FOR
SUPPORTERS OF THE MORNING
AFTER PILL PLAN B.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT
WILL NO LONGER FIGHT A
JUDGE'S RULING THAT MAKES
THE PILL AVAILABLE TO GIRLS
OF ALL AGES NO NEED FOR A
PRESCRIPTION OR PERMISSION
FROM MOM AND DAD.
PLUS, WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR
HOW MUCH THE BIG BANKS
POCKETED LAST YEAR JUST
FROM OVERDRAFT FEES.
NOT MILLIONS OF DOLLARS,
NOT BILLIONS OF DOLLARS,
TENS OF BILLIONS OF
DOLLARS.
YOU GAVE IT TO THEM.
THANKS SO MUCH.
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN ABLE TO BRIGHTEN
YOUR DAY. IT'S JUST HER WAY.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A QUESTION
OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME THE MOMENT'S
RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS THE ONLY DAILY
ED TABLET APPROVED
TO TREAT ED AND SYMPTOMS OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY ENOUGH
FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU TAKE NITRATES
FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE DROP IN
BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS WITH
CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH, DELAYED BACKACHE
OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY, SEEK IMMEDIATE
MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING MORE THAN
FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE OR
LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC REACTIONS
SUCH AS RASH
HIVES, SWELLING OF THE LIPS, TONGUE
OR THROAT
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET MEDICAL
HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS FOR DAILY
USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
HAVE AOOD NIGHT. HERE YOU GO. YOU,
TOO.  'M GOING TO DREAM  ABOUT THAT
STEAK.  I'M GOING TO DREAM  ABOUT
THAT TIRAMISU.
WHAT A NIGHT, HUH?  BUT, UM, CAN THE
TEST DRIVE  BE OVER NOW?  HEAD BACK
TO THE DEALERSHIP?  OH, YEAH.    [
MalAnnouncer ]   IT'S PRACTICALLY
YOURS.  [ Wife ] SORRY.    [ Male
Announcer ] BUT WE STILL    NEED YOUR
SIGNATURE.    VOLKSWAGEN SIGN THEN
DRIVE    IS BACK.    AND IT'S NEVER
BEEN EASIER    TO GET A PASSAT.
THAT'S THE POWER    OF GERMAN ENGINEERING.
GET $0 DOWN,    $0 DUE AT SIGNING,
$0 DEPOSIT    AND $0 FIRST MONTH'S
PAYMENT    ON ANY NEW VOLKSWAGEN.
VISIT VWDEALER.COM TODAY.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE HAS NOW
DROPPED ITS FIGHT OVER THE
PLAN B MORNING AFTER PILL.
THIS NEWS BROKE JUST AFTER
THIS REPORT LAST NIGHT.
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT SAYS
IT WILL OBEY A JUDGE'S
APRIL RULING THAT GIRLS OF
ANY AGE CAN BUY THE
EMERGENCY CONTRACEPTION
WITHOUT A PRESCRIPTION.
THE MAKERS OF PLAN B SAY IT
COULD K. LOWER THE RISK OF
PREGNANCY BY NEAR 90% IF A
WOMAN TAKES IT WITHIN 72
HOURS OF UNPROTECTED SEX.
IT IS NOT THE SAME OF THE
SO-CALLED ABORTION PILL.
EXPERTS SAY THE MORNING
AFTER PILL HAS NO EFFECT ON
WOMEN WHO ARE ALREADY
PREGNANT.
REPRO-TUCKIVE RIGHTS GROUP
CALL THE MOVE MAJOR
VICTORY.
PRO-ACTIVISTS SAYS IT PUTS
POLITICS AHEAD OF SAFETY
AND RIGHTS.
MORE THAN A QUARTER OF ALL
OF BANK CUSTOMERS STILL
FACE HEFTY OVERDRAFT FEES.
THE CONSUMER FINANCIAL
PROTECTION BUREAU REPORTS
ABOUT 27% OF ALL ACCOUNTS
REGISTERED OVERDRAFT
ACTIVITY IN 2011.
THAT'S THE YEAR AFTER THE
FEDS BAND THE BANKS FROM
AUTOMATICALLY ENROLLING
CUSTOMERS IN OVERDRAFT
PROTECTION.
INSTEAD FOLKS HAVE TO OPT
IN TO THE SERVICE.
WHICH CHARGES FEES TO COVER
TRANSACTIONS WHEN ACCOUNTS
ARE DRAINED.
THE REPORT SHOWS THAT
CUSTOMERS WHO PAID THOSE
FEES, PAID ON AVERAGE $225
OVER THE COURSE OF THE
YEAR.
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE.
RICK LEVENTHAL ON THIS.
SOUNDS LIKE THESE FEES HAVE
REALLY ADDED UP.
>> RIGHT SHEP BECAUSE YOU
MIGHT PAY $35 FOR A BOUNCED
CHECK OR MAYBE $10 OR LESS.
BUT THE TOTAL TAKE FOR
FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS IS A
STAGGERING $32 BILLION A
YEAR ACCORDING TO THAT
REPORT FROM THE CONSUMER
FINANCIAL PROTECTION
BUREAU.
CRITICIZING AMERICA'S
BANKING INDUSTRY SAYING THE
RULES ARE CONFUSING.
CUSTOMERS CAN BE CHARGED
MULTIPLE TIMES A DAY AND
PEOPLE WHO OPT FOR
OVERDRAFT PROTECTION MAY
ACTUALLY END UP PAYING
MORE.
SOME UP TO $900 A YEAR
PAYING BILLS WITH BASICALLY
MONEY THEY DON'T HAVE.
>>
>> Shepard: RICK, NONE OF
THIS SILL LEGAL RIGHT?
>> WELL, IT IS ABSOLUTELY
LEGAL.
BUT THE REPORT NOTES THAT
THERE IS A LACK OF INDUSTRY
STANDARDS BECAUSE SOME
BANKS ARE CHARGING UP TO 12
TIMES A DAY FOR OVERDRAFTS
OR NON-SUFFICIENT FUNDS THE
AMOUNTS THAT CUSTOMERS CAN
OVERDRAW VARIES WIDELY.
BIG BANKS CHARGE MORE THAN
SMALLER ONES.
SMALLER BANKS RELY ON FEES
AS A SOURCE OF REVENUE
GROWTH.
NOW THE REPORT DOESN'T CALL
FOR NEW OVERDRAFT FEE RULES
BUT CHANGES COULD BE
COMING, SHEP.
>> Shepard: RICK LEVENTHAL
IN NEW YORK.
THE BANKS HAVE BEEN KNOWN
TO SCALE BACK ON FEES IN
FACE OF PUBLIC ANGER.
YOU MAY REMEMBER A COUPLE
YEARS AGO WHEN BANK OF
AMERICA THE RED BANK
ANNOUNCED PLANS TO CHARGE A
MONTHLY FEE FOR DEBIT
CARDS.
THE BANK QUICKLY DROPPED
THOSE PLANS AFTER HARSH
REACTION FROM LAWMAKERS.
BREAKING NEWS NOW ON THE
TENSE SITUATION UNFOLDING
AT THIS MOMENT IN TURKEY
THE WHITE HOUSE HAS JUST
REPORTED THAT IT IS
FOLLOWING THE EVENTS THERE,
QUOTE:  WITH CONCERN.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO THE
REPORTING OF THE REUTERS
NEWS AGENCY.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS CALLING
ON TURKEY'S LEADERS TO
UPHOLD THE CITIZEN'S RIGHTS
OF EXPRESSION AND ASSEMBLY.
THIS AS COPS FIRED NEW
ROUNDS OF TEAR GAS ON
PROTESTERS IN WHAT IS ONE
OF THE MOST IMPORTANT
ALLIES IN THE ENTIRE
REGION.
THE BREAKING DEVELOPMENTS
COMING UP.
PLUS, THE MAN BEHIND ONE OF
THE LARGEST LEAKS IN OUR
NATION'S HISTORY.
THE PENTAGON PAPERS.
WEIGHING IN ON THIS NEW NSA
SPYING SCANDAL.
AND WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR
WHAT HE HAS TO SAY ABOUT
THIS LATEST LEAK.
AND WE ALL KNOW DRIVING A
CAR CAN BE STRESSFUL.
BUT JUST AS STRESSFUL ASAR
THIS?
THAT'S COMING UP AS WE
APPROACH THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR AND THE TOP
CAUSED ALL THIS?
ART TE I
OF THE NEWS.
FOR AN AGENT, CALL THE NUMBER
THAT APPEARS ON YOUR SCREEN.
[ Male Announcer ]        EVERY INCH.
EVERY MINUTE.         EVERY SECOND
--         WE CHIP AWAY.
AT REDEFINING CAPABILITY.
F WHATEVER DAYS MAY COME.
LIKE BEACH DAYS...
RAINY DAYS...
EVEN VACATION DAYS.
MADE WITH PRIDE.
CRAFTED WITH PASSION.
THIS IS THE NEW 2014   JEEP GRAND
CHEROKEE.
IT IS THE BEST        OF WHAT WE'RE
MADE OF.
WELL-QUALIFIED LESSEES
CAN LEASE THE 2014       GRAND CHEROKEE
REDO 4X4
FOR $359 A MONTH.
THE Kyocera Torque  LETS YOU HEAR
AND BE HEARD  EVEN IN STUPID LOUD
PLACES.  TO PROVE IT, WE SET UP  OUR
CALL CENTER RIGHT HERE...  [ chirp
]  ALL GOOD?  [ chirp ]  GETTY UP.
SERIOUSLY,  THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING!
[ cellphone rings ]  HELLO?  IT'S
A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.    [ Male
Announcer ] GET IT DONE  [ chirp ]
WITH THE ULTRAUGGED    ocera Torque
ONLY FROM Sprint   Direct Conct.
BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE    FOR YOUR
BUSINESS.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR HELP RELIEVING
HEARTBURN, CAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES 24-HOUR
HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE AVAILABLE FOR JUST $18
A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE AND
LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA, CONTACT
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH CONDITIONS MAY
EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT HAND FOR JUST $18 A MONTH.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT NEXIUM.
[ Male Announcer ]    ERICA HAD A
ROUGH DAY.    SHE GOT A PARKING TICKET...
♪ ♪    AND SHE FORGOT TO PAY    HER
CREDIT CARD BILL ON TIME.    GOOD
THING SHE'S GOT    THE CITI SIMPLICITY
CARD.    IT DOESN'T CHARGE LATE FEES
OR A PENALTY RATE. EVER.    AS IN
NEVER EVER.    NOW ABOUT THAT PARKING
TICKET.  [ grunting ]    [ Male Announcer
] TO APPLY    FOR THE CITI SIMPLICITY
CARD    GO TO CITI.COM/SIMPLICITY.
IT'S THE ONLY CARD THAT NEVER    HAS
LATE FEES, A PENALTY RATE,    OR AN
ANNUAL FEE, EVER.    SO APPLY TODAY.
REQUEST THREE AND A HALF
HOURS AGO AND GONE THROUGH
400 ACRES.
AS YOU CAN SEE IS
DESTROYING HOMES AS WELL.
THAT'S BECAUSE OF THE
ERRATIC WINDS THAT YOU HAVE
MENTIONED AND THE LOW
HUMIDITY.
WE HAVE ALSO HAD
RECORD-SETTING HEAT HERE AS
WELL.
THIS IS JUST ONE OF FOUR
FIRES BURNING THROUGHOUT
THE STATE OF COLORADO, SO
THERE IS HELP ON THE WAY
FROM NEVADA, NEW MEXICO AND
IDAHO.
NOW, THE U.S. FOREST
SERVICE SAYS WE HAD THIS
REALLY WET SPRING HERE IN
THE STATE WHICH MEANS THERE
WERE GRASS AND WEEDS THAT
GREW UP AND THEN THE HOT
AIR DRIED IT ALL OUT AND WE
WERE LEFT WITH FUEL JUST
ABOUT EVERYWHERE.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: ALICIA ACUNA
LIVE IN DENVER.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR.
TIME FOR THE TOP OF THE
NEWS.
AND A FOX NEWS URGENT.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT'S
FOLLOWING, QUOTE WITH
CONCERN THE VIOLENT CLASHES
IN TURKEY POLICE FIRING
TEAR GAS AND RUBBER BULLETS
AT DEMONSTRATORS.
THOSE DEMONSTRATORS IN TURN
THROWING STONES AND SETTING
UP BARRICADES.
PROTESTERS SAY THEY ARE
UNHAPPY ABOUT A NUMBER OF
THINGS, INCLUDING WHAT THEY
SEES A A GOVERNMENT
CRACKDOWN ON THEIR
FREEDOMS.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS
TURKEY'S LONG-TERM
STABILITY IS BEST GAINER HE
TEED BY UPHOLDING PEOPLE'S
RIGHTS.
TURKEY IS, OF COURSE, A KEY
ALLY.
SHARING BORDERS WITH SYRIA,
IRAQ AND IRAN.
WE ARE TOLD PROTESTS HAVE
SPREAD TO 78 CITIES THERE.
BUT THE MOST VIOLENT SCENES
ARE PLAYING OUT IN ISTANBUL
IN THE CENTRAL PART OF THE
CITY IN AN AREA KNOWN AS
SQUARE.
THAT'S WHERE WE ARE SEEING
IMAGES OF THE
CONFRONTATION.
WHERE FIRES RAGING AND BOTH
SIDES CONTINUE TO STAND
THEIR GROUND.
ED HENRY LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE WITH REACTION
SPOKESWOMAN FROM THE
SECURITY COUNSEL KATELYN
HAYDEN WHO SAYS THERE IS
CONCERN IT ABOUT THE WHITE
HOUSE ABOUT THE UNREST AND
VIOLENCE.
SHE GOES ON TO SAY QUOTE WE
ARE CONCERNED ABOUT ANY
ATTEMPTS TO PUNISH
INDIVIDUALS FOR EXERCISING
THEIR RIGHT TO FREE SPEECH
AS WELL AS ATTEMPTS BY ANY
PARTY TO PROVOKE VIOLENCE
WE BELIEVE TODAY'S EVENTS
REINFORCE THE NEED TO
RESOLVE THIS SITUATION
THROUGH I DO DOG AS WE HAVE
SAID.
WE BELIEVE THAT TURKEY'S
LONG-TERM STABILITY,
SECURITY AND PROSPERITY IS
BEST GUARANTEED BY
UPHOLDING THE FUNDAMENTAL
FREEDOMS OF EXPRESSION,
ASSEMBLY ASSOCIATION AND A
FREE AND INDEPENDENT MEDIA
YOU CAN SEE THE DEEP
CONCERN THE WHITE HOUSE IS
EXPRESSING TONIGHT ABOUT
THESE PICTURES AND
IMPORTANT TO NOTE IT WAS
JUST LAST MONTH THAT THE
PRIME MINISTER OF TURKEY,
PRIME MINISTER WAS HERE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE MEETING
WITH PRESIDENT OBAMA.
REMEMBER, THEY HAD THAT
NEWS CONFERENCE IN THE ROSE
GARDEN IN THE RAIN WHERE
THE MARINE WAS HOLDING UP
THE UMBRELLA FOR THE
PRESIDENT AND THE PRESIDENT
AT THAT POINT WAS ENGULFED
IN AWFUL THESE
CONTROVERSIES ABOUT THE IRS
AND BENGHAZI, ET CETERA.
LOST IN ALL OF THAT
ATTENTION ON THOSE OTHER
CONTROVERSIES, IS THE FACT
THAT BOTH PRIME MINISTER
AND PRESIDENT OBAMA HAD
VERY SERIOUS SUBSTANTIVE
TALKS ABOUT THE U.S. MAYBE
GETTING MORE AGGRESSIVE IN
SYRIA SINCE THAT IS RIGHT
ON THE TURKISH BORDER.
NOW, THE IDEA THOUGH THAT
TURKEY MIGHT PLAY A
CONSTRUCTIVE ROLE IN
HELPING THE U.S. AND SYRIA
IS ALL BUT LOST, GIVEN THE
FACT THAT HE HAS HIS OWN
PROBLEMS INSIDE THE BORDERS
OF TURKEY.
THE LAST THING HE IS GOING
TO BE FOCUSING ON RIGHT NOW
IS HELPING THE U.S. WITH
THIS SITUATION IN SYRIA,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: WIDELY SEEN AS
POORLY HANDLED IN THE EARLY
GOING HAVE THE PRESIDENT
AND THE PRIME MINISTER OF
TURKEY BEEN IN CONTACT
SINCE ALL OF THIS STARTED?
>> U.S. OFFICIALS SAY SO
FAR THERE HAS NOT BEEN
DIRECT CONTACT BETWEEN THE
PRESIDENT AND PRIME
MINISTER.
INTERESTING THAT WHEN THEY
HAD THOSE TALKS HERE IN MID
PLAY AT THE WHITE HOUSE
ONE OF THE CONCESSIONS
PRESIDENT OBAMA GOT FROM
THE PRIME MINISTER, PRIME
MINISTER WAS TO GET TURKISH
SUPPORT FOR A UPCOMING
CONFERENCE IN GENEVA TO TRY
AND DEAL WITH THE FUTURE OF
SYRIA.
IN TERMS OF MAKING SURE
THAT IF ASSAD DOES GO,
PRESIDENT ASSAD DOES GO IN
SYRIA, THERE WILL BE SOME
SORT OF PEACEFUL
TRANSITION AGAIN THE IDEA
THAT PRIME MINISTER WILL
NOW BE FOCUSED ON A
PEACEFUL TRANSITION IN
SYRIA IS LOST IN THE FACT
HE HAS GOT MAJOR PROBLEMS
ON HIS OWN HANDS RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS A BIG CONCERN FOR
THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT
SHEP, BECAUSE THEY HAVE
ALREADY GOT THIS
INSTABILITY IN SYRIA.
INSTABILITY, INSTABILITY
SPREADING INTO TURKEY, A
KEY U.S. AL FLY THAT REGION
IS A DESPERATE SITUATION
FOR THE WHITE HOUSE
TONIGHT SHEP.
>> Shepard: INDEED IT IS,
ED HENRY AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
AS WE CONTINUE TO LOOK LIVE
THIS IS TAKSIM A LARGE
SQUARE IN THE CENTER OF THE
CITY.
ANOTHER SQUARE NEAR WHERE
ALL OF THIS BEGAN.
IT'S ACTUALLY JUST A VERY
SMALL PARK.
AND IT WAS VERY CLOSE TO
THIS AND HAD WHAT AMOUNTED
TO THE LAST GREEN SPACE IN
ALL OF THIS PART OF THE
CITY.
THAT'S HOW ALL OF THIS
BEGAN WITH A GROUP OF
PROTESTERS WHO WANTED TO
SAVE THE TREES.
THE PRIME MINISTER HAS
ASKED TO MEET WITH THEM
TOMORROW BUT THEY ARE NOW
REFUSING.
AT 2:30 IN THE MORNING WE
KNOW HE WILL BE MEETING
TOMORROW WITH SOME SORT OF
FAMOUS PEOPLE AND THE
PROTESTERS, THE ORIGINAL
PROTESTERS ARE SAYING THIS
IS JUST THE BEGINNING, THAT
THIS WILL NOW SPREAD AND IT
WILL GROW.
JOINING US NOW FROM CONTEXT
AND PERSPECTIVE AMBASSADOR
STEWART HOLIDAY.
HE IS THE FORMER U.S.
AMBASSADOR FOR SPECIAL
POLITICAL AFFAIRS AT THE
UNITED NATIONS.
SIR, WITH WHAT DEGREE OF
CONCERN DO YOU WATCH THIS?
>> WELL, I THINK IT'S
OBVIOUSLY VERY TROUBLING.
BUT THIS IS REALLY WHAT
BEGAN AS A DEMONSTRATION
ABOUT URBAN REDEVELOPMENT
AND THEE TREES IS REALLY
NOW A PROXY FOR THE FIFTH%
OF THE POPULATION OF TURKEY
THAT DOESN'T FEEL THAT THE
PRIME MINISTER REPRESENTS
THEIR INTERESTS.
AND I THINK IT'S ALL GOING
TO BE IN HOW THE PRIME
MINISTER HANDLES THIS AND
SO FAR HE HAS GONE BACK AND
FORTH BETWEEN BEING
CONCILIATORY AND BEING
TOUGH.
IN TURKEY, ULTIMATELY THE
TOUGH CENTRAL GOVERNMENT
RESPONSE IS GOING TO CARRY
THE DAY.
>> RIGHT NOW, THERE THERE
IS -- THEY ARE STILL
ALLOWING THE PROTESTERS TO
BE IN THIS SMALLER PARK.
GIZY PARK I BELIEVE IT'S
PRONOUNCED.
THEY ARE ALLOWING THE
PROTESTS TO CONTINUE THERE
THE CONCERN IS IF POLICE
MOVE IN ON THAT AND SHOULD
ANYBODY BE INJURED, FOUR
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN BEEN
KILLED.
THIS COULD CAN HE IS LATE
TO SOMETHING VERY DIFFICULT
IF NOT IMPOSSIBLE TO
CONTROL.
IS THAT YOUR TAKE ON IT.
>> RIGHT NOW THE MAJORITY
OF PEOPLE WHEN I SAY THAT I
MEAN THE PEOPLE OUT IN THE
RURAL AREAS, THE SILENT
MAJORITY OF THE PEOPLE
SUPPORT THE PRIME MINISTER.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE ASIAN
SIDE OF THE -- THEY SUPPORT
THE POLICE.
BUT, IF THERE IS ANY
FURTHER VIOLENCE OR
ESCALATION OF THIS, IT
COULD TRIGGER A BACK FIRE
FOR THE PRIME MINISTER.
HE HAS GOT TO BE VERY VERY
CAREFUL ABOUT HOW HE
HANDLES THIS IN THE COMING
24 HOUR PEOPLE.
>> Shepard: HE NEEDS
DIALOGUE AND SO FAR THE
PROTESTERS HAVE DENIED IT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HE DOES NEED TO SHOW THAT
HE IS WILLING TO REACH OUT.
HE HAS DEVELOPED THIS
REPUTATION, A VERY TOUGH
LEADER BUT FOR HIM, IS HE
RUNNING FOR PRESIDENT.
AND HE WANTS TO BE THE
FIRST POPULARLY ELECTED
PRESIDENT IN TURKISH
HISTORY IN 2014.
FOR HIM, HE IS GOING TO
NEED TO HANDLE THIS VERY
CAREFULLY.
>> AMBASSADOR STEWART
HOLIDAY WITH THE KNOWLEDGE
THAT HE HAS ALREADY TRIED
TO PUT MORE POWERS TO THAT
OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENCY AN
OFFICE TO WHICH HE WANTS TO
MOVE.
WE SHALL SEE HOW THIS PLAYS
OUT AND WE HAVE CONTINUING
COVERAGE THROUGHOUT THE
NIGHT AND THE WEEKS AHEAD.
THE NACIOUSD WATCHMAN WHO
ADMITS HE SHOT AN UNARMED
TEENAGER NAMED TRAVON
MARTIN BACK IN COURT TODAY
AND LOOKING VERY DIFFERENT.
NOW, HIS BROTHER IS
SPEAKING OUT ABOUT GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN'S DRAMATIC WEIGHT
GAIN.
PLUS, IT'S A GOOD IDEA TO
STAY AWAKE AT WORK.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU ARE
HANDLING SOMEBODY'S MONEY.
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT ONE
WORKER'S NAP ON HIS
COMPUTER KEYBOARD THAT
NEARLY COST HIS BANK
HUNDREDS OF MILLIONS OF
DOLLARS.
FLNK
NO, NO, NO! STOP!
HUMANS.
ONE DAY WE'RE COMING UP  WITH THE
THEORY OF RELATIVITY,
THE NEXT...  NOT SO MUCH.
BUT THAT'S OKAY --  YOU'RE COVERED
WITH GREAT IDEAS LIKE OPTIONAL  BETTER
CAR REPLACEMENT
FROM LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
TOTAL YOUR CAR  AND WE GIVE YOU THE
MONEY
TO BUY ONE A MODEL YEAR NEWER.
LEARN ABOUT IT
AT LIBERTYMUTUAL.COM.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT'S YOUR POLICY?
For all those who sleep
too hot or too cool, and struggle
to sleep comfortably together
now there's a solution.
Introducing Sleep Number DualTemp,the
revolutionary
temperature-balancing layer
with Active Air technology that
works on any mattress, including yours.
Whether you sleep hot or cool,
Sleep Number Dual Temp allows each
of you to
select your ideal temperature.
And it's only at one of our over
400 Sleep Number stores nation wide.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
>> Shepard: SO IT LOOKS
LIKE, NOT SURPRISINGLY THE
ATTORNEYS WILL HAVE A TOUGH
TIME FINDING JURORS FOR
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN.
DAY TWO.
THEY HAVE ALREADY DISMISSED
DOZENS OF THE 500 POTENTIAL
JURORS MANY OF WHOM HAD
SAID THEY HAD ALREADY MADE
UP THEIR MINDS ABOUT THIS
HIGH PROFILE CASE.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN THE ONE
TIME NEIGHBORHOOD WATCHMAN
CHARGED WITH MURDERING THE
UNARMED TEENAGER TRAVON
MARTIN IN CENTRAL FLORIDA.
IT'S SHAPING UP TO BE THE
TRIAL OF THE SUMMER WITH
EMOTIONS RUNNING HIGH ON
BOTH SIDES.
TRAVON MARTIN SUPPORTERS
FURIOUS THAT COPS DIDN'T
ARREST ZIMMERMAN UNTIL
ERUPTION NATIONWIDE.
HE HAS HIS OWN SUPPORTERS
CLAIMING THAT HE WAS ACTING
IN SELF-DEFENSE.
TODAY TRAVON MARTIN'S
PARENTS WERE BACK IN THE
COURTROOM FOR JURY
SELECTION AND SO WAS GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN.
MAN, HE LOOKS DIFFERENT.
WAY DIFFERENT FROM WHAT WE
SAW A YEAR AGO.
TODAY HIS BROTHER SPOKE TO
FOX NEWS ABOUT THE
SHOOTER'S DRASTIC WEIGHT
GAIN.
>> BEING OVERWEIGHT IS NOT
HEALTHY.
I THINK THE STRESS IS
UNCANNY.
I THINK EVERYBODY RESPONDS
TO STRESS IN A DIFFERENT
WAY.
I LOST WEIGHT.
I PICKED UP SMOKING AS A
HABIT.
IT WAS JUST TERRIBLE AND
GEORGE GAINED WEIGHT.
>> ACCORDING TO THE BROTHER
THE WHOLE FAMILY HAS BEEN
GETTING DEATH THRETS
FORCING ALL OF THEM INTO
HIDING.
PHIL KEATING WITH ALL OF
THIS.
SANFORD IN FLORIDA.
WHAT ARE THESE PROSPECTIVE
JURORS SAYING?
>> SHEP, THE BIGGEST
REVELATION OUT OF THEIR
MOUTHS IS THAT PRE-TRIAL
PUBLICITY HAS PERMEATED
EVERY SINGLE HOUSEHOLD HERE
IN SEMINOLE COUNTY,
FLORIDA.
SO FAR EVERY POTENTIAL
JUROR WHO HAS MADE IT THIS
STAGE IN THE COURT CALLED
VOIR DIRE ANSWERED THEY
HEARD ABOUT THIS CASE.
ONE JUROR REMARKED IT'S
HARD NOT TO FOLLOW IT.
IT'S EVERYWHERE.
ANOTHER JUROR, A WHITE
SINGLE MOTHER ALSO FAULTED
TRAVON MARTIN FOR GETTING
SUSPENDED FROM SCHOOL IN
MIAMI WHICH LED HIM TO
SANFORD BEING A SINGLE
PARENT WITH TWO BOYS OF MY
OWN.
I'M VERY STRICT WITH THEM.
I DON'T WANT TO JUDGE, BUT
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT
THIS COULD HAVE BEEN
PREVENTED HAD HE NOT BEEN
UP HERE.
THAT'S ALL.
>> OF THE 100 POTENTIAL
JURORS SUMMONED YESTERDAY
THE COURT SAYS 41 WERE
DISMISSED OUTRIGHT.
40 DISMISSED AFTER FILLING
OUT THE QUESTIONNAIRE AND
ONE DISMISSED AFTER VOIR
DIRE.
AND THIS MORNING SOMETHING
WE HAVE NEVER EVER SEEN
FROM GEORGE ZIMMERMAN SINCE
ALL OF THIS BEGAN LAST
YEAR, A BIG SMILE ACROSS
HIS FACE HE'S REACTED TO A
FUNNY ANSWER FROM A JUROR.
HE ALSO PASSED A NOTE TO
HIS ATTORNEY AND STRAINED
TO STAY ALERT AT OTHER
TIMES.
A FAR MORE ANIMATED AND
ENGAGED GEORGE ZIMMERMAN
THAN WE HAVE EVER SEEN IN
THE PAST.
THIS JUST IN FROM THE COURT
MOMENTS AGO.
OF THE 100 POTENTIAL JURORS
WHO ARRIVED HERE TODAY, 30
WERE DISMISSED AND THIS
COURT IS NOW TRYING TO
GATHER AND FOCUS ON GETTING
30 PERCEIVED FAIR AND
IMPARTIAL JURORS AND THEN
HOPEFULLY PICK A JURY FROM
THEM.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: PHIL KEATING
LIVE IN CENTRAL FLORIDA.
WHAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN A
QUICK FLIGHT FROM VEGAS TO
PHOENIX TURNED INTO A FOUR
HOUR NIGHTMARE FOR MORE
THAN 100 PASSENGERS.
AS NOT ONE BUT TWO
DIFFERENT PLANES GOT STUCK
ON THE CARMACK WITH THE
TEMPERATURE IN THE TRIPLE
DIGITS.
THEY HAD NO FOOD.
THEY HAD NO WATER AND NO
AIRCONDITIONING.
>> NO AIR, WE HAVE BEEN
HERE FOR OVER THREE HOURS.
ALLEGIANT AIR CAUSED THE
DELAYS ON FLIGHT 92.
FIRST PLANE GROUND MORE
THAN 90 MINUTES AS THE
MERCURY HIT 100-DEGREES.
>> THERE WAS A LOT OF
PEOPLE YELLING AND
EXPRESSING THAT THEY WANTED
TO BE OFF OF THE PLANE
IMMEDIATELY.
>> ONE WOMAN OVERCOME BY
THE HEAT LAY IN THE AISLE
AS FELLOW PASSENGERS TRIED
TO HELP.
>> THE WOMAN THAT PASSED
OUT WE ACTUALLY HAD TO FIND
WATER IN OUR LUGGAGE ON
OUR CARRY-ONS, EVERYBODY
WAS SCRAM LING.
>> Shepard: FOLKS JOINED IN
♪ I BELIEVE I CAN CAN FLY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> Shepard: THE AIRLINE
TELL FOX NEWS MECHANICAL
DELAYS ARE PART OF AIR
TRAVEL AND QUOTE WHILE
WE'RE GLAD THAT OYOU ARE
CUSTOMERS WERE ABLE TO MAKE
LIGHT OF THE DELAY BY
SINGING R. KELLY SONG WE
TAKE SERIOUSLY.
ALLEGIANT PASSENGER AND
CREW MEMBERS AND WE'LL
ALWAYS TAKE A DELAY TO
ENSURE THE SAFETY OF ALL
INVOLVED.
ALLEGIANT GAVE 100 CREDIT
FOR TRAVEL FOR SOME THAT'S
JUST NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
>> AS FAR AS I'M CONCERNED
I WOULD RATHER HAVE MY
MONEY BACK.
I DON'T PLAN ON FLYING
ALLEGIANT EVER AGAIN.
>> R. KELLY TO THE RESCUE
TO THE RESCUE AGAIN.
GERMAN BANKER FELL ASLEEP
ON THE JOB AND TRANSFERRED
222 MILLION BUCKS FROM A
RETIREE'S ACCOUNT.
HE WAS SUPPOSED TO TRANSFER
$83.
HE NODDED OFF ON THE
KEYBOARD AND JUST PUSHING
THE 2 KEY.
THE BANK DID FIX THE
MISTAKE.
IT FIRED THE BANKER'S
COLLEAGUE THE ONE WHO HAD
FAILED TO CATCH IT HE HAD
TO GO TO COURT TO GET HIS
JOB BACK.
MAJOR VOTE TODAY IN THE
SENATE ON WHAT COULD BE A
LANDMARK IMMIGRATION REFORM
BILL.
THOUGHT IT WAS DEAD?
NO WAY.
NEXT WHY EVEN OPPONENTS OF
THAT BILL VOTED TO MOVE IT
FORWARD.
THAT'S AHEAD AS FOX REPORTS
LIVE TONIGHT.
OH HE'S A FIGHTER ALRIGHT.  SINCE
AFLAC IS HELPING WITH HIS  EXPENSES
WHILE HE CAN'T WORK  HE CAN FOCUS
ON HIS RECOVERY.  HE DOESN'T HAVE
TO WORRY SO MUCH  ABOUT HIS MORTGAGE
GROCERIES, OR EVEN GAS BILLS.  KICK!
KICK...  FEEL IT! FEEL IT! FEEL IT!
NICE WORK!  ♪ ♪  YOU GOT IT!  YOU
GOT IT! YES!  AFLAC'S GONNA HELP TAKE
CARE  OF HIS EXPENSES.  AND US...WE'RE
GONNA GET HIM  BACK IN FIGHTING SHAPE.
♪ ♪    [ le Announcer ] SEE WHAT'S
HAPPENING BEHIND THE SCENES    AT
AFLAC.COM.
TURK HAVE HAVE DECLINED AND
WE KNOW THAT THOSE
PROTESTERS ARE NOW SAYING
THAT THESE DEMONSTRATIONS
WILL CONTINUE IN ISTANBUL
AND BEYOND UNTIL FURTHER
NOTICE.
THE QUESTION NOW IS HOW
WILL THE PRIME MINISTER
HANDLE THIS.
AND TO WHAT LEVELS WILL HIS
POLICE FORCE GO TO STOP
THIS?
CONTINUING COVERAGE AS
EVENTS WARRANT AS FOX
REPORTS LIVE TONIGHT.
THE IMMIGRATION BATTLE
FINALLY MOVED A BIG STEP
FORWARD TODAY WHEN THE
SENATE VOTED TO ALLOW A
DEBATE ON A COMPREHENSIVE
REFORM BILL FROM THE
SO-CALLED GANG OF 8.
THAT LEGISLATION WOULD
PROVIDE A PATH TO
CITIZENSHIP FOR MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE WHO WERE IN THE
UNITED STATES ILLEGALLY.
IT WOULD ALSO PROVIDE
TIGHTER BORDER SECURITY
AMONG OTHER THINGS.
NOW, KEEP IN MIND SOME
LAWMAKERS SAY THEY OPPOSE
THE BILL IN ITS CURRENT
STATE.
BUT THOSE LAWMAKERS VOLTED
TO PUSH FORWARD WITH DEBATE
SO THEY COULD INTRODUCE
THEIR OWN AMENDMENTS.
A DRAMATIC RESCUE AS SOME
GOOD SAMARITANS SAVE A
WOMAN FROM A BURNING CAR.
THAT TOPS OUR NEWS ACROSS
AMERICA.
OREGON.
POLICE SAY THE DRIVER HIT A
ROCK MOUND AND WENT
AIRBORNE.
HER VEHICLE FLIPPING OVER
ON TO ITS ROOF ALONGSIDE A
HIGHWAY EAST OF PORTLAND.
THE IMPACT REPORTEDLY
KNOCKED THE WOMAN
UNCONSCIOUS.
WITNESSES SAY SEVERAL
PEOPLE RUSHED TO HELP AS
THE CAR WENT UP IN FLAMES.
ONE GUY SAYS HE KICKED IN A
WINDOW.
THEN BROKE THROUGH THE SUN
ROOF WITH A BASEBALL BAT
AFTER THE GROUP ROLLED THE
CAR ON TO ITS SIDE.
>> THEY WERE YELLING FOR ME
TO GET AWAY FROM THE CAR
BECAUSE THE CAR IS GOING TO
BLOW.
I'M NOT GOING TO WATCH THIS
LADY BURN.
>> THE RESCUERS CUT THE
WOMAN'S SEAT BELT AND
REMOVED HER TO SAFETY.
SHED TO BE DOING FINE.
>> HORNET'S NEST RIGHT NEAR
THIS COUPLE'S HOME
TALLAHASSEE.
THE THING IS THE SIZE OF A
VOLTS WAGON.
>> MY GRANDSON WAS ON
FACEBOOK THE OTHER DAY MY
GRANDSON BEN AND HE MADE A
STATEMENT SAID WHY DON'T
YOU THROW A ROCK AT IT HE
SAID I DID AND THEY TOLEDO
IT BACK.
>> COUPLE SAYS THE HORNETS
HAVEN'T BOTHERED THEM YET
AND CALLED ANIMAL CONTROL
WHICH REPORTEDLY PLANS TO
WORK WITH THE UNIVERSITY OF
FLORIDA TO REMOVE THE NEST.
MONTANA COPS AND WILDLIFE
WORKERS RESCUED A BABY
MOOSE FROM A BACKYARD
SWIMMING POOL NEAR THE
CANADIAN BORDER.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE ANIMAL
PROBABLY FELL IN AFTER IT
WANDERED ON TO THE POOL'S
COVER OVERNIGHT.
>> ALL OF THIS HAS
HAPPENING UNDER THE
WATCHFUL EYE OF THE MOTHER
WHICH WAS INTIMIDATING.
SHE TOOK A COUPLE OF
CHARGES AT US AND YOU DON'T
WANT TO MESS WITH MOMMA.
>> FIRST RESPONDER PULLED
THE CALF TO SAFETY AND
GUIDED IT BACK TO MOM.
AND THAT'S A FOX WATCH
ACROSS AMERICA.
>> Shepard: DOES DRIVING A
CAR STRESS YOU SNOUT YOU
SHOULD GO TO THE LONG
ISLAND EXPRESSWAY.
IT CAN BE AS STRESSFUL AS
JUMPING OUT OF A PLANE.
AT LEAST ACCORDING TO SOME
NEW STUDY.
RESEARCHERS AT
MASSACHUSETTS INSTITUTE OF
TECHNOLOGY, SOME LITTLE
THING UP THERE, AND AUDI
TESTED THE HEART RACE AND
OTHER VITAL SIGNS OF FOLKS
BEHIND THE WHEEL IN VARIOUS
SITUATIONS.
AMONG THEIR FINDINGS,
GETTING SIDESWIPED IS JUST
ABOUT AS NERVE-RACKING AS
SKY DIVING.
THAT DOES NOT MEAN DRIVING
CAN'T FIGHT PARENTS' BOTHER
DOM.
FIGHT THESE FOLKS IN
ONTARIO, CANADA.
THEY SAY THEY WERE TRYING
TO JUMP THEIR JEEP OVER
THAT GROUND SWIMMING POOL.
THEY CAME UP SHORT CLEARLY.
THEY AMUSED THEMSELVES
CRASHING THROUGH THE WALL
AND LANDING IN THE DRINK.
DRIVER AND PASSENGER OKAY.
WHOEVER POSTED THE VIDEO
CLAIMS THE JEEP STILL RUNS
JUST FINE.
>> MEN FINALLY GROW UP AT
43.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO A NEW
UK STUDY.
RESEARCHERS SURVEYED MEN
AND WOMEN AND BOTH AGREED
THAT MEN STAY IMMATURE WELL
INTO THE LATE 30'S AND
EARLY 40S.
STUDY FOUND THAT LADIES ON
OR ABOUT MATURE BY AGE 32.
MOST WOMEN SAID MEN NEVER
STOP BEING CHILDISH.
NEARLY HALF SAID IMMATURITY
IS ACTUALLY IMPORTANT IN A
RELATIONSHIP THAT IT KEEPS
THINGS FRESH.
THEN THERE IS TIM TEBOW.
IS HE SPORTING HIS NEW
COLORS TODAY AS HE SUITS UP
FOR HIS FIRST PRACTICE
ALONGSIDE BRADY AND THE
PATRIOTS.
AND NOW WE GET TO HEAR THE
PATS COACH BILL BELICHICK
TALK IF HE HE WILL ABOUT
TEBOW MAIN I CAN'T.
HE IS ALWAYS EXCITING
BELICHICK, ISN'T HE?
TRUE TO FORM TODAY.
STAY TUNED.
'RE SO CHOOSY    ABOUT THE CUTS OF
BEEF    THAT MEET OUR HIGHER    KOSHER
STANDARDS    THAT ONLY A SLOW-MOTION
BITE    CAN CAPTURE    ALL THAT KOSHER
DELIGHT.    AND WHEN YOUR HOT DOG'S
KOSHER    THAT'S A HOT DOG YOU CAN
TRUST.    HEBREW NATIONAL.  LOOK WHAT
MOMMY  IS HAVING.  MOMMY'S HAVING
A FRENCH FRY.  YES SHE IS, YES SHE
IS.  [ bop ]
[ Male Announcer ]    COULD'VE HAD
A V8.    100% VEGETABLE JUICE    WITH
THREE OF YOUR DAILY    VEGETABLE SERVINGS
IN EVERY LITTLE BOTTLE.
>> Shepard: TIM TEBOW TOOK
THE FIELD TODAY FIRST
PRACTICE AS NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOT.
FORMER HEISMAN WINNER THIRD
TEAM SINCE DENVER DRAFTED
HIM IN 2010.
WITH DOMINATING THE
HEADLINES THE PAT'S HEAD
COACH ALREADY SEEMED TIRED
OF TALKING ABOUT HIS NEW
PLAYER.
>> IS HE A TALENTED PLAYER
THAT PLAYS SMART AND WORKS
HARD.
WE HAVE SEEN HIM DO A LOT
OF THINGS.
THINK I WE HAVE ALREADY
TALKED A LOT ABOUT HIM.
SEE HOW HE DOES AND JUST GO
FROM THERE.
>> THAT'S ABOUT IT THAT'S
ALL WE GOT REALLY.
AFTER PRACTICE TEBOW SAID
HE IS VERY THANKFUL FOR THE
OPPORTUNITY.
IS HE LITTLE MORE ANIMATED.
HE SAID HE IS READY NOW
LEARN FROM THE PATRIOTS
STAR QUARTERBACK A GUY
NAMED BRADY YP DATING SOME
OF FOX TOP STORIES TONIGHT.
JUST NOW KEITH ALEXANDER IS
NOW SCHEDULED TO EXPLAIN
HIMSELF TO THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE ON
THURSDAY.
MEANTIME THE AMERICAN CIVIL
LIBERTIES UNION REPORTS
THAT IT IS SUING THE
NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY
OVER ITS MONITORING OF THE
PHONE RECORDS OF MILLIONS
OF AMERICANS.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT IS
FOLLOWING THE VIOLENCE AND
TURMOIL IN TURKEY WITH
CONCERN AS AUTHORITIES
CONTINUE THEIR SCRAKDOWN ON
ANTIGOVERNMENT PROTESTERS
IN ISTANBUL AND BEYOND.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THE
NEWS LIVE THIS AFTERNOON.
TRACE?
>> NEARLY 3:00 IN THE
MORNING IN ISTANBUL, SHEP,
AND THE PROTESTERS ARE
STILL VERY MUCH OUT IN
FORCE IN THE SQUARE.
IN FACT, ROUNDS OF TEAR GAS
FIRED JUST MINUTES AGO.
THERE IS ALSO WORD THERE
ARE CLASHES OUTSIDE THE
U.S. EMBASSY IN ANCHOR
REMARKS TURKEY THESE TYPE
OF PROTESTS HAPPENING VERY
MUCH ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THEY ONCE CALLED THIS THE
TREE REVOLUTION BECAUSE IT
BEGAN WEEKS AGO WITH PEOPLE
PROTESTING THE GOVERNMENT'S
PLAN TO REDEVELOP GEZY
PARK.
PULL OUT THE TREES AND
REPLACE THEM WITH A
SHOPPING CENTER.
THEY AUTO QUATED WITH
TURNING CENTRAL PARK INTO A
MALL IN NEW YORK.
NOW IT'S ABOUT MUCH MORE
THAN THE TREES AND IT'S NOT
QUITE A REVOLUTION.
IT'S ABOUT THE PRIME
MINISTER CRACKINGDOWN ON
ALCOHOL, JAILING
JOURNALISTS, AND PUSHING TO
LIMIT SOCIAL MEDIA IN THAT
COUNTRY BUT THOSE SAME
SOCIAL MEDIA SITES, SHEP,
ARE NOW ABUZZ SAYING THAT
THIS PROTEST OR THESE
PROTESTS HAVE JUST BEGUN
AND AS YOU SAID THE WHITE
HOUSE MONITORING ALL OF
THIS WITH CONCERN.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE, THANKS.
AND ON THIS DAY IN 1955,
TRAGEDY STRUCK THE FAMOUS
24 HOUR RACE IN LEMON
FRANCE WHEN A HIGH SPEED
CRASH KILLED 82 PEOPLE.
THE EVENT HAS BEEN AROUND
SINCE THE 20S.
TEAMS ATTEMPT TO COVER THE
MOST DISTANCE IN A SINGLE
DAY AROUND 8-MILE LONG LOOP
ON COUNTRY ROADS BEFORE THE
DISASTER ONE DRIVER
COMPLAINED THE TRACK WAS
TOO NARROW BETWEEN THE PIT
STOPS AND THE GRANDSTANDS.
DURING THE RACE HE TRIED TO
PASS ANOTHER CAR FOR THE
LEAD NEAR THAT SAME NARROW
SECTION.
THE CARS COLLIDED AT
150 MILES PER HOUR.
THE REAR CAR CATAPULTED
INTO THE CROWD.
THE RACE CONTINUED DESPITE
THE WRECK BUT SEVERAL
NATIONS WOULD ISSUE A BAN
ON RACING AFTER A CLASSIC
ONE TURNED DEADLY 58 YEARS
AGO TODAY.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS
FOR THIS TUESDAY, JUNE THE
11TH, 2013.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THANKS FOR CHECKING IN
TONIGHT.
WE APPRECIATE IT WE'LL SEE
YOU BACK HERE TOMORROW FOR
"STUDIO B" AND "THE FOX
REPORT."
WE HOPE YOU WILL HANG
AROUND NOW.
AUTHOR GUY WILL BE MAD.
>> Bill: THE O'REILLY
FACTOR IS ON.
TONIGHT.
>> I CAN'T FIND OUT
ANYTHING CAN YOU?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
TO BENGHAZI.
IN THE IRSZ.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HAPPENED
WITH JAMES ROSEN.
WITH THIS ONE.
THEY WON'T TELL US
ANYTHING.
>> Bill: THAT'S WHAT I SAID
ON "THE TODAY SHOW" THIS
MORNING AS YET ANOTHER
SCANDAL HAS DROPPED ON THE
NATION.
THIS ONE INVOLVING AN
ALLEGED COVERUP OF CRIMES
BY HILLARY CLINTON'S STATE
DEPARTMENT.
JAMES CARVILLE RAND PAUL,
CAWLEY AND COLMES WILL ALL
ANALYZE.
>> I THINK THAT IT'S
IMPORTANT TO A LOT OF
PEOPLE WHO SUPPORT THE
FAMILY THAT THEY HAVE A
FRONT ROW SEAT.
THEY DON'T TRUST THE MEDIA.
>> WILL THE AMERICAN PRESS
COVER THE ZIMMERMAN MARTIN
TRIAL IN A FAREWELL?
WE WILL TAKE A LOOK AT THAT
QUESTION.