TO BE SHE STARTED
OF NESTING.
APPEARED TO BE PRACTICING
TO BE A MOM.
NO NAME YET.
AS WE TAKE A LIVE LOOK SHE
IS NOT MOVING.
THANKS FOR INVITING US INTO
YOUR HOME TONIGHT.
THAT'S IT FOR THIS "SPECIAL
REPORT," FAIR, BALANCED AND
UNAFRAID.
MAKE A GREAT WEEKEND.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
TONIGHT, LIFE OR DEATH.
THE ARMY PSYCHIATRIST
GUILTY OF KILLING 13 AND
INJURING DOZENS AT FORT
HOOD NOW WAITS TO LEARN HIS
FATE.
MOMENTS AGO SAN DIEGO MAYOR
BOB FILNER AGREED TO RESIGN
AFTER MORE THAN A DOZEN
WOMEN ACCUSED HIM OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT, SOMETHING HE
DENIES.
I WAS PLACED IN THE FILNER
HEAD LOCK.
>> I GOT A VERY WET, IS SALIVA
FILLED KISS.
>> SCRATCH.
>> I'M A HUGGER.
>> Jon: NOW, MAYOR BOB
FILNER WILL HAVE TO DO HIS
HUGGING ON HIS OWN TIME.
PLUS,.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
SOMEBODY CAN DO THIS.
>> Jon: A WORLD WAR II
VETERAN BRUTALLY BEATEN AND
LEFT FOR DEAD.
>> HE DIDN'T DESERVE TO DIE
LIKE THAT.
>> COPS SAY THE SUSPECTS
ARE TEENAGERS.
AND A RAGING WILDFIRE THREE
TIMES THE SIZE OF SAN
FRANCISCO.
THREATENING A NATIONAL PARK
AND THOUSANDS OF HOMES.
I'M JON SCOTT IN FOR
SHEPARD SMITH.
GUILTY ON ALL COUNTS.
THAT'S THE VERDICT
CONFESSED GUNMAN IN THE
FORT HOOD MASSACRE.
NOW MAJOR NIDAL HASAN IS
FACE THE DEATH PENALTY.
THE JURY TOOK LESS THAN
SEVEN HOURS TO CONVICT
HASAN OF KILLING 13 PEOPLE
AND TRYING TO KILL DOZENS
MORE IN THE SHOOTING
RAMPAGE ALMOST FOUR YEARS
AGO.
SOME SURVIVORS ARE STILL
RECOVERING FROM SERIOUS
WOUNDS.
AND SOME TOOK THE STAND TO
TESTIFY AGAINST THE MAN WHO
SHOT THEM.
HASAN IS ACTING AS HIS OWN
LAWYER.
BUT HE DID NOT
CROSS-EXAMINE HIS VICTIMS.
TODAY A POLICE OFFICER WHO
WAS SHOT THREE TIMES WHEN
SHE HELPED TAKE DOWN HASAN
SENT THIS REACTION VIA
TWITTER, QUOTE:  SO
OVERWHELMED WITH JOY AND
TEARS.
GOD BLESS THE VICTIMS IN
THEIR STRENGTH.
CASEY STEGALL LIVE AT FORT
HOOD NOW CASEY?
>> YEAH, JON, WHEN THE
VERDICT CAME DOWN THIS
AFTERNOON.
FAMILY MEMBERS INSIDE THAT
COURTROOM CRIED AND HUGGED
EACH OTHER.
THIS IS A DAY THEY HAVE
BEEN WAITING FOR FOR MORE
THAN FOUR YEARS.
AT THE SAME TIME, THE
MURDERER 42-YEAR-OLD NIDAL
HASAN TUGGED AT HIS BEARD
AND STARED DOWN AT THE
TABLE.
ZERO EMOTION AS HIS FATE
WAS BEING READ.
THE 13 MEMBER PANEL WAS
UNANIMOUS ON ALL 45 CHARGES
AND IT WILL BE UP TO THE
SAME GROUP OF PEOPLE
WHETHER HASAN LIVES OR DIES
FOR THE CRIME.
SENTENCING WILL START FIRST
THING MONDAY MORNING WHERE
WE WILL HEAR EMOTIONAL
TESTIMONY FROM THOSE WHO
LOST LOVED ONES IN THIS
MASSACRE.
WE WILL LIKELY HEAR FROM
HASAN AS WELL JON?
>> A LAWYER FOR ONE OF THE
VICTIMS IS CALLING ON THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT TO NOW
DECLARE THE MASSACRE AN ACT
OF TERRORISM.
THE FEDS HAVE LABELED IT
WORK PLACE VIOLENCE.
THAT MEANS THE SURVIVORS DO
NOT GET THE SAME AS COMBAT
VICTIMS AND VICTIMS ARE NOT
HE WILL I DIDN'T BELIEVE
ELIGIBLE FOR THE PURPLE
HEART.
CALLING HIM A TERRORIST
WOULD HAVE JEOPARDIZED THE
TRIAL.
THE JURORS COULD ARGUE THE
GOVERNMENT HAD ALREADY
FOUND HIM GUILTY.
ANOTHER MILITARY JURY JUST
SENTENCED A U.S. SOLDIER TO
LIFE TO PRISON WITHOUT
PAROLE FOR ANOTHER
MASSACRE.
THE MURDERS OF 16 AFGHAN
VILLAGERS MOST OF THEM
WOMEN AND CHILDREN.
SERGEANT ROBERT BALES
PLEADED GUILTY TO AVOID THE
DEATH PENALTY.
ONLY OTHER OPTION WAS LIFE
WITH THE CHANCE OF PAROLE
AFTER 20 YEARS.
PROSECUTORS SAID BALES
WIPED OUT GENERATIONS WHEN
HE WENT ON A KILLING SPREE
LAST YEAR GOING HOUSE TO
HOUSE SHOOTING PEOPLE IN
THEIR HOMES.
SOME OF THEM AS THEY SLEPT
SOME FLEW FROM AFGHANISTAN
TO WASHINGTON.
ONE MAN LOST 11 RELATIVES
AT THE RAMPAGE.
ONE DEAD.
A PILE OF BURNING BODIES.
BALES WAS ON HIS FOURTH
DEPLOYMENT AT THE TIME.
THE DEFENSE CLAIMED HE
SUFFERED A BRAIN INJURY AND
POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS
DISORDER.
BALES SAYS IS HE TRULY
SORRY FOR THE MASSACRE.
CALLING IT AN ACT OF
COWARDICE THAT HE CANNOT
EXPLAIN.
HE SAYS HE THINKS OF THE
VICTIMS EVERY TIME HE LOOKS
AT HIS OWN TWO CHILDREN.
WE HAVE ALREADY REPORTED
THIS WEEK ON THE TEENAGERS
WHO POLICE SAY KILLED A MAN
OUT OF BOTHER DOM.
NOW WE ARE HEARING OF
ANOTHER CASE OF A SEEMINGLY
RANDOM ATTACK FROM TEENS.
THIS TIMES THE VICTIM WAS
AN 8 WILL-YEAR-OLD VETERAN
OF WORLD WAR II.
HIS NAME WAS DELBERT
BELTON.
FRIENDS CALLED HIM SHORTY.
HE THEY SAY HE TOOK A
BULLET TO HIS LEG IN THE
INFAMOUS BATTLE OF OKINAWA
WHICH LEFT THOUSANDS DEAD.
SHORTY HELPED HIM GET OUT
FROM UNEMPLOYMENT.
EVEN OFFERING HIM A CAR.
>> DELBERT LIKE REALLY DID
IT SEEMS TRIVIAL LIKE HE
REALLY DID SAVE MY LIFE.
HE MADE IT POSSIBLE FOR ME
TO GET A JOB AND FIND WORK.
HE WASN'T JUST MIGRATE
UNCLE HE WAS A GREAT
PERSON.
HE DIDN'T DESERVE TO DIE
LIKE THAT.
>> POLICE SAY TWO TEENS
BEAT HIM TO DEATH OUTSIDE
ALLEGE EAGLES LODGE IN
SPOKANE WASHINGTON.
BELTON HAD BEEN WAITING FOR
ANOTHER FRIEND BECAUSE HE
DIDN'T WANT HER TO WALK
HOME ALONE.
NOW ONE SUSPECT IS UNDER
ARREST BUT ANOTHER IS STILL
ON THE LOOSE.
DAN SPRINGER IS LIVE IN
SEATTLE.
DAN?
>> YEAH JON.
WE ARE LEARNING A LOT MORE
ABOUT THE SUSPECT.
BOTH ARE 16-YEAR-OLD WHO'S
HAD ALREADY BEEN CONVICTED
OF ASSAULT AS JIEWNCHS.
POLICE ARRESTED DEMEET TRIS
GLEN LAST NIGHT AT 8:00
SHORTLY AFTER RELEASING
THIS PICTURE CAPTURED BY A
SECURITY CAMERA.
THEY ARE STILL LOOKING FOR
KEENAN ADAMS KENNARD STILL
SEEN TON THIS WANTED
POSTER.
BARELY OLD ENOUGH TO DRIVE.
BOTH FACING FIRST DEGREE
ROBBERY AND MURDER AND MOST
CERTAINLY BE TRIED AS
ADULTS.
8-YEAR-OLD DELBERT BELTON
WAS WAITING IN HIS CAR FOR
A FRIEND WHEN THE TEENAGER
STARTED BEATING HIM IN THE
HEAD AS THEY ROBBED HIM.
>> IT DOES APPEAR RANDOM.
HE WAS IN THE PARKING LOT.
IT APPEARS THAT HE WAS
ASSAULTED IN THE PARKING
LOT.
AND THERE WAS NO INDICATION
OF ANY SORT OF -- THAT HE
WOULD HAVE KNOWN THESE
PEOPLE PRIOR TO THE
ASSAULT.
>> SHORTY SURVIVED THE
NIGHT BUT THEN DIED
THURSDAY MORNING.
FRIENDS AND FAMILY
DESCRIBED THE WORLD WAR II
VET AS TOUGH.
BUT ALSO KIND AND GENEROUS.
THERE IS ALREADY A
MAKESHIFT MEMORIAL IN THE
LOT WHERE HE WAS KILLED.
JON?
>> DAN SPRINGER, THANKS.
>> A FOX URGENT NOW.
SAN DIEGO MAYOR BOB FILNER
HAS AGREED TO RESIGN A WEEK
FROM TODAY.
AND HE JUST MADE AN
EMOTIONAL SPEECH
APOLOGIZING TO THE CITY AND
AS HE PUT IT, TO THE WOMEN
HE OFFENDED.
BUT HE ALSO DENIED SEXUALLY
HARASSING ANYONE AND CALLED
HIMSELF THE VICTIM OF A
LYNCH MOB.
18 WOMEN HAVE ACCUSED
FILNER OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT.
AND A FORMER AID IS SUING
HIM.
AS A REMINDER, HERE IS JUST
SOME OF WHAT THEY SAY HE
DID TO THEM.
>> HE TRIED TO MOVE MY FACE
TOWARDS HIS TO KISS ME.
>> HE TOUCHED ME ACTUALLY
GROPED ME ON MY BACK SIDE
INAPPROPRIATELY.
>> I POINTED OUT THAT HE
HAD ASKED ME TO WORK
WITHOUT MY UNDERWEAR ON.
>> HE PROCEEDED TO SLIDE
HIS ARM DOWN AND THEN GIVE
A LITTLE GRAB TO MY DARIER.
>> AND I TURNED AND HE JUST
SLOBBERED DOWN MY CHIN.
>> BUT SOME PEOPLE DEFENDED
FILNER AT THE CITY COUNCIL
HEARING TODAY.
WILLIAM LA JEUNESSE LIVE IN
OUR WEST COAST NEWSROOM.
WILLIAM?
>> WELL JON, YOU KNOW THE
OVERWHELMING MAJORITY OF
SAN DIEGO RESIDENTS WANTED
HIM OUT OF OFFICE.
HOW HE LEFT.
FILNER RESIGNED AT THE END
OF NEXT WEEK EFFECTIVELY.
HE ALSO HE RESIGNED IN
PROTEST, BLAMING THE CITY
COUNCIL, CALLING THEM A
LEVERAGE MOB SO TO SPEAK.
HE DID APOLOGIZE TO THE
CITY SAYING HE TOOK
RESPONSIBILITY FOR HIS
ACTIONS.
HE APOLOGIZED TO HIS FORMER
FIANCEE.
SAID HE LOVED HER.
THEN HE APOLOGIZED TO THE
WOMEN HE OFFENDED.
BLAMING HIS PERSONAL
AWKWARDNESS AND HUBER RUSS.
BUT HE SAID AT NO TIME HAVE
ALLEGATIONS BEEN PROVEN
AGAINST HIM.
THEN HE HIT THE CITY
COUNCIL WITH BOTH BARRELS.
NONE OF THE ALLEGATIONS
AGAIN, HE SAID HAVE BEEN
INDEPENDENTLY VERIFIED.
AND HE BLAMED THE CITY
COUNCIL FOR FEEDING A LYNCH
MOB MENTALITY AND SAID THEY
WOULD PAY FOR IT.
>> WHEN MY CHILDREN ME
WHERE WERE YOU WHEN THE
PUBLIC LYNCHING OF MAYOR
FILNER TOOK PLACE, I WILL
TELL THEM I WAS NOT AN
ACCESSORY.
I STOOD ON THE SIDE OF THE
MAN, BOB FILNER WHO HAS
STOOD ON THE SIDE OF US FOR
40 YEARS.
>> CITY COUNCIL CONSIDERED
THE SETTLEMENT.
AFTER 18 WOMEN ACCUSED HIM
OF SEXUAL MISCONDUCT.
GRABBING GROPING, OPEN
MOUTH KISSING.
DEMANDING SEXUAL FAVORS.
ONE FILED A LAWSUIT.
FILNER HAS BARGAINING WITH
THE OPENING CHIP HE HAD
LEFT.
HIS OFFICE.
KEY GO OUT PUBLICLY
PAINFULLY, AND A RECALL
PROCESS?
OR WOULD HE RESIGN QUICKLY
AND LET THE CITY LEGAL
BILLS WHICH THAT IS BEING
EXPLAINED TO THE PUBLIC
RIGHT NOW.
THE CITY WILL PROBABLY
COVER OR SOME OF HIS LEGAL
BILLS AS WELL AS ANY
DAMAGES HE FACES FROM THOSE
LAWSUITS IT WILL NOT APPLY
TO ANY CRIMINAL CHARGES
JON.
THAT IS BEING DESCRIBED
RIGHT NOW.
AN ELECTION WILL BE HELD.
A SPECIAL ELECTION IN 90
DAYS TO CHOOSE HIS
REPLACEMENT.
JON?
>> Jon: WILLIAM LA
JEUNESSE, THANK YOU.
AMERICA NEEDS TO PAY
ATTENTION TO THOSE REPORTS
OF A MASSIVE AND DEADLY
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK IN
SYRIA.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM
PRESIDENT OBAMA.
BUT HE ALSO EXPLAINED WHY
IT COULD HURT US BIG TIME
IF THE U.S. GETS TOO
INVOLVED.
PLUS, A GRIM MILESTONE ON
THE NUMBER OF CHILD
REFUGEES NOW TRYING TO
ESCAPE THAT BLOODY CIVIL
WAR.
THAT'S STILL AHEAD ON "THE
FOX REPORT."
THIS MAN IS ABOUT TO BE  THE MILLIONTH
CUSTOMER.  WOULD YOU MIND IF  I GO
AHEAD OF YOU?
INSTEAD WE HAD SOMEONE  GO AHEAD OF
HIM
AND WIN FIY THOUSAND DOLLARS.
CONGRATULATIONS YOU ARE  OUR ONE MILLIONTH
CUSTOMER.
NOBODY LIKES TO MISS OUT.
THAT'S WHY ALLY TREATS ALL  THEIR
CUSTOMERS THE SAME.
WHETHER YOU'RE THE  FIRST OR THE MILLIONTH.
IF YOUR BANK DOESN'T THINK  YOU'RE
SPECIAL ANYMORE
YOU NEED AN ALLY.
ALLY BANK.
YOUR MONEY NEEDS AN ALLY.
When you realize you need  to switch
to Verizon  it's a reality check.
I had my  reality check when
I'd be sitting there  with my friends
who had their Verizon phones  and
I'd be sitting there like
"mine's still loading!"
I couldn't get email.
I couldn't stream movies.
I couldn't upload  any of our music.
That's when I decided  to switch.
Now that I'm on Verizon,  everything
moves fast.
With Verizon  I have that reliability.
I'm completely happy  with Verizon.
Verizon's 4G LTE  is the most reliable
and in more places than  any other
4G network.
Period.
That's powerful.  Verizon.
Get the Nokia Lumia 928  for free.
Play close.  Good and close.
Discover the new way to help  keep
teeth clean
and breath fresh.
New Beneful Healthy Smile Food  and
Snacks.
He'll love the crunch of the  Healthy
Smile kibbles.
You'll love how they help clean.
With soft, meaty centers
and teeth cleaning texture
Healthy Smile Snacks help keep a
shine on his smile.
It's dental that tastes so good.
New Beneful Healthy Smile Food  and
Snacks.
MY MANTRA?  TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS
TO MAKE THE CALL.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE
MY DOCTOR AND I  WENT WITH AXIRON
THE ONLY UNDERARM  LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE  T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN  OR
ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE  OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO  ARE OR
WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID  CONTACT
WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF  PUBERTY IN
CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE  IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS  TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS  AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD  INCLUDE
INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;  WORSENING PROSTATE
SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;  ANKLE, FEET
OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING  WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR  IRRITATION WHERE
APPLIED
INCREASED D BLOOD CELL COUNT
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING  AND
INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT THE  ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
PRESIDENT OBAMA MAKING
CLEAR IS HE IN NO RUSH TO
GET THE U.S. MILITARY
INVOLVED IN SYRIA'S
2-YEAR-OLD CIVIL WAR EVEN
AMID MOUNTING CLAIMS THE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT AGAIN
USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS
AGAINST ITS OWN PEOPLE THE
SITUATION IN SYRIA IS VERY
DIFFICULT.
AND THE NOTION THAT THE
U.S. CAN SOMEHOW SOLVE WHAT
IS A SECTARIAN, COMPLEXED
PROBLEM INSIDE OF SYRIA
SOMETIMES IS OVERSTATED.
>> BUT DELAY CAN BE DEADLY,
RIGHT, MR. PRESIDENT.
>> THERE IS NO DOUBT THAT
WHEN YOU START SEEING
CHEMICAL WEAPONS USED ON A
LARGE SCALE AND AGAIN
WE'RE STILL GATHERING
INFORMATION ABOUT THIS
PARTICULAR EVENT BUT IT IS
VERY TROUBLESOME.
>> Jon: WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS SAY THERE WAS A
HIGH LEVEL MEETING
YESTERDAY TO DISCUSS
AMERICA'S OPTIONS.
OF COURSE, ALL THIS IS
UNFOLDING AS THE PRESIDENT
WRAPS UP A TWO-DAY BUS TOUR
THROUGH NEW YORK AND
PENNSYLVANIA TO TALK ABOUT
HIS PLANS FOR THE ECONOMY.
ED HENRY IS TRAVELING WITH
THE PRESIDENT.
IS HE IN SCRANTON,
PENNSYLVANIA NOW.
ED?
>> WELL JON, YOU ARE
RIGHT.
THIS BUS TOUR WAS SUPPOSED
TO BEEN ALL ABOUT DOMESTIC
ISSUES.
ON THE INTERNATIONAL STAGE
THE PRESIDENT FACING A
CREDIBILITY TEST.
ONE WEEK AGO THIS WEEK THAT
HE DREW THAT RED LINE ON
CHEMICAL WEAPONS IN SARA I
CAN'TENNED A PROMISED THERE
WOULD BE ENORMOUS
CONSEQUENCES IF SYRIA
CROSSED THAT RED LINE.
NOW THAT IT HAS BEEN
CROSSED SEVERAL TIMES AND
POSSIBLY YET AGAIN THIS
WEEK WITH A MASSIVE
CHEMICAL ATTACK THAT KILLED
UP TO 1800 PEOPLE.
IS HE UNDER PRESSURE TO ACT
IN THAT CNN INTERVIEW THAT
YOU REFERRED TO THE
PRESIDENT LASHED OUT AT
SYRIA OVER THIS ALLEGED
ATTACK, SAID HE IS STILL  EVIDENCE
TO
COME IN.
STOPPED SHORT OF SAYING HE
WOULD USE MILITARY ACTION
LEADING TO CONSERVATIVES TO
CHARGE THAT HE IS DODDLING.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> JUMPING IN TO STUFF THAT
DOES NOT TURN OUT WELL.
GETS US MIRED IN VERY
DIFFICULT SITUATIONS.
CAN RESULT IN US BEING
DRAWN IN TO VERY EXPENSIVE,
DIFFICULT, COSTLY
INTERVENTIONS THAT ACTUALLY
BREED MORE RESENTMENT IN
THE REGION.
WE HAVE TO THINK THROUGH
STRATEGICALLY WHAT'S GOING
TO BE IN OUR LONG-TERM
NATIONAL INTEREST EVEN AS
WE WORK COOPERATIVELY
INTERNATIONALLY TO DO
EVERYTHING WE CAN TO PUT
PRESSURE ON THOSE WHO WOULD
KILL INNOCENT CIVILIANS.
>> THE POLICY IS FOCUSED
AROUND NOT GETTING INVOLVED
SO FAR 100,000 DEAD MOSTLY
KILLED BY BULLETS OR
WHISTLES.
HARD TO SAY HOW 1,000 OR
COUPLE HUNDRED DEAD FROM A
CHEMICAL WEAPON WHILE
DEPLORABLE WOULD IMPACT HIS
CALCULUS.
>> NOW, WHAT'S NEXT?
THE PRESIDENT HAS ALREADY
RULED OUT U.S. GROUND
TROOPS IN SARA I CAN'T.
BUT I'M TOLD THAT THAT HIGH
LEVEL MEETING AT THE WHITE
HOUSE YESTERDAY THAT YOU
MENTIONED ONE OPTION THAT
IS BEING DISCUSSED IS U.S.
AIR STRIKES IN SYRIA AND
POSSIBLY WHOSE MISSILES TO
SEND A MESSAGE TO SYRIAN
PRESIDENT BASHAR AL ASSAD.
>> ED HADN'TRY, THANK YOU.
>> WHILE THE WHITE HOUSE
CONTINUES TO HEDGE ITS
RESPONSE.
BRITAIN'S TOP DIPLOMAT
TODAY WAS A LITTLE MORE
BLUNT.
>> THE ONLY POSSIBLE
EXPLANATION OF WHAT WE HAVE
BEEN ABLE TO SEE IS THAT IT
WAS A CHEMICAL ATTACK.
CLEARLY MANY, MANY HUNDREDS
OF PEOPLE HAVE BEEN KILLED.
SOME OF THE ESTIMATES ARE
WELL OVER A THOUSAND.
THERE IS NO OTHER PLAUSIBLE
EXPLANATION FOR CASUALTIES,
SO INTENSE AND SUCH A SMALL
AREA.
>> Jon: HE DIDN'T GO AS FAR
AS THE FRENCH DID YESTERDAY
IN THE POSSIBILITY OF USING
FORCE.
JONATHAN HUNT IS LIVE IN
OUR NEW YORK CITY NEWSROOM.
JONATHAN THE SYRIAN FORCES
STILL CLAIM THEY DID NOT
CARRY OUT THIS ATTACK.
>> THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT
INTERESTINGLY DENYING THAT
A CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK
TOOK PLACE BUT SAYING AS
THEIR RUSSIAN ALLIES HAVE
ALSO IMPLIED THAT THE
ATTACK WAS CARRIED OUT BY
THE REBELS TO GAIN SYMPATHY
AND PRO-VEHICLE
INTERNATIONAL INTERVENTION
THERE ARE FEW WHO BELIEVE
THAT CLAIM.
BRITAIN, TURKEY, AND FRANCE
LEADING THE WAY AND
POINTING FINGERS PRETTY
DIRECTLY AT THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT FORCES AND
DEMANDING THAT THOSE U.N.
WEAPONS INSPECTORS WHO HAVE
ALREADY ARRIVED IN DAMASCUS
NOW BE ALLOWED TO TRAVEL TO
THE SITE OF THE ALLEGED
ATTACK.
BUT THERE ARE FEW SIGNS
TONIGHT, JON, THAT THE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT IS ABOUT
TO PROVIDE THOSE WEAPONS
INSPECTORS WITH SAFE
PASSAGE FOR THE ADMITTEDLY
DANGEROUS 15 MINUTE
JOURNEY.
FROM THAT HOTEL TO THE SITE
OF THE ATTACK JON.
>> Jon: ENED AT U.N. IS
GIVING US A LOOK AT HOW
SYRIA'S CIVIL WAR IS
EFFECTS THE CHILDREN THERE.
>> YEAH.
U.N. OFFICIALS ANNOUNCING
TODAY THAT OF THE 2 MILLION
REFUGEES THAT HAVE FLED THE
FIGHTING IN SYRIA,
1 MILLION ARE CHILDREN.
1 MILLION CHILDREN HAVING
FLED TO NEIGHBORING
COUNTRIES LIKE TURKEY
JORDAN, AND LEBANON.
1 MILLION CHILDREN NOW
WITHOUT HERMINE, CHILDREN
LIKE THESE LISTEN.
ALL I WISH IS THAT SYRIA
COULD BECOME PEACEFUL
AGAIN, THAT'S ALL I WANT
FOR THE TROUBLE TO STOP.
I LOVE SIERRA AND I MISS
SYRIA.
I LOVED MY FRIENDS AND
PLAYING WITH MY SIS IS
TERES, WE USED TO PLAY
TOGETHER.
WE USED TO RIDE A BICYCLE
TOGETHER AND PLAY WITH
TOYS.
>> NOW, TO PUT THAT
1 MILLION FIGURE IN
PERSPECTIVE, U.N. OFFICIALS
POINT OUT THAT IT IS AS IF
EVERY SINGLE CHILD HAD BEEN
FORCED TO LEAVE THE CITIES
OF L.A. AND BOSTON
COMBINED JON.
>> Jon: JONATHAN HUNT,
THANKS.
A MASSIVE WILDFIRE HAS
SPREAD INTO ONE OF OUR
NATION'S GREATEST NATIONAL
WONDERS.
IT'S BEEN BURNING OUT OF
CONTROL AND EXPLODING IN
SIZE.
DETAILS ON THAT GROWING
THREAT.
PLUS, A BIG DEVELOPMENT THE
LAWSUIT AGAINST A CELEBRITY
CHEF PAULA DEAN WORD OF A
SETTLEMENT OF THE SEXUAL
HARASSMENT AND RACIAL
DISCRIMINATION CLAIMS.
♪
LOOKIN' GOOD, FLO!
FEELIN' GOOD!
FEELIN' REAL GOOD!
[ ENGINE REVS ]
BOAT PROTECTION PEOPLE LOVE.
NOW,  THAT'S  PROGRESSIVE.    CALL
OR CLICK TODAY.
SCWON JON AN OUT-OF-CONTROL
CALIFORNIA WILDFIRE SIZE
TODAY AND IT SPREAD INTO
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
OFFICIALS SAY THE RHYTHM
FIRED HAS GROWN FROM
800 ACRES TO 54,000 ACRES
SINCE MONDAY.
FORCING HUNDREDS TO
EVACUATE CAMP SITES AND
HOMES.
AND THREATENING THOUSANDS
MORE HOMES.
AS OF NOW IT'S ONLY 2%
CONTAINED.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS MAP.
THIS WILDFIRE MORE THAN
FIVE-DAY FORECAST BURNING
ACROSS THE WEST.
LED CALIFORNIA GOVERNOR
JERRY BROWN TO DECLARE A
STATE OF EMERGENCY.
DOMINIC DI-NATALE HAS THE
LATEST.
HE IS LIVE NEAR YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK.
DOMINIC?
>> JON, THIS IS ONE OF THE
FASTEST MOVING FIRES SO FAR
THIS WILDFIRE SEASON IF NOT
THE FASTEST.
NOT ONLY ACREAGE OVERNIGHT
BUT LET ME SHOW YOU WE'RE
HERE IN GROVE HAND AND THIS
IS BEHIND US.
THE RIVER CANYON.
CAN YOU SEE THE LINE OF
SMOKE AND THROUGHOUT THE
COURSE EVER THE DAY IT'S
BEEN PROGRESSING GRADUALLY
NORTH.
ALL THE VEGETATION YOU CAN
SEE IS MIND THE SMOKE IS
EXPECTED TO BE CONSUMED
OVERNIGHT.
IN FRONT OF THAT, YOU HAVE
A SERIES OF HOMES, HUNDREDS
AND HUNDREDS OF HOMES WHICH
THE FIRE AUTHORITIES HAVE
BEEN BUSTING A GUT NIGHT
AND DAY TO PROTECT.
THOSE HOMES ARE EXPECTED TO
BE SAFE OVERNIGHT, THEY
BELIEVE, BUT HERE IS HOW
ONE FIRE OFFICIAL DESCRIBED
THE RISKS.
>> THERE ARE 4500 HOMES AT
RISK AS OF 6:00 THIS
MORNING.
THAT'S UP FROM 2500
YESTERDAY.
AS FAR AS STRUCTURES THAT
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED, WE
HAVE FOUR RESIDENCES THAT
IS UP FROM TWO.
12 OUTBUILDINGS WHICH IS UP
FROM 7.
FIVE ADDITIONAL
OUTBUILDINGS BURNED IN THE
LAST OPERATING PERIOD.
>> THAT FIGURE --
GROVEFIELD WILL BE SAFE.
SOME DETAILS WHAT'S
HAPPENING IN YOSEMITE PARK
APPARENTLY CONSUMING ABOUT
11,000 ACRES A DAY OF
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
THIS IS NEAR THE AREA ON
THE LAKE THERE WE'LL KNOW
IN THE MORNING JUST HOWEVER
THE FIRE HAS SPREAD.
IT ACTUALLY TAKES THERMAL
IMAGING EQUIPMENT TO GET AN
ACTUAL COUNT.
DURING THE DAY THE SMOKE IS
SO THICK THEY CAN'T SEAT
LAY OF THE LAND.
IN THE MORNING WE WILL KNOW
WHETHER OR NOT IT BURNED
JUST AS MUCH AS LAST NIGHT
THAT'S 50,000 ACRES.
JON BACK TO YOU.
>> DON, THANK YOU.
FLOOD WARNINGS STILL IN
EFFECT IN PARTS OF COLORADO
IN THE WAKE OF A STORM THAT
BROUGHT TORRENTIAL
DOWNPOURS AND HAIL TO SOME
AREAS INCLUDING DENVER.
SO MUCH HAIL ACCUMULATED IT
LOOKED AS IF IT SNOWED.
THE COUNTY USED A SNOWPLOW
TO OPEN THAT ROAD ABOUT AN
HOUR LATER.
WELL THE FORMER PLOM IEE
FILED A LAWSUIT AGAINST
PAULA DEEN HAS AGREED TO
DROP HER CLAIM AGAINST THE
CELEBRITY CHEF.
THE TWO SIDES FILED A COURT
DOCUMENT TODAY SAYING THEY
HAVE REACHED A SETTLEMENT
WHICH DOES NOT INVOLVE ANY
MONEY.
THE FORMER EMPLOYEE SUED
DEAN AND HER BROTHER LAST
YEAR ACCUSING THEM OF
SEXUAL HARASSMENT AND
RACIAL DISCRIMINATION.
BUT A JUDGE LAST WEEK
DISMISSED THE RACE CLAIMS.
DEEN RELEASED A STATEMENT
SAYING QUOTE I'M LOOKING
FORWARD TO GETTING THIS
BEHIND ME AND SHE IS QUOTE
WORKING TO WORK PLACE
ISSUES THAT WERE RAISED IN
THIS MATTER.
NEARLY A YEAR AFTER THE
TAKE ATTACK IN BENGHAZI,
LIBYA, SOURCES TELL FOX
NEWS THAT MANY SPECIAL OP.S
IN CHARGE OF CAPTURING OR
KILLING THE SUSPECTS ARE
LEAVING THE COUNTRY.
BUT PENTAGON OFFICIALS SAY
THAT IS NOT ENTIRELY TRUE.
DETAILS NEXT.
PLUS, BANK OF AMERICA IS
TAKING ACTION AFTER ONE OF
ITS INTERNS DROPPED DEAD
REPORTEDLY AFTER PULLING
THREE ALL NIGHTERS IN A
ROW.
AND NOW WE ARE HEARING FROM
A TRAVEL AGENT WORKING TO
GET THIS COUPLE BACK HOME
AFTER THEY SAY A CRUISE
COMPANY STRANDED THEM IN
TURKEY.
IT APPEARS OUR JOURNEY  HAS COME TO
A DELIGHTFUL END.  THEN I BETTER USE
THE Capital One Purchase Eraser  TO
REDEEM MY Venture MILES  FOR THIS
TRIP.  Purchase Eraser?  IT'S THE
EASY WAY TO ERASE  ANY RECENT TRAVEL
EXPENSE.  I JUST PICK A CHARGE  LIKE
MY FLIGHT  WITH A FEW TAPS,  IT'S
TAKEN CARE OF.  IMPRESSIVE BALDWIN.
DOES IT WORK FOR HOTELS?  ABSOLUTELY
THANK GOODNESS.  MRS. VILLAIN AND
I  ARE PLANNING OUR...  YOU SCARE
ME.  AND I LIKE IT.  LET'S GO  WHAT'S
IN YOUR WALLET?
I CAN'T ALWAYS  KEEP MY KIDS' SOCKS
CLEAN.  BUT AT LEAST I CAN HELP  KEEP
THEIR UNDERWEAR CLEAN.
TtVWKUN+og#WVS#q'PPU;V?2V.AC=u)L4#p/WlÑkñ0K9%"@NKGI@
4Z80   WITH  CHARMIN ULTRA STRONG.
Tt@L"bé8Q0   I'LL
TAKE THAT.
GO GET 'EM, BUDDY!
[ Female Announcer ]    CHARMIN ULTRA
STRONG
HAS A DURACLEAN TEXTURE
AND ITS FOUR TIMES STRONGER    THAN
THE LEADING BARGAIN BRAND.
TtVWKUN+og#WVS#q'PPU;V?2V.AC=udJef<p<]fII?@Nqa.@lcg-úJSZD
ENJOY THE GO  WITH CHARMIN ULTRA STRONG.
[ Male Announcer ] COME TO THE
GOLDEN OPPORTUNITY SALES EVENT
TO EXPERIENCE    THE PRECISION HANDLING
OF THE LEXUS    PERFORMANCE VEHICLES
INCLUDING THE GS    AND ALL-NEW IS.
♪ ♪    THIS IS    THE PURSUIT OF PERFECTION.
MY NAME IS PAUL RIDLEY.  TO BENEFIT
CANCER RESEARCH  I RODE ACROSS THE
ATLANTIC.  CROSSING AN OCEAN WITH
YOUR BODY  AS THE MOTOR, IT HURTS.
SO I BROUGHT ADVIL  TO HELP ME STAY
STRONG  DURING THE TOUGHEST JOURNEY
OF MY LIFE.    [ Male Announcer ]
PAUL RIDLEY HAD A CHOICE    OF PAIN
RELIEVERS,    BUT HE CHOSE ADVIL.
BECAUSE NOTHING IS STRONGER    ON
TOUGH PAIN. NOTHING.    NOT TYLENOL.
NOT ALEVE.  [ Paul ]  WHEN PEOPLE
ARE COUNTING  ON ME TO COME THROUGH,
MY ANSWER IS ADVIL.    [ Male Announcer
]    REAL PEOPLE. REAL PAIN.    REAL
RELIEF.    ADVIL. RELIEF IN ACTION.
[ Male Announcer ]    AMERICA'S FAVORITE
ENDLESS SHRIMP IS BACK!  PEOPLE WAIT
FOR THIS PROMOTION  ALL YEAR LONG.
AND NOW THERE ARE ENDLESS WAYS
TO LOVE IT...    FROM CRISPY TO SPICY
TO SAVORY.  [ Man ]  YOU CANNOT MAKE
A BAD CHOICE.    [ Male Announcer
]    RED LOBSTER'S ENDLESS SHRIMP!
AS CH AS YOU LIKE    Y WAY YOU LIKE!
YOU CAN HAVE YOUR SHRIMP.  AND YOU
CAN EAT IT, TOO.    [ Male Announcer
] TRY OUR NEW    SOY WASABI GRILLED
SHRIMP    OR CLASSIC GARLIC    SHMP
SCAMPI.    ALL JUST $15.99    FOR
A LIMITED TIME.  IT'S GONNA BE A HIT
THIS YEAR.    [ Male Announcer ]
RED LOBSTER'S ENDLESS    SHRI IS NOW!
WE WOULD NEVERISS  ENDLESS SHRIMP.
[ Male Announcer ]    BUT IT WON'T
LAST FOREVER.    SO COME    AND SEA
FOOD DIFFERENTLY.
License and registration   please.
What's this?
Uhh, it's my GEICO insurance   ID
card, sir.
It's digital, uh, pretty   cool right?
Maybe.
You know why I pulled   you over today?
Because I'm a pig driving   a convertible?
Tail light's out.. Fix it.
Digital insurance ID cards.
Just a click away with the
GEICO mobile app.
NOBODY THERE SPOKE ENGLISH.
SHE SAID SHE FEARED FOR HIS
LIFE.
TODAY OFFICIALS AT THE
STATE DEPARTMENT TOLD US
THE CONSULATE GENERAL IN
ISTANBUL HAS BEEN IN TOUCH
WITH THE COUPLE AND IS
PROVIDING ALL APPROPRIATE
STANCE.
THE COUPLE'S TRAVEL AGENT
INSURANCE COMPANY HAS
AGREED TO PAY FOR THE
COUPLE'S RETURN TRIP BUT
SHE SAYS THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
>> I KNOW THAT THEY LOVE
CRUISING BUT IF THEY HAD
GONE OVER 30 CRUISES AND
THEY HAVE BEEN WITH ROYAL
CARIBBEAN MOST OF THE TIME
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF
DOLLARS THAT THEY SPENT.
I THINK THEY NEED MORE
COMPENSATION AT THIS POINT.
>> NO WORD FROM ROYAL
CARIBBEAN ON ANY PAYMENT.
I'M JON SCOTT IN FOR
SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
IT SEEMS MAYBE THE THREAT
OF GETTING KILLED OUTWEIGHS
THE PROMISE OF MAKING YOUR
VOICE HEARD IN EGYPT.
AS PLANNED TODAY,
SUPPORTERS OF MOHAMMED
MORSI HELPED PRO-SAYS IN
SUPPORT OF THE
DEMOCRATICALLY ELECTED
PRESIDENT WHICH THE
MILITARY THREW OUT OF
OFFICE LAST MONTH.
AFTER A BRUTAL CRACKDOWN BY
THE GOVERNMENT THERE WERE
FAR FEWER DEMONSTRATORS
THAN WE HAVE SEEN IN
PREVIOUS WEEKS.
LELAND INDIVIDUAL TERRITORY
IN JERUSALEM HAS MORE.
LELAND?
>> JON, TODAY WE SAW WHAT A
WEEK OF MASS ARRESTS AND
MARTIAL LAW WILL DO.
THE MUSLIM BROTHERHOOD
LEADERSHIP IN JAIL AND NOT
ABLE TO TURN OUT PEOPLE ON
THE STREET LIKE THEY COULD
BEFORE.
HERE IS WHAT WE DID SEE
TODAY, THE GROUP'S
SUPPORTERS CHANTED THE COUP
IS TERRORISM AS THEY
MARCHED THROUGH SOUTHERN
CAIRO.
MILITARY COUNCIL CONTINUES
TO CONTROL THE COUNTRY THIS
REVOLUTION WILL CONTINUE
SAID ONE MAN IN THE CROWD.
IS HE SUPPORTING OUSTED
PRESIDENT MOHAMMED MORSI.
THE EGYPTIAN MILITARY
PATROLLED CAIRO WITH TANKS
AND ARMORED PERSONNEL
CARRIERS THEY CAN SHOOT TO
KILL IF THREATENED LIKE WE
SAW WITH THE VIOLENCE
EARLIER THIS WEEK.
EVEN THE ARMY'S
CONTROVERSIAL DECISION TO
MOVE FORMER DICTATOR HOSNI
MUBARAK FROM A PRISON TO
MARITAL HOSPITAL COULDN'T
ENERGIZE EGYPTIANS TO FILL
THE STREETS MUBARAK ORDERED
OF PROTESTERS DURING THE
2011 EGYPTIAN REVOLUTION.
TAKING CONTROL OF THE
STREET IS STILL THE FIRST
WAVE OF MANY BATTLES.
GEARED UP WITH WEAPONS AND
AMMUNITION BROUGHT IN FROM
LIBYA.
RAISING THE FEAR OF MORE
VIOLENCE.
THINGS LIKE SUICIDE
BOMBINGS, ATTACKS ON
MILITARY BASES EVEN THE
KIDNAPPING OF TOURISTS,
JON?
>> Jon: LELAND VITTERT
THANKS.
THE SUSPECT IN THE DEADLY
TERROR STRIKE ON OUR
CONSULATE IN BENGHAZI
LIBYA REMAIN AT LARGE
NEARLY ONE YEAR AFTER THE
ATTACK.
NOW SOURCES NOW TELL FOX
NEWS THAT MUCH OF THE U.S.
SPECIAL OPERATIONS TEAM
THAT'S HELPED TRACK THOSE
SUSPECTS IS SET TO LEAVE
LIBYA.
PENTAGON OFFICIALS DENY
THAT CLAIM.
THEY SAY THE GROUP WAS ONLY
IN THE COUNTRY TO PROVIDE
COUNTER TERRORISM TRAINING.
AND WAS NEVER SPECIFICALLY
TASKED WITH HUNTING THE
SUSPECTS.
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
DID FILE CRIMINAL CHARGES
AGAINST SEVERAL SUSPECTS
ABOUT TWO WEEKS AGO THAT
ATTACK LAST SEPTEMBER 11TH
KILLED I FORMER KNAVE SEAL
TYRONE WOODS AND GLEN
DAUGHTERY.
WHERE TOO WE STAND IN THE
INVESTIGATION WASHINGTON
TEAM FROM FORT BRAD MAY BE
GOING.
IN THE TEAM THAT WENT IN
LAST NOVEMBER TO TRAINES
COUNTER TERRORISM.
TEAM TRAIN FIND FIX AND
FINISH THOSE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE BENGHAZI ATTA THAT ENTIRE
TREATMENT OTHER
THAN TWO ARE BEING PULLED.
IN FACT THEY WERE AT THE
TRAINING CAMP WHEN THE NEW
LIBYAN DEFENSE MINISTER
WALKED IN AND SAID YOU WHYS
ARE DONE.
THAT CAMP PARTLY FUNDED BY
TAXPAYER DOLLARS.
FORCED THESE MEN WHO HAD
BEEN THERE TO FIND THESE
SUBJECTING TO GO BACK TO
VILLA AND WAIT FOR THEIR
ORDERS JON.
IS THE SECURITY SITUATION
IN LIBYA HAS ONLY GOTTEN
WORSE?
>> YEAH, IN FACT, A COLONEL
TODAY, A LIBYAN COLONEL WAS
ASATSZ SIN NATEED THERE HAS
BEEN A NUMBER OF PRISON
BREAKS.
A MASSIVE ONE WHERE OVER
1,000 PEOPLE ESCAPED.
A COUPLE OTHER PRISON
BREAKS AS WELL.
KINGS, SAME OPERATORS IN
THE REGION WILL TELL THAT
YOU EASTERN LIBYA HAS
BECOME A WAR ZONE IN FACT
THE MUSLIM BROTHERHOOD IN
LINE WITH ANSAR SHARIA
GOVERNMENT THERE PROVIDED
INFORMATION ON THESE
SUSPECTS MONTHS AGO.
WE REPORTED THIS BEFORE
BACK IN NOVEMBER AS WELL AS
IN JANUARY.
AND EVEN MORE RECENTLY THEY
SAY A REPORT WAS GIVEN TO
THE PRESIDENT ON ONE OF
THESE BENGHAZI SUSPECTS AS
RECENTLY AS AUGUST 7TH AND
NOTHING HAS BEEN DONE THUS
FAR.
JON.
>> Jon: ADAM HOUSLEY
THANKS.
THE UNEXPECTED DEATH OF AN
INTERN HAS PROMPTED
OFFICIALS AT BANK OF
AMERICA TO REVIEW THE
WORKING CONDITIONS OF ALL
JUNIOR EMPLOYEES, THAT
ACCORDING TO A COMPANY
STATEMENT TODAY.
AS WE REPORTED THAT
21-YEAR-OLD GERMAN WAS
ABOUT A WEEK SHY OF
COMPLETING HIS SUMMER
INTERNSHIP IN LONDON.
HE REPORTEDLY WORKED THREE
BACK-TO-BACK ALL NIGHT
SHIFTS.
NEARLY 72 HOURS STRAIGHT
WITH LITTLE BREAK.
SHORTLY BEFORE HE COLLAPSED
AND DIED.
BANK OFFICIALS RELEASED A
STATEMENT TODAY SAYING HIS
DEATH DEEPLY SHOCKS AND
SADDENS THEM.
AND THAT IN RESPONSE THEY
BROUGHT TOGETHER A GROUP TO
INVESTIGATE WHAT HAPPENED
AND TO QUOTE:  LISTEN TO
EMPLOYEES AT ALL LEVELS AND
LEARN FROM THEM.
A FOX URGENT NOW, FORMER
NEW YORK KNICKS BASKETBALL
GREAT DEAN MEMINGER DIED
ACCORDING TO POLICE.
HAD HIS GOLD RING ON HIS
FINGER.
THEY FOUND THE 6 A-YEAR-OLD
UNCONSCIOUS AND
UNRESPONSIVE INSIDE A ROOM
THERE TODAY.
AND THAT EMERGENCY CREWS
PRONOUNCED HIM DEAD AT THE
HOTEL.
MEMINGER WAS KNOWN AS
DREAM.
WIN A CHAMPIONSHIP IN 1973.
HE BATTLED COCAINE ABUSE
DURING HIS LIFE BUT THERE
IS NO WORD YET ON WHAT
CAUSED HIS DEATH.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE PLAN
TO CONFRONT POLICE OFFICERS
DURING TRAFFIC STOPS AND
EXECUTE THEM IF THEY
RESISTED.
NEXT.
THE CHILLING DETAILS OF
WHAT AUTHORITIES CALL A
HOMEGROWN TERROR PLOT ON
THE DAY THE SUSPECTS
APPEARED IN COURT.
AND WHAT KIND OF PERSON
SHOOTS A BABY IN ITS
STROLLER?
THE SAME KIND OF PERSON WHO
GIVES DETECTIVES A HARD
TIME WHEN THEY START ASKING
QUESTIONS OR AT LEAST THAT
WAS THE ARGUMENT IN COURT
TODAY.
AND IT'S NEXT.
For a strong bag that    grips the
can...
get Glad ForceFlex.
Small change
big difference.
[ Male Announcer ]    THESE DAYS,
A SMALL BUSINESS    CAN SAVE BY SHARING.
LIKE CARPOOLS...  POLLY WANTS TO KNOW
IF WE CAN PICK HER UP.  YEAH  WE CAN
MAKE ROOM.  YEAH.    [ Male Announcer
]    ...OFFICE SPACE.  YES, WE'RE
LOVING THIS  COMMUNAL SEATING. IT'S
GREAT.    [ Male Announcer ]    THE
BEST THING TO SHARE?    A DATA PLAN.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
ONE BUCKET OF DATA    FOR EVERYONE
ON THE PLAN    UNLIMITED TALK AND
TEXT    ON SMART PHONES.    NOW, EVERYONE'S
IN THE SPIRIT    OF SHARING.  HEY,
CAN I BORROW YOUR BOAT  THIS WEEKEND?
NO.    [ Male Announcer ]    SHARE
MORE. SAVE MORE.    AT&T MOBILE SHARE
FOR BUSINESS.  ♪ ♪
VO: Two years of grad school.
20 years with the company.
Thousands of presentations.
And one hard earned partnership.
It took a lot of work  to get this
far.
So now I'm supposed to take  a back
seat when it
comes  to my investments?
There's zero chance  of that happening.
AVO: When you work with a  Schwab
financial consultant,
you'll get the guidance you need
with the control you want.
Talk to us today.
>> Jon: COPS SAY A COUPLE
PLOTTED TO KIDNAP, TORTURE
AND KILL POLICE OFFICERS AS
PART OF A DOMESTIC TERROR
MOVEMENT CALLED SOVEREIGN
CITIZENS.
AND TODAY THEY STOOD IN
FRONT OF A JUDGE AND TOLD
HIM THEY DID NOT RECOGNIZE
HIS AUTHORITIES.
THE JUDGE'S RESPONSE?
SO NOTED.
ACCORDING TO POLICE IN LAS
VEGAS, AN UNDERCOVER
OFFICER FOLLOWED THE COUPLE
FOR NEARLY FOUR MONTHS AS
THEY SHOPPED FOR GUNS HELD
SOVEREIGN CITIZEN SEMINARS
RIGGED AN EMPTY HOUSE TO
TIE UP POTENTIAL CAPTIVES
TO CROSS BEAMS.
THE MAN TOLD THE JUDGE I
OBJECT TO THE ENTIRE
PROCEEDINGS OF THIS COURT
FOR THE RECORD THE JUDGE
SET HIS BAIL AT MORE THAN
HALF BILLION DOLLARS.
CITING A CRIMINAL HIS THAT
I HAVE INCLUDED A SEX
OFFENSE INCLUDING A CHILD.
THE WOMAN'S BAIL HEARING
SET FOR NEXT WEEK.
SPEAKING FROM JAIL SHE SAID
SHE NEVER INTENDED TO HURT
ANYBODY.
>> I DO LOOK LIKE A
DOMESTIC TERRORIST?
I HAVE NEVER BEEN ARRESTED
IN MY LIFE.
I HAVE NEVER DONE ANYTHING
FOR WHICH I COULD BE
ARRESTED.
>> Jon: SHE ALSO SAYS SHE
MET HER PARTNER WHILE HE
WAS SELLING WATER BOTTLES
ON THE VEGAS STRIP.
THE TEEN CHARGED WITH
FATALLY SHOOTING A 13 MONTH
OLD IN THE HEAD AS THE
INFANT'S MOTHER PUSHED HIM
IN A STROLL DER NOT
COOPERATE WITH
INVESTIGATORS.
THAT ACCORDING TO TESTIMONY
TODAY OF ONE OF THE POLICE
OFFICERS WHO INTERVIEWED
THAT SUSPECT DEMARCUS
ELKINS.
YESTERDAY WE HEARD FROM THE
ACCUSED SHOOTER'S ACCUSED
ACCOMPLICE DOMINIC LANG WHO
TESTIFIED ELKINS TRIED TO
ROB THE MOTHER.
ELKINS COUNTED DOWN FROM 5
THREATENING THE BABY.
HE THEN SHOT THE INFANT'S
MOTHER IN THE LEG AND AIMED
AT THE BABY'S FOREHEAD AND
PULLED THE TRIGGER.
JOHN ROBERTS WITH THE NEWS
LIVE IN MARIETTA GEORGIA.
JOHN JON THE DEFENSE IS
FIGHTING HARD TO KEEP
EVIDENCE OUT OF THIS TRIAL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
EVERYTHING AGAINST THE WALL
TRYING TO GET SOMETHING TO
STICK.
YESTERDAY THEY TRIED TO
PRESENT THE CO-ACCUSED
DOMINIC LANG IDENTIFYING
DOMINIC ELKINS AS THE
TRIGGER MAN.
TODAY THEY TRIED
UNSUCCESSFULLY TO EXCLUDE A
POTENTIALLY DISCRIMINATING
STUDENT.
INTERVIEW IN WHICH POLICE
ACCUSED HIM OF SHOOTING 13
MONTH OLD SANTIAGO AND TOLD
ENELKINS THAT IMAGE OF
KILLING THE BABY WOULD
LIKELY STAY WITH HIM FOR
THE REST OF HIS LIFE.
INVESTIGATOR ROD PICKS UP
THE STORY.
>> HE SAID YOU ONLY GOT
[BLEEP] ON ME.
Y'ALL AIN'T GOT NO GUN.
Y'ALL AIN'T GOT NO
FINGERPRINTS.
ALL YOU HAVE [BLEEP]
ACQUITTAL.
INVESTIGATOR SMILED AT HIM
AND HE LOOKED BACK AND
FORTH BETWEEN ME AND
INVESTIGATOR BLAZE AGAIN
AND THEN ASKED US OH, YOU
GOT THE GUN?
THE JURY ALSO SAW FOR THE
FIRST TIME EVIDENCE
COLLECTED FROM DEMARCUS
ELKINS' ROOM INCLUDING A
RED SWEATER HE WAS SEEN
WEARING ONE THE DAY OF THE
SHOOTING AND A .22 CALIBER
LONG RIFLE BULLET.
THE BABY WAS SHOT WITH A
.22 CALIBER GUN.
THE WHOLE TRIAL NEARLY CAME
OFF THE RAILS TODAY WHEN AN
ATTORNEY FROM ELKINS MOTHER
REFERRED TO ELKINS JUVENILE
RECORD.
THE COURT HAS SPECIFICALLY
FORBIDDEN ANY REFERENCE TO
ELKINS' PRIORS.
HAD THAT WITNESS ANSWERED
THE QUESTION AND SHE
DIDN'T, THE WHOLE TRIAL
COULD HAVE STOPPED RIGHT
THEN AND THERE.
JON?
>> Jon: THE MOTHER OF THE
SLAIN BABY SHERRI WEST IS
EXPECTED TO TESTIFY ON
TUESDAY.
MEANWHILE, WE ARE NOW
HEARING FROM THE FAMILY OF
CHRISTOPHER LANE.
HE IS THE STRALLIAN COLLEGE
BASEBALL PLAYER WHOM POLICE
SAY THREE TEENAGERS
RANDOMLY GUNNED DOWN IN
OKLAHOMA LAST WEEK OUT OF
BOTHER DOM.
BOREDOM.
THANKING THE FAMILY FOR
QUOTE WE WANT PEOPLE TO
KNOW WE DON'T BELIEVE WHAT
HAPPENED IS A REFLECTION ON
THE PEOPLE OF DUNCAN OR
OKLAHOMA.
AUTHORITIES HAVE CHARGED
THE TWO TEENS ON THE LEFT
OF YOUR SCREEN WITH FIRST
DEGREE MURDER.
WHILE THE ONE ON THE RIGHT
IS CHARGED WITH BEING AN
ACCESSORY TO MURDER.
EARLIER THIS WEEK, A FORMER
TEAMMATE STARTED AN ONLINE
FUND TO HELP COVER COSTS OF
RETURNING ELLAYNA'S BODY TO
AUSTRALIA.
THE INITIAL GOAL $15,000.
IT'S WELL PAST THAT
RECEIVING 150 GRAND IN
DONATIONS AT LAST CHECK.
WE ARE TOLD ANY MONEY LEFT
OVER WILL GO TOWARD
ESTABLISHING A MEMORIAL IN
ELLAYNA'S HONOR.
GARRETT TENNEY HAS THE
LATEST DEVELOPMENTS.
GARY?
>> JON, THE LANE FAMILY
SAYS THAT THAT MEMORIAL L.
MAKES DONATIONS TO
ORGANIZATIONS IN CHRIS'
NAME TO HELP OTHERS FULFILL
THEIR DREAMS JUST AS THEIR
SON WAS DOING.
THE FAMILY'S STATEMENT
READS IN PART.
THE CHRISTOPHER WAS CHASING
HIS DREAMS AND WE BELIEVE
EVERYONE SHOULD DO THE
SAME.
CHRISTOPHER WOULD BE SO
PROUD HE HAD MADE A
DIFFERENCE IN SO MANY
LIVES.
THANKS TO THOSE FUNDS, THE
22-YEAR-OLD'S GIRLFRIEND
AND HER FAMILY ARE NOW ON
THEIR WAY TO AUSTRALIA.
TO RETURN HIS REMAINS TO
HIS GRIEVING PARENTS.
THEY ARE EXPECTED TO ARRIVE
IN MELBOURNE SOMETIME
TOMORROW AND FUNERAL PLANS
ARE IN THE WORKS FOR SOME
TIME EARLY NEXT WEEK.
BACK IN OKLAHOMA THOUGH
FRIENDS AND TEAMMATES ARE
PREPARING TO GATHER FOR A
MEMORIAL SERVICE IN CHRIS'
HONOR TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
THEY ARE PLANNING TO RECORD
THE SERVICE SO THAT HIS
FAMILY BACK IN AUSTRALIA
CAN FEEL AS IF THEY ARE A
PART OF IT.
MEANWHILE, PROSECUTORS TELL
US THEY ARE CONTINUING TO
MEET WITH ONE OF THE THREE
TEENS WHO HAS BEEN
COOPERATING WITH THE
INVESTIGATION.
17-YEAR-OLD MICHAEL JONES.
HE IS THE ONE POLICE SAY
WAS DRIVING THE CAR WHEN
CHRISTOPHER LANE WAS SHOT
IN THE BACK.
AND WE'RE TOLD THE OTHER
TWO TEENS REMAIN
UNCOOPERATIVE AT THIS TIME.
JON?
>> Jon: ACCORDING TO THE
DISTRICT ATTORNEY IT LIKELY
WILL BE 18 TO 24 MONTHS
BEFORE THIS CASE GOES TO
TRIAL.
HE SAYS HE EXPECTS THAT
TRIAL TO LAST NO MORE THAN
TWO WEEKS.
OFFICIALS SEIZED MORE THAN
A QUARTER BILLION DOLLARS
WORTH OF COCAINE FROM A
YACHT.
OUR TOP STORY AS WE GO
AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
AUSTRALIA.
U.S. AND AUSTRALIAN AGENTS
SAY THEY FOUND MORE THAN
1600 POUNDS OF COCAINE
HIDDEN IN THE ENGINE ROOM
WHILE THE YACHT WAS IN THE
SOUTH PACIFIC ISLAND.
THEY SAY THE BOAT WAS ON
ITS WAY TO AUSTRALIA I
CAN'T UNDERSTAND AT DRUGS
ARE WORTH AROUND
$330 MILLION.
NO ARRESTS YET.
SINCE 2010 THE U.S. AND
AUSTRALIA HAVE WORKED WITH
SOUTH PACIFIC GOVERNMENTS
TO CRACK DOWN ON THE USE OF
YACHTS TO SMUGGLE COCAINE
FROM SOUTH AMERICA TO
AUSTRALIA.
PORTUGAL.
CREWS BATTLED DEADLY
WILDFIRES IN THE CENTRAL
PART OF THE COUNTRY.
SIX DIFFERENT FIRES
SPREADING ACROSS THAT
REGION.
ACCORDING TO LOCAL REPORTS
A COMMANDER SAYS ONE
FIREFIGHTER WAS KILLED WHEN
POWERFUL WINDS CAUSED A
FIRE TO SUDDENLY CHANGE
DIRECTION.
AND THAT CREW MEMBER RAN
THE WRONG WAY.
NINE OTHER FIREFIGHTERS
HURT.
RUSSIA:  THE WORST FLOODING
IN 120 YEARS FORCING
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE FROM
THEIR HOMES IN THE EAST.
OFFICIALS SAY THE WATER HAS
REACHED HISTORIC HIGH OF
24 FEET AND THAT IT WON'T
PEAK UNTIL THIS WEEKEND.
ARGENTINE ARGENTINA
♪ DANCERS FROM 37 COUNTRIES
HAVE FLOCKED TO BUENAS ARE
A REISS FOR THE WORLD TANGO
CHAMPIONSHIPS.
IT SOME FROM CHINA RUSSIA
AND PAKISTAN.
THAT'S A WRAP ON THIS FOX
TRIP AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
PLEASURE NOW THE STORY OF A
MOTORCYCLE, A TRAIN AND A
BEAR.
IT'S A SHORT STORY, ONE YOU
ARE ALREADY ON THE
MOTORCYCLE.
THE TRAIN IS ABOUT TO COME
UP ON THE LEFT.
BUT WHERE IS THE BEAR?
OH, THERE T. IT IS.
THE END.
CANADIAN INVESTIGATORS SAY
THE DRIVER WHO WAS WEARING
THIS HELMET CAM WAS DRIVING
RECKLESSLY AND GOING TOO
FAST.
THEY TELL US HE SURVIVED
WITH SIGNIFICANT INJURIES.
THE BEAR WE'RE TOLD WALKED
AWAY.
♪ A DOUBLE DOSE OF COOL
CRITTERS TONIGHT.
FIRST UP, WE'RE GOING TO
NEED A MUCH BIGGER POOL.
THAT'S WHAT THE HEAD OF THE
FORT WORTH ZOO IS SAYING
ABOUT THIS LITTLE GUY THE
BABY ELEPHANT ABOUT TO
OUTGROW HIS KID DID I POOL.
ALMOST THREE WEEKS OLD AND
WEIGHS ALMOST 200 POUNDS.
7TH MEMBER OF AN EXTENDED
ELEPHANT FAMILY AT THE ZOO.
THERE IS A NEW ARRIVAL AT
THE SMITHSONIAN'S NATIONAL
ZOO IN WASHINGTON.
A BABY PANDA BORN JUST A
COUPLE OF HOURS AGO.
NOT SO GIANT RIGHT NOW BUT
A BIG BOOST FOR AN
ENDANGERED SPECIES.
THERE IS WORD THE FEDS ARE
CONSIDERING SOME CHANGES IN
THE WAKE OF YESTERDAY'S
COMPUTER GLITCH AT THE
NASDAQ.
NEXT A PREVIEW OF THE
POSSIBLE FALLOUT OVER THE
FLASH FREEZE.
PLUS, ONE WOMAN REPORTEDLY
STRUCK A DEAL AFTER RACKING
UP MORE THAN $100,000 IN
PARKING TICKETS.
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR HOW
MUCH SHE WILL HAVE TO PAY
AND WHO IS BLAMING FOR THE
WHOLE NECESSARY.
-- MESS.
Reinforced with scratch-  resistant
glass
and a unibody  Made Kevlar Strong.
Okay Google Now.  Call My Droid.
The new  Droid Ultra by Motorola.
When strength matters,  Droid Does.
HOW DO YOU DO A SUMMER    CLEARANCE
EVENT THE DODGE WAY?    FIRST WAIT
TILL SUMMER.
THEN GET THE CARS READY.
NOW ADD THE DODGE PART.
♪ ♪
THE DODGE SUMMER    CLEARANCE EVENT.
RIGHT NOW GET 0% FINANCING FOR
TO 72 MONTHS
AND NO PAYMENTS FOR 90 DAYS ON
ALL DODGE VEHICLES.
FEMALE NARRATOR:
The mattress
price wars are on
at Sleep Train. We challenged the
manufacturers to offer even lower
prices.
Now it's Posturepedic versus Beautyrest
with big savings of up to $400 off.
Serta iComfort and Tempur-Pedic
go head-to-head
with three years' interest-free financing.
Plus, free same-day delivery, set-up
and removal of your old set.
When brands compete, you save.
Mattress Price Wars are on now at
Sleep Train.
♪ Your ticket to a better night's
sleep ♪
WHAT GLICH.
THE FREEZE AT THE NASDAQ.
STOCKS ROD FOR A SECOND
STRAIGHT DAY GIVING YOUR
401(K) A BOOST.
THE DOW GAINED 47 POINTS.
NASDAQ UP 19.
THE S&P ADDED 7.
MEANWHILE THE HEAD OF THE
SECURITIES AND EXCHANGE
COMMISSION SAYS THE FEDS
WILL PUSH FOR NEW TRADING
RULES.
DESIGNED TO ENHANCE
SAFEGUARDS.
SOME ANALYSTS SAY THAT
BASICALLY MEANS MORE
REGULATION.
THE FOX BUSINESS NETWORK
RICH EDSON WITH THE NEWS
LIVE IN WASHINGTON.
RICH, WHAT KIND OF REACTION
CAN WE EXPECT OUT OF D.C.?
>> JON REGULATORS AND
CONGRESSIONAL STAFF SAY
THEY ARE STILL EXAMINING
THE INCIDENT.
NASDAQ'S FREEZE REINFORCES
WASHINGTON'S NEED TO FOCUS
ORK RELIABILITY AND
CYBER SECURITY.
>> THAT'S GOING TO
HIGHLIGHT SOME OF THE
ISSUES THAT KEEP COMING UP
WHICH AS YOU KNOW WE ADOPT
MORE TECHNOLOGY TO
INTEGRATE INTO OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE, WE ARE
GOING TO HAVE TO THINK MORE
ABOUT WHAT ARE THE
VULNERABILITIES AND WHERE
DO THEY COME FROM?
>> AND THE SEC SAYS
OFFICIALS WANT TO MEET WITH
EXCHANGE AND MARKETING
EXECUTIVES ABOUT THIS, JON.
>> WHAT MORE DO WE KNOW
ABOUT THE GLITCH?
>> DESPITE CONCERNS HACKERS
INFILTRATED THE EXCHANGE.
NASDAQ SAYS THERE IS NO
EVIDENCE OF A INTRUDER ON
COMPUTER NETWORK OR OF A
LARGE COORDINATED ATTACK.
NASDAQ SIMPLY BLAMES A
TECHNICAL PROBLEM.
JON?
>> Jon: RICH YESTERDAY'S
GLITCH JUST THE LATEST
EMBARRASSMENT FOR THE
NASDAQ.
A FEW MONTHS AGO IT AGREED
TO PAY THE LARGEST PENALTY
EVERY AGAINST THE STOCK
EXCHANGE $10 MILLION TO
SETTLE CHARGES OVER HOW IT
HANDLED TRADING AND
GLITCHES WHEN FACEBOOK WENT
PUBLIC.
THOSE GLITCHES AMONG OTHER
THINGS TANKED FACEBOOK'S
STOCK PRICES BUT THE SOCIAL
NETWORK APPARENTLY HAS
BOUNCED BACK AND THEN SOME.
TODAY, IT CLOSED ABOVE $40
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
TWO BUCKS A SHARE MORE THAN
ITS INITIAL PRICE.
AND CHECK OUT THIS CHART
SHOWING THE PAST THREE
MONTHS, PRICES UP MORE THAN
50% SINCE JULY.
THE MAN WHO TOOK OVER FOR
BILL GATES TOP EXECUTIVE AT
MICROSOFT IS STEPPING DOWN.
STEVE BALMER HAS BEEN CEO
OF THE WORLD'S LARGEST
COMPANY SINCE 2000.
HE ANNOUNCED TODAY HE WILL
RETIRE SOMETIME OVER THE
NEXT YEAR ONCE MICROSOFT
FINDS A REPLACEMENT.
IN A STATEMENT HE SAID
THERE IS NEVER A PERFECT
TIME FOR THIS TYPE OF
TRANSITION BUT NOW IS THE
RIGHT TIME.
MICROSOFT HAS STRUGGLED
UNDER HIS WATCH.
THE COMPANY'S WORTH DIPPED
FROM A REPORTED 600 BILLION
TO LESS THAN 300 BILLION.
NOW TO THE CASE OF THE
WOMAN FACING $100,000 IN
PARKING TICKETS.
THAT'S 678 TICKETS TOTAL
LING CHICAGO'S BIGGEST
PARKING TICKET BILL EVER
ACCORDING TO THE CHICAGO
TRIBUNE.
THE NEWSPAPER REPORTS THE
WOMAN BLAMES HER
EX-BOYFRIEND AS THE STORY
GOES:  SHE SAYS HE PUT A
CAR IN HER NAME AND LEFT IT
IN A PARKING LOT AT O'HARE
AIRPORT FOR THREE YEARS.
THE WOMAN REPORTEDLY HAS
NOW STRUCK A DEAL WITH THE
CITY AND HER EX.
SHE WILL PAY JUST LESS THAN
$4,500.
DISCOUNT OF MORE THAN
95,000.
THE EX HAS ALSO REPORTEDLY
AGREED TO PAY SOME OF IT
COUNTRY MUSIC STAR CARRIE
UNDERWOOD IS SET TO PLAY
MARIA VON TRAP UPCOMING
PRODUCTION.
JULIE ANDREWS MADE THE FILM
FAMOUS.
NOW WE HAVE LEARNED WHO IS
SET TO PLAY THE ROLE
CHRISTOPHER PLUMMER HAD AS
CAPTAIN VON TRAP.
HERE IS A HINT.
THE GUY IS KIND OF A
VAMPIRE.
THAT'S NEXT.
♪ WHISKERS ON KITTENS.
♪ BRIGHT COPPER KETTLES
♪ AND WARM WOOLEN MITTENS.
HEY, IT'S ME  PROGRESSIVE INSURANCE.
YOU KNOW, FROM OUR 4,000  TELEVISION
COMMERCIALS.
YEP, THERE I AM WITH FLO.
HOO-HOO! WATCH IT!
[Chuckles] ANYHOO, 3 MILLION  PEOPLE
SWITCHED TO ME LAST YEAR,
SAVING AN AVERAGE  OF $475.
[Sigh] IT FEELS GOOD  TO HELP PEOPLE
SAVE...
WITH GREAT DISCOUNTS LIKE  SAFE DRIVER,
MULTICAR,
AND MULTIPOLICY.
SO CALL ME TODAY.  YOU'LL BE GLAD
YOU DID.
CANNONBOX!
[SPLASH!]
EVERY DAY WE'RE WORKING TO  BE AN
EVEN BETTER COMPANY -  AND TO KEEP
OUR COMMITMENTS.
AND WE'VE MADE A BIG  COMMITMENT TO
AMERICA.
BP SUPPORTS NEARLY  250,000 JOBS HERE.
THROUGH ALL OF OUR  ENERGY OPERATIONS,
WE INVEST MORE IN THE U.S. THAN  ANY
OTHER PLACE IN THE WORLD.
IN FACT, WE'VE INVESTED  OVER $55
BILLION HERE
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS -
MAKING BP AMERICA'S  LARGEST ENERGY
INVESTOR.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS  NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
Max and Penny kept our bookstoreexciting
and would always me  to my rescue.
But as time passed, I stted to  notice
Max just wasn't himself.
And I knew he'd feel better if  heost
a little weight.
So I switched to Purina Cat ow  Healthy
Weight formula.
I just fed the recommended  amount...
And they both loved the taste.
After a few months Max's  "speal powers"
returned...
And I got my hero back.
Purina Cat Chow Healthy Weight.
♪ ♪    [ Male Announcer ]    STAYING
WARM AND DRY    HAS NEVER BEEN OUR
PRIORITY.  ♪ ♪    CATERING TO    THE
CONVENIENTLY LATED    HAS NEVER BEEN
OUR PRIORITY.    OUR PRIORITY IS,
WAS    AND ALWAYS WILL BE    SERVING
YOU,    THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.    WE
GET TO SEE EVERYONE    IN AMERICA
ALMOST EVERY DAY.    AND WE'VE NOTICED
THAT YOU'RE    SENDING AND RECEIVING
MORE PACKAGES THAN EVER.    SO WE
WANTED TO GIVE YOU    A MORE RELIABLE
WAY    TO SHIP THEM.    WITH IMPROVED
PRIORITY MAIL    FLAT RATE.    DON'T
JUST TAKE OUR WORD    FOR IT --
NOW WE'LL PROVE IT    EVERY STEP OF
THE WAY    WITH TRACKING    UP TO
ELEVEN SCANS    SPECIFIED DELIVERY
DATES,    AND FREE INSURANCE UP TO
$50    ALL FOR THE SAME LOW RATE.
WE'LL NEVER STOP DELIVERING    FOR
EVERY PERSON    IN THIS COUNTRY.
[ Woman ] WE ARE THE  UNITED STATES
POSTAL SERVICE.  [ Man ] WE ARE THE
UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.  [ Woman
#2 ] WE ARE THE  UNITED STATES POSTAL
SERVICE.    [ Male Announcer ] WE
ARE THE    UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.
AND OUR PRIORITY IS YOU.    GO TO
USPS.COM®    AND TRY IT TODAY.
>> Jon: THE MAN WHO GAVE
THE WORLD ARE A GO AGELE IS
THE NOTRE DAME NEXT BAT
MAP.
BEN AFFLECK WILL PLAY THE
DARK NIGHT BRINGING BATMAN
AND SUPERMAN TOGETHER.
THAT DECISION NOT SITTING
WELL WITH FANS.
MORE THAN 17,000 PEOPLE
HAVE SIGNED ONLINE PETITION
TO REMOVE THE ACTOR FROM
THE ROLE.
IT'S NOT AFFLECK'S FIRST
ATTEMPT IT AT SUPER HERO.
STARTED DARE DEVIL.
CRITICS PANNED IT.
EVEN HE AGREED IT WAS A
TERRIBLE MOVIE.
NBC IS TACKLING THE SOUND
OF MUSIC AND LISTEN TO THIS
CASTING.
TRUE BLOOD STAR STEPHAN
MOYER WILL PLAY OPPOSITE
KERRY UNDERWOOD HE WILL
PORTRAY WORLD WAR I HERO
VON TRAP AND CARRIE
UNDERWOOD.
BEST PICTURE IN 1965.
ACCORDING TO THE PRODUCERS
THIS WILL NOT BE A REMAKE
OF THE MOVIE BUT LIVE
PERFORMANCE THAT THEY WILL
BROADCAST FROM A SOUND
STAGE.
BASED ON THE ORIGINAL
195 TONY AWARD WINNING
BROADWAY PRODUCTION AND IS
SET TO PREMIER
DECEMBER 5TH.
UPDATING SOME OF OUR TOP
STORIES TONIGHT.
A MILITARY JURY REACHED A
UNANIMOUS GUILTY VERDICT
FOR ARMY MAJOR NIDAL HASAN
ON ALL 13 COUNTS OF
PREMEDITATED MURDER IN THE
FORT HOOD MASSACRE.
THAT MAKES HIM NOW ELIGIBLE
FOR THE DEATH PENALTY.
ANOTHER MILITARY JURY HAS
SENTENCED U.S. ARMY STAFF
SERGEANT ROBERT BALES TO
LIFE IN PRISON WITHOUT
PAROLE.
BALES PLEADED GUILTY IN
JUNE TO THE BRUTAL MURDERS
OF 16 AFGHAN CIVILIANS
LITTLE MORE THAN AN HOUR
AGO BOB FILNER AGREED TO
STEP DOWN EFFECTIVE
AUGUST 30TH.
>> NOT ONE ALLEGATION
MEMBERS OF THE COUNCIL HAS
EVER INDEPENDENTLY BEEN
VERIFIED OR PROVEN IN
COURT.
I HAVE NEVER SEXUALLY
HARASSED ANYONE.
BUT THE HYSTERIA THAT HAS
BEEN CREATED, AND MANY OF
YOU HELPED DEFEAT IS THE
HYSTERIA OF A LYNCH MOB.
>> Jon: FILNER BOWED TO
ENORMOUS PRESSURE FOLLOWING
SEX ALLEGATIONS BY 16
DIFFERENT WOMEN.
HE WAS JUST NINE MONTHS
INTO THE JOB.
AND ON THIS DAY IN 1973
THE HOSTAGE STANDOFF THAT
SPAWNED THE TERM STOCKHOLM
SYNDROME BEGAN.
THAT'S WHEN TWO MEN
ATTEMPTED TO ROB A BANK IN
STOCKHOLM, SWEDEN.
IT TURNED INTO IS SIX DAY
ORDEAL AND AT THE END OF IT
HOSTAGES REFUSED TO TODAY
AGAINST CAPTORS.
THEY USED THE TERM
STOCKHOLM SYNDROME WHICH
DESCRIBES THE WHEN HOSTAGES
IDENTIFY WITH HEIR CAPTORS.
BEST KNOWN EXAMPLE OF THAT
WAS PATTY HURST WHO JOINED
HER KIDNAPPERS IN A SERIES
OF BANK ROBBERIES.
BUT THE SYNDROME GOT ITS
CITY 40 YEARS AGO TODAY.
AND THAT'S "THE FOX REPORT"
FOR FRIDAY, AUGUST 23RD U
2013.
I'M JON SCOTT IN TONIGHT
FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
SEE YOU AGAIN ON MONDAY.
THE FACTOR IS UP NEXT.
♪
>> THE O'REILLY FACTOR IS
ON TONIGHT.
>> I MADE THIS ARGUMENT TO
MY REPUBLICAN FRIENDS
PRIVATELY AND BY THE WAY
SOMETIMES THEY SAY TO ME
PRIVATELY I AGREE WITH BUT I'M
WORRIED ABOUT A PRIMARY FOR
SOMEBODY IN THE TEA PARTY.
>> Scott: PRESIDENT OBAMA
AT IT AGAIN, BLAMING THE
TEA PARTY FOR THE TROUBLES
IN D.C.
BUT CAN HE STILL SELL THAT
TIRED TALLY TO THE TALE TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE THE
FACTOR WILL INVESTIGATE.
>> DON'T GET CONFUSED ABOUT
MY WAY OF LIFE.
IT'S GANGSTER MILITANT.
I LEAVE A FEDERAL BUILDING
BENT.
>> Scott: WHO IS BEHIND
THIS VIAL WEB SITE IN THE
ARMED REVOLUTION IN THE
KILLING OF WHITE