TAG DAILY BRIEFING ON INSTAGRAM
OR POST ON FACEBOOK.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I'M DANA PERINO.
HERE'S SHEPARD SMITH.
>> Shepard: IT'S 3:00 ON THE
EAST COAST.
NOON IN LAS VEGAS.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE REVEALED
STUNNING NEWS ABOUT THE CONCERT
KILLER.
FROM HIS APPARENT ESCAPE PLAN
AND HIS INTEREST IN OTHER MUSIC
FESTIVALS TO HIS MYSTERIOUS
PAST.
>> STEPHEN PADDOCK IS A MAN THAT
SPENT DECADES ACQUIRING WEAPONS
AND AMMO AND LIVING A SECRET
LIFE.
MUCH OF WHICH WILL NEVER BE
FULLY UNDERSTOOD.
>> INVESTIGATORS ARE WORKING TO
UNRAVEL HIS STORY AND WHETHER HE
HAD HELP.
WE'RE ALSO HEARING ABOUT THE
FIRE DEPARTMENT'S FIRST
RESPONDERS THAT RISKED THEIR
LIVES TO SAVE CIVILIANS ON THE
NIGHT OF THE SHOOTING.
POLICE WITHIN THE LAST HOUR, THE
WHITE HOUSE WEIGHING IN ON A
CONTROVERSIAL GUN DEVICE WHICH
MAY HAVE HELPED THE VEGAS
SHOOTER CARRY OUT HIS MADNESS.
LET'S GET TO IT.
AND FIRST FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK
THIS THURSDAY AFTERNOON, THE
WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT'S OPEN TO
THE IDEA OF REGULATING BUMP
STOCKS.
THOSE ARE THE DEVICES THAT THE
SHOOTER IN LAS VEGAS APPARENTLY
USED TO ALLOW HIS RIFLES TO FIRE
MUCH LIKE AUTOMATIC WEAPONS.
IT COMES JUST AFTER THE NATIONAL
RIFLE ASSOCIATION CALLED ON THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT TO REVIEW
WHETHER BUMP STOCKS COMPLY WITH
THE LAW.
IN A STATEMENT LEADERS OF THE
GUN RIGHTS GROUP WROTE "THE NRA
BELIEVES THAT DEVICES DESIGNED
TO ALLOW SEMIAUTOMATIC RIFLES TO
FUNCTION LIKE FULLY AUTOMATIC
RIFLES SHOULD BE SUBJECT TO
ADDITIONAL REGULATIONS."
MORE AHEAD ON THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S RESPONSE TO THE
MASSACRE IN VEGAS.
WE'RE LEARNING THE GUNMAN MAY
HAVE HAD OTHER TARGETS IN MIND.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM THE
INVESTIGATORS.
THEY SAY STEPHEN PADDOCK RENTED
ROOMS OVERLOOKING TWO OTHER
MUSIC FESTIVALS.
ONE IN LAS VEGAS THE WEEKEND
BEFORE THIS SHOOTING AND ANOTHER
IN LAST AUGUST IN CHICAGO DURING
THE LOLLAPALOOZA MUSIC FESTIVAL.
THERE'S REPORTS THAT PADDOCK
SCOUTED OUT HOTELS IN FENWAY
PARK IN BOSTON AND WE'RE
LEARNING HE MIGHT HAVE PLANNED
TO ESCAPE AFTER THE VEGAS
ATTACK.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO THE SHERIFF
WHO DIDN'T GIVE ANY OTHER
DETAILS.
POLICE SAY THE GUNMAN KILLED
HIMSELF IN HIS HOTEL ROOM AS
SWAT UNITS CLOSED IN.
HE KILLED 58 PEOPLE AND INJURED
HUNDREDS MORE AT THE COUNTRY
MUSIC FESTIVAL ACROSS THE
STREET.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY'RE STILL
STRUGGLING WHY HE DID THIS.
FBI AGENTS QUESTIONED THE
GUNMAN'S GIRLFRIEND YESTERDAY.
HER LAWYER SAYS SHE HAD NO IDEA
WHAT STEPHEN PADDOCK WAS
PLANNING WHEN HE SENT HER TO THE
PHILIPPINES TO BE WITH HER
FAMILY.
SHE SAID WHEN HE SENT HER
$100,000 AND TOLD HER TO BUY A
HOUSE, SHE THOUGHT HE WAS
BREAKING UP WITH HER.
WE HAVE TEAM FOX COVERAGE.
LET'S BEGIN WITH KEVIN CORKE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
KEVIN?
>> THE WHITE HOUSE CONTINUES TO
MAINTAIN A LASER-LIKE FOCUS ON
THE HEALING AND THE AFTER MATH
OF THE DEVASTATION IN NEVADA BUT
THAT DOESN'T TAKE AWAY FROM THE
FACT THAT THERE'S QUESTIONS,
ESPECIALLY ABOUT AS WHAT YOU
JUST LAID OUT, THE BUMP STOCK
THAT WAS USED IN THIS ASSAULT ON
SO MANY INNOCENT LIVES IN THE
NEVADA DESERT.
WE HEARD FROM SARAH SANDERS NOT
LONG AGO.
SHE SAID THIS AS FAR AS THE
ADMINISTRATION'S VIEW OF A
POSSIBLE BAN.
>> OUR FOCUS, AS WE SAID THE
LAST COUPLE DAYS, HAS BEEN ON
HEALING AND UNITING THE COUNTRY.
THE INVESTIGATION STILL
CONTINUES TO BE IN VERY EARLY
STAGES.
WE KNOW THAT BOTH MEMBERS OF
BOTH PARTIES IN MULTIPLE
ORGANIZATIONS ARE PLANNING TO
TAKE A LOOK AT BUMP STOCKS AND
RELATED DEVICES.
WE WELCOME THAT.
>> GOT TO DO IT.
HAVE TO TAKE A VERY CLOSE LOOK
AT IT.
WE'LL SEE HOW QUICKLY
CONGRESSIONAL LAWMAKERS CAN
UNPACK SOMETHING LIKE THAT,
SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: KEVIN, THE WHITE
HOUSE WEIGHING IN ON THE REPORT
THAT SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON THREATENED TO RESIGN
AND CALLED THE PRESIDENT A
MORON.
THE REPORTING IS FROM CARROLL
LEE FROM NBC NEWS.
AT A CONFERENCE YESTERDAY,
SECRETARY TILLERSON NEVER
CONSIDERED QUITTING BUT HE
DIDN'T DEFLY HE CALLED THE
PRESIDENT A MORON.
HE DENY IT A FEW HOURS LATER
THROUGH A SPOKESMAN.
HERE'S THE EXCHANGE.
>> WAS THE PRESIDENT UPSET THAT
HIS SECRETARY OF STATE DIDN'T
DENY CALLING HIM A MORON IN HIS
PUBLIC REMARKS YESTERDAY?
>> AS THE SECRETARY STATE SAID,
THIS IS A PETTY RIDICULOUS
ACCUSATION.
FRANKLY I THINK IT'S BENEATH THE
SECRETARY OF STATE TO WEIGH-IN
ON EVERY RUMOR OUT THERE.
HIS SPOKESPERSON, HOWEVER, DID
COME OUT
AND CLARIFY THAT THE
SECRETARY OF STATE HAS NEVER
USED THOSE WORDS.
>> Shepard: BACK TO KEVIN CORKE
AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
KEVIN, CAROL LEE IS A
WELL-RESPECTED JOURNALIST THAT
SAYS SHE HAS MORE THAN TEN
SOURCES ON THE MATTER BUT THE
PUSH-BACK IS STRONG.
>> HERE'S MORE OF WHAT SARAH
SANDERS HAD TO SAY ABOUT THE
PRESIDENT'S ACCUSATION THAT THIS
IS ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF FAKE NEWS.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS A GREAT
FRUSTRATION WITH THE FACT THAT A
LOT OF TIMES YOU HAVE INACCURATE
INFORMATION THAT IS BEING
PRESENTED AS FACTUAL.
A LOT OF TIMES OPINIONS ARE
BEING PRESENTED AS NEWS AND
THEY'RE NOT.
THAT IS A REAL CONCERN AND
SOMETHING THAT SHOULD BE LOOKED
AT.
>> HAVE TO BE CAREFUL ON THIS IF
YOU'RE SARAH SANDERS.
YOU NEVER KNOW WHAT CAN ALSO
COME OUT OF THE CONVERSATION
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT A
REPORTER OF THE ESTEEM OF CAROL
LEE.
>> Shepard: THE WHITE HOUSE
WALKING BACK COMMENTS FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE TOLD FOX NEWS HE MIGHT HAVE
TO WIPE OUT PUERTO RICO'S TENS
OF MILLIONS IN DEBT TO HELP
RECOVER FROM HURRICANE MARIA.
BUT MAYBE NOT.
KEVIN CORKE IS AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
I DON'T KNOW.
THERE'S CONFUSION ON THIS.
>> YEAH, THERE'S CONFUSION.
AS IS OFTEN THE CASE, THE
PRESIDENT WILL MAKE A COMMENT,
BUT IT'S SORT OF OFF THE CUFF.
DOES IT EQUAL POLICY?
HERE AGAIN IS SARAH SANDERS ON
TRYING TO MAKE MOST SENSE, IF
SHE CAN, OUT OF WHAT THE
PRESIDENT SAID PREVIOUSLY.
>> RIGHT NOW, THE PRIMARY FOCUS
IS TO PROVIDE RELIEF TO PUERTO
RICO AND SUPPORT IN THE
REBUILDING EFFORTS.
WHILE WE'RE STILL DEALING WITH
THE IMMEDIATE DISASTER, IT ISN'T
INAPPROPRIATE TO FOCUS ON THE
DIFFICULTIES THAT PUERTO RICO
WAS DEALING WITH BEFORE THE
STORM.
THERE'S A PROCESS FOR HOW TO
DEAL WITH PUERTO RICO'S DEBT.
IT WILL HAVE TO GO THROUGH THAT
PROCESS TO HAVE A LASTING
RECOVERY AND GROWTH.
THIS IS A PROCESS THAT WAS PUT
IN PLACE AND SET UP UNDER OBAMA.
THAT HAS A BOARD OF ADVISERS
THAT DEALS WITH THAT DEBT AND IT
WILL GO THROUGH THAT PROCESS.
>> I'VE BEEN WATCHING THE BACK
AND FORTH ON THIS, SHEPARD,
BLAKE BURMAN IN PARTICULAR.
SEEMS THE PRESIDENT MADE A
STATEMENT THAT HAD TO BE WALKED
BACK.
MAYBE HIS PRAISE FOR WHAT COULD
HAPPEN DOESN'T LINE UP WITH
WHERE THE DOLLARS MAY END UP.
SHEPARD?
>> KEVIN CORKE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
"THE WASHINGTON POST" IS
REPORTING THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
PLANS TO ANNOUNCE NEXT WEEK THAT
HE WILL DE-CERTIFY THE
INTERNATIONAL NUCLEAR DEAL WITH
IRAN.
>> "THE WASHINGTON POST" SAYS HE
WILL WALK AWAY FROM IT.
BUT IT'S MORE COMPLICATED.
THERE'S THIS REVIEW THAT WAS SET
UP BY LAW BY SENATORS CORKER AND
CARDIN.
CLEARLY WHAT THEY WANT TO DO IS
MAKE SURE CONGRESS HAS A HAND IN
THIS, SHEPARD.
SO WHILE HE MAY DECIDE TO
DE-CERTI
DE-CERTIFY, DOESN'T MEAN THAT
THE UNITED STATES IS NOT A PART.
>> Shepard: LET'S GO TO ANNA
PALMER FROM POLITCO.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> Shepard: A LOT TO GET TO
HERE.
THIS TILLERSON THING, YOU WONDER
UNDER ANY CIRCUMSTANCES
SPECIFICALLY ABOUT THIS, A
MATTER THAT IS NOT IN QUESTION
BY ANYBODY.
WHEN TILLERSON IS NEGOTIATING
MATTERS REGARDING NORTH KOREA,
THE PRESIDENT TWEETS DON'T
BOTHER.
WE'RE GOING TO DO WHAT HAS TO BE
DONE.
HOW CAN YOU CONTINUE -- I DON'T
UNDERSTAND IT.
>> I THINK WHAT WE SAW THIS WEEK
IS KIND OF HOW THIS RELATIONSHIP
AND THIS DANCE BETWEEN REX
TILLERSON AND THE PRESIDENT HAS
BEEN EVOLVING OVER THE PAST
SEVERAL WEEKS IF NOT MONTHS.
YOU KNOW, I THINK ONE OF THE BIG
QUESTIONS IS DOES THE PRESIDENT
HAVE CONFIDENCE --
>> Shepard: HE SAYS HE DOES.
>> HE HAS SAID HE DOES.
THE QUESTION IS, RESULT ALSO
DIDN'T WALK BACK TO THE FACT
THAT HE CALLED THE PRESIDENT A
MORON OR NOT.
ONE OF THE BIG ISSUES WITH THIS
PRESS CONFERENCE, HE WAS TRYING
TO SAY LOOK, I'M ON THE AMERICA
FIRST AGENDA.
I HAVE AMERICA'S BACK.
IT WAS NOT ONLY A MESSAGE TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP BUT A MESSAGE TO
THESE COUNTRIES THAT I HAVE TO
DEAL WITH ON A DAILY BASIS.
>> Shepard: WHAT DO WE MAKE OF
THE IRAN TALK.
IF YOU BACK OUT OF THE DEAL,
IT'S NOT LIKE YOU CAN COME UP
WITH A NEW DEAL.
YOU HAD TO GET THESE COUNTRIES
TOGETHER ON THIS THING.
WITHOUT THIS DEAL, WHERE ARE WE?
>> I THINK WHAT WE'RE SEEING --
PRESIDENT TRUMP WHEN HE WAS ON
THE CAMPAIGN TRAIL RAILED AT THE
DEAL OF BEING BAD.
SO THEY'RE TRYING TO THREAD THE
NEEDLE SAYING THEY WANT TO PULL
OUT OF IT.
IT'S A PROCESS.
SO YOU KNOW, IT DOESN'T THROW
THE WHOLE DEAL AND THE WORLD
INTO CHAOS.
HE'S TRYING TO HAVE IT BOTH
WAYS.
>> Shepard: I READ HE MIGHT BE
TRYING TO KNOCK IT DOWN A PEG
AND THEN LIFT IT BACK UP AGAIN.
IN OTHER WORDS, TAKE CREDIT FOR
FIXING SOMETHING.
>> RIGHT.
MY COLLEAGUE WROTE ABOUT THIS A
COUPLE DAYS AGO.
BASICALLY SAYING EXACTLY THAT.
HE WANTS TO HAVE THIS PUBLIC
STATEMENT THAT GOES VERY
AGGRESSIVELY BUT ABLE TO COBBLE
TOGETHER SOMETHING WITH CONGRESS
TO COME BACK AND SAY, LOOK,
WE'RE NOT GOING TO PULL OUT OF
IT.
>> Shepard: WHAT IS THE STORY
FOR AID WITH PUERTO RICO?
IS THIS A TEST OF THE WINDS ON
THIS MATTER OR IS IT A TRIAL
BALLOON?
I DON'T UNDERSTAND WHAT IS
HAPPENING THERE EITHER.
>> LISTEN, CONGRESS AND THE
PRESIDENT SAID THEY'RE GOING TO
HAVE THE MONEY THEY NEED WHEN
THEY NEED IT.
SO FAR CONGRESS HAS HAD THE
MONEY FOR TEXAS AND THE
DIFFERENT HURRICANES THIS YEAR
AND THE FLOOD INSURANCE PROGRAM.
SO I THINK THE MONEY WILL BE
THERE, BUT AS FAR AS WHAT WILL
HAPPEN WITH THE PUERTO RICAN
DEBT, CLEARLY THE PRESIDENT GOT
AHEAD ON WIPING THAT AWAY.
THE ACTUAL PROCESS IS, YOU CAN'T
JUST WIPE IT AWAY.
>> Shepard: THE VICE PRESIDENT
IS AT J.B.A., JOINT BASE
ANDREWS.
USED TO BE ANDREWS AIR FORCE
BASE.
THIS IS WHERE VICE PRESIDENTS GO
BEFORE THEY HEAD OFF PLACES.
HE'S GOING DOWN TO ORLANDO AND
TOUR SOME OF THE HURRICANE
DAMAGE DOWN THERE.
THE FUNDING OF THESE DISASTERS
IS GOING TO BE A REAL LONG-TERM
CHALLENGE.
THE PRESIDENT TALKING ABOUT
CUTTING TAXES ACROSS THE BOARD,
DEPENDING WHO YOU BELIEVE,
ADDING A TRILLION DOLLARS TO THE
DEBT OVER TIME.
NOW YOU HAVE TENS OF BILLIONS IN
TEXAS AND TENS OF BILLIONS IN
FLORIDA AND MAYBE MORE THAN THAT
IN PUERTO RICO.
IT'S DAUNTING.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I THINK THIS IS GOING TO BE ON
THE SCALE OF -- KATRINA IS WHAT
PEOPLE ARE TALKING ABOUT AND HOW
THEY JUDGE THAT.
IT'S SO EXPENSIVE.
YOU SEE SOME OF THE CONSERVATIVE
WING ON THE REPUBLICAN HOUSE
SIDE SAYING HOW ARE WE GOING TO
PAY FOR THIS?
ARE WE GOING TO KEEP WRITING
THESE CHECKS AND NOT ACTUALLY
BALANCE THE BUDGET?
AS YOU CONTINUE TO HAVE FUNDING
AND THE NEED CONTINUES AND THE
WEEKS AND MONTHS AS IT GOES
FORWARD, YOU'LL START HAVING
CONSERVATIVE -- START TO ASK THE
QUESTION, WHERE IS THIS MONEY
COMING FROM, HOW ARE WE GOING TO
GET TO A TAX CUT SITUATION, A
TAX PACKAGE IF WE'RE CONTINUING
TO WRITE THESE CHECKS.
>> SO MOVEMENT NOT ON GUN
CONTROL, BUT ON REGULATING
OUTSIDE DEVICES.
SOME CONSERVATIVES AND
REPUBLICANS HAVE COME OUT IN
FAVOR OF TAKING A LOOK AT BUMP
STOCKS.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT I
PERSONALLY NEVER HEARD OF BEFORE
THIS.
AND NOW THE NRA SAYING YEAH, YOU
OUGHT TO LOOK AT IT.
IS THERE AN APPETITE FOR REAL
GUN CONTROL?
WE KNOW THIS PRESIDENT WAS AT
ONE POINT A NEW YORK LIBERAL.
YOU WINDER IF HE WON'T MIGRATE
IN THAT DIRECTION.
>> THIS IS THE ONE AREA AT BEST
THAT YOU'LL FIND IF YOU'RE FOR
GUN CONTROL OR GUN CONTROL OF
THIS TYPE THAT YOU'LL FIND ANY
KIND OF COALESCING OF PEOPLE
SUPPORTING IT.
YOU'RE NOT SEEING ANYTHING ON
HIGH CAPACITY MAGAZINES.
THE NRA EVEN SAYING THIS IS
SOMETHING THAT SHOULD BE LOOKED
AT.
CERTAINLY -- I'VE COVERED SOME
OF THESE TRAGEDIES A LONG TIME.
THIS IS AS MUCH COALESCING
AROUND ONE PROACTIVE THING THAT
THEY COULD DO IN LEGISLATION
THAT WILL HAPPEN.
YOU HAVE TO REMEMBER 2018
ELECTION YEAR, A LOT OF
DEMOCRATS THAT DON'T WANT THIS
TO BE AN ELECTION YEAR ISSUE.
JOE MANCHIN, HEIDI HEIDCAMP,
THAT'S NOT WHAT THEY WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
>> Shepard: OKAY.
AHEAD, WHY INVESTIGATORS SAY THE
KILLER IN LAS VEGAS MAY HAVE HAD
HELP.
THAT'S COMING UP FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK ON A THURSDAY
AFTERNOON.
GLAD TO HAVE YOU IN.
This woman is laughing
because she's listening
to a hilarious
audiobook on Audible.
And this woman is laughing
because she's pretending
her boss's terrible
story is funny.
Still actually laughing.
No longer making
a human noise.
Experience the comedy,
not your commute.
Dial STAR-STAR-Audible on
your smartphone
to start listening today.
If you're not content
to remain where you are,
why should your teeth be?
Invisalign clear aligners
can shape your smile
up to 50% faster.
Don't let anything slow
you down.
Visit Invisalign.com
Remember that accident I got in
with the pole, and I
had to make a claim
and all that?
Is that whole thing
still dragging on?
No, I took some pics
with the app and...
filed a claim, but...
You know how they send you
money to cover repairs and...
They took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid
right away, but...
at the very end of
it all, my agent...
Wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy.
But if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience
for any reason,
they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim Satisfaction
Guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> Shepard: WE'RE HEARING FROM
FIRST RESPONDERS THAT RUSHED
INTO HARM'S WAY AND FIRED INTO A
CROWD OF 22,000 PEOPLE.
THEY SPOKE ABOUT THE CHALLENGES
THEY FACE.
TRACE GALLAGHER ONCE AGAIN FROM
LAS VEGAS NOT FAR FROM WHERE THE
SHOOTING HAPPENED.
TRACE?
>> SHEP, THERE WAS A GROUP OF
FIREFIGHTERS THAT WAS HANDLING A
CAR NEAR MANDALAY BAY BEFORE
THIS STARTED.
THEY WERE ON THE SCENE WITHIN
FIVE SECONDS.
THEY'RE SAYING WITHIN A FEW
MINUTES, THERE WAS MORE THAN 100
FIREFIGHTERS ON SCENE TO HEAR
THEIR PERSPECTIVE IS FRIGHTENING
AND VERY FASCINATING.
THEY WERE WORKING THIS WHOLE
TRIAGE SETUP UNDER FIRE.
KIND OF LIKE A BATTLEFIELD.
AT ONE POINT IN TIME, THE RADIO
TRAFFIC WAS SO JUMBLED THAT THE
FIREFIGHTERS DIDN'T REALLY KNOW
WHERE THE SHOOTING WAS COMING
FROM.
THEY THOUGHT THEY WERE WORKING
WITH MULTIPLE SHOOTERS.
THEN THEY SAID THE FEEL OF
VICTIMS WAS ALMOST A MILE LONG.
LISTEN TO THIS.
>> THEY WERE LAYING IN BETWEEN
THE RUNWAYS, TRYING TO TAKE
COVER.
THE AREAS ARE CARVED OUT BETWEEN
THE RUNWAYS AND THE TAXIWAYS.
THEN WE HAD REPORTS OF GUN SHOTS
AT THE AIRPORT.
ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF WE HAD A LOT
ON OUR HANDS.
A LOT WE THOUGHT WAS ESCALATING
WHEN IT WAS REALLY CONTAINED BUT
WE DIDN'T KNOW BECAUSE OF SO
MANY CALLS COMING IN.
>> WHEN HE SAID ON THE RUNWAY OF
McCARRAN AIRPORT, HE'S TALKING
ABOUT A MILE FROM WHERE WE ARE
RIGHT NOW.
THEY PUSHED DOWN THE FENCES AND
RAN TO GET AWAY AND ENDED UP
BETWEEN THE RUNWAYS AND THE
TAXIWAYS.
IT'S PHENOMENAL.
THE FIREFIGHTERS SAID THEY HAD
REHEARSED, TRAINING FOR THIS
SCENARIO FOR MANY YEARS BECAUSE
THEY'RE A HIGH TARGET
DESTINATION.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: NOTHING SPECIFIC,
TRACE, ON WHAT APPEARS TO BE
OTHER POSSIBLE TARGETS?
>> WELL, WE HAVE DEFINITELY
CONFIRMED THAT STEPHEN PADDOCK
DID BOOK A HOTEL ROOM IN CHICAGO
OVERLOOKING GRANT PARK IN AUGUST
DURING THE LOLLAPALOOZA CONCERT
THAT MALIA OBAMA WAS IN
ATTENDANCE THERE.
THE BLACKSTONE HOTEL RELEASED A
STATEMENT.
IT SAYS "ON BEHALF OF THE
BLACKSTONE, WE CAN CONFIRM THERE
WAS NO GUEST UNDER THE NAME WHO
STAYED AT OUR HOTEL IN AUGUST
DURING THE LOLLAPALOOZA MUSIC
FESTIVAL.
WE CAN CONFIRM A RESERVATION WAS
MADE UNDER THE NAME OF STEPHEN
PADDOCK.
HOWEVER, AUTHORITIES HAVE NOT
CONFIRMED THAT THIS IS THE SAME
PERSON AS THE LAS VEGAS SHOOTER.
WE'RE COOPERATING WITH THE
AUTHORITIES ON THAT MATTER."
NOW THE CHICAGO POLICE HAVE IN
FACT CONFIRMED THIS IS THE VERY
SAME STEPHEN PADDOCK THAT DID
BOOK THAT HOTEL AT THE
BLACKSTONE OVERLOOKING
LOLLAPALOOZA.
WE SHOULD ALSO NOTE THAT HE
BOOKED A HOTEL ROOM AT THE
MANDALAY BAY AND ANOTHER CONCERT
CALLED LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL BY
CHANCE THE RAPPER.
SO WE SHOULD ALSO POINT OUT ON
THE REPORTS OF THE AVIATION FUEL
TANKS, WE JUST MENTIONED
McCARRON AIRPORT, THE AVIATION
FUEL TANKS WERE HIT BE SOME
BULLETS.
THE LAS VEGAS REVIEW JOURNAL
SAID HE WAS TARGETING IT.
WE DON'T HAVE ENOUGH INFORMATION
TO CONFIRM THAT WE DON'T HAVE
ENOUGH TO RULE IT OUT.
THE BULLETS DID HIT THE TANK.
WERE THEY BULLETS THAT WERE
BEING RANDOMLY FIRED?
POSSIBLE.
WAS IT TARGETED?
ALSO POSSIBLE.
THE SHERIFF LAST NIGHT IN THIS
ASTOUNDING NEWS CONFERENCE MADE
MENTION OF A POTENTIAL
ACCOMPLICE.
HE BELIEVES THAT STEPHEN PADDOCK
DID HAVE AN ACCOMPLICE.
OTHERWISE, IT WOULD BE A SUPER
HUMAN EFFORT TO PULL OFF WHAT HE
DID ALONE.
THERE ARE MULTIPLE REPORTS
SAYING IN THE DAYS LEADING UP TO
THIS ATTACK AT THE MANDALAY BAY
HOTEL WHERE HE WAS GAMBLING FOR
HOURS AND HOURS, HE WAS WITH A
WOMAN THAT WAS NOT HIS
GIRLFRIEND AND NOW POLICE ARE
INTERESTED TO FIND OUT WHO
EXACTLY THAT WOMAN WAS WITH HIM
IN THOSE DAYS LEADING UP TO IT,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: LOTS OF GREAT
INFORMATION, TRACE.
TRACE GALLAGHER ON SCENE.
THANKS AGAIN.
A LOT WE STILL DON'T KNOW ABOUT
THE LAS VEGAS GUNMAN, STEPHEN
PADDOCK.
AHEAD WE'LL TALK WITH A FORMER
FBI INVESTIGATOR ABOUT THE
QUESTIONS HE SAYS THAT
INVESTIGATORS NEED TO GET
ANSWERED.
♪
When food is good
and clean and real,
it's ok to crave.
And with Panera catering,
there's more to go around.
Panera.
Food as it should be.
that just tastes better.
So fresh from the farm.
Delicious.
Perfect.
Only one egg
with more great nutrition-
now with 5 times
more vitamin D,
10 times more vitamin E,
and 25% less saturated fat.
Only one egg good enough
for my family.
Because why have ordinary
when you can have the best.
Eggland's Best.
The only egg that
gives you so much more:
Better taste.
Better nutrition.
Better eggs.
>> THE NUMBER 2 OFFICIAL IN THE
ANYBODY SAYS HE'S SURPRISED THAT
INVESTIGATORS HAVE NOT LEARNED
MORE YET ABOUT WHAT DROVE
STEPHEN PADDOCK TO COMMIT MASS
MURDER.
ANDREW McCABE SAID WE HAVE A LOT
OF WORK TO DO.
WHAT IS MISSING?
WHAT ARE THE BIG MISSES PIECES?
>> THERE'S NO EASY BOX TO PUT
PADDOCK IN.
IF AN ATTACK HAPPENS, IT'S AN
ISLAMIC ATTACK OR RACIALLY
MOTIVATED ATTACK.
PADDOCK DIDN'T HIT ANY OF THOSE
TRIP WIRES.
THE INVESTIGATORS HAVE TO DIG
DEEP AND FIGURING OUT WHAT HIS
MOTIVATION WAS, WHAT CAUSED HIM
TO DO WHAT HE DID.
>> Shepard: WE KNOW HE'S A
MILLIONAIRE REAL ESTATE
INVESTOR.
HE GAMBLED A LOT.
IF HE BLEW ALL OF HIS MONEY
GAMBLING THEY WOULD KNOW THAT BY
NOW, WOULDN'T THEY?
>> AND THEY SHOULD.
THAT'S WHAT THE INVESTIGATION
WILL GO.
IT WILL GO INTO HIS FINANCIAL
BACKGROUND, GOES INTO ANYBODY HE
CONTACTED.
THEY NEED TO GO BACK TO THE
FIRST WIFE, THE SECOND WIFE,
PEOPLE HE WORKED WITH.
HE SEEMED TO HAVE VARIOUS
DIFFERENT JOBS, ALL GOOD JOBS,
BUT DIFFERENT AGENCIES AND
DIFFERENT JOBS.
THEY SHOULD GO BACK TO THOSE
CO-WORKERS AND BOSSES TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT MADE THIS GUY TICK.
>> Shepard: THERE WAS A NOTE.
WE DON'T KNOW MUCH ABOUT IT.
>> WE DON'T.
I THINK THE LAS VEGAS
METROPOLITAN POLICE HAVE THAT
NOTE AND THEY'RE NOT GIVING UP
ANYTHING ON IT.
>> Shepard: I WONDER IF THEY
HAVE -- POLICE CAN WITHHOLD
WHATEVER THEY WANT IN THE COURSE
OF AN INVESTIGATION.
IF THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE THEY
NEED TO GET TO, THEY CAN
WITHHOLD INFORMATION.
I WONDER IF THEY DON'T KNOW
ABOUT MOTIVE THAN WHAT WE'RE
HEARI
HEARING?
>> AND THEY MAY.
IN AN INVESTIGATION, YOU DON'T
WANT TO TIP YOUR HAT.
INVESTIGATORS ARE GOING TO HOLD
THE INFORMATION THEY HAVE TO
FURTHER THEIR INVESTIGATION
WITHOUT TIPPING THEIR HAND OR
LETTING PEOPLE KNOW THAT I MAY
BECOME A SUBJECT OF AN
INVESTIGATION.
IT DOESN'T DO ANY GOOD.
>> Shepard: IS THIS IDEA THAT HE
WAS WITH A WOMAN GAMBLING BEFORE
COMMITTING THIS ATTACK SOMEONE
WHO HASN'T COME FORWARD, MUST
REALIZE WOW, THIS IS THE GUY I
WAS WITH THAT NIGHT, YOU HAVE TO
HAVE QUESTIONS FOR WHOEVER THAT
IS.
>> THAT'S ANOTHER QUESTION.
IN THE COURSE OF THE
INVESTIGATION, THEY NEED TO TALK
TO THAT WOMAN.
I DON'T KNOW ANYTHING MORE.
I JUST HEARD ABOUT IT WHEN YOU
SAID IT.
THAT'S SOMETHING THAT CAN TELL
US HOW OR WHAT PADDOCK WAS
FEELING.
THAT'S ALL PART OF THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> Shepard: THERE'S ALWAYS A
REASON, RIGHT?
I DON'T REMEMBER A MATT ATTACK
WHERE IN THE END NO ONE CAN
FIGURE OUT WHY THEY DID IT.
MAY NOT BE A REASONABLE REASON
BUT THERE IS USUALLY A REASON.
>> RIGHT.
YEAH, ALWAYS A REASON.
IT MAY BE ONE THAT NOBODY CAN
AGREE WITH.
PERSON MAY BE CRAZY.
SOME OF THE THINGS YOU SAID,
MAYBE HIS FINANCIAL SITUATION
TURNED BAD.
MAYBE THE FACT THAT HE HAD BEEN
PURCHASING 33 WEAPONS OVER THE
COURSE OF A YEAR.
HE MAY HAVE BEEN PLANNING THIS
AS FAR AS A YEAR AND DIDN'T HIT
ANY TRIP WIRES.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JEFFERY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS
IT'S TIME FOR THE SENATE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE TO MOVE
ON AFTER THE TOP REPUBLICAN SAYS
THEY'RE STILL LOOKING INTO THE
POSSIBILITY OF COLLUSION BETWEEN
MOSCOW AND THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
THAT'S COMING UP.
>> Shepard: HEADLINES FROM THE
FOX NEWS DECK.
U.S. OFFICIALS SAY MILITANTS
LINKED TO AL-QUAIDA ARE LIKELY
TO BLAME FOR AN AMBUSH THAT
KILLED THREE GREEN BERETS AND
WOUNDED TWO OTHERS IN AFRICA.
IT HAPPENED IN NIGER.
ACCORDING TO THE PENTAGON, U.S.
SPECIAL FORCES ARE WILL TRAINING
AND SUPPORTING THE LOCAL
MILITARY IN THEIR FIGHT AGAINST
EXTREMISTS.
TRACES OF VX, THE DEADLIEST
NERVE AGENT WERE FOUND ON THE
CLOTHES OF WOMEN SUSPECTED OF
ASSASSINATING KIM JONG-UN'S HALF
BROTHER.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO A CHEMIST
THAT TESTIFIED AT THEIR TRIAL.
THE WOMEN COMPLAINED AGENTS
TRICKED THEM THEY WERE THINKING
THEY WERE PLAYING PART IN A
HIDDEN CAMERA PRANK AT A
MALAYSIAN AIRPORT.
ONE DROP OF VX IS ENOUGH TO KILL
YOU, A SPANISH COURT ATTEMPTING
TO BLOCK CATALONIA FROM
DECLARING INDEPENDENCE.
LAWMAKERS IN THE NORTHEASTERN
REGION OF SPAIN ARE THREATENING
TO BREAKAWAY NEXT WEEK.
THERE'S BEEN MASSIVE PROTESTS
AND FIGHT WITH POLICE IN SPAIN.
THE NEWS CONTINUES NEXT.
I was always
"the girl with psoriasis."
People don't stare anymore.
I never joined in.
That wasn't fair to any of us.
I was covered.
I tried lots of things
over the years.
But I didn't give up.
I kept on fighting.
I found something that worked.
That still works.
Now?
SEE ME.
I found clear skin that lasts.
See if COSENTYX could make a
difference for you-
COSENTYX is proven to help
people with moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis...
...find clear skin that
can last.
Don't use if you're allergic
to COSENTYX.
Before starting COSENTYX,
you should be checked
for tuberculosis.
An increased risk of infections
and lowered ability
to fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection or symptoms.
Or if you have received a
vaccine or plan to.
If you have inflammatory
bowel disease,
tell your doctor if symptoms
develop or worsen.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
SEE ME
to know...
...clear skin can last.
Don't hold back...
...ask your dermatologist if
COSENTYX can help you
find clear skin that lasts.
Mom,on my car insurance of money
by switching to GEICO.
I should take a closer
look at GEICO...
You know, GEICO can help you
save money
on your homeowners
insurance too?
Great! GEICO can help insure
our mountain chalet!
How long have we been sawing
this log?
Um, one hundred
and fourteen years.
Man I thought my arm would
be a lot more jacked by now.
I'm not even sure
this is real wood.
There's no butter in this churn.
Do my tris look okay?
Take a closer look at GEICO.
Great savings.
And a whole lot more.
>> Shepard: THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS FRUSTRATED
THAT THE INVESTIGATION INTO
POSSIBLE COLLUSION BETWEEN
MEMBERS OF THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
AND THE RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT IS
STILL GOING ON.
>> IT'S LITERALLY FOUND ZERO
EVIDENCE OF COLLUSION BETWEEN
THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND RUSSIA.
I THINK THAT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
WOULD LIKE THEM TO FOCUS ON SOME
OTHER THINGS.
I KNOW THAT WE CERTAINLY HAVE
SAID THIS ALL ALONG AND WE'RE
GLAD THAT AS THEY CONTINUE THIS
PROCESS THEY'RE COMING TO THE
SAME CONCLUSION.
>> Shepard: THEY HAVEN'T COME TO
THAT CONCLUSION.
THIS COMES AFTER THE REPUBLICAN
CHAIRMAN OF THE SENATE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE SAID THE
POSSIBILITY OF COLLUSION BETWEEN
RUSSIA AND THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN IS
STILL OPEN.
IN OTHER WORDS, NO CONCLUSION.
SEVERAL CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEES
AND SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT
MUELLER ARE LOOKING INTO THE
MEDDLING INTO THE ELECTION BY
RUSSIA AND TIES TO TEAM TRUMP.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE IS LIVE IN
WASHINGTON.
CATHERINE, THE COMMITTEE IS
ASKING FOR MORE DOCUMENTS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE SENATE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE ASKED FOR RECORDS
DOCUMENTING COMMUNICATIONS OR
CONTACT WITH RUSSIANS GOING BACK
SEVEN YEARS, TRAVEL TO RUSSIA,
CAMPAIGNS, E-MAILS OR TEXTS.
A LETTER SENT UNDER THE
SIGNATURE OF THE SENATE
COMMITTEE'S REPUBLICAN CHAIRMAN
CALLS FOR THE PRESERVATION OF
RECORDS, TO INCLUDE NO EDITING,
DELETION, SHREDDING OR
MIGRATION.
>> THE INQUIRY HAS EXPANDED
SLIGHTLY.
INITIAL INTERVIEWS AND DOCUMENT
REVIEW GENERATED HUNDREDS OF
ADDITIONAL REQUESTS ON OUR PART
FOR INFORMATION.
IT IDENTIFIED MANY LEADS THAT
EXPANDED OUR INITIAL INQUIRY.
>> A ONE-TIME FOREIGN POLICY
ADVISER CARTER PAGE SAID THE
REQUEST MOUNTED TO A FISHING
EXPEDITION.
HE SAID THERE'S SOME LEVEL OF
FALSE TESTIMONY.
THE COMMITTEE HAS GIVEN PAGE
UNTIL OCTOBER 18 TO COMPLY.
>> Shepard: WHAT DO WE KNOW
ABOUT THIS REPORT THAT RUSSIAN
HACKERS STOLE SENSITIVE
INFORMATION FROM AN NSA
CONTRACTOR?
>> WE HAVE HAD A STATEMENT FROM
BEN SASSE ON THIS REPORTING THAT
WAS FIRST DONE BY THE "WALL
STREET JOURNAL."
THE SENATOR ACCUSED THE NSA OF
PUTTING THEIR HEAD IN THE SAND
OVER CONTRACTING PROBLEMS.
SAYING THE NSA NEEDS TO GET
THEIR HAND OUT OF THE SAND AND
SOLVE THE CONTRACTOR PROBLEM.
WE CAN'T AFFORD THESE
SELF-INFLICTED INJURIES.
WHAT WE KNOW INDEPENDENTLY
THROUGH OUR OWN REPORTING IS
THAT THERE REMAINS VERY DEEP
CONCERN ABOUT THE CONSPIRACY
SOFTWARE AND THAT IT CAN BE
EXPLOITED BY RUSSIAN AFFILIATED
OR RUSSIAN BACKED HACKERS.
WE HAVE LINES OUT TO THE NSA FOR
COMMENTING BY THE REPORTING THAT
HACKERS WORKING FOR THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT STOLE DETAILS ABOUT
THE U.S. CYBER TACTICS INCLUDING
HOW WE GET INSIDE FOREIGN
COMPUTER NETWORKS AND DEFEND
AGAINST CYBER ATTACKS.
THE CLASSIFIED MATERIAL
ACCORDING TO THE "WALL STREET
JOURNAL" WAS REMOVED AND PLACED
ON A CONTRACTOR'S HOME COMPUTER.
THAT IS A MAJOR VIOLATION THERE.
AND THAT COMPUTER USED THIS
CONSPIRACY ANTI-VIRUS SOFTWARE.
LAST MONTH YOU PROBABLY REMEMBER
THE ACTING SECRETARY OF HOPE
LAND SECRETARY ELAINE DUKE GAVE
AGENCIES TO WIPE CONSPIRACY
SOFTWARE FROM THEIR SYSTEMS.
OFFICIALS HAVE NOT DISCUSSED THE
EVIDENCE.
THE ORDER SHOWS THE EVIDENCE WAS
DEEMED CREDIBLE AND SIGNIFICANT.
CURRENT AND FORMER GOVERNMENT
OFFICIALS TOLD FOX NEWS THE REAL
CONCERN IS THAT CONSPIRACY
EXECUTIVES HAVE TIES TO THE
RUSSIAN MILITARY AND THE
INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES.
THOUGH THE COMPANY DENIES THOSE
CONNECTIONS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: SO THEY STOLE SPY
TOOLS.
THAT'S NOT A NEW THING.
>> IF YOU THINK BACK IN THE LAST
SIX MONTHS, WE HAD A SIMILAR
SITUATION WITH THE CIA AND THEIR
CYBER TOOLS INVOLVING
CONTRACTORS.
WHAT I WOULD SAY IS THAT THESE
ARE SERIOUS SITUATIONS BUT TO A
CERTAIN EXTENT, YOU NEED TO
THINK ABOUT THE CYBER TOOLS.
LIKE WHEN YOU BUY MILK AT THE
STORE.
THEY HAVE A BEST BUY DATE.
THE LIFETIME IS TYPICALLY 12 TO
18 MONTHS.
WHEN YOU HAVE A BREACH OR A
THEFT, PART OF THE FEELING IN
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY IS
THEY'RE GOING TO EXPIRE IN THE
SHORT TO MEDIUM TERM.
BUT THE BREACH OF TAKING IT HOME
IS AVOIDABLE AND SELF-INFLICTED.
>> THANKS CATHERINE HERRIDGE.
TOM, THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
THERE'S ONE PERSON THAT SAYS
THIS IS FAKE NEWS, AND THAT'S
THE PRESIDENT.
THE RUSSIANS MEDDLED WITH OUR
ELECTION IS NOT A MATTER THAT IS
IN DISPUTE.
WHAT ARE THEY CONTINUING TO DO
AND WHAT WILL THEY DO NEXT?
DO WE HAVE AN IDEA ABOUT WHAT IS
HAPPENING?
>> IT'S FASCINATING.
YOU LOOK AT THAT PRESS
CONFERENCE YESTERDAY WITH
SENATORS BURR AND WARNER.
THERE'S TWO DIRECTIONS.
IT'S LOOKING BACK AT WHAT
HAPPENED IN THE CAMPAIGN AND
TRYING TO DECIDE WHETHER THERE
WAS SOME COLLUSION.
THAT IS AN OPEN QUESTION RIGHT
NOW.
IT'S ALSO LOOKING FORWARD.
RIGHT?
WE'RE AT THE PRECIPICE OF
ANOTHER CAMPAIGN HERE, THE 2018
MID-TERMS.
SO THIS IS -- IT'S A HUGE
EXPANSIVE INVESTIGATION GOING ON
RIGHT NOW.
MULTIPLE PROBES GOING ON.
YOU KNOW, EVERY TIME YOU GET
FACEBOOK COMES OUT, REVEALS ADS.
EVERY ONE OF THOSE THINGS OFFERS
MORE FOR THEM TO LOOK INTO.
THAT'S WHAT BURR AND WARNER SAID
YESTERDAY.
THEY'RE EXPANDING SLIGHTLY.
>> Shepard: IT'S ONE THING BURR
AROUND WARNER.
THERE'S A BIGGER THING GOING ON
AND THAT IS MUELLER.
WHATEVER MUELLER IS DOING, IT'S
NOT LEAKING.
HE HAS AN ARMY OF PROSECUTORS.
IT'S VERY CLEAR THE DIRECTION
HE'S GOING IN, ISN'T IT?
>> YEAH.
BASED ON EVERYTHING WE KNOW AND
WE'VE SEEN, THERE'S AN INTENSE
INTEREST ON FINANCIAL
STATEMENTS, FINANCIAL
INVESTIGATIONS.
THOSE ARE THE EXPERTS THAT HE'S
BROUGHT ON AS YOU POINT OUT.
IT'S A PRETTY LOCK DOWN
INVESTIGATION.
A CREDIT TO THEM THERE.
THERE'S NO LEAKING IN THIS TOWN
AT LEAST.
>> Shepard: THEY'RE FOLLOWING
THE MONEY.
>> EXACTLY.
YOU KNOW, THAT'S REALLY THE BIG
ONE.
LIKE THESE CONGRESSIONAL PROBES
ARE GOING TO FIND THINGS.
IT'S A WEIRD DYNAMIC.
ON ONE HAND, WE KIND OF RELY ON
THE CONGRESSIONAL PROBES
PUBLICLY TO FIND OUT WHAT IS
GOING ON.
THAT'S REALLY YOUR BEST CHANCE
AT FINDING SOMETHING.
THERE'S AN ASSUMPTION AND A
PRETTY GOOD POSSIBILITY IF
MUELLER TURNS UP NOTHING THAT WE
DON'T SEE ANYTHING.
AS A STANDARD PRACTICE IN THE
JUSTICE COMMUNITY.
>> Shepard: IT APPEAR WHAT'S
MULER IS GOING AFTER IS
FINANCIAL TRANSACTION.
WHETHER MONEY CHANGED HANDS
BETWEEN ONE PARTY AND ANOTHER,
IF IT DID, WHAT THAT TRANSFER OF
MONEY WAS ABOUT.
WHAT SERVICES WERE RENDERED.
IS THAT FAIR?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THAT IS BASED ON THE EXPERTS
THEY HAVE HIRED ON THAT TEAM,
ABSOLUTELY.
THAT SEEMS TO BE WHERE IT IS
RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE HEADING INTO A PRECARIOUS
MOMENT FOR THE WHITE HOUSE.
THEY'RE STARTING TO BRING IN
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS, CURRENT
AND FORMER OFFICIALS FOR
INTERVIEWS WITH MUELLER'S TEAM.
YOU KNOW, THIS IS -- IT'S WHEN
IT GETS REAL.
LOOK BACK TO THE PRESIDENT'S
TWEET EARLIER TODAY WHERE HE
SAYS, WHY ISN'T THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE INVESTIGATING FAKE
NEWS?
HE TENDS TO REACT TO WHAT IS
HAPPENING.
HERE THIS IS LAPPING AT HIS DOOR
STEP, LAPPING AT THE FRONT OF
THE OVAL OFFICE, THIS IS GETTING
SERIOUS.
>> Shepard: THINGS THAT DON'T
MAKE SENSE.
IF YOU HAVE DONE NOTHING AND YOU
WONDER IF PEOPLE AROUND YOU
HAVE, THINGS THAT ARE AS ILLEGAL
AS CONSPIRING WITH ANOTHER
GOVERNMENT TO CHANGE THE COURSE
OF HUMAN EVENTS IN OUR NATION, I
MEAN YOU WOULD THINK WHAT YOU
WOULD DO IS OPEN THE DOOR AND
SAY PLEASE, COME FIND OUT
ANYTHING THAT WENT WRONG.
THAT'S NOT WHAT THIS WHITE HOUSE
IS DOING.
>> REMEMBER, THERE'S A GREAT
REPORTING BY KEN VOGEL, "THE NEW
YORK TIMES."
INCREDIBLE SIT-DOWN NEXT TO TY
COBB AND JOHN DOWD, THAT'S A
FIGHT INSIDE THE LEGAL TEAM.
YOU HAVE DON McGANN, THE WHITE
HOUSE COUNSEL.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO SET A
PRECEDENT OF TURNING OVER THINGS
YOU DON'T HAVE TO.
THE FLIP SIDE IS TY COBB, THE
PRESIDENT'S PERSONAL COUNSEL
THAT SAYS NO, WE SHOULD BE
TOTALLY COOPERATIVE AND TRY TO
GET AS MUCH TO THEM AS POSSIBLE.
NOTHING HAPPENED IS WHAT THEY
SAY.
THEREFORE THIS SHOULD BE OVER
SOON.
BUT THE FLIP SIDE OF THAT, AS
YOU POINT OUT, THIS IS A SPECIAL
COUNSEL INVESTIGATION.
THIS COULD GO ANY NUMBER OF
DIRECTIONS.
>> Shepard: TOM LOBIANCO, NICE
TO SEE YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> THANKS.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
TAX PLAN PASSING MAJOR HURDLE
TODAY.
THE HOUSE OF REPRESENTATIVES
APPROVED A BUDGET FRAME WORK
THAT GIVES SENATE REPUBLICANS
THE POWER TO PASS A TAX BILL
WITH 50 VOTES INSTEAD OF THE 60
YOU NORMALLY NEED.
THEY ALSO HAVE THE POWER TO PASS
A HEALTHCARE BILL BUT DIDN'T
MANAGE TO GET IT DONE.
OUR SEASON CAPITOL HILL
PRODUCER, CHAD PERGRAM REPORTS
IF THE HOUSE HAD NOT APPROVED
THIS BUDGET FRAME WORK, THE
REPUBLICAN TAX PLAN PROBABLY
WOULD HAVE BEEN DEAD LIKE
IMMEDIATELY.
MIKE EMANUEL HAS MORE.
ARE THEY OPTIMISTIC UP THERE
NOW, MIKE?
>> YEAH, THEY SEEM MORE HOPEFUL.
IF YOU NEEDED 60 YES VOTES IN
ORDER TO DO TAX REFORM, THAT
WOULD HAVE GIVEN DEMOCRATS
TREMENDOUS LEVERAGE.
YOU ONLY HAVE 52 REPUBLICANS.
SO BOTTOM LINE, THEY WANTED TO
PASS THIS BUDGET FRAME WORK WITH
THE TAX REFORM LANGUAGE IN IT IN
ORDER TO GET THAT DONE.
THAT WAS A POINT THE HOUSE
SPEAKER MADE ON THE HOUSE FLOOR
EARLIER TODAY.
>> THERE'S ONE MORE THING THAT
THIS BUDGET DOES THAT IS SO
IMPORTANT.
IT PAVES THE WAY FOR HISTORIC
TAX REFORM.
UNLOCKS THE RECONCILIATION
PROCESS.
WE NEED TO PASS THIS BUDGET SO
THAT WE CAN DELIVER REAL RELIEF
FOR MIDDLE INCOME FAMILIES.
>> MITCH McCONNELL IS SELLING
THIS AS A ONCE IN A GENERATION
OPPORTUNITY TO FIX A BROKEN TAX
CODE.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: WHAT ARE DEMOCRATS
SAYING ABOUT THE BUDGET FRAME
WORK PASSING?
>> TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE HOUSE
BUDGET COMMITTEE IS BLASTING IT.
HE SAYS THIS IS NOT ABOUT
DELIVERING CONSERVATIVE
PRINCIPLES IN TERMS OF CUTTING
DEFICITS AND DEBT.
HE SAYS THIS IS ABOUT USING
SENATE RULES TO RAM THROUGH
GIANT TAX GIVE AWAY TO THE
WEALTHY AND CORPORATIONS.
THE HOUSE DEMOCRATIC LEADER
RIPPED IT AS WELL.
>> THIS IS REALLY -- I USE THIS
WORDS FROM TIME TO TIME AND SO
APPROPRIATE -- PATHETIC.
THIS BUDGET THAT THEY'RE PUTTING
FORTH COMBINED WITH THEIR TAX
PROPOSAL WILL ADD AROUND $2.4,
NEARLY $2.5 TRILLION TO THE
NATIONAL DEBT.
>> ALL HOUSE DEMOCRATS AND 18
HOUSE REPUBLICANS VOTED AGAINST
IT.
IT STILL HAD ENOUGH VOTES TO
PASS.
SHEP?
>> MIKE EMANUEL LIVE AT THE
ROTUNDA.
THANKS A LOT.
THE U.S. IS BRACING FOR ANOTHER
POTENTIAL HURRICANE THIS
WEEKEND.
RIGHT NOW IT'S A TROPICAL STORM.
THE NAME IS NATE HEADED INTO THE
GULF AND GENERALLY, AS YOU CAN
SEE THERE, GENERALLY TOWARDS
LOUISIANA, SOUTH MISSISSIPPI,
LOWER ALABAMA.
FORECASTERS SAY IT COULD GAIN
SOME STRENGTH.
DON'T EXPECT A MONSTER
CATEGORY FIVE.
NOTHING LIKE THAT.
BUT RAIN, OH, THE RAIN IS
COMING.
Prudential asked these couples:
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
WE'RE ON A MISSION TO
SHOW DRIP COFFEE DRINKERS,
IT'S TIME TO WAKE UP TO KEURIG.
WAKEY! WAKEY! RISE AND SHINE!
OH MY GOSH!
HOW ARE YOU?
WELL WATCH THIS.
I POP THAT IN THERE.
PRESS BREW.
THAT'S IT.
LOOK HOW MUCH
COFFEE'S IN HERE?
FRESH COFFEE.
SO RICH.
I LOVE IT.
THAT'S WHY YOU SHOULD
BE A KEURIG MAN!
FULL-BODIED.
ARE YOU SURE YOU'RE DESCRIBING
THE COFFEE AND NOT ME?
DO YOU WEAR THIS EVERY DAY?
EVERYDAY.
I'D NEVER TAKE IT OFF.
ARE YOU READY TO
SAY GOODBYE TO IT?
GO! GO!
TA DA! A TERRARIUM.
THAT'S IT.
WE BREWED THE LOVE, RIGHT GUYS?
(ALL) YES.
Thisto a hilarioushing
WE Bbaudiobook on Audible.gUYS?
And this woman is laughing
because she's pretending
her boss's terrible
story is funny.
Still actually laughing.
No longer making
a human noise.
Experience the comedy,
not your commute.
Dial STAR-STAR-Audible on
your smartphone
to start listening today.
>> Shepard: WEEKS AFTER MAJOR
STORMS CAUSED SO MUCH
DESTRUCTION IN TEXAS, FLORIDA
AND PUERTO RICO AND BEYOND, THE
GULF COAST IS BRACING FOR
ANOTHER POSSIBLE HURRICANE.
TROPICAL STORM NATE IS MAKING
ITS WAY TO THE GULF OF MEXICO.
FORECASTERS SAY IT COULD
STRENGTHEN AND MAKE LANDFALL AS
A HURRICANE THIS WEEKEND.
AS YOU CAN SEE, THE CONE OF
UNCERTAINTY ANYWHERE FROM
EASTERN LOUISIANA ALL OF SOUTH
MISSISSIPPI AND PARTS OF LOWER
ALABAMA.
EVEN INTO THE FLORIDA PANHANDLE.
LET'S GO TO RICK REICHMUTH.
WHAT DO YOU THINK?
>> RIGHT NOW CENTRAL AMERICA IS
TAKING A WALLOP FROM THIS.
A LOT OF MOISTURE AND
MOUNTAINOUS TERRAIN ACROSS HERE.
BECAUSE OF THAT, WE'LL SEE SOME
SIGNIFICANT FLOODING.
THE CENTER OF THIS IS OVER LAND
RIGHT NOW.
NO STRENGTHENING GOING.
IT WILL MOVE BACK OUT
ACROSS
PARTS OF THE WESTERN CARIBBEAN
AND MAKE A SECOND LANDFALL
BEFORE GETTING BACK TO THE GULF.
THAT'S WHERE WE'LL SEE MORE
STRENGTHENING.
SHORT TERM, SHEPARD, A LOT OF
MOISTURE FOR CENTRAL AMERICA.
SOME SPOTS,20 INCHES.
THAT WILL CAUSE LANDSLIDES AND
LOCAL FLOODING HERE.
>> RICK, WHAT SHOULD PEOPLE
ACROSS THE GULF BE PREPARED FOR
NOW?
>> SO A LOT OF OUR MODELS ARE
KEEPING THIS KIND OF A STRONG
TROPICAL STORM.
A COUPLE OF MODELS GETTING IT
TOWARDS HURRICANE STRENGTH.
NONE OF THE MODELS MAKING THIS A
MAJOR HURRICANE, WHICH IS A VERY
IMPORTANT THING TO NOTE.
OCTOBER, STILL AN ACTIVE TIME,
ESPECIALLY FOR THE GULF AND THE
CARIBBEAN.
WE'RE GOING TO SEE RAIN HERE.
BUT IT'S MOVING SO FAST, THE
RAINFALL TOTALS WILL BE KEPT
DOWN A LITTLE BIT.
PROBABLY 4 TO 8 INCHES RANGE.
IT WILL CAUSE SOME FLOODING.
THE BIGGER QUESTION IS WHEN DO
WE GET GOING ONCE IT'S BACK OUT
OVER THE GULF.
THE GULF IS PLENTY WARM AT THIS
TIME.
THERE'S LIKELY WIND SHEAR TO
BREAK THIS THING APART.
THE TWO MODELS WE RELY ON MOST,
GOOD AGREEMENT HERE, SOMEWHERE
AROUND LOUISIANA, MAYBE OVER
TOWARDS MISSISSIPPI OR THE
ALABAMA COASTLINE.
BECAUSE OF THAT, OUR CONE IS
ACTUALLY NARROW AT THIS POINT.
A LOT OF THE MODELLING PRETTY
GOOD AGREEMENT.
WHETHER WE GET TO THE HURRICANE
STATUS OR NOT REMAINS TO BE
SEEN.
WE'LL HAVE A STRONG TROPICAL
STORM HERE ACROSS PARTS OF THE
GULF.
THAT'S SATURDAY NIGHT INTO
SUNDAY.
WEEKEND A BAD WEEKEND.
WE'LL SEE THE LOCALIZED FLOODING
THERE AND AVOID ANY KIND OF A
MAJOR HURRICANE FROM THIS ONE,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: HOPE SO.
THANKS, RICK.
WE'RE LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
LAS VEGAS GUNMAN'S GIRLFRIEND.
HER LAWYER SPEAKING NOW AFTER
HOURS OF FBI QUESTIONING.
WE'LL HAVE THAT NEXT.
>> Shepard: THE GIRLFRIEND OF
THE GUNMAN THAT KILLED 58
PEOPLE
IN LAS VEGAS THIS WEEK SAYS SHE
HAD NO IDEA THAT HE WAS PLANNING
THE MASSACRE.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO HER
ATTORNEY.
THE LAWYER READ A STATEMENT TO A
CROWD OUTSIDE FBI HEAD QUARTERS
IN L.A. AFTER AGENTS QUESTIONED
HER FOR HOURS.
HER NAME IS MARILOU DANLEY.
SHE SAID THE KILLER SENT HER TO
THE PHILIPPINES WHERE SHE HAD
FAMILY AND SHE WAS OUT OF THE
COUNTRY FOR MORE THAN TWO WEEKS.
WILLIAM LA JEUNESSE IN THE WEST
COAST NEWS HUB THIS AFTERNOON.
WILLIAM?
>> INVESTIGATORS HOPED THAT
DANLEY WOULD TELL US WHY.
A QUIET MILLIONAIRE WOULD
SUDDENLY SHOOT 58 PEOPLE.
SHE DIDN'T.
SHE SAID THAT PADDOCK SENT HER A
CHEAP TICKET AND SENT HER TO THE
PHILIPPINES AS A GIFT.
AS FOR THE $100,000 THAT
FOLLOWED, SHE THOUGHT IT WAS
GOOD-BYE MONEY THAT PADDOCK WAS
ENDING THEIR RELATIONSHIP.
AT NO TIME DID SHE KNOW WHAT HE
WAS GOING TO DO HERE'S DANLEY'S
ATTORNEY READING HER STATEMENT.
>> I KNEW STEPHEN PADDOCK AS A
KIND, CARING, QUIET MAN.
HE NEVER SAID ANYTHING TO ME OR
TOOK ANY ACTION THAT I WAS AWARE
OF THAT I UNDERSTOOD IN ANY WAY
TO BE A WARNING THAT SOMETHING
HORRIBLE LIKE THIS WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> STILL DANLEY'S HELP REMAINS
CRUCIAL IN REBUILDING HIS LIFE,
MENTAL HEALTH, WHAT HE BOUGHT
AND WHEN HE BOUGHT IT.
ANOTHER POSSIBLE LEAD THAT THE
FBI HAS SAID THEY HAVE NOT HAD A
PROBLEM ACCESSING PADDOCK'S
ELECTRONIC FILES, COMPUTER AND
PHONE THAT COULD CORROBORATE HER
STORY.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU, WILLIAM.
THE UNLV FOOTBALL PLAYERS WILL
BE WEARING A SPECIAL HELMET TO
HONOR THE VICTIMS OF THE
SHOOTING.
THE SCHOOL TWEETED THIS PHOTO.
THE PLAYERS TO WEAR THIS HELMET
THIS SATURDAY AND THROUGH THE
END OF THE SEASON.
THE CAMPUS FROM UNLV IS A FEW
MILES FROM THE SHOOTING.
UNLV ANNOUNCED THAT SATURDAY
NIGHT'S GAME AGAINST SAN DIEGO
STATE WILL BE CALLED HERO'S
NIGHT.
THE PREGAME CEREMONY IS TO HONOR
THE VICTIMS AND FIRST RESPONDERS
OF THE DAY.
WE'LL BE BACK WITH A LOOK AT
WHEN THE WORLD'S MOST FAMOUS
SECRET AGENT FIRST SHOWED UP ON
THE BIG SCREEN.
IT HAPPENED ON THIS DAY IN
HISTORY.
(Bell ringing)
So, I was at Mom and Dad's
and found this.
CDs, baseball cards.
Your old magic set?
(Sigh)
And this wrestling ticket.
Which you still owe me for.
Seriously? $25?
I didn't even want to go.
Ahh, your diary!
"Mom says it is
totally natural..."
$25 is nothing.
(Alert beep)
Abracadabra, bro.
Settle up with your friends
on October 17th
with the Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
If you have moderate to severe
Ulcerative Colitis or Crohn's,
and your symptoms have left you
with the same view,
it may be time for a different
perspective.
If other treatments haven't
worked well enough,
ask your doctor about ENTYVIO,
the only biologic developed
and approved
just for UC and Crohn's.
ENTYVIO works by focusing right
in the GI-tract
to help control damaging
inflammation
and is clinically proven to
begin helping many patients
achieve both symptom relief as
well as remission.
Infusion and serious allergic
reactions
can happen during or after
treatment.
ENTYVIO may increase risk of
infection,
which can be serious.
While not reported with ENTYVIO,
PML, a rare,
serious brain infection caused
by a virus may be possible.
Tell your doctor if you have
an infection,
experience frequent infections,
or have flu-like symptoms,
or sores.
Liver problems can occur
with ENTYVIO.
If your UC or Crohn's medication
isn't working for you,
ask your gastroenterologist
about ENTYVIO.
ENTYVIO. Relief and remission
within reach.
It's OK
that everybody
ignores me
when I drive.
It's fine, 'cause I get
a Safe Driving Bonus Check
every six months
I'm accident-free.
And I don't share it
with Mom. Right, Mom?
Right.
Safe Driving Bonus Checks,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> Shepard: THE ASTRONAUTS ON
THE INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION
HAVE PERFORMED A HAND
TRANSPLANT.
THE PATIENTS A GIANT ROBOTIC
ARM.
IT'S A 58-FOOT ARM THAT HELPS
GRAB INCOMING SPACE CRAFT.
ONE OF THE TWO HANDS
MALFUNCTIONED A COUPLE MONTHS
AGO AND ASTRONAUTS OUT
INSTALLING A NEW ONE SO THE ARM
CAN GRAB A SUPPLY SHIP SCHEDULED
FOR NEXT MONTH.
ON THIS DAY IN 1962, THE VERY
FIRST JAMES BOND MOVIE
PREMIERED.
"DR. NO" DEBUTED IN LONDON BASED
ON A BOOK BY IAN FLEMING.
SEAN CONNERRY WAS THE FIRST OO7.
THE FIRST SOPHISTICATED SUPPLY
WITH THE TASTE FOR DRY MARTINIS
AND GADGETS.
THIS ALL HAPPENED 55 YEARS AGO
TODAY.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
BREAKING NEWS CHANGES EVERYTHING
ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
ANOTHER INCREDIBLE DAY ON THE
DOW.
WE HAVE A LOT OF FINANCIAL
PEOPLE THAT WORK IN THIS
BUILDING.
NOT ON THE FLOORS WHERE WE ARE.
ONE EXPLAINED TO US YESTERDAY,
THE PRICES AND THE EARNINGS
AND -- I'M LOOK NO.
IS IT GOING UP OR DOWN?
HE WAS LIKE IF I KNEW THAT, I
WOULDN'T BE HERE.
TODAY THE ANSWER IS UP.
IT'S UP ALSO HALF A POINT.
THE S&P IS UP.
SO IS THE RUSSELL AND EVERYTHING
IS UP.
WHY IS IT ALL UP?
BECAUSE CAVUTO IS IN CHARGE.
WHEN NEIL CAVUTO IS IN CHARGE,
EVERYTHING ALWAYS GOES UP.
"YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL CAVUTO IS
NEXT ON THE NETWORK AMERICA
TRUSTS FOR NEWS AND INFORMATION
ON CABLE.
THIS IS FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT.
INDEED STOCKS ARE UP ACROSS THE
BOARD.
ALL THE MAJOR AVERAGES RUNNING A
LONG YEAR, THE S&P, THE DOW AND
THE NASDAQ.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT WE
HAVEN'T SEEN IN 20 YEARS.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THAT IN A
SECOND.
WE MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN A PUSH TO
THIS WITH SPEAKER PAUL RYAN
WRAPPING UP REMARKS EARLIER ON
IN MARYLAND WHERE HE WAS
ACTUALLY PUSHING FOR TAX CUTS.
THE HOUSE APPROVED A BUDGET SORT
OF PLAN OF THEIR OWN THAT
THEY'RE KICKING TO THE SENATE TO
COME UP WITH THEIR OWN.
IN THE COURSE OF HIS REMARKS,
BESIDES PUSHING FOR TAX CUTS
THAT LOOK LIKE A BETTER THING,
HE DID TALK ABOUT THE NEED TO
LOOK INTO THIS BUMP STOCK
MECHANISM THAT COULD ALLOW A