ADOPTED
CHILDREN.
[ LAUGHTER ]
PRETTY BRETT FINALLY A
LAUGH.
THANKS FOR INVITING US INTO
YOUR HOME TONIGHT,THAT'S IT
FOR "SPECIAL REPORT," FAIR
BALANCED AND UNAFRAID.
"SPECIAL REPORT" ONLINE
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>
>> Trace: TONIGHT, THE FBI
TO BRIEF US ANY TIME ON THE
BOSTON BOMBING CASE.
AND NOW WE'RE LEARNING THE
FEDS ARE LOOKING FOR TWO
MEN SEEN IN PHOTOS NEAR THE
BOMB SITE.
TONIGHT, EXAMINING THE
EVIDENCE OF THE ATTACK HERE
AT THE BOSTON MARATHON.
>> Bill: A WOMAN WOUNDED
IN THE BOMBING LOOKS FOR
HER HERO.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS HE
SAID TO HER TO CALM HER
DOWN WAS TO SHOW HER HIS
OWN SHRAPNEL WOUNDS FROM
WHEN HE WAS IN AFGHANISTAN.
HIS NAME IS TYLER.
THAT'S ALL WE KNOW.
TYLER.
>> Bill: NOW HE'S FOUND.
>> I SAID MY NAME IS TYLER.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
AND LETTERS TESTING
POSITIVE FOR POISON.
ONE SENT TO THE PRESIDENT.
OTHER SUSPICIOUS LETTERS TO
U.S. SENATORS.
TONIGHT, ANOTHER PLOT
UNFOLDS.
MUCH I'M BILL HEMMER IN
TONIGHT FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
WE ARE LIVE BOILSTON STREET
ON THE BACK BAY OF BOSTON.
A FEW BLOCKS FROM THE SCENE
OF MONDAY'S BOMBING AND
WHAT HAS BEEN A SOMEWHAT
CHAOTIC DAY HERE.
JUST MINUTES AGO A FEDERAL
SOURCE TELLING FOX NEWS
INVESTIGATORS ARE LOOKING
FOR TWO PERSONS OF INTEREST
IN CONNECTION WITH MONDAY'S
ATTACK.
NOW, BOTH MEN CAPTURED IN
PHOTOS FROM THE SCENE.
MORE ON THAT IN A MOMENT.
OF COURSE, HOURS AGO WE
HEARD REPORTS THAT AN
ARREST WAS IMMINENT IN THE
ATTACKS.
SOME TALK THAT AN ARREST
HAD ALREADY HAPPENED.
THE FBI LATER SAYING THERE
WERE NO ARREST AND HAS NOT
BEEN ONE.
NOBODY TO BRING TO COURT
HERE IN BOSTON.
BUT AT THIS HOUR, WE'RE
STILL AWAITING A NEWS
CONFERENCE FROM
INVESTIGATORS THAT HAS BEEN
RESCHEDULED OVER AND OVER
AGAIN.
POSTPONED WAS THE WORD WE
HEARD LATE TONIGHT.
RICK LEVENTHAL MONITORING
DEVELOPMENTS ALL DAY.
IS HE LIVE IN BOSTON WITH
ME AS WELL.
RICK, YOU BROKE THE NEWS OF
THESE TWO PERSONS OF
INTEREST.
WHAT MORE YOU CAN REPORT?
>> WELL, OBVIOUSLY BILL,
THE FOCUS HERE HAS TO BE ON
CAPTURING THE PERSON OR
PERSONS RESPONSIBLE FOR
THIS HORRIFIC ATTACK ON THE
BOSTON MARATHON THAT KILLED
THREE AND WOUNDED NEARLY
180 OTHERS.
WE HAVE SEEN THE
PHOTOGRAPHS OF TWO MEN WHO
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES ARE
LOOKING FOR AS PERSONS OF
INTEREST.
POSSIBLE SUSPECTS IN THOSE
TWIN BOMBINGS ON MONDAY.
WE ARE NOT SHARING THOSE
PHOTOGRAPHS WITH OUR
VIEWERS YET BECAUSE THE FBI
IS NOT SHARING THOSE
PHOTOGRAPHS WITH THE
PUBLIC.
WE DON'T WANT TO JENNIFER
DYES THIS INVESTIGATION.
BUT, I HAVE SEEN THESE
PICTURES.
THEY ARE VERY CLEAR.
THERE ARE TWO MEN ONE
APPEARS TO BE CARRYING A
BACKPACK.
THE OTHER APPEARS TO HAVE A
BAG.
THESE BAGS MATCH THE
DESCRIPTION THAT THE
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES HAVE
TOLD US ARE BELIEVED TO BE
CARRIED THE TWO BOMBS ON
MONDAY.
AGAIN NOT SHOWING THE
PHOTOS UNTIL THE FEDERAL
AUTHORITIES ASK THE MEDIA
TO SHARE THESE PICTURES
BECAUSE WE WANTED TO MAKE
SURE WE DON'T JEOPARDIZE
ANY INVESTIGATION AND THAT
IF THE FBI DOES HAVE LEADS
AND IS AFTER THESE MEN THAT
THEY HAVE EVERY CHANCE TO
CATCH THEM.
I THINK, BILL, ONE OF THE
REASONS WHY ALL OF THOSE
REPORTS SURFACED EARLIER
TODAY ABOUT POSSIBLE
SUSPECTS EITHER BEING
IDENTIFIED OR BEING IN
CUSTODY IS BECAUSE THESE
PHOTOS BEGAN CIRCULATING
AMONG LAW ENFORCEMENT AND
THERE WAS CONFUSION ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT THERE HAD
BEEN ARREST BUT ABOUT THE
FACT THAT THERE HAVE BEEN
SUSPECTS OR PERSONS OF
INTEREST WHO HAVE BEEN
IDENTIFIED OR AT LEAST
ISOLATED BY LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
>> Bill: SO YOU HAVE SEEN
THE PHOTOS, RICK, AND BASED
ON THE IMKNOWLEDGES YOU
SAW, HOW CLEAR ARE THE
FACES ON THESE PHOTOS?
>> THEY ARE PRETTY CLEAR.
THERE ARE MULTIPLE ANGLES
AND YOU CAN DEFINITELY SEE
THEIR FACES.
AND I HOPE AND I BELIEVE
THAT LAW ENFORCEMENT USING
THOSE PHOTOS CAN POSITIVELY
IDENTIFY THE MEN AND
WHETHER OR NOT THEY'RE THE
MEN WHO ARE ACTUALLY
RESPONSIBLE REMAINS TO BE
SEEN.
>> QUICKLY RICK, WE HAVE
ALSO LEARNED EARLIER TODNVESTIGATORS
FOUND
MORE POSSIBLE PARTS FROM
THE BOMB.
WHAT'S DIFFERENT TODAY THAN
FROM LAST NIGHT ON THAT?
>> WELL, YOU KNOW, WE KNOW
THAT THESE CRIME SCENE
TECHNICIANS HAVE BEEN ON
SCENE ON BOILSTON STREET
FOR DAYS NOW COLLECTING
EVIDENCE, INCLUDING
APPARENTLY THE LID FROM A
PRESSURE COOKER THAT BLEW
UP ON TO ONE OF THE ROOFS
ALONG BOILSTON STREET AFTER
THE BLAST.
WE ARE TOLD BY FEDERAL
AUTHORITIES THAT A PRESSURE
COOKER WAS BELIEVED TO HAVE
BEEN USED IN AT LEAST ONE
OF THE TWO BOMBS.
IT WAS PACKED WITH NAILS
AND BALL BEARINGS AND WE
HAVE SEEN THE PHOTOS OF
THOSE NAILS AND BALL
BEARINGS.
WE HAVE ALSO SEEN THE PHOTO
OF THE BLACK BACKPACK THAT
WAS SHREDDED AFTER THAT
BOMB WENT OFF.
WE ALSO KNOW THAT FEDERAL
AUTHORITIES ARE CAREFULLY
SCANNING HUNDREDS, IF NOT
THOUSANDS OF IMAGES, STILL
PICTURES AND VIDEO FROM THE
SCENE.
AGAIN, TRYING TO LINK UP
THE MEN WHO ARE BELIEVED TO
BE RESPONSIBLE WITH IMAGES
FROM BOILSTON STREET, BILL?
>> Bill: THANK YOU, RICK.
GOOD WORK TODAY.
RICK LEVENTHAL THROUGHOUT    THROUGH
THE
THROUGHOUT THE NIGHT HE
WILL BE WITH US.
INVESTIGATORS HAD ARRESTED
A SUSPECT AND WAS BRINGING
HIM THERE.
ALTHOUGH LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIALS LATER DENYING
REPORTS OF AN ARREST.
THOSE DENIALS CAME AFTER A
CRUSH OF MEDIA DESCENDED ON
THE COURTHOUSE LOOKING FOR
ANY GLIMPSE OF A POSSIBLE
SUSPECT.
EVERYONE ON HIGH ALERT
THERE AS CAN YOU IMAGINE.
THIS IS WHERE A SUSPECT
MIGHT GO IF THE FEDS HAD
MADE AN ARREST.
THEN WORD OF A BOMB THREAT
INSIDE -- INSIDE THE
COURTHOUSE, FORCING WORKERS
TO LEAVE.
THEY SAID IT WAS A CODE RED
IN THE MEDIA WAS FORCED TO
STEP BACK.
WE'RE TOLD THAT ULTIMATELY
TURNED OUT TO BE A FALSE
ALARM.
AND YOU CAN SEE WORKERS
PUSHING CRIBS DOWN THE
STREET, POSSIBLY FROM THE
DAY CARE CENTER INSIDE THAT
COURTHOUSE IN BOSTON.
TOP INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY
HAVE RECEIVED PROMISING
INTELLIGENCE FROM THE
PHOTOS AND THE VIDEO TAKEN
BEFORE THE TWIN BOMBINGS,
THAT'S WHAT A CONGRESSIONAL
SOURCE IS TELLING FOX NEWS
TONIGHT.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE IS LIVE
IN THAT PART OF THE STORY
IN WASHINGTON.
WHAT DO WE KNOW ABOUT ANY
POSSIBLE LEADS ON, THIS
CATHERINE?
>> WELL, THANK YOU BILL.
CONGRESSIONAL SOURCES
TELLING FOX NEWS THAT THE
FBI DID NOT BRIEF THE FULL
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE AS EXPECTED.
SETTING A CITING A FLUID
INVESTIGATION BUT THE
NATIONAL TERRORISM CENTER
SET UP AFTER 9/11 TO ASSESS
THREATS AND SHARE THE
FINDINGS, TELLING A HANDFUL
OF LAWMAKERS THAT VIDEOS
AND PHOTOS LEADING UP TO
THE MOMENT ARE ALREADY
PROVIDING, QUOTE PROMISING
INTELLIGENCE ON THE CASE.
ACCORDING IT TO AN
INVESTIGATIVE SOURCE, ONE
OF THE WORKING THEORIES IS
THAT THE DEVICE USING LOW
EXPLOSIVES WAS PROBABLY PUT
TOGETHER FAIRLY CLOSED TO
THE BLAST SITE ITSELF.
TODAY THE "WALL STREET
JOURNAL" AND OTHERS
REPORTING THAT THE FBI AND
BOSTON POLICE ARE
CANVASSING HOTELS AND
SHORT-TERM RENTALS IN THE
AREA, BILL.
>> Bill: INVESTIGATORS ALSO
TAKING A CLOSE LOOK AT THE
COMPONENTS OF THOSE
EXPLOSIVES RIGHT
CATHERINE?
>> WELL, FOX NEWS HAS TOLD
BOMB COMPONENTS ARE NOW AT
THE FBI CRIME LAB IN
QUANTITY CO, VIRGINIA WHERE
THEY ARE BEING ANNUALIZED
AND THAT THE CIRCUIT BOARD
WAS RECOVERED.
KEY COMPONENTS DESCRIBED TO
US AS RELATIVELY INTACT,
WHICH SEEMS TO BODE WELL
FOR INVESTIGATORS.
THIS LAW ENFORCEMENT
BULLETIN OBTAINED BY FOX
FROM FBI AND HOMELAND
SECURITY SENT TO LAW
ENFORCEMENT CONFIRMING ONE
BOMB WAS A PRESSURE COOKER
WITH SHRAPNEL INCLUDING
NAILS, B B AND BALL
BEARINGS.
THE SECOND DEVICE IS SO
BADLY DAMAGED IT WAS ONLY
DESCRIBED SIMPLY AS A METAL
CONTAINER.
BOTH DEVICES SAY THE TYPE
OF LOW EXPLOSIVE A MODE OF
DETONATION ARE ACTIVELY
BEING DETERMINED.
THE MANUFACTURER OF THIS
BATTERY SAYS IT'S VERY
COMMON.
FOUND IN KIDS' RADIO
CONTROLLED TOYS AND THEY
SELL TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
THESE BATTERIES EVERY YEAR.
THE THREAT OF AN IMPROVISED
EXPLOSIVE DEVICE HERE IN
THE U.S. IS UNFORTUNATELY
NOT NEW.
AND WHILE THE ATTACKS ARE
TYPICALLY ASSOCIATED
OVERSEAS, IT'S SOMETHING
THAT IS WELL UNDERSTOOD
HERE.
>> YOU KNOW, I THINK THE
GENERAL MESSAGE THAT I HAVE
GOTTEN TALKING TO PEOPLE
WHO ARE WORKING THIS, AS
WELL AS BASED ON MY OWN
EXPERIENCE, IS THAT WE HAVE
ANTICIPATED SOMETHING LIKE
THIS COULD HAPPEN.
WE HAVE WORKED HARD TO
PREVENT IT FROM HAPPENING.
BUT YOU CAN'T BE 100%
SUCCESSFUL THAT THE KEY
HERE IS TO BE QUICK AND
DILIGENT IN THE
INVESTIGATION, BUT ALSO TO
BE RESILIENT.
>> FOX NEWS ASKED THE FBI
TO COMMENT ON THE STATUS OF
THE BOMB ANALYSIS BUT THERE
WAS NO IMMEDIATE RESPONSE,
BILL.
>> Bill: CATHERINE, THANK
YOU FROM WASHINGTON.
>> YOU ARE WELCOME.
>> TO OUR VIEWERS AT HOME
WE HAD EXPECTED AN FBI
BRIEFING.
THAT WAS POSTPONED.
THEIR WORDS FROM EARLIER
TONIGHT.
IT STILL MAY HAPPEN THIS
EVENING.
IF IT DOES DURING THIS
BROADCAST, WE WILL
CERTAINLY BRING THAT TO YOU
LIVE.
ALSO, A MAJOR STORY
BREAKING EARLIER TODAY AND
THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
THE FBI TELLING FOX THERE
IS NO SIGN OF ANY
CONNECTION BETWEEN THE
BOMBINGS HERE IN BOSTON AND
THOSE SUSPICIOUS LETTERS
TURNING UP IN WASHINGTON.
INVESTIGATORS SAY EARLY
TESTS ON LETTERS SENT TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA AND
MISSISSIPPI REPUBLICAN
SENATOR ROGER WICKER WERE
POSITIVE FOR RICIN.
THAT'S A DEADLY POISON.
6,000 TIMES MORE POISONOUS
THEY SAY THAN MANY OTHER
ITEMS E% SAY PRELIMINARY
TESTS CAN BE WRONG AND
THEY'RE WAITING FOR FINAL
RESULTS.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY
INTERCEPTED BOTH LETTERS
BEFORE THEY GOT TO THE
WHITE HOUSE OR THE CAPITOL
BUILDING.
MIKE EMANUEL IS LIVE ON THE
HILL THERE.
THERE ARE SOME SIMILARITIES
BETWEEN THE TWO LETTERS.
WHAT ARE THEY?
>> WELL, BILL, THAT'S
RIGHT.
AN FBI OPERATIONS BULLETIN
OBTAINED BY FOX REVEALS
SIMILARITIES.
BOTH WERE POSTMARKED
MEMPHIS, TENNESSEE ON APRIL
THE 8TH.
THERE WAS SOME IDENTICAL
WORDING.
AND THE SAME SIGNATURE IMKC
AND I APPROVE THIS MESSAGE.
AT THE WHITE HOUSE WE
RECEIVED THIS UPDATE.
>> THERE WAS A LETTER SENTTO THE
PRESIDENT, THAT AT AN OFF
SITE MAIL FACILITY WASES NOTICED
TO HAVE CONTAINED A
SUSPICIOUS SUBSTANCE AND
TESTS WERE UNDERTAKEN.
THE FBI HAS THE LEAD IN
THAT INVESTIGATION.
>> IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT
BOTH LETTERS DID NOT REACH
THE WHITE HOUSE OR THE
CAPITOL COMPLEX.
THEY WERE FLAGGED AT
OFFSITE FACILITIES, BILL.
MR. .
>> Bill: YEAH, RICIN CAN BE
A KILLER.
IT'S MORE POISONOUS.
WE HAD AN EXPERT ON TODAY
SAYING 6,000 MORE TIMES
POISON NEWS THAN CYANIDE.
THIS IS DANGEROUS MATERIAL
HERE.
THERE WERE SUSPICIOUS
PACKAGES SENT IT LAWMAKERS
IN YOUR HOME STATE WHAT DO
YOU HAVE ON THAT MIKE?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
TWO SENATORS HOME OFFICES.
TWO OF THEM ARE GETTING
SOME CLOSER SCRUTINY.
SENATOR CARL LEVIN
DEMOCRAT OF MICHIGAN SAYS
HE GOT A SUSPICIOUS LETTER
TO HIS SAGINAW MICHIGAN
OFFICE AND AN OLDER STAFF
IS IN THE HOSPITAL TONIGHT
AS A PRECAUTION THOUGH HAS
NO SYMPTOMS.
TEXAS REPUBLICAN SENATOR
JOHN CORNYN'S OFFICE SAYS
IT RECEIVED A SUSPICIOUS
LETTER AT ITS DALLAS OFFICE
THAT WAS TESTED AND TURNED
OVER TO A POSSESSION
INSPECTOR.
A TOP SENATE LEADER SAYS SO
FAR THE SYSTEM HAS WORKED.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO
RECOGNIZE THE POSTAL AND
LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS
FOR THEIR EXCELLENT WORK IN
DETECTING AND PREVENTING
THIS THREAT BEFORE IT EVEN
REACHED THE CAPITOL.
THEY PROVED THAT THE
PROACTIVE MEASURES WE PUT
IN PLACE DO, IN FACT, WORK.
>> EVERYBODY IS BEING EXTRA
CAUTIOUS CAUTIOUS.
NOBODY UP HERE WANTS TO BE
WRONG.
BILL?
>> Bill: INDEED.
THANK YOU, MIKE.
MIKE EMANUEL ON THE HILL
TONIGHT.
WE ARE WATCHING THOSE
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE RICIN
MATTER.
CERTAINLY THE FALLOUT HERE
IN BOSTON AFTER MARATHON
ATTACKS ON MONDAY.
WE'RE WAITING FOR A NEWS
CONFERENCE.
AS I MENTIONED, IF IT
HAPPENS TONIGHT YOU WILL
SEE IT HERE ON THE FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
MAJOR DEVELOPMENTS NOW ON
GUN CONTROL.
LIVE IN THE NATION'S
CAPITOL FOR A LOOK AT WHAT
LAWMAKERS DID AND WE'LL GET
SOME REACTION FROM
PRESIDENT OBAMA.
THAT IS ALL COMING UP.
SO MUCH MORE TONIGHT ON THE
FOX REPORT.
WE ARE LIVE ON BOYLESTON
STREET IN BOSTON'S BACK
BAY.
ARE YOU STILL SLEEPIJUST WANTED TO
CHECK AND MAKE  SURE THAT WE WERE
ON SCHEDULE.
THE FIRST TECHNOLOGY  OF ITS KIND...
MOM AND DAD, I HAVE GREAT NEWS.
IS NOW PROVIDING  ANSWERS FAMILIES
NEED.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
EXPANDED BACKGROUND CHECKS
TO COVER GUN SHOWS AND THE
INTERNET INSTEAD OF JUST
LICENSED DEALERS.
IT EXEMPTED SALES BETWEEN
FRIENDS AND FAMILY MEMBERS
AND BANNED THE GOVERNMENT
FROM CREATING A NATIONAL
FIREARMS REGISTRY.
AFTER THE VOTE LATE TODAY
PRESIDENT OBAMA MET AT THE
WHITE HOUSE WITH FORMER
CONGRESSWOMAN GABRIEL
GIFFORDS FROM ARIZONA AND
SOME THE SANDY HOOK
FAMILIES AND THEY VOWED NOT
TO GIVE UP THE FIGHT.
IN BE.
>> NO ONE SHOULD FEEL OUR
PAIN OR THE PAIN FELT BY
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
WHO LOST LOVED ONES TO
SENSELESS GUN VIOLENCE.
>> A SPOKESMAN FOR THE NRA
SAYING QUOTE EXPANDING
BACKGROUND CHECKS AT GUN
SHOWS OR ELSEWHERE WILL NOT
REDUCE VIOLENT CRIME OR
KEEP OUR KIDS SAFE IN THEIR
SCHOOLS, END QUOTE.
ED HENRY FOLLOWING THIS
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
TONIGHT.
ED, WHAT DID THE PRESIDENT
SAY AFTER THIS VOTE?
>> WELL, BILL, IT WAS A
PRETTY EMOTIONAL EVENT IN
THE ROSE GARDEN THAT YOU
MENTIONED.
IN ADDITION TO THE NEW TOWN
FAMILIES AND GABBY GIFFORDS
SEBILITIMENT FROM THE
FATHER THAT YOU MENTIONED
ARE NOT GOING TO BE
DETERRED.
THEY ARE GOING TO FIGHT ON.
THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF WAS
PRETTY DEFIANT AS WELL BY
SAYING THIS IS JUST ROUND
ONE IN THE FIGHT.
TAKE A LISTEN.
THIS WAS A PRETTY SHAMEFUL
DAY FOR WASHINGTON BUT THIS
EFFORT IS NOT OVER.
I WANT TO MAKE IT CLEAR TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE, WE
STILL BRING ABOUT
MEANINGFUL CHANGES THAT
REDUCE GUN VIOLENCE SO LONG
AS THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
DON'T GIVE UP ON IT.
>> IT'S UNCLEAR THOUGH WHEN
SENATE MAJORITY LEADER
HARRY REID WILL BRING THIS
BACK UP FOR A POTENTIAL
VOTE.
IT'S INTERESTING AFTER THE
VOTE ONE OF THE DEMOCRATS
ON THE HOT SEAT, SENATOR
MAX BAUCUS WAS ASKED WHY HE
VOTED NO ON THE EXPANDED
BACKGROUND CHECKS HE SAID
ONE WORD, MONTANA.
WHICH MEANS SOME OF THESE
SWING STATE DEMOCRATS DON'T
WANT TO COME ABOARD.
BILL?
>> Bill: MOST REPUBLICANS
AND SOME DEMOCRATS VOTED
AGAINST EXPANDING
BACKGROUND CHECKS.
WE JUST HEARD FROM THE
PRESIDENT.
WHAT DOES HE SAY ABOUT
WHERE THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
ARE ON THIS ISSUE, ED.
>> THE PRESIDENT IS
FRUSTRATED BECAUSE HE KEEPS
CITING VARIOUS NATIONAL
POLLS INCLUDING FOX NEWS
POLLING SUGGEST IN THE
RANGE OF 90% OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE SUPPORT
EXPANDED BACKGROUND CHECKS.
THE NRA IS PUSHING BACK BY
SAYING THIS PARTICULAR
CHANGE WOULDN'T HAVE DONE
ANYTHING TO PREVENT SOME OF
THE RECENT TRAGEDIES.
IT'S A POINT THAT A LOT OF
REPUBLICAN SENATORS LIKE
CHUCK GRASSLEY ARE MAKING.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> MANCHIN TOOMEY WOULD
NOT HAVE STOPPED NEWTOWN.
PEOPLE WHO STEAL GUNS DO
NOT SUBMIT TO BACKGROUND
CHECKS.
>> NOW SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER HARRY REID DID VOTE
NO.
THAT MEANS HE CAN BRING
THIS UP AT A LATER DATE
PROCEDURALLY.
HE PLANS TO DO THAT BUT WE
DON'T KNOW WHEN, BILL.
>> Bill: ED HENRY LIVE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT AND FIRST
LADY WILL BE HERE IN BOSTON
TOMORROW MORNING.
WE WILL FOLLOW THAT TRIP
LIVE HERE IN AMERICA'S
NEWSROOM.
MEANWHILE, WE NOW KNOW THE
IDENTITY OF THE THIRD
VICTIM KILLED IN THE ATTACK
HERE IN BOSTON.
A YOUNG WOMAN WHO CAME TO
THIS COUNTRY TO G.E.D. AN
EDUCATION AT BOSTON
UNIVERSITY AND WILL NEVER
RETURN HOME.
HER STORY IN A MOMENT.
PLUS THE SEARCH FOR A HERO
WHO HELPED COMFORT ONE
VICTIM.
AS SHE LAID LEADING AFTER
THE BLAST AND TONIGHT TYLER
HAS BEEN FOUND.
AND HE HAS A MESSAGE FOR
THE WOMAN WHO IS TRYING TO
FIND HIM.
THAT'S COMING UP AS FOX
REPORTS LIVE TONIGHT FROM
BOSTON.
OR GOOD DECISIONS?
ONES I'VE MADE.  ONES WE'VE ALL MADE.
ABOUT MARRIAGE. CHILDREN. MONEY.
ABOUT TOMORROW.
HERE'S TO GOOD DECISIONS.
WHO MATTERS MOST TO YOU    SAYS THE
MOST ABOUT YOU.
AT MassMutual WE'RE OWNED    BY OUR
POLICYOWNERS,
AND THEY MATTER MOST TO US.
READY TO PLAN    FOR YOUR FAMILY'S
FUTURE?
WE'LL HELP YOU GET THERE.
[ alarm clock ringing ]    [ Female
Announcer ] IF YOU    HAVE RHEUMATOID
ARTHRITIS,    CAN YOU START THE DAY
THE WAY YOU WANT?    CAN ORENCIA (ABATACEPT)
HELP?  [ Woman ] I WANTED TO GET UP
WHEN I WAS READY,  NOT MY JOINTS.
[ Female Announcer ] COULD YOUR
"I WANT" BECOME "I CAN"?    TALK TO
YOUR RHEUMATOLOST.    ORENCIA REDUCES
MANY RA SYMPTOMS    LIKE PAIN, MORNING
STIFFNESS    AND THE PROGRESSION
OF JOINT DAMAGE.    IT'S HELPED NEW
RA PATIENTS    AND THOSE NOT HELPED
ENOUGH    BY OTHER TREATMENTS.
DO NOT TAKE ORENCIA    WITH ANOTHER
BIOLOGIC MEDICINE    FOR RA    DUE
TO AN INCREASED RISK    OF SERIOUS
INFECTION.    SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS
CAN OCCUR    INUDING FATAL INFECTIONS.
CAS OF LYMPHOMA AND    LUNG CANCER
HAVE BEEN REPORTED.     YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU ARE    PRONE TO OR HAVE ANY
INFECTION    LIKE AN OPEN SORE OR
THE FLU    OR A HISTORY OF COPD,
A CHRONIC LUNG DISEASE.    ORENCIA
MAY WORSEN YOUR COPD.  [ Woman ] HERE'S
INFORMATION  YOU NEED TO KNOW.  ORENCIA
IS AVAILABLE  IN TWO FORMS,  INFUSION
AND ALSO  SELF-INJECTION.  TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR TO SEE  IF ORENCIA IS
RIGHT FOR YOU.  AND SEE IF YOU CAN
CHANGE  "I WANT"  TO "OH, YES I CAN!"
>> Bill: WE NOW KNOW THE
IDENTITY OF THE THIRD
VICTIM KILLED IN THE BOSTON
MARATHON ATTACKS.
B.U. CONFIRMS, BOSTON
UNIVERSITY CONFIRMING SHE
WAS A GRAD STUDENT BY THE
NAME OF LU LING G.P.S. ZI.
A CHINESE CITIZEN STUDYING
MATT AND STATISTICS AND
WATCHING THE RACE NEAR THE
FINISH LINE WHEN THE BOMB
EXPLODED.
OTHER TWO 8-YEAR-OLD MARTIN
RICHARD AND 29-YEAR-OLD
CHRIS KRYSTLE CAMPBELL.
TODAY WE GOT UPDATE HOW
SOME OF THEM ARE DOING.
MIKE TOBIN WAS AT THE
HOSPITAL A LITTLE BIT
EARLIER.
IS HE LIVE AT THE CHURCH
WHERE TOMORROW PRESIDENT
OBAMA IS SET TO ATTEND A
PRAYER SERVICE THAT WE WILL
COVER CERTAINLY.
BUT, MIKE, FIRST WHAT DO
WE KNOW ABOUT THOSE STILL
IN THE HOSPITAL AND THEIR
CONDITION TONIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW, BILL, THE NEWS
COMING OUT OF THE HOSPITALS
OVERALL IS OPTIMISTIC.
DOCTORS DON'T ANTICIPATE
ANY FURTHER LOSS OF LIFE
AND THEY DON'T ANTICIPATE
THE NEED FOR ANY
AMPUTATIONS.
THAT BEING SAID, THERE IS A
SOMBER NOTE COMING OUT OF
BOSTON MEDICAL.
DOCTORS WARNING TO KEEP A
SHARP OUT FOR
POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS.
>> PTSD IS NOT JUST ABOUT
THE PATIENTS IT'S ABOUT
THEIR FAMILIES AS WELL.
WE WORK WITH THEM FROM THE
BEGINNING.
THERE IS NO, AS FAR AS I
KNOW ANY MAGIC BULLETS TO
PREVENT THIS.
BUT WE NEED TO, AGAIN, IT'S
A PROCESS AND EVOLVES OVER
TIME AND IT'S SOMETHING
AGAIN, THAT PEOPLE NEED NOT
TO FORGET ABOUT THAT IT'S
SOMETHING THAT CAN BE WITH
THESE PATIENTS FOREVER.
>> NOW HOSPITALS DIFFER
WITH THE DESCRIPTIONS OF
THE SHRAPNEL COMING OUT OF
THE BOMBING VICTIMS.
MASSACHUSETTS GENERAL
BRINGMAN'S WOMEN'S BOTH SAY
THEY'RE REMOVING BALL
BEARINGS AND NAILS FROM THE
PATIENTS.
BOSTON MEDICAL AND TUSC
MEDICAL CENTER DESCRIBE
BITS RANDOM METAL AND
DEBRIS THINGS PICKED UP
FROM THE ENVIRONMENT.
ALL OF THAT BEING PULLED
OUT OF THE BOMBING VICTIMS
BILL.
>> Bill: TOMORROW IS GOING
TO BE ANOTHER EMOTIONAL
DAY.
WHAT ARE THE PLANS AS WE
UNDERSTAND THEM TONIGHT
MIKE FOR THE PRESIDENTS
VISIT AT THAT CHURCH BEHIND
YOU?
>> WELL, THE PRESIDENT WILL
COME HERE TO THE CATHEDRAL
OF THE HOLY CROSS JUST
ABOUT 11:00.
HE WILL BE ACCOMPANIED BY
THE FIRST LADY.
IT WILL BE AN INTERFAITH
SERVICE.
THE PRESIDENT IS SAID TO BE
DELIVERING A MESSAGE OF
SHARED PAIN NOT JUST WITH
THE PEOPLE WHO WERE IN THE
RUN ITSELF OR THE PEOPLE
WHO LIVE HERE IN BOSTON BUT
THE PEOPLE -- THE PEOPLE IN
THE RUN ITSELF.
AND A SHARED SENSE OF
RESPECT TO THE PEOPLE WHO
RESPONDED AND SAVED LIVES.
NO WORD NOW IF THE
PRESIDENT INTENDS TO VISIT
WITH THE VICTIMS AND/OR
THEIR FAMILIES, BILL.
>> Bill: MIKE, THANKS.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
MIKE TOBIN FROM THE CHURCH
TONIGHT.
WE ARE ALSO HEARING TONIGHT
FROM A HERO BY THE NAME OF
TYLER WHO HELPED COMFORT A
YOUNG WOMAN SUFFERING
SHRAPNEL WOUNDS FROM THE
TERRORIST ATTACKS.
YESTERDAY THE MASSACHUSETTS
GOVERNOR DEVOL PATRICK SAID
HE VISITED THE WOMAN
VICTORIA IN THE HOSPITAL
AND SHE SAID THAT TYLER
HELPED CALM HER DOWN, EVEN
SHOWING HER HIS OWN SCAR ON
HIS BODY.
>> VICTORIA VERY VERY MUCH
WANTS TO THANK TYLER
PERSONALLY SO.
IF TYLER IS OUT THERE AND
LISTENING OR READING YOUR
REPORTS, WE WOULD LOVE TO
HEAR FROM TYLER SO THAT WE
CAN CONNECT HIM TO VICTOR I
CAN'T.
>> WELL, OUR LOCAL
AFFILIATE FOX BOSTON CAUGHT
UP WITH A MAN TYLER DODD
IS HIS NAME.
HE SAID THAT INSIDE THE
MEDICAL TENT HE COULD SEE
THE TERROR IN VICTORIA'S
EYES.
>> I JUST KNEW THAT I HAD
TO TALK TO HER.
IF THERE WAS NOTHING ELSE I
COULD DO, I COULD TALK TO
HER.
I ASKED HER TO LOOK AT ME.
I THINK I ASKED HER WHAT
HER NAME WAS.
AND SHE KIND OF LOOKED AT
ME FUNNY LIKE WHY IS THIS
GUY ASKING MY NAME?
SHE SAID VICTORIA IS MY
NAME.
I SAID MY NAME IS TYLER.
IT'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
>> WELL, JOB WELL DONE,
TYLER.
CONTRARY TO SOME EARLY
REPORTING THOUGH, TYLER
DODD SAYS HE NEVER SERVED
IN THE MILITARY BUT HE
ADDED THAT VICTORIA'S
STRENGTH PROVED TO BE
INSPIRING.
>> WHOEVER IS RESPONSIBLE
FOR THIS, IT WAS MEANT TO
INSTILL TERROR AND FEAR AND
CHAOS.
WHAT I TAKE AWAY FROM IT IS
THE TRUE HUMAN SPIRIT AND
MULTIPLE NARNLTS
NATIONALITIES AND CULTURES
COMING TOGETHER TO HELP
EACH OTHER OUT.
>> YEAH, FOX BOSTON ALSO
REPORTS THAT TYLER AND
VICTORIA, THEY ARE
ARRANGING TO MEET EACH
OTHER YET AGAIN THIS TIME
AT MEDICAL CENTER WHERE
VICTORIA IS RECOVERING AND
THAT WILL BE QUITE A
REUNION.
SOME CRIME SCENE PHOTOS NOW
SPREADING OVER THE INTERNET
COULD HELP FEDERAL
INVESTIGATORS IN THEIR
SEARCH FOR A SUSPECT.
AND WE WILL EXPLAIN WHY IN
A MOMENT ON THAT.
PLUS, A NEW TWIST IN THE
KILLINGS OF A TEXAS
DISTRICT ATTORNEY AND HIS
WIFE.
NOW, THE WIFE OF A MAN
ALREADY UNDER ARREST HAS
JUST MADE A BIG CONFESSION.
THAT IS NEXT AS FOX REPORTS
LIVE FROM BOSTON TONIGHT.
[ Male Announcer ]    IT'S SIMPLE
PHYSICS...    A BODY AT REST    TENDS
TO STAY AT REST...    WHILE A BODY
IN MOTION    TENDS TO STAY IN MOTION.
STAYING ACTIVE CAN ACTUALLY    EASE
ARTHRITIS SYMPTOMS.    BUT IF YOU
HAVE ARTHRITIS,    STAYING ACTIVE
CAN BE DIFFICULT.    PRESCRIPTION
CELEBREX    CAN HELP RELIEVE ARTHRITIS
PAIN    SO YOUR BODY    CAN STAY IN
MOTION.    BECAUSE JUST ONE    200MG
CELEBREX A DAY    CAN PROVIDE 24 HOUR
RELIEF    FOR MANY WITH ARTHRITIS
PAIN    AND INFLAMMATION.    PLUS,
IN CLINICAL STUDIES    CELEBREX IS
PROVEN TO IMPROVE    DAILY PHYSICAL
FUNCTION    SO MOVING IS EASIER.
CELEBREX CAN BE TAKEN    WITH OR WITHOUT
FOOD.    AND IT'S NOT A NARCOTIC.
YOU AND YOUR DOCTOR    SHOULD BALANCE
THE BENEFITS    WITH THE RISKS.
ALL PRESCRIPTION NSAIDS,    LIKE CELEBREX,
IBUPROFEN    NAPROXEN AND MELOXICAM
HAVE THE SAME    CARDIOVASCULAR WARNING.
THEY ALL MAY INCREASE    THE CHANCE
OF HEART ATTACK OR STROKE    WHICH
CAN LEAD TO DEATH.    THIS CHANCE
INCREASES    IF YOU HAVE HEART DISEASE
OR RISK FACTORS    SUCH AS HIGH BLOOD
PRESSURE    OR WHEN NSAIDS ARE TAKEN
FOR LONG PERIODS.    NSAIDS, LIKE
CELEBREX    INCREASE THE CHANCE OF
SERIOUS    SKIN OR ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR STOMACH AND INTESTINE    PROBLEMS
SUCH AS BLEEDING AND ULCERS    WHICH
CAN OCCUR WITHOUT WARNING    AND MAY
CAUSE DEATH.    PATIENTS ALSO TAKING
ASPIRIN    AND THE ELDERLY    ARE
AT INCREASED RISK FOR    STOMACH BLEEDING
AND ULCERS.    DON'T TAKE CELEBREX
IF YOU HAVE BLEEDING    IN THE STOMACH
OR INTESTINE    OR HAD AN ASTHMA ATTACK,
HIVES    OTHER ALLERGIES TO ASPIRIN,
NSAIDS OR SULFONAMIDES.    GET HELP
RIGHT AWAY IF YOU HAVE    SWELLING
OF THE FACE OR THROAT,    OR TROUBLE
BREATHING.    TELL YOUR DOCTOR
YOUR MEDICAL HISTORY.    AND FIND
AN ARTHRITIS TREATMENT    FOR YOU.
VISIT CELEBREX.COM AND ASK    YOUR
DOCTOR ABOUT CELEBREX.    FOR A BODY
IN MOTION.
>> Bill: A MAJOR
DEVELOPMENT IN THE MURDERS
OF A DISTRICT ATTORNEY, HIS
WIFE, AND A DEPUTY D.A.
PROSECUTORS SAYING THAT
SOMEBODY HAS CONFESSED TO
BEING INVOLVED IN THOSE
KILLINGS, BUT IT'S NOT THE
REPORTED PRIME SUSPECT.
INSTEAD, IT IS HIS WIFE,
KIM WILLIAMS.
THE SHERIFF'S SPOKESMAN
SAYS THAT SHE WILL FACE
CAPITAL MURDER CHARGES IN
ALL THREE DEATHS ON
SATURDAY COPS ARRESTED HER
HUSBAND ERIC WILLIAMS, A
FORMER JUSTICE OF THE
PEACE.
THEY SAY HE MADE
TERRORISTISTIC THREAT
AGAINST COUNTY EMPLOYEES.
HE LOST HIS JOB ABOUT A
YEAR AGO AFTER PROSECUTORS
CONVICTED HIM OF STEALING
COMPUTERS.
NOW, THOSE SAME PROSECUTO
RECENTLY TURNED UP DEAD
ALONG WITH THE D.A.'S WIFE
CASEY STEGALL HAS MORE IN
OUR DALLAS NEWSROOM.
DID THE WIFE SAY THAT SHE
WAS THE ONE WHO PULLED THE
TRIGGER.
>> BILL, GOOD EVENING TO
YOU.
ACCORDING TO THESE ARREST
WARRANT EAFTS THAT WE HAVE
OBTAINED, SHE DESCRIBED
BOTH HER ROLE AND HER
HUSBAND'S ROLE IN THESE
KILLINGS AND 46-YEAR-OLD
KIM WILLIAMS TOLD
INVESTIGATORS THAT HER
HUSBAND ERIC IS THE ONE WHO
SHOT AND KILLED ALL THREE
OF THE VICTIMS.
SHE DID, HOWEVER CONFESS
HER INVOLVEMENT IN THE
SCHEME BUT WE HAVE NO
FURTHER DETAILS.
SHE IS BEING HELD ON
$10 MILLION BOND AND MURDER
CHARGES WE UNDERSTAND
EXPECTED TO BE BROUGHT
AGAINST HER HUSBAND LATER
THIS WEEK, BILL.
>> WE ARE ALSO LEARNING
ABOUT SOME OF THE EVIDENCE
POLICE COLLECTED, IS THAT
RIGHT.
>> YES.
LAST WEEK STATE AND FEDERAL
OFFICIALS CONVERGED AND
EXECUTED MULTIPLE SEARCH
WARRANTS AT THE WILLIAMS'
HOME, THE HOME OF THEIR
IN-LAWS AND AT A STORAGE
UNIT THEY RENTED ABOUT
10 MILES FROM THE CRIME
SCENE.
A LOCAL NEWS STATION HERE
NOW REPORTING NEARLY 50
GUNS WERE FOUND AT THAT
STORAGE UNIT.
ALSO A CROWN CRITIC TORE I
CAN'T SEDAN SPOTTED IN THE
MCCLELLAND NEIGHBORHOOD THE
MORNING OF THE MURDERS.
COPS HAVEN'T SAID YET
BILL, HOW ALL OF THIS
EVIDENCE TIES THESE PEOPLE
TOGETHER.
>> CASEY STEGALL IN DALLAS
ON THE BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT THERE FROM TEXAS.
>> THERE IS MORE BREAKING
NEWS NOW HERE ON THE FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
WE ARE NOW HEARING THE FBI
WILL BE HOLDING A LONG
AWAITED BRIEFING IN 30
MINUTES.
8:00 EASTERN TIME FOX NEWS
WILL CARRY THAT BRIEFING
LIVE AS INVESTIGATORS TELL
US THE LATEST ON THE CASE.
BUT THE BOSTON POLICE
DEPARTMENT JUST ABOUT 12
MINUTES AGO ON THEIR
OFFICIAL TWITTER FEED SAID
THAT AT 8:00 EASTERN TIME
THE FBI WILL MAKE A
STATEMENT ABOUT THE LATEST
EVENTS TODAY.
WHETHER IT'S A PRESS
CONFERENCE OR A STATEMENT
ONLY, EITHER WAY WE WILL
COVER THAT LIVE FOR YOU
HERE IN BOSTON.
MEANWHILE, CHECKED OUT ONE
TIME I'M JUST HEARING NOW
FROM OUR PRODUCERS IN NEW
YORK THAT THE STATEMENT
THAT WAS SCHEDULED AT 8:00
EASTERN TIME IN COPLY SCARE
-- COPLEY SQUARE,
THAT'S NOW BEEN CANCELLED.
SO THAT'S ACCORDING TO THE
BOSTON POLICE DEPARTMENT
THAT HAD SENT OUT ONE TWEET
13 MINUTES AGO SAYING THERE
WOULD BE A STATEMENT AND
NOW SAYING THAT THAT
STATEMENT OR SCHEDULED
STATEMENT HAS BEEN
CANCELLED SO WE ARE TRYING
TO PING-PONG THROUGH ALL OF
THIS AND FOLLOW IT AS BEST
WE CAN.
IF SOMETHING HAPPENS AT
8:00 CERTAINLY WE WILL
HAVE IT COVERED RIGHT NOW
IT'S NOT CLEAR THAT THAT
WILL HAPPEN.
AS I SAY IT, IT IS
CLARIFIED AND CRAIG BOSS
WELL IS LIVE HERE IN BOSTON
WITH ME ON THIS.
CRAIG, GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
WHAT MORE DO YOU KNOW ABOUT
THIS?
>> BILL, GOOD EVENING TO
YOU, YEAH.
WE CERTAINLY HAVE A LOT OF
UNANSWERED QUESTIONS.
THERE IS A LOT OF
ANTICIPATION TRYING TO GET
THIS INFORMATION OUT FROM
FOX REPORTING FROM OUR
COLLEAGUE RICK LEVENTHAL A
COUPLE OF KEY PIECES OF
INFORMATION THAT
INVESTIGATORS ARE LOOKING
AT TWO PERSONS OF INTEREST
THAT THEY HAVE PICTURES OF.
THINK ARE DISTRIBUTING
AMONG LAW ENFORCEMENT.
NOT DISTRIBUTING AMONG THE
PUBLIC JUST YET THAT ONE OF
THEM HAS CARRYING A
BACKPACK.
THE OTHER SOME TYPE OF BAG.
NOW, THIS IS A VERY
ENCOURAGING FOR PEOPLE
WALKING BY BECAUSE THEY ARE
ASKING ABOUT THIS HERE.
ALSO VERY FRUSTRATING.
THAT FRUSTRATION SHOWING UP
AT THE COURTHOUSE WHEN
THERE WASSER REASON REPORTS
OF AN ARREST.
THEY WANTED TO SEE WHO
INFLICTED SUCH PAIN ON
THEIR STILL AND THEN, OF
COURSE, THE CHAOS THAT
ENSUED WHEN THERE WAS SOME
TYPE OF THREAT AND THEY HAD
TO EVACUATE THE COURTHOUSE.
THAT IS UNDERSCORING THE
UNDERLYING TENSION THAT
STILL REMAINS HERE IN
BOSTON, NOW TWO DAYS AFTER
THAT BOMBING THERE AT THE
FINISH LINE, BILL.
>> Bill: CRAIG, THANK YOU.
CRAIG BOSWELL ON THE
STREETS OF BOSTON TONIGHT.
IT'S REMARKABLE THING TO
FOLLOW ALL THE EVENTS
THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
SOMETIMES THESE EVENTS
TURNED ON THE MINUTE
LITERALLY YET AGAIN THEY
HAVE RECORDING FROM THE
BOSTON POLICE DEPARTMENT.
19 MINUTES AGO A TWEET WENT
OUT O.
THE FBI WILL MAKE A BRIEF
STATEMENT 8:00 P.M. WESTIN
HOTEL.
FIVE MINUTES AGO THE FBI
HAS CANCELLED THE 8:00 P.M.
BRIEFING TONIGHT.
SO FOR THE MOMENT THAT WILL
NOT HAPPEN.
NOW, THE FEDS ARE NOT THE
ONLY ONES POURING OVER
PICTURES LOOKING FOR LEADS
THE INTERNET IS ABUZZ WITH
WOULD BE DETECTIVES.
WEB SITE LIKE CHANGE AND
RED IT.
PAGES IDENTIFYING POTENTIAL
SUSPECTS.
MOST OF THEM MEN AT THE
MARATHON WHO CARRIED BLACK
BACKPACKS OR OTHERWISE
LOOKED SUSPICIOUS.
WE WILL NOT SHOW YOU THOSE
PICTURES HERE SINCE THERE
IS NOTHING YET TO SUGGEST
THAT THEY ARE GUILTY, BUT
RICK LEVENTHAL REPORTED ONE
HOUR AGO THAT THERE ARE
PHYSICAL COPIES OF PICTURES
NOW BEING DISTRIBUTED
THROUGH THE LAW ENFORCEMENT
IN THE SEARCH FOR TWO
PERSONS OF INTEREST.
IT WAS SPOTTED AROUND THE
FINISH LINE AT 2:45 TO
2:50 P.M. MONDAY AFTERNOON.
WE WILL GET MORE ON THAT AS
WE GET IT THROUGH OUR
SOURCES HERE IN BOSTON
TONIGHT.
NOW, ANY DOCTOR WILL TELL
YOU IT IS PERFECTLY NATURAL
TO FEEL ON EDGE, ESPECIALLY
AFTER NEWS OF AN ATTACK.
BUT THE BOMBINGS IN BOSTON,
THEY ARE NO EXCEPTION WITH
THE SCENES OF BLOOD AND
SUFFERING, IT IS IMPORTANT
TO UNDERSTAND THAT COMPARED
TO DECADES PAST, THIS TYPE
OF HORRIFIC EVENT IS NOW
SUBSTANTIALLY LESS COMMON.
"THE FOX REPORT'S"
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
LIVE TONIGHT WITH MORE ON
THAT.
IT DOES NOT LESSEN THE PAIN
THOUGH CERTAINLY FOR ANY OF
THE VICTIMS.
ACCORDING TO THE NUMBERS
THEY SUGGEST WE HE HAVE
BEEN SAFER SINCE 9/11.
JONATHAN?
>> THE BOMBINGS IN BOSTON,
BILL, ARE PARTLY SHOCKING
PURELY BECAUSE WE ARE THAT
MUCH SAFER THAN WE WERE
PRIOR TO 9/11.
PRIOR TO 9/11, THE BOMBINGS
WERE MUCH MORE COMMON ON
AMERICAN SOIL.
YOU ONLY NEED TO LOOK BACK
TO 1993, OF COURSE, AND THE
FIRST BOMBING OF THE WORLD
TRADE CENTER.
AND THEN IN 1995, OF
COURSE, THERE WAS THE
OKLAHOMA CITY BOMBING AND
MANY MORE SMALL SCALE BUT
DEADLY BOMBINGS IN THE
1970S.
NOW, A LOT OF EXPERTS SAY
THAT SINCE THE 9/11 ATTACKS
OUR INTELLIGENCE SERVICES
AND LAW ENFORCEMENT HAVE
BECOME MUCH BETTER AT
IDENTIFYING AND PREVENTING
ANY POTENTIAL ATTACKS.
SO WHILE WE MIGHT NOT FEEL
IT RIGHT NOW STAIVE TIS
PARTICULARLY SPEAKING, WE
ARE MUCH SAFER NOW THAN WE
WERE IN THE DECADES BEFORE
9/11.
BILL?
>> YOU KNOW, JONATHAN, WE
KNOW AT LEAST ONE OF THESE
DEVICES WAS MADE USING A
PRESSURE COOKER, PERHAPS
BOTH OF THEM IN THE END.
THAT IS NOT A NEW TACTIC,
IS IT?
>> NO.
IT'S CERTAINLY NOT.
IN FACT, RIGHT HERE, LOOK
AT THESE DATES.
IN 1976, THERE WAS A BOMB
USING A PRESSURE COOKER SET
BY CROATIAN SEPARATISTS
RIGHT HERE IN NEW YORK
CITY.
IN THE 1970S AND 1980S, IT
WAS A COMMON TACTIC USED BY
THE IRISH REPUBLICAN ARMY
IN THE UK AND ALSO IT WAS
USED IN THE 1980S BY
COLOMBIAN REBELS.
EXPERTS SAY THERE IS A VERY
GOOD REASON WHY PRESSURE
COOKER STYLE BOMBS HAVE
LONG BEEN IN THE
TERRORIST'S ARSENAL
LISTEN.
>> THIS IS A DEVICE THAT'S
MADE HOMEGROWN, THAT YOU GO
OUT AND YOU TAKE ELEMENTS
OF A STORE THAT YOU CAN'T
REALLY TRACE AND YOU PUT
THEM TOGETHER SO THAT YOU
GO BELOW THE SCREEN.
THAT'S WHY NOBODY KNOWS YOU
ARE.
SO HE SEY TO STAY BELOW THE
RADAR SCREEN.
HARD TO DEFECT.
>> DIRECTIONS HOW TO MAKE A
PRESSURE COOKER BOMB
PUBLISHED IN A BOOK POP
BLAR ANARCHISTS BILL IN
1971.
BILL?
>> Bill: REMARKABLE.
JONATHAN HUNT TONIGHT FROM
OUR NEWSROOM IN NEW YORK.
THANK YOU, JONATHAN.
LEADERS FROM AROUND THE
WORLD DESCENDING UPON
LONDON TODAY FOR THE
FUNERAL OF THE FORMER PRIME
MINISTER MARGARET THATCHER.
♪
[ APPLAUSE ]
BEFORE THE FUNERAL A GUN
CARRIAGE CARRIED HER COFFIN
TO THE STREETS OF THE
BRITISH CAPITOL TO SAINT
PAUL'S CATHEDRAL, THE SITE
OF TODAY'S SERVICE.
THERE QUEEN ELIZABETH SAT
IN THE FRONT ROW AND FORMER
VICE PRESIDENT DICK CHENEY
AMONG THE DIGNITARIES THAT
GATHERED TO REMEMBER
BRITAIN'S IRON LADY.
THATCHER WAS BRITAIN'S
FIRST AND ONLY BRITISH
PRIME MINISTER.
SHE SERVED 11 YEARS IN THAT
POSITION.
SHE DIED LAST WEEK AT THE
AGE OF 87.
HER REMAINS SCHEDULED TO BE
CREMATED TODAY IN KEEPING
WITH HER WISHES AND ASHES
TO BE PLACED NEXT TO THOSE
OF HER LATE HUSBAND.
WHAT A LIFE.
SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN
KERRY HAD AN EMOTIONAL
REACTION TODAY TO THE
BOMBINGS HERE IN HIS
HOMETOWN.
HE ALSO HAD A WARNING FOR
CONGRESS ABOUT NORTH
KOREA'S YOUNG LEADER.
PLUS A COP TRIES TO STOP AN
ILLEGAL TAXI BUT THE
DRIVER, HE HAS OTHER IDEAS.
WE WILL SHOW YOU THE REST
OF THAT VIDEO.
PLUS, BREAKING NEWS IN THE
RICIN SCARE CASE OUT OF
WASHINGTON.
WE'RE GETTING WORD OF AN
ARREST TONIGHT AS FOX
REPORTS LIVE FROM BOSTON ON
THIS WEDNESDAY EVENING.
>> Bill: ALL RIGHT
BREAKING NEWS NOW HERE ON
"THE FOX REPORT."
WORD THAT POLICE HAVE JUST
ARRESTED SOMEONE FOR
MAILING LETTERS CONTAINING
THE POISON RICIN.
INVESTIGATORS SAYING EARLY
TEST ON LETTERS SENT TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA AND
MISSISSIPPI REPUBLICAN
SENATOR ROGER WICKER WERE
POSITIVE FOR RICIN.
NOW WORD THEY HAVE ARRESTED
A MAN IN TUPELO,
MISSISSIPPI IN THAT CASE.
MIKE EMANUEL HAS BEEN ON
THE STORY THROUGHOUT THE
DAY.
IS HE LIVE ON THE HILL LATE
FOR US TONIGHT.
WHAT CAN WE REPORTED, MIKE?
WHAT ARE YOU GETTING?
>> BILL, WE HAVE SEVERAL
LAW ENFORCEMENT SOURCES WHO
TELL US THAT A MAN BY THE
NAME OF KENNETH CURTIS OF
TUPELO, MISSISSIPPI HAS
BEEN ARRESTED IN CONNECTION
WITH THESE LETTERS THAT
HAVE TESTED POSITIVE FOR
RICIN THAT HAVE BEEN SENT
TO -- ADDRESSED TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA AND SENATOR
ROGER WICKER OF
MISSISSIPPI.
SOURCES EARLY ON IN THE
INVESTIGATION WERE TELLING
US THAT IT WAS SOMEBODY
FROM MISSISSIPPI FROM
SENATOR WICKER'S HOME STATE
AND THE FBI BULLETIN THAT
WE HAVE BEEN REPORTING FROM
THAT WE OBTAINED EARLY
TODAY SAYS THE TWO LETTERS
THAT WERE SENT WERE SIGNED
I AM K.C. AND I APPROVE
THIS MESSAGE.
K.C. MAY TRANSLATE TO
KENNETH CURTIS IT IS
UNCLEAR WHEN CHARGES WILL
BE FILED.
WHETHER IT WILL BE LATER
TONIGHT OR TOMORROW.
BUT, AGAIN TO RECAP
SEVERAL FEDERAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT SOURCES SAY
ARREST HAS BEEN MADE.
KENNETH CURTIS FROM TUPELO,
MISSISSIPPI.
WE ARE GATHERING FACTS AS
QUICKLY AS POSSIBLE.
BILL?
>> Bill: MIKE, THROUGHOUT
THE DAY, YOU HAVE BEEN
REPORTING THAT WHOMEVER WAS
THE PERSON WHO MAILED THESE
LETTERS APPARENTLY -- HE
WAS PRETTY WELL KNOWN AMONG
LEGISLATORS THERE ON THE
HOUSE AND THE SENATE SIDE.
S SO DOSS THIS COINCIDE
WITH THAT INFORMATION THAT
YOU HAVE TONIGHT?
>> IT DOES.
THEY SAID THAT THIS GUY WAS
A FREQUENT LETTER WRITER TO
LAWMAKERS HERE ON CAPITOL
HILL.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS THROUGH
THE WASHINGTON.
AND, AGAIN, FROM THE FBI
BULLETIN THAT WE OBTAINED
EARLY TODAY, THEY SAID THAT
HE SIGNED IT I AM K.C. AND
I APPROVE THIS MESSAGE.
AND SO HE SEEMED PRETTY
CAVALIER ABOUT THAT HE DID
NOT PUT A -- OR THE SUSPECT
DID NOT PUT A RETURN
ADDRESS ON THESE LETTERS.
BUT THEY SEEMED FAIRLY
CONFIDENT EARLY ON THAT
THEY KNEW IT WAS SOMEBODY
FROM MISSISSIPPI SOMEBODY
WHO FREQUENTLY WROTE
LETTERS TO LAWMAKERS AND
OTHER FEDERAL OFFICIALS AND
TO RECAP AN ARREST MADE
WITHIN THE LAST HOUR OR SO,
BILL.
>> Bill: NOW, TO BE CLEAR,
SINCE THE ANTHRAX ATTACKS
IN THE FALL OF 2001, YOU
KNOW, CONGRESS CHANGED THE
TWAY RECEIVES MAIL.
WE KNOW AT THE WHITE HOUSE
THE MAIL RECEIVING CENTER
IS NOT AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
IT'S IN SOME OTHER PART OF
WASHINGTON D.C.
BUT HOW DID THE SENATE AND
THE HOUSE CHANGE THEIR
TACTICS BECAUSE MITCH
MCCONNELL SAID EARLIER
TODAY THAT THE SYSTEM THAT
WAS PUT IN PLACE BACK THEN
WORKED TODAY.
GO AHEAD AND EXPLAIN THAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY RIGHT BILL.
THEY MOVED IT OFF SITE AND
IT WENT TO FATAL IN
LANDOVER, MARYLAND WHERE
ALL OF THE MAIL THAT COMES
TO THE UNITED STATES
SENATOR'S OFFICE IS
SCREENED TESTED, OPENED,
AND ESSENTIALLY CHECKED TO
MAKE SURE IT IS CLEAR
BEFORE THEY PASS IT ON TO
THE CAPITAL COMPLEX.
SO IT DID NOT GET ANYWHERE
CLOSE TO THE CAPITAL
COMPLEX AND JAY CARNEY TOLD
US TODAY AT THE WHITE HOUSE
THAT IT DID NOT GET
ANYWHERE CLOSE TO THE WHITE
HOUSE OR TO PRESIDENT
OBAMA.
SO, SENATOR MCCONNELL WAS
QUITE HAPPY THIS MORNING.
SAID JUSTICE WOULD PREVAIL.
BUT SAID THE BOTTOM LINE
WAS THEY LEARNED A LOT FROM
THOSE 2001 ANTHRAX LETTER
ATTACKS AND THEY MADE SURE
THAT THESE LETTERS IN THIS
CASE DID NOT GET ANYWHERE
CLOSE TO THE LAWMAKER AND
TO THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
AND SO BOTTOM LINE THE
SYSTEM WORKED IN THIS CASE,
BILL.
>> Bill: YEAH, ONE MORE
THING HERE MIKE.
IS THE CASE CONSIDERED
CLOSED OR IS THERE A
POSSIBILITY OF MORE LETTERS
BEING RECEIVED OUT THERE?
>> THEY ARE ON THE LOOKOUT
FOR OTHER SUSPICIOUS
LETTERS.
WE HAD A BUNCH OF OFFICES
EVACUATED OR CLEARED AND
HAS MAT UNIFORMS COME INTO
THE CAPITOL OR OFFICES
AROUND THE CAPITOL COMPLEX
AND ALSO SOME TO SOME
DISTRICT OFFICES JUST TO BE
ABUNDANTLY CAUTIOUS TO MAKE
SURE IF THERE WAS ANYTHING
SUSPICIOUS, THAT IT WAS
CAREFULLY CHECKED OUT
BECAUSE OF COURSE ONE THING
WE KNOW THAT RICIN IN VERY
SMALL AMOUNTS CAN BE
QUIETLY THAT, QUITE DEADLY.
EVERY PRECAUTION WAS TAKEN
HERE ON CAPITOL HILL.
AND IN MANY SENATORS'
OFFICES AROUND THE COUNTRY
TO MAKE SURE ANYTHING FUNNY
IN THE MAIL WAS
DOUBLE-CHECKED BILL.
>> Bill: THANK YOU, MIKE.
GOOD WORK.
MIKE EMANUEL WITH THE
BREAKING NEWS FROM CAPITOL
HILL TONIGHT.
WE'RE AWAITING MORE
DEVELOPMENTS OUT OF TUPELO,
MISSISSIPPI WITH THE LATEST
ON THIS.
THERE WAS A LOT OF NEWS TO
FOLLOW AS YOU CAN CLEARLY
SEE FROM THE PAST 47
MINUTES.
AND THERE ARE DEVELOPMENTS
HERE IN BOSTON THAT WE WILL
BRING YOU IN A MATTER OF
MOMENTS AS OUR COVERAGE
CITIZEN -- CONTINUES HERE
ON THE BOSTON BOMBINGS HERE
ON "THE FOX REPORT."
Shoot.
Now with the Share  Everything Plan
from Verizon
connect your  camera
along with your  smartphone and tablet.
All your devices  connected
by one simple plan on  the powerful
network.
Record video.
Connect more.
So you can  do more.
The Share Everything  Plan from Verizon.
Add additional  devices like
the Samsung Galaxy Camera
for $5 monthly access.
>> Bill: BACK TO THE
BREAKING NEWS NOW, THERE
HAS BEEN AN ARREST IN THE
RICIN SCARE THAT HAS
GRIPPED WASHINGTON, D.C.
FOR THE PAST 24 HOURS.
A MAN IN TUPELO,
MISSISSIPPI, WELL KNOWN TO
AUTHORITIES APPARENTLY ON
CAPITOL HILL HAS BEEN
ARRESTED NOW.
WITH ME NOW IS DAVID CATS.
FOUNDER, PRESIDENT AND CEO
OF GROUP.
FORMER D.E.A. AND
INSTRUCTOR AT THE ACADEMY.
YOU HAVE A SPECIFIC
STRATEGY WHEN DEALING WITH
THESE MATTERS.
WHAT'S NOT CLEAR TO ME,
DAVID IS WHETHER OR NOT
THEY FOUND THE RICIN AND
WHETHER THEY TRACED IT BACK
TO MISSISSIPPI OR IF THEY
LOOKED AT HIS RETURN
ADDRESS ON AN ENVELOPE IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
IF HE WERE THAT WELL KNOWN
TO AUTHORITIES.
>> YEAH, WELL, YOU KNOW,
THE ORIGINAL REPORT
INDICATED THERE WAS NO
RETURN ADDRESS.
THAT MAY OR MAY NOT BE SO.
BUT IF HE IS FAMILIAR TO
THEM, A CERTAIN STYLE OF
WRITING OR THE ENVELOPES HE
SEND ARE VERY DISTINCTIVE
THAT MAY BE HOW THEY TRACE
HIM.
I ASSUME THE NEXT STEP IS
TO GO INTO HIS RESIDENCE OR
ANY AREA HE HAD CONTROL
OVER AND SEE WAS THERE ANY
OTHER RESIDUAL COMPONENTS.
THAT'S PROBABLY THE NEXT
STEP TO MAKE THE CASE
AGAINST HIM SOLID.
>> Bill: DAVID, THERE IS NO
INDICATION THAT ANYONE WAS
AFFECTED BY THIS RICIN.
HAD HE BEEN SUCCESSFUL,
WHAT HAPPENS TO A HUMAN
BEING WHEN THEY COME IN
CONTACT WITH IT?
>> RICIN IS AN INCREDIBLY
DEADLY TOXIN.
CLASSIFIED AS A WEAPON OF.
CASTER BEAN MORE DEADLY
THAN CYANIDE.
THERE IS NO RELIABLE
ANTIDOTE.
THEY ARE TRYING TO
MANUFACTURE ANTIDOTES NOW
BUT TO MY KNOWLEDGE NONE OF
THEM HAVE BEEN SUCCESSFULLY
MANUFACTURED.
IF SO INGESTED IT.
IF SOMEONE HAD A BROKEN
SKIN OR A CUT ON THEM ON
THEIR HAND, FOR EXAMPLE AND
HANDLED THE LETTER, COULD
VERY WELL BE TALKING ABOUT
IN TWO TO THREE DAYS
FATALITIES AS A RESULT OF
THIS.
>> Bill: LET'S BE CLEAR
THOUGH, IF SOMEBODY PUTS
RICEN IN AN ENVELOPE AND
PUTS IT IN THE MAIL, THEY
ARE OUT TO DO HARM, AREN'T
THEY?
>> YEAH, IT'S LIKE OPENING
A CANISTER FROM CYANIDE
BREATHE DEEPLY.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY 100%
INTENTIONAL ACT AND
INTENTIONAL ATTEMPT TO KILL
SOMEBODY IT'S UNLIKELY
THAT SOMEONE WOULD SURVIVE
SIGNIFICANT EXPLOSION TO
RICIN.
HOW WOULD THEY FIND THIS
SHORT OF OPENING A PACKAGE
OR AN ENVELOPE?
>> THE POSTAL SERVICE HAS
VERY VERY SOPHISTICATED
TECHNOLOGIES IN DETECTING A
ARE A VARIETY OF BIOLOGICAL
WEAPONS.
IN ADDITION, I'M ASSUMING
THEY WOULD DO EVEN X-RAY
SCAN POWDER IN ENVELOPE AND
THAT WOULD BE NECESSITATE A
NEXT LEVEL INSPECTION WHICH
WOULD PUT IT ON A FIELD
TEST AND THAT'S PROBABLY
HOW THEY GOT THE POSITIVE
RESULT FOR RICIN.
>> YEAH.
WE WERE SPEAKING WITH MIKE
EMANUEL A MOMENT AGO.
GO BACK TO MIKE IN A MOMENT
HERE.
IF THIS MAN HAS BEEN
ARRESTED, THEN HIS CASE IS
CLOSED.
BUT IT'S NOT CLEAR WHETHER
OR NOT THERE ARE OTHER
ENVELOPES OR PACKAGES OUT
THERE THAT STILL MIGHT
CONTAIN RICIN THAT HAD BEEN
MAILED PRIOR TO HIS ARREST.
>> THAT'S AN EXCELLENT.
>> Bill: WHAT DO THEY DO
NOW, DAVID?
>> EVERYONE NEEDS TO
UNDERSTAND.
I THINK IT'S CLEAR IS HE
TARGETING GOVERNMENT
OFFICIALS.
I'M SURE ALL THE MAIL
HANDLING FACILITIES,
WHETHER IT BE FEDERAL
OFFICIALS, STATE AND LOCAL
GOVERNMENT, THEY WILL BE ON
HEIGHTENED ALERT.
THAT'S AN EXCELLENT POINT
YOU RAISE.
TWO LETTERS HAVE
INTERCEPTED.
WHO KNOWS HOW MANY HE PUT
IN THE MAIL?
IT'S NOT DIFFICULT.
IT'S KIND OF LIKE IT'S A
NON-SOPHISTICATED
TECHNOLOGY.
SOMEONE WHO IS INTENT ON
CAUSING, YOU KNOW,
WIDESPREAD PANIC AND FEAR,
AND THEY DIDN'T HAVE THE
SOPHISTICATION TO
MANUFACTURE ANTHRAX OR --
RICIN MAKE SUFFICIENT
QUANTITY AND ALL THEY NEED
TO DO IS PUT IN ENVELOPES
PUT ON THE STAMPS AND DROP
THEM IN MAILBOXES AND YOU
HAVE MASS TERROR ALL OVER
THE COUNTRY.
>> Bill: DAVID, STAND BY
ONE FROM ONE MOMMY.
MIKE EMANUEL FROM CAPITOL
HILL HAS BEEN REPORTING ON
THIS STORY THROUGHOUT THE
DAY.
WHAT ARE THE PRECAUTIONS IN
PLACE NOW.
WHAT ARE THEY TELLING YOU
WHETHER IT'S TONIGHT OR
TOMORROW OR THE COMING DAYS
ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY OF
MORE LETTERS.
>> ESSENTIALLY BILL,
EVERYBODY SON THE LOOKOUT
FOR MORE LETTERS ANYTHING
THAT COMES IN NOT WITH A
RETURN ADDRESS.
THEY ARE TAKING A CLOSER
LOOK AT.
BOTTOM LINE IS THE LETTERS
THAT WERE SENT ADDRESSED TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA AND TO
SENATOR WICKER WERE BOTH
MAILED OUT ON APRIL THE 8TH
LAST WEEK FROM MEMPHIS
TENNESSEE.
AND SO THAT IS SOMETHING
THAT WAS IN COMMON BETWEEN
THE TWO LETTERS.
ALSO.  SO LANGUAGE THAT WAS
IN BOTH LETTERS, THE WAY IT
WAS SIGNED WAS IN BOTH
LETTERS.
AND SO THERE ARE
UNDOUBTEDLY SOME CLASSIFIED
ASPECTS AS PART OF THIS
INVESTIGATION THAT WILL
ALSO BE SIMILARITIES THAT
THEY ARE ON THE LOOKOUT
FOR.
BUT THE UNCLASSIFIED
VERSION THAT WE HAVE
OBTAINED ESSENTIALLY SAID
THAT SOME THE LANGUAGE WAS
THE SAME, POSTMARK WAS THE
SAME.
SOME OF THE RANTS INSIDE
WERE THE SAME.
AND SO THAT IS HOW THEY
WERE FAIRLY CONFIDENT IT
CAME FROM THIS PERSON.
IT WAS SIGNED THE SAME WAY
SAYING I AM K.C. AND I
APPROVE THIS MESSAGE.
TO SO THAT'S THE THINGS
THAT THAT HE ARE LOOKING
FOR AT THIS POINT, BILL.
>> Bill: THANK YOU MIKE.
MIKE EMANUEL LIVE ON THE
HILL.
DAVID CATS THANKS TO YOU AS
WELL.
AND YOUR EXPERTISE NOT ONLY
NOW BUT EARLIER TODAY ON
"STUDIO B."
DAVID, THANK YOU.
WE ARE WATCHING ALL THE
DEVELOPMENTS TONIGHT IN A
STRANGE TWIST AGAIN ONLY
MOMENTS AGO THE BOSTON
POLICE DEPARTMENT SENT OUT
A MESSAGE THAT THE FBI
WOULD PUT A STATEMENT OUT
AT 8:00 AND THEN QUICKLY
RETRACTED THAT.
THERE WILL BE NO STATEMENT
TONIGHT BUT THE NEWS
CONTINUES IN ONEa MOMENT.
u're treating  it well?
Yes I am.
There are a lot of places  you could
take your Explorer
for service, why do you bring   it
back to the Ford Dealership?
They specifically  work on Fords.
It seems to me like  the best care.
And it's equal or less Money  so it's
a value for me.
Get a free brake inspection and
brake pads installed for just
49.95 after rebates when you
use the Ford Service Credit  Card.
Who doesn't enjoy value?
Man: The charcoal went out  already?
... Forget it.
VO: There's more barbeque time  in
every bag of
Kingsford Original Charcoal.
Kingsford.
Slow down and grill.
♪
(Train Horn)
VO: Wherever our trains go,
the economy comes to life.
Norfolk Southern.
One line
infinite possibilities.
>> Bill: THERE IS BREAKING
NEWS ON TWO SIGNIFICANT
STORIES TONIGHT.
FIRST ON THE BOMBING HERE
IN BOSTON.
FOX NEWS CONFIRMS THAT A
PICTURE, AN IMAGE OF TWO
MEN, TWO PERSONS OF
INTEREST IS NOW BEING
CIRCULATED THROUGH THE LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS HERE
IN BOSTON ACROSS THE
COUNTRY LOOKING FOR THE
IDENTITY OF TWO MEN WHO
WERE SEEN NEAR THE SCENE OF
THE BOMBING EXPLOSIONS ON
MONDAY AFTERNOON NEAR THE
FINISH LINE BEHIND ME ON
BOYLSTON STREET.
THIS IS AN ACTIVE
INVESTIGATION THAT IS
ONGOING TONIGHT.
THERE SAN EXPECTED FBI
BRIEFING EARLIER TONIGHT.
THAT WILL NOT HAPPEN.
AS WE MENTIONED A MOMENT
AGO, THERE WAS AN EXPECTED
STATEMENT FROM THE FBI.
THAT, TOO, WAS CANCELLED.
SO, AS THIS INVESTIGATION
MOVES FORWARD SOME TRACE
EVIDENCE HAS BEEN MADE
PUBLIC.
SOME PHOTOGRAPHS OF SOME OF
THE BOMB RESIDUE THAT WAS
FOUND ON THE STREET A
QUARTER MILE BEHIND US
HERE, THAT IS CIRCULATING
THROUGHOUT THE LAW
ENFORCEMENT COMMUNITY.
AND THE PUBLIC, FOR THAT
MATTER AS WELL.
THAT'S THE LATEST ON THE
BOSTON BOMBINGS.
AND THERE IS MORE BREAKING
NEWS HERE ON THE FOX NEWS
CHANNEL, I'M BILL HEMMER
AND GOOD EVENING.
WE WILL JOIN THE ROIFERL
FACTOR IN A MOMENT.
BUT, FIRST, FOX NEWS
CONFIRMING POLICE HAVE
ARRESTED SOMEONE FOR
MAILING LETTERS CONTAINING
THE DEADLY TOXIN RICIN.
THOSE LETTERS ADDRESSED TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA AND
MISSISSIPPI REPUBLICAN
SENATOR ROGER WICKER.
WE HAVE LEARNED THE SUSPECT
IS A MAN FROM TUPELO,
MISSISSIPPI, A MAN WITH A
LONG HISTORY OF SENDING
LETTERS TO LAWMAKERS IN
WASHINGTON.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THAT
EARLY TESTS ON THOSE
LETTERS WERE POSITIVE.
THAT MAIL NEVER CAME CLOSE
TO THE PRESIDENT OR THE
SENATOR FOR THAT MATTER.
THEY SET OFF ALARMS THOUGH
IN POSTAL SCREENING
FACILITIES AWAY FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE AND AWAY FROM
CHILL.
I WANT TO START OUR
COVERAGE THIS HOUR NOW WITH
MIKE EMANUEL WHO IS LIVE ON