FREEZER TO ESCAPE THIS
TORNADO.
WE'LL CONTINUE OUR COVERAGE
ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL AS WE
ALWAYS DO.
FAIR BALANCED AND
UNAFRAID.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING
COVERAGE NOW WITH BREAKING
NEWS AS FOX REPORTS LIVE
TONIGHT, AN ABSOLUTE
DISASTER IN THE HEART LAND
OF AMERICA.
WE ARE WATCHING FOR THE
SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
WHERE DURING "STUDIO B"
THIS AFTERNOON.
ENORMOUS TORNADO CUT A PATH
OF DESTRUCTION ACROSS THAT
CITY.
GOING THESE ARE LIVE
PICTURES COMING IN FROM
MOORE NOW.
HOMES AND BUSINESSES IN AT
LEAST TWO ELEMENTARY
SCHOOLS BADLY DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED.
WE DO NOT YET KNOW EXACTLY
HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE HURT OR
DEAD.
A LOCAL CBS NEWS STATION
REPORTS THAT ALL KIDS ARE
NOW ACCOUNTED FOR IN ONE OF
TWO ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS THAT
WERE HIT BRIAR WOOD
ELEMENTARY.
WE HAVE NOT YET CONFIRMED
THAT BUT WE ARE NOW HEARING
THAT RESCUERS HAVE PULLED
SEVERAL CHILDREN ALIVE FROM
THE RUBBLE AT PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY.
WE DO NOT YET KNOW WHAT
SORT OF INJURIES THEY HAVE,
SEPTEMBER WHAT YOU HAVE
HEARD IN THE LAST HOUR.
WITNESSES SAY THE TORNADO
WAS A MILE OR UP TO TWO
MILES WIDE IN SOME AREAS.
THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE REPORTS THIS STORM
IS AT LEAST AN -- THIS
TORNADO AT LEAST AN EF-4 ON
THE SCALE THAT
METEOROLOGISTS USE.
THAT'S THE SECOND HIGHEST
LEVEL.
IT MEANS WINDS OF BETWEEN
166 AND 200 MILES PER HOUR.
THE TORNADO WAS ON THE
GROUND FOR AT LEAST 45
MINUTES.
THERE WERE WARNINGS, 16
MINUTES BEFORE THE TORNADO
HIT MOORE OKLAHOMA.
16 MINUTES IN ADVANCE THEY
GOT A WARNING A TORNADO
WARNING THAT A TORNADO WAS
ON THE GROUND AND HEADED
FOR THEM.
WE DO NOT YET KNOW HOW MANY
COUNTLESS LIVES THAT SAVED.
BUT IT'S ALWAYS HOW MANY
TOOK THEM SERIOUSLY AND
TOOK SHELTER.
VOLUNTEERS AND FIRST
RESPONDERS ARE ON THE
GROUND IN MOORE LOOKING FOR
ANYBODY WHO MAY STILL BE
TRAPPED BENEATH THE DEBREE
HOPING THAT EVEN WITH THE
MAGNITUDE LIKE NOTHING WE
HAVE YEARS IN THIS NATION
THAT THEY WILL FIND ANY
NEIGHBORS FRIENDS, BAND
MEMBERS -- MEMBERS WHO MAY
BE MISSING.
JEFF WHAT YOU HAVE SEEN?
SHEP,UNBELIEVABLE
AFTERNOON.
NEAR THE NEW CASTLE EXIT
WHERE THIS ALL STARTED ALL
AFTERNOON WE WERE ON THE
STORM JUST SOUTHWEST OF
OKLAHOMA CITY BEFORE THE
TORNADO DEVELOPED IN
OKLAHOMA CITY.
I HAVE GOT OTHER ON THE
GROUND IN MOORE IN THAT
AREA TELLING ME MASS
CASUALTIES EXTENT OF
INJURIES I CANNOT TELL YOU
HOW MANY IF A TALLAHASSEE
TATTLES THEY ARE SEEING AT
THIS POINT.
IT'S WORSE THAN MAY 3RD OF
1999.
VERY SIMILAR TRACK.
SIMILAR NEIGHBORHOODS HIT
NOW LEVELED.
I JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE
WITH MY CHASERS IN MOORE.
PUT A PLEA OUT ON FACEBOOK
OR TWITTER ASKING
MANAGEMENT PEOPLE TO
RESPOND TO MOORE.
THERE ARE PEOPLE STILL
TRAPPED IN BUILDINGS UNDER
HOUSES AND BUILDINGS ALL
THROUGH THE MOORE AREA.
BOTH IN APARTMENT COMPLEXES
AS WELL AS THE RESIDENTIAL
AREAS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE ON FOOT
AND THERE IS A LOT OF
PEOPLE INJURED --
[INAUDIBLE]
>> Shepard: JEFF, THANK
YOU.
WE HAVE GOTTEN WORD FROM
THE MAYOR OF MOORE THAT
MUCH OF THE TOWN IS
DESTROYED.
THE HOSPITAL IS PRETTY MUCH
DESTROYED SAYS THE MAYOR.
MAYOR LEWIS.
GLEN LEWIS.
AND IN ADDITION, WORD THERE
ARE TWO ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS
INVOLVED HERE.
ONE, PLAZA ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL WHERE EVERYONE IS
ACCOUNTED FOR.
AND THERE IS ANOTHER SCHOOL
BRIER CREEK ELEMENTARY
WHICH WE WATCHED AS
RESIDENTS WERE TRYING TO
BRING PEOPLE FROM
UNDERNEATH THE RUBBLE THE
SCHOOL CHILDREN HIT IN A
BATHROOM IN ONE CASE AS THE
TORNADO SWEPT RIGHT OVER.
THESE ARE LIVE PICTURES
COMING IN.
IT'S JUST THREE MINUTES
PAST 6:00 IN THE CENTRAL
TIME ZONE AND IN MOORE
OKLAHOMA A THE FOREVER
PIEWLS OUT YOU CAN SEE THE
PATH THAT THIS STORM CUT.
OUR STORM CHASER MENTIONED
A STORM THAT HIT IN 1999
THAT IS THE BELLWETHER FOR
EVERYBODY IN THIS PART OF
THE COUNTRY.
IT CUT A PATH THROUGH MOORE
AND SURROUNDING AREAS LIKE
NOTHING ANYONE HAD EVER
SEEN.
THE PATH OF THIS ONE IS
SIMILAR, THOUGH LONGER,
SIMILAR, THOUGH WIDER.
SO THIS STORM IS SIMILAR
BUT WORSE.
AND THAT WAS THE STORM BY
WHICH ALL OTHERS WERE JUDGE
DOLLARS.
IT IS AS IF HURRICANE
CAMILLE IN SOUTH
MISSISSIPPI AND LOUISIANA
WAS ORIGINALLY YOUR
HURRICANE OF RECORD.
THIS IS THE THING TO WHICH
WE POINT AS THE WORST IT
CAN BE.
THAT IS UNTIL HURRICANE
KATRINA CAME THROUGH.
AND CHANGED THE LANDSCAPE
ENTIRELY IT IS OUR BELIEF
THAT THAT THAT'S WHAT WE
HAVE HAD HERE.
HERE IS THE GOOD NEWS AFTER
999, THE PROBLEM WAS THAT
SO MANY PEOPLE DID NOT HAVE
ADEQUATE STORM SHELTERS.
THERE WAS AN AREA WIDE PUSH
TO INCREASE THE NUMBER OF
STORM SHELTERS.
EMERGENCY WARNING SYSTEMS
WERE NOT UP TO DATE THERE
WAS AN AREA WIDE PUSH TO DO
THAT AND TODAY THEY GOT 16
MINUTES' WARNING WHICH, IN
TORNADO ALLEY IS, A LONG
TIME THAT STORMS WERE ON
THE WAY.
IN TORNADO ALLEY YOUR
FAMILY HAS A PLAN IF YOU
HAVE ANY SENSE AT ALL OF
WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN WHEN
THAT SIREN GOES OFF.
AND JUST YESTERDAY, THEY
HAD SEVERE DAMAGE FROM
ANOTHER STORM.
SO THEY WERE PAYING
ATTENTION.
AND HOPEFULLY TODAY MANY
PEOPLE'S LIVES WERE SAVED
AS A RESULT.
KOKH IS ON SCENE AT ONE OF
THESE ELM TRI SCHOOLS AND
LIVE.
LISTEN.
>> FMENTS.
>> SOME OF THE PHOTOS
GETTING IN FROM YOU THAT
TAKES OK FOX.COM.
CONTINUE TO SEND THEM TO
US.
HERE IS A PICTURE RIGHT
HERE WHERE IT LOOKS LIKE.
>> Shepard: KILL THAT
AUDIO, PLEASE, THANK YOU.
THE RESCUE EFFORTS ARE
CONTINUING I-35 HAS BEEN
DESTROYED ACROSS THIS AREA
AND IS NOW CLOSED AND
RESCUE ATTEMPTS ARE STILL
UNDERWAY.
RIGHT NOW AUTHORITIES ARE
WORKING TO CORE CON OFF AN
AREA AROUND THIS ENTIRE
DEVASTATED CITY SO THAT
PEOPLE CANNOT GET IN AND
OUT.
AS THEY CONTINUE THEIR
RESCUE WORK WE DO HAVE A
REPORT FROM THE LOCAL CBS
STATION AND A TRAGIC ONE IT
IS FROM KFOR, A FAN AS IT
IT PARTICULAR NEWS
OPERATION THEY RUN THERE.
CAN I TELL YOU FIRST HAND.
FOUR PEOPLE KFOR REPORTS
ARE DEAD AND MORE NEAR
FOURTH STREET AND TELEPHONE
ROAD.
A MOTHER AND BABY INCLUDED
IN THE COUNT.
AS THE REPORT INDICATE FROM
THE LOCAL NBC I MEANT TO
SAY, THEY TRIED TO GET INTO
A FREEZER DURING THE
TORNADO.
WERE UNABLE TO DO SO AND
ALL WERE KILLED.
THERE IS NO WAY FOR US TO
KNOW AT THIS MOMENT HOW
DEVASTATING THIS HAS BEEN
IN THE WAY OF HUMAN INJURY
AND LOSS OF LIFE.
WE DO KNOW THAT DOZENS OF
PEOPLE ARE BEING TREATED.
WE WATCHED TRIAGE CENTERS
BEING SET UP ON SCENE.
IN SOME CASES WITHOUT
APPARENTLY MEDICAL
PERSONNEL AVAILABLE.
THEY COULDN'T GET IN AND
OUT THEREOF IN THE EARLY
GOING.
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL CHILDREN
PULLED FROM THE RUBBLE THAT
WAS THEIR SCHOOL AND
WATCHED RESIDENTS COME TO
ASSIST LITTLE CHILDREN ON
CURBS.
WAITING FOR MOM AND DAD TO
WALK THERE TO PICK THEM UP.
WE'RE TOLD THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENED.
AS WE SEE THIS DEVASTATION
AND A BULLDOZER COME IN TO
TRY TO HE REMOVE.
MAKE SURE NO ONE IS STILL
INJURED.
THIS TORNADO SITUATION IS
STILL VERY ACTIVE THERE ARE
V. BEEN WARNING ALL
AFTERNOON AND THERE STILL
ARE JANICE DEAN IN OUR
WEATHER SERVICE.
WHAT DO WE KNOW?
>> THE PRELIMINARY REPORTS
THAT WE ARE GETTING IN OVER
THIS TWO-DAY TORNADO
OUTBREAK.
37 REPORTS OF TORNADOES.
AND THE TORNADO THAT WE
HAVE SEEN THE EXTENSIVE
DAMAGE FROM, THE MOORE
OKLAHOMA WE THINK RIGHT NOW
IS AN EF-4.
BUT THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE HAS TO GO OUT AND
ASSESS THE DAMAGE.
I REMEMBER WITH THE JOPLIN,
MISSOURI TORNADO TWO YEARS
AGO ALMOST TO THE DATE.
THEY DEEMED IT AN EF 4 AND
THEN THEY WENT OUT AND DID
THE ASSESSMENT AND UNDER IT
TO AN EF 56789 IN DAMAGE IS
SO EXTENSIVE.
WE'RE REALLY GOING TO HAVE
TO WAIT UNTIL THE N S GOES
OUT AND DOES THEIR FINAL
REPORT.
40 MINUTES ON THE GROUND IS
WHAT WE ARE ALSO HEARING
FROM THE STORM PREDICTION
CENTER NORMAN, OKLAHOMA.
AS YOU MENTIONED 16 MINUTES
WARNING FROM THE TORNADO
WARNING.
AND THE SIRENS GOING OFF.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THE
ENHANCED FUJITA SCALE
THAT'S WHAT WE GO OUT THE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE
GOES OUT THERE.
WE DO THINK THE WINDS WERE
UP TO 200 MILES PER HOUR
WITH THIS PARTICULAR STORM.
>> Shepard: JANICE, THE
OKLAHOMA GOVERNMENT, A MARY
FALLON HAS DEPLOYED 80
OKLAHOMA NATIONAL GUARD
MEMBERS TO ASSIST WITH THE
SEARCH AND RESCUE
OPERATIONS.
THE TROOPS WILL ALSO HELP
ESTABLISH THIS PERIMETER
ARRANGEDS DEVASTATED AREAS
INCLUDING MOORE.
SHE SPOKE WITH THE
PRESIDENT TODAY WHO OFFERED
THE NATION'S HELP AND GAVE
A DIRECT LINE TO HIS
OFFICE.
IN ADDITION, THE MAYOR OF
OKLAHOMA CITY NEARBY, THIS
IS A SUBURB OF SORTS
SENDING ITS EMERGENCY
RESPONSE RESOURCES TO THIS
AREA TO HELP.
OF THE OKIN WHICH IS THE
NEWSPAPER OF RECORD FOR THE
AREA.
THE HEADLINE SUMS IT UP
THIS WAY.
OKLAHOMA SUCKER PUNCHED BY
SECOND ROUND OF TWISTERS
STILL STAGGERING FROM
YESTERDAY'S TORNADOES.
OKLAHOMA PICK THEMSELVES UP
FROM THE KANSAS ON MONDAY
ONLY TO BE HIT BY A SECOND
IS ROUND OF FIERCE TWISTERS
TODAY.
THIS MASSIVE ONE RECORD
THROUGH MOORE AND SOUTH
OKLAHOMA CITY THIS
AFTERNOON.
GRINDING UP NEIGHBORHOODS
AND RAVAGING AT LEAST ONE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN ITS
PATH.
OF COURSE, ANOTHER STRUCK
AS WELL.
AGAIN I'M READING FROM THE
OKLAHOMAN.
RUSHED GLANCES TO BRIAR
WOOD ELEMENTARY COOL ONE OF
TWO WE MENTIONED TO THE
MOORE SCHOOL DISTRICT AND
SEVERAL HOMES BUSINESSES
AND INTERSECTIONS SPAWNING
TO MULTIPLE INJURIES.
PARENTS OF THESE CHILDREN
COULD BE SEEN RUSHING TO
THE SCHOOL, DODGING DOWNED
POWER LINES AND SCATTERED
DEBRIS.
IT HAS BEEN A SEEN OF
UNBELIEVABLE CHAOS.
A GIRL HO A TENDS BRIAR
WOOD ELEMENTARY TELLS KOKH
TELEVISION THE REPORTER
THAT HER SCHOOL WAS
TRASHED.
THERE WAS SIMPLY NOTHING
LEFT THERE.
SEVERAL CHILDREN HAVE NOW
BEEN PULLED OUT OF THE
RUBBLE ALIVE IN ONE OF
THESE SCHOOLS.
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL THERE IN MOORE AFTER
THE MASSIVE TORNADO HIT.
RESCUE WORKERS LIFTED THE
KIDS FROM THE RUBBLE BEFORE
THEY WERE PASSED DOWN A
HUMAN CHAIN AND TAKEN TO IT
A TRIAGE CENTER SET UP
RIGHT THERE IN THE PARKING
LOT OF THAT DEVASTATED
SCHOOL AGAIN SOUTHWEST OF
OKLAHOMA CITY.
THE ROOF IS GONE.
THE WALLS HAD FALLEN OR
BEEN MANGLED.
AND SO MANY OF THESE
STUDENTS SHELTERED IN PLACE
IN THE HALLS.
THESE ARE NEW PICTURES THAT
WE ARE JUST GETTING IN HERE
AT FOX NEWS CHANNEL ON THE
RIGHT-HAND SIDE OF YOUR
SCREEN.
AND LIVE PICTURES THAT ARE
COMING IN FROM THE SEARCH
AND RESCUE OPERATIONS.
I MENTIONED THE STORM THAT
HIT THERE IN 1999.
IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE
DEVASTATION.
THIS ONE IT APPEARS IN THE
EARLY GOING ACCORDING TO
EVERYONE THERE IS EVEN
WORSE.
THE FIRST OF THESE STORMS
HAPPENED LAST NIGHT AND
THEY CAME ACROSS LIKE A
FREIGHT TRAIN.
THIS MORNING, IN THE EARLY
GOING THEY WERE CLEANING
UP AND THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE BEGAN TO WARN JUST
AS IT HAD THE NIGHT BEFORE,
GET OUT NOW.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT THE
WARNING WAS LAST NIGHT IN
ONE PARTICULAR TOWN.
THE STORM IS COMING.
GO TO A STORM SHELTER OR
GET OUT OF ITS PATH
IMMEDIATELY.
THE NATIONAL WEATHER    NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE BEGAN WITH THE SAME
WARNINGS TODAY AND THE HOPE
IS MANY PEOPLE HEEDED THEM.
OTHER CORRESPONDENT CASEY
STEGALL IS IN MOORE
OKLAHOMA NOW.
HE HAD BEEN DOWN THE LINE
FROM THE STORM FOR OUR
COVERAGE OF WHAT HAPPENED
LAST NIGHT.
AND IS NOW IN MOORE.
CASEY, WHAT DO YOU SEE?
>> SHEPARD I'M AT 7/11 GAS
STATION AND I WALKED UP TO
AN OKLAHOMA CITY POLICE
OFFICER.
ALTHOUGH THIS IS THE CITY
OF MOORE OBVIOUSLY FIRST
RESPONDERS FROM ALL OVER
THE STATE HAVE COME IN
OKLAHOMA CITY POLICE
OFFICER HAVE TOLD ME FOUR
HAVE DIED AT THE 7/11 WHERE
I'M STANDING NOW.
IT IS A SCENE OF CHAOS.
GENTLEMAN DESCRIBE IT I'M
LOOKING AROUND ME, I'M
LOOKING THROUGH RUBBLE.
PEOPLE ARE THROWING DEBRIS
UP IN THE AIR TRYING TO
REACH PEOPLE IT'S ALMOST
LIKE PEOPLE ARE IN
DISBELIEF IN SHOCKS.
CAN'T SAY ANY SPECIFICS
ABOUT THE 7/11 WHERE WE
ARE.
DESPERATELY TRYING TO
ESTABLISH TOUR CONNECTION
BRING YOU LIVE PICTURES OUT
OF THE GROUND.
>> Shepard: WE LOOK FORWARD
TO THAT THE GOVERNOR SAID
THE COMMUNICATIONS IS THE
BIGGEST PROBLEM.
GOVERNOR FALLON SAID THE
SCOPE OF THE DISASTER IS SO
GREAT THAT STATE OFFICIALS
NEED MORE TIME TO EVEN OPEN
LINES OF COMMUNICATIONS IS
RESCUERS.
AS A RESULT OF THIS
GOVERNOR FALLON HAS NOT
BEEN ABLE TO RECEIVE THE
REPORTS THAT WE HAVE NOW
CONFIRMED OF THESE
FATALITIES, FOUR THAT YOU
MENTIONED THERE OF THE
7/11.
FOUR MORE IN A HOME AS
REPORTED BY KFOR TELEVISION
IN OKLAHOMA CITY.
THEY SAID THE GOVERNOR SAYS
THE LAND LINES ARE DOWN IN
THE MOORE AREA AND SO MANY
PEOPLE USING THEIR MOBILE
PHONES THAT CELL LINES ARE
CONGESTED AND MANY CASES
THE CELL LINES ARE DOWN
MARC AGE IN DAMAGE AS STORM
RIPS THROUGH NEIGHBORHOODS
SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA CITY.
TWO MILES WIDE RIPS THROUGH
AREAS SOUTH OF MOORE.
INITIAL REPORTS FROM KFOR
NBC STATION THERE AT LEAST
FOUR PEOPLE KILLED.
NOW THIS REPORT OF FOUR
MORE AT THE 7/11.
SADLY WE BELIEVE THAT THE
NEWS WILL GET WORSE BEFORE
IT GETS BETTER.
THE CHOPPERS ARE IN THE
AIR, OUR CORRESPONDENTS ARE
ON THE GROUND.
THIS IS BREAKING NEWS ON
FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ Male Announcer ]    HOUSE RULE NUMBER
53.    BIG TIME TASTE    SHOULD FIT
IN A LITTLE TIME CUP.    NEW SINGLE
SERVE CAFE    COLLECTIONS FROM MAXWELL
HOUSE    NOW AVAILABLE FOR USE
IN THE KEURIG K-CUP BREWER.    ALWAYS
GOOD TO THE LAST DROP.
I'M SO GLAD YOU CALLED.  THANK YOU.
WE'RE NOT IN LONDON,  ARE WE?  NO.
WHY?  APPARENTLY  MY DEBIT CARD IS.
WHAT?  I KNOW.  DON'T WORRY,  WE HAVE
CANCELLED YOUR OLD CARD.  GREAT. THANK
YOU.  IN ADDITION TO US  MONITORING
YOUR ACCOUNTS  FOR UNUSUAL ACTIVITY,
YOU COULD ALSO SET UP  FREE ACCOUNT
ALERTS.  OKAY.    [ Female Announcer
]    AT WELLS FARGO WE'RE WORKING
AROUND THE CLOCK    TO HELP PROTECT
YOUR MONEY    AND FINANCIAL    INFORMATION.
HERE'S YOUR  TEMPORARY CARD.  WELCOME
BACK.  HOW WAS LONDON?    [ Female
Announcer ]    WHEN PEOPLE TALK,
GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.  YOU MAKE A GREAT
TEAM.  IT'S BEEN THAT WAY  SINCE E
DAY YOU MET.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
ITLD BE A QUESTION  OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL  FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE  READY ANYTIME  THE MOMENT'S
RIGHT.
YOU CABE  MORE CONFIDENT  IN YOUR
ABILITY  TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME  CIALIS IS THE  ONLY
DAILY  ED TABLET
APPROVED TO  TREAT ED AND  SYMPTOMS
OF BPH
LIKE NEEDING TO GO  FREQUENTLY OR
URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS  AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU  TAKE NITRATES
FOR CHEST PAIN
AS THIS MAY CAUSE  UNSAFE  DROP IN
BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL  IN EXCESS WITH
CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE  HEADACHE,
UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,  SEEK IMMEDTE
MEDICAL HEL
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING  MORE THAN
4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE  OR
LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC  REACTIONS
SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS  TONGUE OR THROAT
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING  OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET  MEDICAL
HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT  CIALIS FOR
DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
It's Monday.  A brand new start.
Your chance to rise and shine.  With
CenturyLink as your  trusted technology
partner  you can do just that.  With
our visionary   cloud infrastructure
global broadband network and  custom
communications solutions,  your business
is more   reliable - secure - agile.
And with responsive,  dedicated support,
we help you shine  every day of the
week.
What makes the Sleep
Number store different?  You walk
into a  conventional mattress
store, it's really not  about you.
They say, "Well, if you  wanted a
firm bed you can
lie on one of those.
We provide the exact  individualization
that
your body needs.
Oh, yeah!
Wow.
Once you experience it  there's no
going back.
At the Sleep Number  Memorial Day
Sale,
save on the closeout of  our Classic
Special
Edition bed set.
Now just $1299-a savings  of $600.
Only at the Sleep Number  store.
Sleep Number.
Comfort Individualized.
rd: 16 MINUTES PAST
6:00 IN MOORE OKLAHOMA.
WHERE WE ARE GETTING NEWS
NOW FROM BRIAR WOOD
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
ONE OF TWO ELEMENTARY
SCHOOLINGS STRUCK BY THIS
MASSIVE TORNADO THIS
AFTERNOON ALL STUDENTS AT
BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL ARE NOW ACCOUNTED
FOR.
IT'S OUR UNDERSTANDING THAT
EVERYONE IN THAT SCHOOL
SOMEHOW SURVIVED.
THE REST OF THE NEWS IS NOT
AS GOOD AS WE WOULD HOPE
BUT FOUR DEAD AT 7/11 STORE
THERE FOUR MORE DEAD AS
THEY TRIED TO GET INTO A
FREEZE TORE ESCAPE THIS
STORM DEFICIT ALL AROUND.
REMINISCENT OF JOPLIN,
MISSOURI.
BARK RIPPED OFF THE TREES.
TREES SPLIT IN HALF.
ITS INSULATION UP IN THE
BRANCHES.
IT IS TWISTED METAL AROUND
TELEPHONE POLES.
AT THE 7/11 IT' AS TO BE A
GAS PUMP BUT IT'S NOTHING
BUT ELECTRONICS AND WIRES
HANGING OUT.
THE PUMP STILTED SIDEWAYS
IT GIVES YOU CHILLS.
IS IT DOESN'T MATTER LAST
WHEN I WAS ON THE GROUND
COVERING DEADLY TORNADOES
AND LAST NIGHT COVERING
THESE AND NOW IT DOESN'T
MATTER HOW MANY TIMES YOU
SEE THIS.
IT'S JUST ABSOLUTELY GIVES
YOU THE SHIVERS AND TO SIT
HERE RIGHT NOW.
FIRST RESPONDERS FROM ALL
OVER FLOODING IN HERE.
YELLING AT EACH OTHER.
SHEP THEN EXCUSE ME FOR
JUST A MOMENT.
LIVE WITNESS FROM K NEXT
THING YOU KNOW COMING
ACROSS.
BRICKS HEAR IF COMING IN.
IT WAS TRYING TO STUCK THE
STORM SELLER OUT OF THE
GROUND UNLASTLED LATCH THE
DOOR.
CAVED THE DOOR.
IN ONCE IF ENDED HE WE OF
COURSE GOT OUT.
I CAR IS GONE.
I CAN'T FIND IT INSPECTS
NOWHERE TO BE FOUND AND
THERE IS AN SIN ANGEL OF
BRANDON BROUGHT ME HOME.
WHEN I GOT HOME I REALIZED
THAT THERE IS NOTHING LEFT
OF MY HOUSE.
THE FRONT IS STILL STANDING
BUT THE BACK GONE.
MY BATHROOM HONESTLY SUN
TOUCHED.
WE HAVE LOST ANIMALS.
WE HAVE LOST EVERYTHING.
WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING LEFT
MY PARENTS I CAN'T GET
AHOLD OF THEM.
WE HAVE NO CELL.
SO IF THEY ARE OUT THERE
AND THEY ARE WATCHING,
PLEASE LET THEM KNOW THAT I
AND MY FAMILY IS OKAY.
WE WILL MAKE IT.
WE WILL BE OKAY BUT
EVERYTHING IS GONE.
>> AND A LOT OF FOLKS
WATCHING RIGHT NOW ARE WON
DRG WHAT THEY CAN DO TO
HELP YOUR FAMILY.
WHAT DO YOU GUYS NEED RIGHT
NOW.
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I HONESTLY DON'T KNOW.
I KNOW THAT -- I DON'T KNOW
WHERE WE ARE GOING TO GO
TONIGHT.
WE OBVIOUSLY CAN'T STAY
HERE.
I DON'T KNOW HOW TO PROTECT
MY HOUSE FROM PEOPLE THAT
MIGHT NOT WANT TO BE ON THE
GOOD SIDE.
I REALLY DON'T KNOW.
I MEAN I THINK WE NEED, YOU
KNOW THIS WHOLE COMMUNITY
RIGHT HERE PLAZA TOWERS
PEOPLE NEED A LOT.
THEY NEED HELP CLEANING UP.
WE ARE OBVIOUSLY GOING TO
NEED THAT I JUST -- I
HONESTLY DON'T KNOW AT THIS
POINT.
I'M JUST IN SHOCK.
I'M STILL IN SHOCK.
>> Shepard: SHOCK ACROSS
THE HEART LAND OF AMERICA
AND BEYOND AS WE WATCH
ABSOLUTE DEVASTATION IN AND
AROUND MOORE OKLAHOMA.
TORNADO WARNINGS ARE STILL
UP AND IN FORCE.
RESCUERS ARE OUT TRYING TO
MAKE SURE THAT NOBODY NEEDS
ASSISTANCE.
BUT THE CHANCES ARE THERE
ARE PLENTY WHO DO.
OUR COVERAGE WILL CONTINUE
AFTER THIS.
YOU HURT MY FEELINGS  TODD.  I DID?
WHEN VISA SIGNATURE  ASKED EVERYBODY
WHAT UPGRADED EXPERIENCES  REALLY
MATTERED...  YOU SUGGESTED  LUXURY
CAR SERVICE  INSTD OF "STRENGTH TRAINING
WITH PATRICK WILLIS."
COME ON TODD!  FLAP THEM CHICKEN WINGS.
[ grunts ]  WELL,  I TRAVEL A LOT
AND UMM...
[ Male Announcer ]    AT VISA SIGNATURE,
EVERY UPGRADEDXPERIENCE    COMES FROM
LISTENING    TO OUR CARDHOLDERS.
VISA SIGNATURE.    YOUR IDEA    OF
WHAT A CARD SHOULD BE.
ARE YOU STILL SLEEPING?
JUST WANTED TO CHECK AND MAKE  SURE
THAT WE WERE ON SCHEDULE.
THE FIRST TECHNOLOGY  OF ITS KIND...
MOM AND DAD, I HAVE GREAT NEWS.
IS NOW PROVIDING  ANSWERS FAMILIES
NEED.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
[ engine revving ]  ♪ ♪    [ Male
Announcer ]    EVERY CAR WE BUILD
MUST MAKE ADRENALINE PUMP    AND PULSES
QUICKEN.  ♪ ♪    TO HELP YOU    NOT
JUST TO STAY ALIVE...    BUT FEEL
ALIVE.    THE C-CLASS IS NO EXCEPTION.
IT'S A MERCEDES-BENZ    THROUGH AND
THROUGH.    SEE YOUR AUTHORIZED
MERCEDES-BENZ DEALER    FOR EXCEPTIONAL
OFFERS    THROUGH MERCEDES-BENZ
FINANCIAL SERVICES.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS
OUT OF OKLAHOMA CITY IN THE
TOWN OF MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
WHERE THE CHOPPERS CONTINUE
TO HOVER ABOVE WHAT IS JUST
AN UNBELIEVABLE SCENE.
A HOME AFTER HOME BUSINESS
AFTER BUSINESS.
EVEN SOME SCHOOLS SCHOOLS
DEVASTATED WITH A MASSIVE
TORNADO CAME ROARING
THROUGH TODAY.
AND DOWN BELOW YOU CAN SEE
PEOPLE JUST TRYING TO
BECOME RESCUERS THIS
AFTERNOON LOOKING FOR
ANYBODY WHO MIGHT BE
TRAPPED BENEATH ANYBODY WHO
MIGHT NEED HELP:  THEY ARE
COMPARING THIS TO THE GREAT
STORM OF 1999 WHICH RECORD
THROUGH THIS AREA BETWEEN
9:00 P.M. AND MIDNIGHT.
IN OTHER WORDS IT WAS DARK
OUTSIDE.
MORE DIFFICULT TO TAKE
SHELTER.
THIS AFTERNOON'S STORM HIT
AROUND 3:00 LOCAL TIME AND
ON THE GROUND FOR 45
MINUTES.
LIGHT OF DAY AND MANY OF
THEM HOPEFULLY GET AWAY.
OFFICIALLY THE DEATH TOLL
IS AT 6 THUS FAR.
BUT WE KNOW OF FOUR PEOPLE
ACCORDING TO THE REPORTING
OF THE LOCAL NBC STATION OR
I SHOULD SAY THE CBS
STATION WHO DIED WHILE
TRYING TO SHELTER IN A
FREEZER AND FOUR OTHERS WHO
DIED AT 7/11.
COMMUNICATIONS ARE
IMPOSSIBLE AT THIS POINT.
AND THE NUMBERS LIKE THAT
WILL BE HARD TO COME BY FOR
THE FORESEEABLE FUTURE.
OUR METEOROLOGIST RICK
REICHMUTH WAS IN THE AREA
COVERING THE STORMS WHICH
HIT LAST NIGHT AND
ANTICIPATING THOSE FROM
TODAY.
RICK, THIS IS HARD TO
BELIEVE.
>> IT'S VERY HARD TO
BELIEVE, SHEP.
YOU KNOW, WE HE HAVE BEEN
UNDER THIS THREAT AND THESE
BIG CITIES FOR A COUPLE
DAYS.
STORM CUTTING TO THE.
CUTTING JUST TO THE SOUTH
AND MOORE.
TWO DAYS THAT THEY HAVE
BEEN DEALING WITH.
YOU KNOW, AFTER YOU HAD
WHAT YOU SAW YESTERDAY
REALLY SIGNIFICANT DAMAGE
RIGHT AROUND HERE.
YOU DIDN'T THINK IT WOULD
HAPPEN THAT BIG AGAIN.
THIS IS ONE OF THOSE THINGS
THAT PEOPLE ARE HAVING HARD
TIME GETTING THEIR MINDS
AROUND EXACTLY HOW BIG THIS
IS.
>> Shepard: USUALLY RICK,
AFTER A TORNADO LIKE THIS
HITS THE FRONT MOVES ON
AND YOU ARE ABLE TO AT
LEAST CLEAN UP AFTER WHAT'S
HAPPENED.
THIS TIME IT'S DAY AFTER
DAY.
WHY?
>>
>> IT HAS BEEN.
IT'S A REALLY SLOW MOVING
SYSTEM IS.
WE HAVE A MODERATE RISK
ISSUED FOR SEVERE WEATHER
TOMORROW AGAIN JUST A
LITTLE BIT FARTHER OFF
TOWARD THE EAST.
IT IT'S A SLOW-MOVER.
TOMORROW THIS PARTICULAR
AREA IS OUT OF THE RISK
IT'S GOING TO BE A COOLER
DAY.
SO THEY ARE DONE WITH IT WE
ARE STILL PROBABLY GOING TO
SEE A FEW MORE SHOWERS GO
THROUGH.
THE BIG SEVERE WEATHER AT
LEAST THE OKLAHOMA CITY
AREA RIGHT NOW IS GONE.
>> Shepard: RICK REICHMUTH.
ON THE LEFT SIDE OF YOUR
SCREEN CONTINUE ITING
COVERAGE FROM LIVE CHOPPER
PICTURES.
IT IS ASTOUNDING TO SEE
OKLAHOMANS DO WHAT
OKLAHOMANS HAVE SO MANY
TIMES.
THOSE WHO SURVIVED HAVE
BECOME RESCUE WORKERS.
THIS IS THE CASE,
NEIGHBORHOOD AFTER
NEIGHBORHOOD ACROSS THIS
DEVASTATED AREA.
AFTER THE TORNADO BLEW
THROUGH AND THE CAME OUT.
MANY RAN TOWARD THESE TWO
ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS BRIAR
WOOD ELEMENTARY AND THE
OTHER ESCAPES ME AT THE
MOMENT WITHOUT NOTES IN
FRONT OF ME TO TRY TO JUST
SAVE THEIR NEIGHBORS.
AND THAT'S WHAT'S HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW.
WE THE PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IS THAT
SECOND ONE.
THE TRUTH IS, THEY WON'T BE
ABLE TO GET THEIR HANDLE ON
THIS AT LEAST UNTIL SOME
TIME TOMORROW BECAUSE THE
COMMUNICATIONS ARE SO BAD.
6:27 P.M. THERE.
IN THE CENTRAL TIME ZONE
AND THE SUN WILL SET
SHORTLY.
VASTLY COMPLICATING MATTERS
FOR PEOPLE WHO ARE HERE.
IN MANY CASES THEY ARE
CERTAINLY NO ELECTRICITY.
THERE IS NO COMMUNICATION.
THE SALVATION ARMY AND THE
RED CROSS ARE SETTING UP
SHELTERS FOR PEOPLE WHO
NEED THEM.
AND THE NUMBERS WILL BE
MANY.
OUR CASEY STEGALL IS IN THE
AREA AND HAS BEEN REPORTING
ON WHAT HE HAS SEEN FROM
THIS 7/11 THAT WAS BLOWN
AWAY.
THAT IS JUST ONE TINY AREA
OF HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS
ACROSS THAT SPOT THAT ARE
TRYING TO DEAL WITH HOW TO
MOVE ON.
>> IT IS, IT'S VERY
ISOLATED.
AS YOU START TO DRIVE IN
YOU SEE THAT THIS IS
PLAYING OUT REALLY FOR
MILES AND MILES AND MILES
ALL AROUND.
THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE, IN FACT, SAYING
THAT THERE WERE SOME
20 MILES SCORED INTO THE
EARTH WHEN THIS THING CAME
THROUGH.
REALLY WANT I WANT TO GET
OUT OF OF THE WAY AND GET
BACK TO IT I'M GETTING
FEEDBACK IN MY EAR.
BEAR WITH ME.
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY RAW AS WE
ARE TRYING TO GET THIS OUT
TO YOU.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS
DESCRIBING TO YOU EARLIER.
PEOPLE DIGGING AT THE
RUBBLE AT THE REAR OF THIS
7/11.
THEY ARE SEARCHING FOR
SOMEBODY I'M LOOKING ALL
AROUND.
AND I SEE THIS GOING ON
BACK IN THE DISTANCE WHERE
THAT IS A NEIGHBORHOOD JUST
ON THE OTHER SIDE.
THEY HAVE BEEN THROWING
BOTTLES.
DEBRIS OVER THERE AND IT'S
PLAYING OUT I SEE IT IN
THREE SPOTS IN THE
BACKGROUND PEOPLE DIGGING
THROUGH THE RUBBLE TRYING
TO SEE IF SOMEONE IS UNDER
IT AND IF SOMEONE IS ALIVE
WE KNOW THE NEWS
HELICOPTERS NO-FLY ZONE.
BUZZING AROUND RECENTLY
ONLY EMERGENCY HELICOPTERS
SHEPARD.
THEY DON'T WANT THE NEWS
CHOPPERS UP BECAUSE THEY
WANT TO BE ABLE TO HEAR IF
SOMEONE IS, PERHAPS
INJURED AND THEY ARE
YELLING OUT FROM UNDERNEATH
THE RUBBLE THE FIRST
RESPONDERS CLEARLY WANT TO
HEAR THEM THIS IS VERY MUCH
A SEARCH AND RESCUE
SITUATION RIGHT NOW AND
HARD TELLING HOW LONG IT'S
GOING TO LAST, SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: IT'S MY
UNDERSTANDING THIS TORNADO
SPENT SO MUCH TIME ON THE
GROUND THAT 30 SQUARE MILES
HAVE BEEN HIT BY IT IT IF
TRUE, WE ARE IN
RECORD-BREAKING TERRITORY.
>> THE LIVE PICTURES FROM
THE CHOPPER CONTINUE TO
COME IN.
ON THE RIGHT-HAND SIDE OF
THE SCREEN THAT'S THE
TORNADO AS IT WAS
DEVELOPING.
IT WAS JUST BEFORE 4:00
THIS AFTERNOON EASTERN
TIME.
SO 3:00 THERE.
WE HAVE LOTS OF MONITORS
COMING IN FROM ALL OVER THE
COUNTRY AND WE WERE
WATCHING AS THIS TORNADO
JUST A LITTLE SLIVER OF A
THING CAME DOWN OUT OF A
CLOUD AND IF YOU ARE A
FLORIDIAN AND YOU LIVE IN
THE SOUTH.
IT'S THE KIND OF THING YOU
MIGHT SEE COME DOWN OVER
THE GULF OF MEXICO AND JUST
SORT OF SLIP INTO THE WATER
AND AGAIN GO BACK INTO THE
SKY.
IT WAS JUST A TINY SKY.
CLOUD CEILING LOWERED AND
LOWERED.
THE CLOUDS WERE GETTING
CLOSER TO THE GROUND.
THE SIZE OF THE TORNADO AT
THE GROUND KEPT GETTING
WIDER AND WIDER.
GOING APPEAR WHAT APPEARED
TO BE WIDE OPEN SPACES.
THEN SUDDENLY YOU COULD
TELL THERE IS A FARM THERE
IT TURNS OUT THAT WAS ORB
FARM.
AT THIS POINT IT'S BETWEEN
1 AND 2 MILES WIDE.
106-ACRE FARM THERE WHERE
75 TO 100 HORSES WERE
EITHER TAKEN AWAY BY THIS
STORM OR KILLED BY THIS
STORM.
FROM MOORE OKLAHOMA.
THAT THIS TORNADO WAS ON A
PATH SO EERILY SIMILAR TO
ONE FROM 1999.
AND SURE ENOUGH, THROUGH
THAT TOWN IT WENT, A MILE
WIDE AT THE BOTTOM, TO TWO
MILES AT SOME POINTS.
WITH WINDS UP TO 200 MILES
PER HOUR.
LIKE CLEAR CUTTING A
NEIGHBORHOOD LIKE CLEAR
CUTTING TREES WHERE HOUSES
COULD REPLACE THEM.
YET TODAY THE HOUSES WERE
ALREADY THERE AND MEN,
WOMEN AND CHILDREN WERE IN
BASEMENTS LISTENING TO THE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE
RADIO AND HOPEFUL OTHERS
WERE SHELTERING IN PLACE IN
BATHROOMS.
DOZENS OF KIDS IN A HALLWAY
AT AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
THEIR SAFE PLACE WHEN THE
ROOF CAME OFF THAT SCHOOL
AND THE WALLS BEGAN TO
SWAY.
AND THE WINDS WERE HOWLING
LIKE A FREIGHT TRAIN AS YOU
HAVE HEARD IT SO MANY
TIMES.
AND BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY,
ALL OF THOSE CHILDREN
PULLED AWAY BY RESCUE
WORKERS WHO CAME IN SOME
CASES FROM THE HOUSE NEXT
DOOR TO PULL THE KIDS FROM
WHAT'S LEFT.
WE ARE HALF PAST THE HOUR.
WE ARE CONTINUING COVERAGE
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF BREAKING NEWS
FROM MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
OUTSIDE OF OKLAHOMA CITY
WHERE TWO ELEMENTARY
SCHOOLS HAVE BEEN STRUCK BY
A VERY POWERFUL TORNADO
WHICH HAS CUT A SWATH OF
DESTRUCTION LIKE RARELY
HAVE WE SEEN IN THIS
NATION'S HISTORY, FRANKLY.
WE NOW KNOW THAT ALL OF THE
CHILDREN ARE ACCOUNTED FOR
AT ONE OF THOSE TWO
ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS.
BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
THE NEWS IS MORE DISTURBING
FROM PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
A PLACE WHERE WOULD SAW
RESIDENTS AND NEIGHBORS AND
OFFICIALS TRYING TO PULL
PEOPLE FROM THE RUBBLE,
WHERE WE KNOW THEY AFFECTED
A NUMBER OF RESCUES OF
CHILDREN.
THE LOCAL NBC STATION IS
REPORTING THAT SOME 24
CHILDREN ARE STILL TRAPPED
THERE AND THERE ARE
REPORTS, IN FACT, THAT THE
SITUATION IS EVEN WORSE.
IMAGINE COMING OUT OF YOUR
HOME AND REALIZING THAT
YOUR HOME HAS BEEN
DESTROYED AND THAT THE
SCHOOL ACROSS THE STREET IS
IN THE KIND OF CHAOS THAT
YOU NEVER EVEN IMAGINED
THAT WAS THE CASE FOR A MAN
WHICH I SPOKE LIVE JUST TWO
HOURS AGO.
>> THERE IS A RED CAR UP ON
TOP OF THE SCHOOL THAT WAS
TOSSED THERE THERE IS
CHILDREN ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
PARENTS TRYING TO FIND
THEIR CHILDREN.
THERE IS CHILDREN STILL
INSIDE THE SCHOOL THAT THEY
ARE TRYING TO LOCATE.
THAT'S ONE EFFORT WE ARE
TRYING TO TAKE CARE OF
RIGHT NOW.
EVERYTHING IN MY SIGHT IS
COMPLETELY GONE.
IT REMINDS ME WHEN I DROVE
THROUGH JOPLIN, MISSOURI TO
GO SEE MY PARENTS WHERE THE
HEART OF THAT FRMT-5 HIT.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT I'M
LOOKING AT RIGHT NOW.
EVERYTHING THAT CAN I SEE
IS GONE.
IT'S JUST -- IT'S SAD.
IT REALLY IS.
>> Shepard: JAMES, IT'S MY
UNDERSTANDING YOUR HOME WAS
HIT AS WELL.
[CRYING]
>> YES SIR.
I'M LOOKING AT THE -- WE
SAVED OUR WEDDING PICTURES.
I TOLD MY DAUGHTERS THIS IS
AN OPPORTUNITY FOR YOU TO
GO SHOPPING FOR NEW
CLOTHES.
THE HOUSE IS COMPLETELY
GONE.
>> REPORTING FROM A COUPLE
OF HOURS AGO AS WE WERE
TRYING TO GET A HANDLE ON
EXACTLY HOW SERIOUS THIS
SITUATION IS.
YOU CAN TELL FROM THE
DESTRUCTION THAT THE
PHYSICAL DAMAGE IS BEYOND
BELIEF.
BUT OUR HOPE WAS THAT THE
VAST MAJORITY OF PEOPLE HAD
BEEN ABLE TO TAKE SHELTER
AND THAT THE LOSS OF LIFE
WOULD BE MINIMIZED.
WITH THAT AS A BACKGROUND,
I CAN TELL IT YOU THAT THE
LOCAL NBC STATION HAS HE A
REPORTER ON SCENE AT PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
AND JUST REPORTED THAT
EMERGENCY CREWS NOW BELIEVE
UP TO TWO DOZEN CHILDREN
ARE BELIEVED TO BE TRAPPED
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE SCHOOL
DEBRIS AND THAT THE LOCAL
AUTHORITIES ARE NOW TURNING
FROM A SEARCH AND RESCUE
MISSION TO A RECOVERY
MISSION.
THE REPORTER FROM THE NBC
STATION SAID AND I QUOTE:
I UNDERSTAND THEY ARE GOING
TO START PULLING THESE
LITTLE BODIES OUT OF THE
RUBBLE VERY SOON.
TWO DOZEN CHILDREN BELIEVED
TO HAVE BEEN KILLED AT
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
A SCENE OF UNTHINKABLE
DEVASTATION.
WE EARLIER REPORTED THAT
THE CHILDREN WHO HAD
HUDDLED IN PLACE AND GONE
TO THEIR SAFE ZONE IN THAT
SCHOOL PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY HAD GONE TO A
HALLWAY THEIR SAFE SPOT 3RD
GRADERS.
24 OF THEM NOW MISSING.
AND BELIEVED TO BE DEAD
BENEATH THE RUBBLE.
IN 1999, 36 PEOPLE WERE
KILLED WHEN THE WORST
TORNADO STRIKE THIS HEART
LAND OF AMERICA HAD EVER
KNOWN FOR EVER CHANGED
THEIR LIVES.
CHANGED EMERGENCY
EVACUATION ORDERS.
THEY VASTLY INCREASED THE
NUMBER OF SHELTERS TORNADO
SHELTERS STORM SHELTERS
THEY GOT WORD TODAY 16
MINUTES BEFORE THIS MASSIVE
TORNADO CAME TO TOWN THEY
NEED TO TAKE SHELTER
IMMEDIATE CATTILY.
AND THEY RECEIVED THAT WORD
AFTER KNOWING THAT
NEIGHBORS IN A NEARBY TOWN
HAD HAD A DEVASTATING
TORNADO LESS THAN 18 HOURS
BEFORE.
THE WARNINGS WERE OUT.
THE EVACUATION ORDERS WERE
SENT OR THE SHELTER IN
PLACE ORDERS WERE SENT.
LATE IN THE SCHOOL DAY AT
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
PLACE DID NOT DO IT.
AUTHORITIES BELIEVE 24
THIRD GRADERS WILL NOT COME
OUT ALIVE.
IF YOU ARE LIKE ME, YOU ARE
WONDERING HOW CAN I HELP
THESE PEOPLE?
YOU CAN DONATE TO THE
NATIONAL -- YOU CAN DONATE
TO THE RED CROSS AND SO THE
SALVATION ARMY THERE WILL
BE WEEKS AND MONTHS AHEAD.
REMEMBER JOPLIN, MISSOURI
AND THE WIPING OUT OF A
LARGE PART OF THAT TOWN.
THE AREA OF DEVASTATION
HERE IS MUCH LARGER.
THE EXTENT OF THE
DEVASTATION IS MUCH WIDER.
AND WE HAVE NO IDEA HOW
MANY LIVES HAVE BEEN TAKEN
TORNADO DEREK HAS NOT
PASSED.
NEXT TWO DAYS THE HEARTLAND
OF AMERICA CAN EXPECT THIS
SAME SORT OF THING.
SO IF YOU ARE IN THAT PART
OF THE WORLD PROBABLY THE
FIRST THING YOU CAN DO IS
TO GET A PLAN TOGETHER FOR
HOW TO BE SAFE.
IN CASE YOU GET 16 MINUTES
OF WARNING WHICH FRANKLY
IS A LONG TIME.
THIS STORM WAS MOVING VERY
SLOWLY.
UNBELIEVABLE 200
MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT
PATH.
THE BROWN AREA IS WHERE THE
TORNADO WAS MOVING.
THE GREEN AREAS ARE TO THE
SIDE OF IT.
THAT'S THE PATH THE TORNADO
TOOK.
HOW MANY HOMES YOU CAN
COUNT ACROSS THERE THE CITY
MANAGER IS WITH US.
NIC NAZAR FROM NEARBY NEW
CASTLE CITY, OKLAHOMA.
MR. CITY MANAGER THIS NEWS
OF THESE SCHIRN IS VERY
DIFFICULT TO DISSEMINATE.
AND I WONDER HOW THE PEOPLE
OF YOUR SMALL TOWN ARE
COPING THIS LATE AFTERNOON.
I THINK THE THING FOR US
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
HAPPENED IN THE PAST TO OUR
COMMUNITY AT MOORE.
[INAUDIBLE] VICTIMS AND
ESPECIALLY WHENEVER THEY
ARE CHILDREN.
TOUCHES EVERYONE.
THE THING THAT WE TRY TO
HOLD ON TO IS THAT THE
EFFORTS THAT WE MAKE,
SHELTER THEY ARE SAFE,
DURING ONE OF THESE EVENTS.
REALLY ARE ONE OF OUR
BIGGEST [INAUDIBLE] MAKE
SURE THAT WE KEEP PEOPLE
SAFE.
AND WE THINK THAT SAFE
SHELTERS ARE REALLY
IMPORTANT IN ALL SCHOOLS.
HOPEFULLY AS IT GOES ON
THAT WILL BE SOMETHING
THAT'S MANDATED.
>> Shepard: THE CITY
MANAGER OF NEARBY NEW
CASTLE CITY, OKLAHOMA, NIC
NAZAR, WHO HAS DEVASTATION
IN HIS TOWN AS WELL
NEIGHBORS ARE GOING HOUSE
TO HOUSE IF YOUR HOUSE WAS
ONE THAT DIDN'T GET
DESTROYED RIGHT NOW PULLING
THE RUN AWAY TO SEE WHO IS
THERE.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I'M PHYLLIS  AND I HAVE DIABETIC NERVE
PAIN.  WHEN I FIRST FELT  THE DIABETIC
NERVE PAIN,  OF COURSE  I HAD NO IDEA
WHAT IT WAS.  I FELT LIKE  MY FEET
WERE GOING TO SLEEP.  IT PROGRESSED
FROM THERE  TO BURNING  LIKE I WAS
WALKING  ON HOT COALS...  TO LIKE
1,000 BEES  THAT WERE JUST STINGING
MY FEET.  I HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DOCTOR...  HE FOUND LYRICA
FOR ME.    [ Female Announcer ] IT'S
KNOWN    THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED    TO TREAT
DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.    LYRICA IS
NOT FOR EVERYONE.    IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIO    OR SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS    OR ACTIONS.    TELL YOUR
DOCTOR T AWAY    IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRON    OR UNUSUAL
CHAES    IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.    OR
SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,    RASH,
HIVES, BLISTERS,    CHANGES IN EYESIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,    MUSCLE
PAIN WITH FEVER    TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.    COMMON
SIDE EFFES ARE    DIZZINESS, SLEESS,
WEIGHT GAIN AND SWELLING    OF HANDS,
LEGS AND FEET.    DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKI LYRICA.    DON'T DRIVE
OR USE MACHINERY    UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.    THOSE WHO
HAVE HAD A DRUG    OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY    TO MISUSE LYRICA.
HAVING LESS PAIN --  IT'S A WONDERFUL
FEELING.    [ Female Announcer ] ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT    FOR DIABETIC
NERVE PAIN.    TO HEAR MORE OF PHYLLIS'S
STORY, VISIT LYRICA.COM.  COME ON,
SULLEY  IT'S THE LAST PLAY OF THE
GAME!  WHOA, WAIT FOR ME!  OH NO!
MY MOM JUST CLEANED THIS PLACE!  CALM
DOWN, SQUISHY  THIS'LL BE EASY TO
CLEAN.    [ Female Announcer ]
SWIFFER WETJET PADS    HAVE THE SCRUBBING
POWER    OF MR. CLEAN MAGIC ERASER.
THEY TRAP AND LOCK AWAY    EVEN MONSTROUS
MESSES    TO MAKE TOUGH CLEANING
A BREEZE.  NOW THAT'S CLEAN.  WOW.
SCOTTIE! WE WON!  UH-HUH, UH-HUH.
MOM?!!    [ Female Announcer ]
SWIFFER GIVES CLEANG    A MONSTROUS
NEW MEANING.    MONSTERS UNIVERSITY,
IN THEATERS, IN 3D.
It's Monday.  A brand new start.
Your chance to rise and shine.  With
CenturyLink as your  trusted technology
partner  you can do just that.  With
our visionary   cloud infrastructure
global broadband network and  custom
communications solutions,  your business
is more   reliable - secure - agile.
And with responsive,  dedicated support,
we help you shine  every day of the
week.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF BREAKING NEWS
FROM MOORE OKLAHOMA.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH IN NEW
YORK.
AND THE LOCAL NBC STATION
KFOR TELEVISION IS NOW
REPORTING THROUGH A
REPORTER ON SCENE AT PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN
MOORE THAT 24 CHILDREN ARE
TRAPPED BENEATH THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL AND THAT
ALL ARE DEAD AND THAT THEY
NOW HAVE A RECOVERY EFFORT
UNDERWAY TO REMOVE THE
BODIES OF THESE THIRD
GRADERS.
WE DO NOT HAVE THIS
INDEPENDENTLY CONFIRMED.
ALL WE CAN DO IS HOPE THAT
THAT REPORTER, WHO IS
STANDING THERE AND SPEAKING
TO LOCAL OFFICIALS BY SOME
MIRACLE IS WRONG.
THIS IS ONE THAT I HOPE IS
WRONG.
THE CHIEF MEDICAL EXAMINER
HAS CONFIRMED SIX DEATHS IN
MOORE.
WE KNOW OF EIGHT.
ASIDE FROM THOSE AT THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL ABOUT
WHICH WE HAVE BEEN
SPEAKING.
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
THIS IS IRNLT STATE 35 I
BELIEVE WHICH IT IS.
SHUT DOWN IN THE AFTERMATH
OF THIS.
THE CITY OF OKLAHOMA LOOK
AT THE BACKUP.
AS PEOPLE TRY TO GET IN AND
HELP OR TRY TO MAKE THIS
LATE AFTERNOON.
MOORE HAS NOW SENT OUT WORD
THAT THEY NO LONGER NEED
HELP FROM OTHER CITIES AND
TOWNS THE RESCUE THEY CAN
ACCOMPLISH.
THEY HAVE ENOUGH PEOPLE TO
DO SO.
AT THIS MOMENT THEY ARE
JUST WORKING TO TRY TO FIND
WHO MAY BE ALIVE OUT THERE.
IT'S OUR UNDERSTANDING THAT
THEY HAVE ENOUGH PEOPLE TO
GET TO ALL OF THE AREAS
AFFECTED NOW.
WHETHER THEY ARE ABLE TO
GET INTO ALL OF THEM IS
ANOTHER MATTER.
AND IF YOU LOOK AT OUR
LOCAL STATION THERE THEY
ARE SHOWING WHERE THE STORM
SYSTEM IS NOW.
KOKH WITH THE WEATHER MAP.
SO ANYBODY WHO THINKS THIS
IS OVER IS SADLY MISTAKEN.
AGAIN, WE HAVE
CORRESPONDENTS ON THE
GROUND INCLUDING OUR OWN
CASEY STEGALL AND IF HE IS
AVAILABLE WE WILL GET TO
HIM.
HE HAS BEEN ABLE TO BRING
US FIRST-HAND REPORTING OF
THE DEATH OF FOUR MORE
PEOPLE AND THE LIVE
PICTURES SHOW A RESCUE
AND/OR RECOVERY EFFORT
WHICH IS UNDERWAY RIGHT
NOW.
THIS IS BREAKING NEWS ON
FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
WE WILL GO LIVE TO THE
SCENE AFTER THIS.
Why are twice as many people  choosing
Verizon  over any other carrier?
Many choose us because we have  the
largest 4GLTE network.
Others, because of our  reputation
for reliability.
Or maybe it's because  we've received
JD Power
and Associates' customer service
award 4X in a row.
In the end  there are countless reasons.
But one choi.
If you're suffering from  constipation
Miralax or Metamucil may take  days
to work.  or faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.  Dulcolax provides
gentle relief  overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up  to
3 days.  For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.  You thought this beach
couldn't  get any more tempting...
... you thought  wrong.
Get up to 50% off  Memorial Day hotels.
Final Days.
Book now with Travelocity.
>> SEVEN MINUTES BEFORE
7:00 IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
THESE ARE LIVE PICTURES
ABOVE PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WHERE THE
LOCAL NBC TELEVISION
STATION IS REPORTING FROM A
REPORTER ON SCENE THAT 24
CHILDREN ARE TRAPPED AND
DIED IN THIS SCHOOL IN
THIS POWERFUL TORNADOT
STRUCK IN THE MID AFTERNOON
THERE.
WE HAVE BEEN WATCHING AS
RESCUE WORKERS CLAD IN
YELLOW CLIMB OVER THE
DEBRIS THAT WAS THE SCHOOL.
THE REPORTER ON SCENE
INDICATES THAT WHAT THEY
ARE DOING NOW IS TRYING TO
REMOVE THE VICTIMS.
HOW SUCCESSFUL THEY HAVE
BEEN THUS FAR REMAINS TO BE
SCENE.
BUT WE HAVE WATCHED VERY
CLOSELY AS THEY HAVE TAKEN
A NUMBER OF ITEMS OUT OF
THIS WRECKAGE.
ITEMS THAT WERE COVERED SO
WE COULD NOT SEE WHAT THEY
WERE.
AGAIN, WE CAN'T CONFIRM
WHAT HAS OR HAS NOT
HAPPENED THERE.
BUT THE LATEST NEWS IS BAD.
OUR CASEY STEGALL IS NEAR
THIS SPOT AT A LOCAL 7/11
STORE WHERE FOUR PEOPLE
DIED THIS AFTERNOON DURING
THE STORM ACCORDING TO
THOSE HE HAS INTERVIEWED
WITH AND HE IS HE WITH US
NOW.
CASEY?
>> YEAH, SHEPARD.
A LITTLE AFTER 3:00 IN THE
AFTERNOON.
PEOPLE GETTING GAS GO
INSIDE TO GRAB A COLD SODA.
THEY ARE HOT.
WE KNOW FOR SURE A WOMAN
AND HER INFANT HAVE BEEN
RECORD DEAD FROM THE 7/11
RIGHT BACK THERE BEHIND ME.
YOU SEE THAT GROUP OF
PEOPLE THEY ARE SEARCHING
FOR A FOURTH VICTIM BECAUSE
THERE WAS A THIRD LAID OUT
ON THE SIDEWALK THERE WHEN
SOME OF THE FIRST
RESPONDERS GOT HERE.
SO, A WOMAN AN INFANT
CHILD, A MAN ALREADY
RECOVERED.
WE HAVE SEEN THE MEDICAL
EXAMINER PULLING UP IN THIS
PARKING LOT AS THOSE PEOPLE
WAIT TO PULL A FOURTH BODY
FROM THIS LOCATION.
ANDREA ASH'S HUSBAND AND
HER SON ARE OVER THERE
TRYING TO GET DESPERATELY
TO THAT VICTIM.
ANDREA YOU LIVE JUST A
SHORT WHILE FROM HERE.
HOW DID YOU MAKE IT THIS
WAY?
>> WE JUST GOT IN OUR TRUCK
AND HOPPED TO TRY TO GO WE
THOUGHT OUR FRIENDS'
CHILDREN MIGHT HAVE BEEN
TRAPPED.
THAT'S WHAT WE SAW ON THE
NEWS.
THIS IS THE FIRST PLACE
THEY COULD GET TO THEY
STOPPED AND STARTED
HELPING.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AT YOUR
COMMUNITY AND SEE THIS
DESTRUCTION WHAT DO YOU
THINK.
>> IT REMINDS ME OF
MAY 3RD.
IT'S DEVASTATING.
THERE ARE NO WORDS.
>> YOU HAVE TWO YOUNG ONES
SITTING OVER HERE.
YOU SAID YOU WERE IN A
STORM.
>> YOU RUN AND GO DOWN INTO
THE SHELTER AND WAIT.
>> ANDREA, OUR SHOUTS AND
PRAYERS ARE WITH YOU.
SHEPARD BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: CASEY STEGALL
ON SCENE.
CASEY, WE ARE STILL
WATCHING FROM ABOVE AS THEY
WORK FRANKLY MUCH MORE
SLOWLY THAN BEFORE IN THE
WRECKAGE OF THIS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL I DON'T HAVE TO TELL
YOU HAS BEEN DEVASTATED.
VERY LITTLE LEFT HERE
EXCEPT FOR WHAT THE
AUTHORITIES HAVE TOLD THE
NBC STATION IS A SEARCH AND
RECOVERY MISSION.
THERE ARE SCENES LIKE THIS
PLAYING OUT ALL OVER THIS
TOWN IT'S OUR BELIEF.
OF COURSE, THE CHOPPERS
HOVER.
HOUSE AFTER HOUSE AFTER
HOUSE STORIES UNBELIEVABLE
DAY AND MORE.
OUR COVERAGE CONTINUES
AFTER THIS.
>> Shepard:  :00 ON THE
EAST COAST AND':00 IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, WHERE THE
DEATH TOLL IS RISING
FOLLOWING TODAY'S
DEVASTATING TORNADOES THAT
TORE ACROSS THAT AREA AND
LEFT UNSPEAKABLE DAMAGE.
THIS IS THE O'REILLY FACTOR
HOUR FOR THE MOMENT AT
LEAST AND FOR THE
FORESEEABLE FUTURE WE'LL
CONTINUE WITH NEWS COVERAGE
HERE AND O'REILLY WILL BE
WITH YOU AT SOME POINT WE
BELIEVE.
BUT NOW WE CAN TELL YOU
THAT KFOR, THE NBC STATION
THERE, WHICH HAS BEEN
REPORTING THAT 24 PEOPLE --
24 CHILDREN ARE DEAD INSIDE
THE SCHOOL WHICH YOU -- OR
WHAT'S LEFT ON THE SCHOOL
THAT SAME REPORTER IS
REPORTING THAT SEVEN OF