>> THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
>> HIS MOTHER INSISTING HE'S
INNOCENT.
>> I AM LIKE 1 MONEY% SURE THAT
THIS IS A SET-UP.
>> TONIGHT, HEARING FROM HIS
FAMILY.
PLUS WHAT WE NOW KNOW ABOUT THE
STAND-OFF THAT BROUGHT HIM TO
JUSTICE.
AND THE SHOOTOUT THAT TERRIFIED
A NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> I WAS THINKING JUST TO KEEP
MY FAITH.
>> AFTER THE BOMB, THE SHOOTING,
THE LOCKDOWN AND THE CHAOS.
NOW THE RECOVERY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
, YOU CAN BEAT US UP, BUT WE'LL
GET BACK UP AGAIN AND THAT'S IT.
THAT'S HOW WE DO IT AROUND HERE.
>> TONIGHT BOSTON BOUNCES BACK.
>> THAT IS FIRST ON FOX THIS
SATURDAY NIGHT.
WE'RE WAITING TO HEAR WHETHER
THE DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE FILES
CHARGES AGAINST THE ONLY
SURVIVING SUSPECT IN THE BOSTON
MARATHON ATTACK.
WE HAVE AN IMAGE THAT SHOWS THE
SUSPECT AT THE BOAT WHERE POLICE
CAPTURED HIM AFTER YESTERDAY'S
INTENSE GUNFIGHT.
OTHER PHOTOS FROM A
MASSACHUSETTS STATE POLICE SHOW
THE BOAT DURING THE STAND-OFF.
AND IN THE LOWER LEFT OF YOUR
SCREEN, YOU CAN SEE A POLICE
VEHICLE WITH SOME SORT OF PROBE
EXTENDED.
YESTERDAY WE TOLD YOU HOW POLICE
WERE USING A THERMAL IMAGING
CAMERA TO CHECK OUT WHAT THE
SUSPECT WAS DOING.
AND HERE IS A PHOTO FROM THAT
CAMERA.
YOU CAN SEE IT SHOWS THE SUSPECT
APPARENTLY LYING DOWN AT THE
BOTTOM OF THAT BOAT.
THE SHOOTOUT IN WATERTOWN LEFT A
19-YEAR-OLD IN SERIOUS
CONDITION.
A SPOKMAFOR THE BUREAU
ALCOHOL, TOBACCO AND FIREARMS
SAYS THE SUSPECT HAS GUNSHOT
WOUNDS TO HIS NECK AND LEG.
THE TEEN-AGER NOW AT BETH ISRAEL
MEDICAL CENTER, A LOT OF POLICE
THERE GUARDING
CONDITION TONIGHT?
>> WE JUST HEARD FROM THE U.S.
ATTORNEY'S OFFICE.
THE SUSPECT IS IN SERIOUS BUT
STABLE CONDITION HERE WITH
MULTIPLE INJURIES.
WE ARE TOLD ONE OF THOSE
INJURIES CAME FROM THE FIRST
SHOOT OUT.
THE SECOND INJURY COULD HAVE
COME FROM THERE AND THEY
HAVEN'T TOLD US IT IS FROM
THERE BUT THE MORE RECENT ONE
IS FROM LAST NIGHT.
THERE ARE GUARDS IN EVERY
ENTRANCE AND EXIT.
ANYBODY THAT GETS INTO THE
FACILITY OF BETH ISRAEL IS
SUPPOSED TO HAVE PURSES AND
BAGS CHECKED.
>> IS THERE A PLAN FOR
CHARGING HIM?
>> THEY HAVE NOT YET FILED
CHARGES.
WE ARE TOLD THEY COULD COME HE
IS IN A HOSPITAL BED.
THEY HAVE A TEAM OF
INVESTIGATORS READY TO
QUESTION HIM.
THEY ARE LITERALLY ON STAND
BY.
WE SAW INVESTIGATORS COME OUT
AND CAR PARKED HERE LAST
EVENING AFTER THE SUSPECT
BROUGHT HERE.
WE SAW THEM LEAVE, WE KNOW
THERE ARE INVESTIGATORS HERE
AND THEY'RE NOT SAYING MUCH OF
ANYTHING AS THE INVESTIGATION
CONTINUES, SHEPHERD.
>> IT IS IT A NAIL-BITING
STAND OFF UNFOLDED ON LIVE
TELEVISION AROUND THE WORLD.
WE COULD ONLY HEAR GUNSHOTS
ANDS AND CHOPPERS OVER HEAD.
WE ARE GETTING A
SECOND-BY-SECOND STORY HOW IT
WENT DOWN FROM THE OFFICERS
WHO LIVED IT NOW THE AUDIO
FROM THE POLICE RADIO.
>> WE HAVE A REPORT FROM
WATERTOWN OF 67 FRANKLIN
STREET, THERE IS A BOAT WITH
BLOOD ON IT AND BELIEVE
SOMEONE IS IN THE BLOOD.
>> YEAH, WHERE AT.
OKAY?
WE ARE HEARING THERE IS
SOMEBODY IN THE REAR.
LET'S GRET THE PERIMETER
AROUND 67 FRANKLIN.
>> THERE IS A HOLE.
>> CAN WE GET THE CHOPPER OUT
OF HERE.
>> WE HAVE.
YEAH.
I HAVE THE OWNER OF THE HOUSE
HERE AND HE SAID THERE IS A
BODY IN THE BOAT.
>> WE KNOW THAT.
THAT IS WHERE CAN CAN WE ARE
SURROUNDING THE BOAT.
WE ARE WAITING FOR THE --
HE POKED A HOLE.
WE HAVE A PERSON IN THE BOAT.
A PARTY TRYING TO POKE A HOLE
IN THE BOAT.
LIVE PARTY IN THE BOAT
CONFIRMED.
>> YEAH, WE HAVE THE BOAT
SURROUNDED HERE FROM ALL
CORNERS.
WE HAVE A TACTICAL.
WE CAN SEE HIM POKING A HOLE
NOW IN THE BOAT.
YEAH, EVERYONE STAND OFF OF
THE AIR.
OFF OF THE AIR.
SHOTS FIRED.
WE HAVE MULTIPLE SHOTS FIRED
HERE.
EVERYONE HOLD THEIR FIRE.
HOLD THEIR FIRE.
>> ALL UNITS HOLD YOUR FIRE.
>> WE HAVE A TACTICAL TEAM
GOING TO THE REAR OF THE HOUSE
TO APPROACH THE BOAT.
OKAY, NO ONE FIRE IN HERE.
WE ARE PUTTING DUMMY ROUNDS IN
THE BOAT.
THEY ARE DUMMY ROUNDS FIRED IN
THE BOAT SO EVERYBODY HOLD
FIRE.
YOU WILL HEAR DUMMY ROUNDS
GOING INTO THE BOAT.
HOLD YOUR FIRE.
>> ALL UNITS HOLD YOUR FIRE.
DUMMY ROUNDS INTO THE BOAT.
>> THERE IS GOING TO BE GAS
DEPLOYED AND FIRING GAS IN THE
BOAT.
ALL UNITS BE ADVISED GAS GOING
INTO THE BOAT.
>> 9:03.
STATE POLICE IS PUTTING THE
STANDARD RIM ON THE FRONT OF
THE ARMOR AND MAKE THEIR WAY
IN THE BACK YARD AND TRY TO
RIP THE TOP OFF OF THE TOP OF
THE BOAT.
BE AWARE OF THIS.
IF THEY ARE ABLE TO
SUCCESSFULLY RIP THAT OFF HE
WILL BE FULLY EXPLOSED.
ANYBODY ON THE PERIMETER BE
AWARE OF CROSS FIRE
SITUATIONS.
>> BE ADVISED F.B.I. POSSIBLE
LAUNCHING A DEVICE.
STAND BY.
NFTD DEVICE AND DO NOT RETURN
FIRE.
IT IS A FLASH BANG.
>> ALL UNITS DON'T RETURN
FIRE.
THERE MIGHT BE A FLASH BACK.
DON'T RETURN FIRE.
>> NO FURTHER MOVEMENT AT THIS
TIME.
>> NO MOTHER MOVEMENT IN THE
BOAT AT THIS TIME.
>> WE HAVE HIM ON HIS BACK.
HIS ARM IS BLOOD AND HE
BROUGHT IT BACK DOWN.
HEAP'S ON THE LEFT SIDE OF THE
BOAT LOOKING AT IT FROM THE
DRIVEWAY.
>> HE'S ON THE LEFT SIDE OF
THE BOAT.
>> THE BOAT.
>> HIS HEAD TO THE LEFT OF THE
BOAT WHEN YOU ARE LOOKING AT
THE BOAT FROM THE DRIVEWAY.
HIS HEAD IS AT THE LEFT.
>> HOLD.
I AM NOT SURE IF THEY WILL
WORK THEIR WAY ON THE BOAT
AGAIN.
I DON'T WANT YOU ON TOP OF THE
BOAT WHILE THEY ARE DOING
ANYTHING.
>> WE'LL MEET YOU.
>> KEEP AN EYE ON THE GARAGE.
>> HE'S IN CUSTODY.
SUSPECT IS INODY.
SUBJECT IS IN CUSTODY.
>> GOOD JOB, GENTLEMEN.
>> AND WITH THAT, THE DAY OF
FEAR ALL OVER THE REGION OVER.
MIKE TO BIN 10 MIMES OUT'VE
BOSTON WHAT IS THE SCENE
TONIGHT?
>> SHEPHERD, PEOPLE IN THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD ARE GETTING OUT
AND LOOKING AT THE AFTERMATH
OF THE MANHUNT THAT ENDED IN A
BLAZE OF GUNFIRE RIGHT HERE.
>> WE GRABBED OUR PHONES AND
CAM RAS AND STARTED RECORDINGS
AND WITHIN A COUPLE OF SECOND
AND THEY OPENED UP FIRE AND
MASSIVE ARTILLERY AND IT SO
LOUD.
WE WERE FOUR HOUSES DOWN AND
WE ARE RIGHT THERE ON TOP OF
IT WE KEPT THE FILM ROLING AND
KIND OF DUCKED DOWN A LITTLE
BIT.
>> BOB GLATZ SHOT THAT VIDEO.
HE LIKE MANY PEOPLE DIDN'T
FEEL EVER COMFORTABLE AS THE
EMERGENCY LOCK DOWN HAD
LIFTED.
THEY FELT LIKE THERE COULD BE
A THREAT.
THEY ARE GIVING IN TO THEIR
OWN CUROSITY AND RECORDING
THIS BIT OF HISTORY, SHEP.
>> MIKE, THANK YOU.
WEDNESDAY NIGHT, THE SUSPECT
WORKING OUT IN A GYM, HANGING
OUT AND PARTYING.
THAT'S ACCORD TOTH REPORT OF
THE BOSTON GLOBE.
THE STUDENT SAID HE SAW HIM IN
A PARTY WEDNESDAY NIGHT AND HE
WAS JUST RELAXED.
RELAXED DAYS AFTER HE WAS SAID
TO HAVE ATTACKED THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
THOUSANDS OF INVESTIGATORS
HUNTED FOR HIS BROTHER AND
HIM.
THE SCHOOL EVACUATED THE
CAMPUS AFTER THE SCHOOL
REALIZED THAT THE SUSPECT WAS
A STUDENT.
OFFICERS WERE VERY CAREFUL
WITH APPROACHING THE BOAT.
WE ARE LEARNING ABOUT THE
DEADLY ARSNIL AS THE TWO
BROTHERS TRIED TO MAKE A
DESPERATE ESCAPE.
WE'LL GET MORE FROM THE HEAD
JOURNALIST OF FOX NEWS .
What do you think?
Thats's great.
It won't take long,
will it?
Nah.
Ok!
This won't take long,
will it?
No, not at all.
How many of these can
we do on our budget?
More than you think.
That didn't take
very long did it!
This spring, dig in and save.
That's nice, post it.
Already did.
More saving. More doing. That's
the power of The Home Depot.
Dig in and save
with Earthgro Mulch,
a Special Buy at 3
bags for just 10 bucks.
THIS IS KATE.
SHE LIKES A MAN
WITH A LITTLE HAIR ON HIS CHEST.
BUT DEFINITELY NOT ON HIS BACK.
THIS IS HANNAH.
SHE LIKES A GUY
WITH A SMOOTH STOMACH
TO SHOW OFF HIS SIX-PACK.
[ ding! ]
AND THIS IS GENESIS.
SHE LIKES MEN
COMPLETELY HAIRLESS
AND, NO, SHE DOESN'T
THINK THAT'S WEIRD.
I DON'T.
THE PROGLIDE STYLER.
TRIM, SHAVE AND EDGE.
THE ONE TOOL YOU NEED
TO GET THE LOOK SHE WANTS.
THE NIGHT IS YOURS.
GILLETTE.
THE BEST A MAN CAN GET.
>>ITAL YENT GUTS AND GLORY,
THAT'S HOW THE POLICE CEF
DESCRIBED THE OFFICER THAT
CAPTURED THE TERRORIST ATTACK.
IT LASTED MORE THAN AN HOUR.
WITH US NOW IS THE CHIEF
HIMSELF LIVE FROM WATTWATT.
CHIEF, CONGRATULATION AND
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, SIR.
>> I LISTENED WH GREAT
INTEREST BEFORE THE TAKE DOWN
WE DOWN.
YOU WERE SAYING WE DIDN'T HAVE
THE MANPOWER TO LOCK THE PLACE
DOWN.
APPARENTLY YOU DID.
>> YEAH, AS IT TURNS OUT WE
BLOCK PERIMETER, IT DIDN'T
TALK LONG TO GET THE GUY.
>> IT DIDN'T SEEM LIKE HE WAS
ABLE TO DO MUCH MOVING AT ALL.
DO YOU KNOW IF HE ALL DAY OR
IF THAT BOAT WAS SRCHED IN
ADVANCE.
>> THAT BOAT WAS OUTSIDE OF
OUR 20 BLOCK PERIMETER.
WHAT WE HAD SET UP AND THOUGHT
WE HAD HIM PINNED DOWN 1:30
A.M. THAT MORNING, WE JUST
MISSED IT AND DIDN'T GET THE
PERIMETER AS WIDE AS WE NEEDED
TO DO .
SO THAT'S WHAT CAUSED THAT
SHOT.
>> AND I WONDER IF GOVERNOR
PATRICK HAPPENED AROUND 7
O'CLOCK LIFTED THAT ORDER TO
STAY IN PLACE IF YOU WOULD
HAVE FOUND HIM ALIVE?
>> THAT'S A GOOD QUESTION.
YOU KNOW, WE HAD ASKED OUR
COMMUNITY TO BE DILIGENT AND
RESPECT OUR SHELTER IN PLACE
AND THAT'S WHAT THAT GENTLEMEN
DID.
HE DID NOT EVEN LEAVE HIS
HOUSE AT ALL EVEN TO GO IN HIS
BACK YARD UNTIL WE TOLD HIM IT
WAS OKAY BY SIX CAN BE
O'CLOCK.
WE HAD RESPOND HAD OUR BAD GUY
PINNED DOWN.
WEMENTED TO MAKE SURE WE DID
IT SAFELY AS POSSIBLE FOR THE
NEIGHBORHOOD AND ALL OF THE
OFFICERS INVOLVED.
>> LAST THING YOU NEEDED WAS
SOMEBODY ELSE HURT.
>> DID HE SAY ANYTHING OR
COMMUNICATE IN ANY WAY?
>> NO.
WE TRIED TO TALK TO HIM AND WE
WERE IN 15 OR 20 MINUTES OF
HARD NEGOTIATION AND MAKING
DEMANDS OF HIM AND HE DID NOT
RESPOND.
WE HAD PUT SOME FLASH BANGS IN
TO THE BOAT TO GET HIM TO
COOPERATE AND ALL HE ENDED UP
DOING IN THE END MEETING OUR
DEMAND AND PULLING HIS HANDS
FREE AND SHOWING HIMSELF AND
LIFTING HIS SHIRT.
>> SO HE WAS ABLE TO LIFT HIS
SHURT -- SHIRT.
HE WAS NOT UNCUSHIOUS.
>> RIGHT.
HUM.
WELL, BECAUSE OF THAT, I
WONDER WHAT KIND OF SHAPE YOU
THOUGHT HE WAS IN?
>> WE KNEW HE HAD SERIOUS
INJURIES FROM THE GUN FIGHT AT
12:30 A.M..
THE CAR HE ABANDONED HAD BLOOD
STAINS AND WE DID A SEARCH
INSIDE OF THE PERIMETER.
WE FOUND APE HOUSE WHERE THERE
A POOL OF BLOOD OR A CIRCLE OF
BLOOD.
WE KNEW HE WAS LOSING BLOOD
BUT DIDN'T KNOW HOW EXTENSE
ITCH HIS INJURIES.
CHIEF, YOU ARE NOT A LARGE
DEPARTMENT ANDIM GUESSING
AFTER THE BOMBING.
THE LAST THING YOU WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT WAS THIS.
AND IT IS BOSTON CAMBRIDGE AND
WE HAD OUR SHARE OF INCIDENTS.
>> I HOPE THE MEN AND WOMEN
AND THE COMMUNITY ARE --
IT IS A GUN FIGHT AT 12:25
WITH MY OFFICERS AND THE BAD
GUYS.
AND THEY'RE EXCHANGED.
IT WOULD BE BEYOND HEROIC .
IT IS AMAZING .
WE CAN GIVE THEM TALENT AND
TRAINING.
BUT THE DETERMINATION THEY HAD
TO SURVIVE THAT IS INCREDIBLE
TO ME.
>> THERE IS A MEMORIAL GOING
ON RIGHT NOW, CHIEF AND WE'LL
PUT IT UP ON THE SCREEN.
IS THIS FOR THE MIT OFFICER?
>> I AM ASSUMING THAT IS
RIGHT, YES.
>> IN FACT THE PRODUCERS TOLD
MY IT IS.
IT JUST POPPED UP.
WE'LL LISTEN ALONG WITH OUR
VIEWERS.
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE BRAVE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> HOLDING A BANNER THAT READS
WATERTOWN RAIDER PRIDE.
A LOT OF PRIDE IN THAT TOWN
TONIGHT.
>> THAT IS VERY NICE.
WOW, THE SUPPORT THAT WE HAVE
GOTTEN FROM OUR COMMUNITY HAS
BEEN INCREDIBLE AT THIS TIME.
I CAN'T SAY ENOUGH ABOUT MY
DEPARTMENT AND COMMUNITY.
>> A LOT OF LOVE HERE TOO,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> HE DID NOT HAVE THE RIGHT
TO REMAIN SILENT.
HE DID NOT HAVE THE RIGHT TO
AN ATTORNEY.
OFFICERS ARE NOT READING THE
SUSPECTS RIGHTS IN THE CASE.
DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THE
EXCEPTION HERE AND THE CRITISM
THAT CAME WITH IT.
WHO WILL REPRESENT THE MAN IN
COURT.
THAT'S ALL AHEAD.
It doesn't matter
where a good idea comes from,
it only matters that
it shows up
and makes things better.
In that spirit,
Verizon is proud to announce
the Powerful Answers Award.
10 million dollars in
prizes for the best ideas.
Ideas so big,
they have the power to change
everything.
Whether it's our
inspiration, or yours,
the world's biggest
challenges
deserve even
bigger solutions.
The Powerful Answers Award
from Verizon.
>> INVESTIGATORS SAY THE
SUSPECT IS IN NO SHAPE TO FACE
QUESTIONING REGARDING THE
BOSTON BOMBING.
BUT WHEN HE RECOVERS,
INTERROGATORS WILL NOT TELL
HIM HE HAS THE RIGHT TO REMAIN
SILENT.
THE WHITE HOUSE DECIDED NOT TO
READ HIM MIRANDA RIGHTS.
HE'S NOT GETTING THAT.
FEDS ARE ENVOKING AN EXCEPTION
TO THE RULE AND ALREADY THE
AMERICAN CIVIL LIBERTIES IS
SLAMMING THAT DECISION .
WE MUST NOT WAIVER FROM THE
TRIED AND TRUE JUDICIAL
SYSTEM.
WE'LL BREAK DOWN THE
COMPLICATED LEGAL ISSUINGS.
CRIMINAL DEFENSE ATTORNEY
HEATHER HANSON IS WHERULSE.
>> YOU CATCH SOMEBODY WHO
MIGHT HAVE LEFT A BOMB
SOMEWHERE .
YOU WANT TO KEEP THEM SAFE AND
QUESTION THEM RIGHT NOW FOR
THE PUBLIC SAFETY.
>> THAT TIMES PASSED HASN'T
IT.
>> THE LAW WAS IN 1984 .
THAT IS WHAT IT AT THAT TIME.
SINCE THEN SPECIFICALLY AFTER
THE TIMES SQUARE BOMBING IN
2010,
>> ATTEMPTED.
>> THE F.B.I. PUT OUT A MEMO
THAT ADDRESSES THE TERRORIST
CASES THAT THEY COULD EXPAND
THE TIME IN WHICH THEY CAN
QUESTION A SUSPECT WITHOUT
READING THEM THEIR RIGHTS.
THE QUESTION IS HOW LONG OF A
TIME IS THERE.
WE DON'T KNOW THE ANSWER.
>> WAS IT NOT THE LETTER OF
THE LAW.
BUT WAS IT THE INTENT OF THE
LAW TO STOP AN IMMINENT THREAT
AGAINST THE PEOPLE.
FOR INSTANCE TIMES SQUARE
BOMBER HAD BLOWN SOMETHING OUT
THERE AND HAD BLOWN SOMETHING
THAT THE AUTHORITIES NEEDED TO
KNOW ABOUT IT >> IT IS IT JUST
A DIFFERENT THING AND WE DON'T
KNOW IF THERE IS SOMEONE IN
CHICAGO AND PHILADELPHIA AND
CALIFORNIA AND THAT THE NATURE
OF TERRORISM IS DIFFERENT.
WE'LL EXPAND THIS EXCEPTION.
THIS IS NOT THE LAW, SHEP.
IT IS JUST A MEMO .
THERE WAS TALK TOO.
AS TO WHETHER OR NOT IT SHOULD
GO BEFORE CONGRESS.
THEY FEMENT IT APPROPRIATE AT
THE TIME.
THEY COULD DETERMINE IF THERE
INTELLIGENCE OR NOT.
>> AND SO THEY HAVE A GOOD
CASE AGAINST THIS GUY.
AND SINCE YOU DIDN'T READ THAT
ANYTHING YOU CAN'T USE AGAINST
HIM.
THEY HAVE PLENTY.
>> YEAH.
>> MY QUESTION IS A BIGGER
ONE.
IS THE INTENTION TO TRY HIM IN
COURT.
IT SOUNDED LIKE THAT FROM THE
PRESIDENT.
HE SAID COURTS.
>> THE MILITARY TRIBUNAL IDEA
FELL OUT OF FAVOR.
WE HAVE TRIED 500 CASES IN THE
FEDERAL COURT AND ONLY A
HANDFUL OF MILITARY CASE .
YET LINDSAY GRAHAM AND JOHN
MCCAIN WANT HIM IN MILITARY
COURT.
>> YOU CALL HIM ENEMY
COMBATANT THAT IS TAKEN AWAY A
LOT OF RIGHTS.
HE SHOULD BE ARRAIGNED IN 24
HOURS AND THEY HAVE MADE
EXCEPTIONS IN THE OF OSAMA BIN
LADEN'S SON IN LAW AND
ATTEMPTED TIMES SQUARE BOMBER
F. YOU ARE AN ENEMY COMBATANT
IT COULD BE MONTHS BEFORE
COMING TO COURT.
>> WE LEARNED YESTERDAY THALT
F.B.I. HAD INVESTIGATED THE
OLDER BROTHER'S POSSIBLE TIE
TO TERROR GROUPS AND TURNS OUT
THAT IS NOT ALL OFFICIALS WERE
INVESTIGATING.
THERE IS AN INVESTIGATION
RIGHT NOW AND THE DETAILS ARE
AHEAD.
♪
(VO) Purina Cat Chow.
50 years of feeding great
relationship
I HONESTLY LOVED SMOKING,
AND I HONESTLY DIDN'T THINK
I WOULD EVER QUIT.
[ Male Announcer ]
ALONG WITH SUPPORT,
CHANTIX (VARENICLINE) IS PROVEN
TO HELP PEOPLE QUIT SMOKING.
IT REDUCES THE URGE TO SMOKE.
IT PUT ME AT EASE THAT YOU COULD
SMOKE ON THE FIRST WEEK.
[ Male Announcer ] SOME PEOPLE
HAD CHANGES IN BEHAVIOR,
THINKING OR MOOD,
HOSTILITY, AGITATION,
DEPRESD MOOD AND SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS OR ACTIONS
WHILE TAKING
OR AFTER STOPPING CHANTI
IF YOU NOTICE ANY OF THESE
STOP TAKING CHANTIX AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ANY HISTORY OF DEPRESSION
OR OTR
MENTAL HEALTH PROEMS,
WHICH COULD GET WORSE
WHILE TAKING CHANTIX.
DON'T TAKE CHANTIX IF
YOU'VE HAD A SERIOUS ALLERGIC
OR SKIN REACTION TO IT.
IF YOU DEVELOP THESE
STOP TAKING CHANTIX
AND SEE YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
AS SOME CAN BE
LIFE-THREATENING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HISTORY
OF HEART OR BLOOD VESSEL
PROBLEMS,
OR IF YOU DEVELOP
NEW OR WORSE SYMPTOMS.
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
OF A HEART ATTACK OR STROKE.
USE CAUTION WHEN DRIVING
OR OPERATING MACHINERY.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
INCLUDE NAUSEA,
TROUBLE SLEEPING
AND UNUSUAL DREAMS.
WITH CHANTIX AND WITH THE
SUPPORT SYSTEM IT WORKED FOR ME.
[ Male Announcer ]
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF CHANTIX
IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
AND DIDN'T KNOW WHERE TO START.
USED A CONTRACTOR BEFORE
WITH CHANTIX AND WITH THE
SUPPORT SYSTEM IT WORKED FOR ME.
AT ANGIE'S LIST,
YOU'LL FIND REVIEWS
ON EVERYTHING
FROM HOME REPAIR TO HEALTHCARE
WRITTEN BY PEOPLE
JUST LIKE YOU.
NO COMPANY CAN PAY
TO BE ON ANGIE'S LIST,
SO YOU CAN TRUST
WHAT YOU'RE READING.
ANGIE'S LIST IS LIKE HAVING
THOUSANDS OF CLOSE NEIGHBORS
WHERE I CAN GO ASK
FOR PERSONAL RECOMMENDATIONS.
THAT'S THE IDEA.
BEFORE YOU HAVE ANY WORK DONE,
CHECK ANGIE'S LIST.
FROM ROOFERS TO PLUMBERS
TO DENTISTS AND MORE,
ANGIE'S LIST --
REVIEWS YOU CAN TRUST.
I LOVE YOU, ANGIE.
SORRY, HONEY.
>> COMMUNITY MIDWEST ARE
DEALING WITH SEVERE FLOODS
AFTER HEAVY RAIN.
THERE IS IT PREDICT WOULD
MAJOR FLOODING THIS WEEKEND
AND NEXT WEEK
A. NOT ONLY THE MISSISSIPPI,
BUT DOZENS OF MIDWESTERN
RIVERS ARE OVER THEIR BANKINGS
IN SIX STATES FROM MISSOURI TO
WISCONSIN.
MORE RAIN IS IN STORE FOR THE
PLACES.
>> UNFORTUNATELY ON TOP OF THE
RECORD-SETTING RAIN, LOOK AT
CHICAGO RECEIVED TWO AND HALF
USUAL THE TYPE THEY GET IN A
MONTH.
LOOKING OVER 7 INCHES AND
UNFORTUNATELY MORE RAIN IS ON
THE WAY.
FLOOD ADVISORY POSTED FOR A
DOZENS OF STATES AS ALL OF THE
TRIBITARIES GET IN THE
MISSISSIPPI.
IT WILL BE ON FOR MUCH OF THE
SPRING.
WE ARE HEAD START HERE.
LOOK AS THE OTHER SYSTEM
BUILDS AND PUSHES IN THE
MIDWEST AND BRINGING MORE RAIN
AND MORE SNOW IF YOU CAN
BELIEVE IT.
SOME CASES 6-12 INCHES MORE
SNOW IN THE AREAS THAT ARE SO
DONE WITH WINTER, BACK TO YOU.
>> WE ARE, JANICE DEAN THANK
YOU SO MUCH.
>> I AM SHEPHERD SMITH.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
IT IS THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR
AND TIME FOR THE TOP OF THE
NEWS AND THE UNCLE OF THE
BOSTON TERROR SUSPECT SPEAKING
OUT SAYING HE IS RELEGALED
THAT THE YOUNGER BROTHER IS
STILL ALIVE.
>> I HOPE HE WILL PULL
THROUGH.
HE WILL BE ABLE FOR HIS OWN
SAKE.
FOR HIS OWN SAKE TO GET
FORGIVENESS FOR THOSE WHO HAVE
BEEN HARMED AND HAVE BEEN
HURT.
FROM THE FAMILIES OF THE
VICTIMS.
FROM MARTIN'S FAMILY AND
KRYSTAL'S FAMILY AND LINDSAY'S
FAM DISPAM THE OFFICER.
FOR ALL 180 WHO SUFFERED.
AS I SAID FOR HIS OWN SAKE.
>> REMEMBER THE UNCLE CALLED
HIS NEPHEWS LOSERCE AND
ANGRILY DEMANDED THAT THE
YOUNGER SON TURN HIMSELF IN.
HE CLAIM THAT WOULD HIS OLDER
NEPHEW WAS SET AGAINST HIM.
THE YOUNG MAN CALLED HIM IN
2009 TO SAY HE CHOSE GOD'S
BUSINESS OVER SCHOOL OR WORK.
THAT THE LAST TIME THEY EVER
SPOKE TO EACH OTHER.
THE F.B.I. REPORTS THAT THEY
INVESTIGATED HIS REPORT TO
GROUPS AND EVENTUALLY RELEASED
HIM.
THE F.B.I. RELEASING A STRONG
STATEMENT.
>> IN 2011, THE RUSSIAN
GOVERNMENT ASKED THE F.B.I. TO
INVESTIGATE THE BROTHER
BECAUSE HE WAS A FOLLOWER OF
RADICAL ISLAM AND A STRONG
BELIEVER AND CHANGED TO LEAVE
TO THE UNITED STATES TO JOIN
UNSPECIFIED UNDER GROUND
GROUPS.
THE F.B.I. FOUND NO EVIDENCE
OF TERRORIST ACTIVITY.
THAT IS CREATING UNEASE AT THE
BUREAU.
>> THERE IS A LOT OF PAL
PAITATIONS IN THE F.B.I. ABOUT
WHAT THEY SAW WHEN THEY LOOKED
AT THIS AND WHAT DID THEY
MISS.
THAT WILL BE SCUTINIZED.
>> TONIGHT FOX NEWS IS TOLD
THAT THE F.B.I. IS WORKING
THROUGH A LONG LAUNDRY LIST
AND THE FORMER MEMBER OF THE
FEBRUARY FIB TASK FORCE SAID
THE VOLUME .
EXPLOSIVES REQUIRE A
SIGNIFICANT AND SUSTAINED
TRAINING, SHEPHERD.
>> YOU HAVE LEARNED OF ANOTHER
INVESTIGATION GOING ON
TONIGHT, RIGHT?
>> FOX NEW SYSTEM TOLD THAT
INVESTIGATORS ARE EXPLORING
LINKINGS BETWEEN THE OLDER
BROTHER AND THE CACK CAUSUS
EMERATE BASED ON THE TRAVEL TO
RUSSIA IN THE FIRST HALF OF 20
12 AND INCLUDED DAGIS STAN AND
CHECHNYA .
KNOWN FOR THE ATTACKS ON THE
RUSSIAN TRAINS AND MOSCOW
AIRPORT AND CONFLICT WITH THE
RUSSIAN GOVERNMENT THEY WERE
DESINATED A TERRORIST
COMMUNITY .
THE GROUP IS SEEN AS A FRINGE
PLAYER, THE STATE DEPARTMENT
SAID THE DESINATION OF
CAUCUSES EMERIT IS IN RESPONSE
TO THE U.S. AND RUSH YAMPT IT
ILLUSTRATES THE GLOBAL NATURE
OF THE TERRORIST PROBABLE WE
EXPERIENCE TODAY.
THAT THE SAME YEAR THE RUSSIA
GOVERNMENT ASKED THE U.S. TO
INVESTIGATE WHETHER THE OLDER
BROTHER HAD TIES TO THE GROUP.
>> CATHERINE HARRIS, GOOD WORK
IN WASHINGTON TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> WE'LL LOOK AT SPECIAL
INSIGHT WITH DAVID WILLIAMS
WHO IS LIVE WITH US IN
WASHINGTON.
>> THANK YOU FOR HAVING ME.
>> WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT THIS
GROUP, AND WHAT IS YOUR SENSE
OF WHAT WENT WRONG TWO YEARS
AGO.
>> FIRST QUESTION, WHAT DO I
KNOW ABOUT THE GROUP, VERY
LITTLE.
EVERYBODY WHO WORKED COUNTER
TERRORISM IS FULLY AWARE OF
THE ISSUES THAT ARE GOING ON
IN THE CAUCUS OF DAGIS STAN
AND CHECHNYA AND THERE IS A
LOT THERE.
BUT MOST OF THEIR HISTORIC
ATTACKS ARE AGAINST THE
RUSSIAN ENTITIES.
THEY HISTORICALLY HAVE NOT
ATTACKED THE UNITED STATES.
THAT IS TO ESTABLISH A LEVEL
OF AUTONNY FOR CHECHNYA AND
THEY ARE PART OF THE GLOBAL
JIHADIST AND SEES UNITED
STATES AS A PRIMARY ENEMY.
I AM NOT SURED THAT THEY WOULD
COME TO TARGET US.
>> FROM WHAT YOU LEARN BODY
HOW THESE TWO SEPARATED AND
ACCOMPLISH, IS IT SENSE IT WAS
A TRAINING THING OR WOULD THEY
HAVE HAD HELP WITH THIS.
>> THAT IS DIFFICULT TO
ANSWER.
IT WOULD SEEM THERE A NUMBER
MUCH IED'S BUILT .
IT WOULD SEEM GENERALLY THEY
WORKED AND ACCORDINGLY I THINK
THEY CERTAINLY HAD TRAINING TO
DO THAT .
FURTHER MORE WHEN I WATCHED
THEM MARCH INTO THE SCENE
WHERE THEY LAID DOWN THE
IED'S.
THEY WERE PREPARE ALMOST LIKE
TWO SOLDIERS WALKING DOWN BOL
STON STREET TO DO THAT.
IT WOULD SEEM LIKE THEY HAD
TRAINING ON HOW TO LAY OUT AN
ATTACK PLAN AND FOLLOW THROUGH
WITH IT.
>> SINCE THE ATTACKS OF 9/11
IN 2001, IT A CONCERN THAT
THIS SORT OF THING WOULD
HAPPEN, AND THAT JUST A COUPLE
OF LONE WOLFLESS MIGHT
ACCOMPLISH SOMETHING ON THE
SUBWAY STATION OR SOMEWHERE
ELSE.
IS OUR CONCERN GREATER TODAY
THAN IT A WEEK AGO?
>> I THINK THE INTELLIGENCE
COUNTER TERRORISM COMMUNITY IS
AWARE .
POTENTIAL OF IT HAPPENING.
WHY IT IS NOT HAPPEN NEGLIGENT
PAST WE DON'T KNOW.
PART OF THAT AND I AM NOT JUST
PATTING THE F.B.I. ON THE
BACK.
THERE IS SO MANY PLOTS IN THE
LAST 10 OR 11 YEARS.
SOMETHING LIKE THE GOALIE,
BOUND TO GET BY AND IT DID ON
MONDAY.
>> THANK YOU.
>> LAST NIGHT IN WATTWATT,
SCOW MANY PEOPLE HUDDLED IN L
HOUSES.
CONSIDER THE EXPERIENCE OF ONE
WOMAN WHO HID IN HER HOME AND
HER EIGHT YEAR OLD SON
LISTENING TO GUNFIRE.
>> IT STARPTING TO GET
SURROUNDED AND THEY YELLED AT
US TO GET IN THE HOUSE AND AS
I WALKED THROUGH MY LIVING
ROOM, I HEARD RAPID FIRE.
AND THAT'S WHEN I GRABBED MY
SON'S HAND AND SAID I DON'T
WANT YOU TO HEAR THIS.
WE HAVE TO GO IN THE BATHROOM
.
WE JUST SAT DOWN IN THE FLOOR
AND TOLD HIM WE WOULD BE OKAY.
YOU WILL HEAR MORE GUNSHOTS
AND SMALL BLASTS AND I FLUSHED
THE TOILET SO HE WOULD NOT
HEAR IT.
I HEARD THEM YELL DOWN MY
DRIVE WAY.
I DIDN'T KNOW IF THERE WOULD
BE GUNFIRE AND I LAIDD OVER MY
SON AND I DIDN'T WANT HIM TO
KNOW HOW SCARED I WAS.
I LAID OVER HIM AND I SOBBED
FOR A MINUTE.
MY PHONE STARTED TO RING AND
MY COUSIN SAID THEY CAUGHT HIM
AND I COULD GO OUT .
I DIDN'T BELIEVE HER AND SO I
CRAWLED OUT OF THE BATHROOM TO
PEEK AT MY TELEVISION AND WHEN
I DID THAT, I SAW HOW MUCH
ENFORCEMENT WAS OUT HERE AND I
CAME OUT OF THE BATHROOM AND
BROUGHT HIM OUT WITH ME.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WHAT GAVE ME CLOSURE, THE
OFFICER WALKED BY AND I SAID
ARE YOU A HAPPY OFFICER AND HE
GAVE ME THUMBS UP A BIG SMILE
AND THEN I KNOW THEY GOT HIM,
IT IS DONE.
>> ONE WOMAN'S EXPERIENCE WITH
HER EIGHT YEAR OLD FLUSHING
THE TOILET SO THE CHILD WOULD
NOT HEAR.
THEY ARE OKAY .
RECOVERING WITH A NIGHT OF
GUNFIRE AND ENDED WITH WILD
CHEERS.
>> AND JUST INTO FOX NEWINGS.
A PHOTY OF THE BOAT IN THE
CENTER OF THE STAND OFF.
OUR STATION IN BOSTON THAT
UN-- INVAL AUTOMOBILE.
THE BOAT WITH THE BLUE TARP
OVER IT .
THIS IS WHERE THE MARATHONE
YOU CAN SEE BLOOD ON ONE
SPHOT.
FIRST TIME I AM SEEING IT
ALONG WITH YOU.
THERE IS IT BLOOD ON THE
OUTSIDE OF IT .
WE ARE NOT SURE WHETHER THAT
GOT THERE AS HE GOT NINETY-TWO
IN I HIDE OR AUTHORITIES
BRINGING HIM OUT.
THAT IS THE SPOT IT ENDED FOR
HIM AND HIS LIFE OF FREEDOM IS
MOST LIKELY OVER .
WHILE POLICE SEARCHED FOR
SUSPECTS.
THERE HEART BREAK IN TEXAS.
TODAY, A MAJOR ANNOUNCEMENT
FOR THE HUNDREDS OF FAMILIES
THAT HAD TO EVACUATE.
>> THAT'S NEXT.
MINE WAS EARNED IN
DJIBOUTI, AFRICA, 2004.
THE BATTLE OF BATAAN,
1942.
[ all ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA, IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]
USAA AUTO INSURANCE
IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN FROM
GENERATION TO GENERATION
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE THE MILITARY,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY.
GET AN AUTO-INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA.
WE KNOW WHAT IT MEANS TO SERVE.
ARE YOU STILL SLEEPING?
JUST WANTED TO CHECK AND MAKE
SURE THAT WE WERE ON SCHEDULE.
THE FIRST TECHNOLOGY
OF ITS KIND...
MOM AND DAD, I HAVE GREAT NEWS.
IS NOW PROVIDING
ANSWERS FAMILIES NEED.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
ALRIGHT,
RIGHT IN THE OLD BUCKET.
GOOD TOSS!
SEE THAT'S MUCH BETTER!
THAT WAS GOOD.
YOU HAD YOUR SHOULDER POINTED,
YOU KEPT YOUR EYES
ON YOUR TARGET.
LET'S DO IT AGAIN --
WATCH ME.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
PASS DOWN SOMETHING
HE WILL BE GRATEFUL FOR.
THE RDABLE MIDSI PASSAT.
AND YOU'LL BE GRATEFUL
RIGHT NOW
DURING SPRINGTOBERFEST
WHERE YOU CAN LEASE
ONE OF FOUR DIFFERENT
VOLKSWAGEN MODELS
FOR UNDER $200 A MONTH.
THAT'S THE POWER
OF GERMAN ENGINEERING.
>> THE ATTACK IN BOSTON
OVERSHADIED THE MASSIVE DEADLY
EXPLOSION AT A FERTILIZER
PLANT IN TEXAS.
SOME FOLKS MAY BE ABLE TO COME
BACK HOME.
>> IT IS SAFE, IT IS SAFE, IT
IS SAFE FOR OUR CITIZENS.
>> OF COURSE, MANY PEOPLE, NO
LONGER HAVE A HOME AFTER
WEDNESDAY'S BLAST IN THE STAVE
WEST, OUTSIDE OF DALLAS.
>> I CAN'T HEAR.
I CAN'T HEAR.
GET OUT OF HERE, PLEASE.
>> THAT EXPLOSION LEVEL WOULD
DOZENS OF HOUSES AND KILLED 14
PEOPLE AND HURT 200 OTHERINGS.
FOLKS SAID THEY COULD HEAR
THAT BLAST 40 MILES AWAY .
TODAY A PARAMEDIC AND SAID
LEAKING GAS TANKINGS TRIGGERED
NEW FIRES AND DOWN PLAYED THE
THREAT OF ANOTHER DEADLY
BLAST.
>> DOMINIC?
>> SHEP, THE THOUGHT OF
ANOTHER EXPLOSION IN THE TOWN
TRAUMATIZED OF THE BLAST ON
WEDNESDAY STRUCK FEAR.
PEOPLE ARE TERRIFIED THEY
COULD BE HURT AGAIN.
THERE ARE NO LEAKS AND THAT IS
ALLAYING THE FEARS HERE AND
THE FACES OF THE DEAD STARTED
TO EMERGE AND THE NAMES OF 10
OF THE 14 BODIES THAT SO FAR
HAVE BEEN RECOVERED.
MOST AFFECTED IS THE VOLUNTEER
FIRE DEPARTMENT AND ACTING
FIRE CHIEF IS THE SON OF THE
FIRE CHIEF WHO WAS INJURED AND
IN THE HOSPITAL IN DALLAS.
GEORGE NORIS JUNIOR SAID HE
WAS TOO EMOTIONAL TO TALK
ABOUT THE FATE -- STATE OF HIS
FATHER.
>> A LOT OF THE CHAPLAIN FROM
THE OTHER DEPARTMENTS ARE TALK
GET OFF OF YOUR CHEST AND LET
YOU KNOW THEY ARE HERE TO UPON
HAD US AND WORK THROUGH THIS
IS NOT AN OVERNIGHT FIX IT IS
GOING TO BE YOU KNOW, A DRAWN
OUT FIX I GUESS YOU COULD SAY
.
THEY ARE HERE TO SUPPORT US
AND HELP US GET BACK UP.
>> AND SHEP, JUST A FEW
MOMENTS AGO, THE ASSISTANT
FIRE MARSHALL OF THE TOWN
DOESN'T KNOW WHAT THE CAUSE OF
THE ORIGINAL FIRE .
IN THE PAST FEW HOURS IT WAS
POSSIBLE TO ACSESS THE SITE.
>> OLD GLORY ON DISPLAY IN FEN
WAY PARK THIS AFTERNOON.
THE SOX AT HOME FOR THE FIRST
TIME SINCE THE ATTACK AND
PAYING TRIBUTE TO THE
VOLUNTEERS AND VICTIMS AND
RESCUER WORKER OF THE BOMBING.
>> THIS IS OUR CITY.
HE ADD A CITY.
SPORTS HELPING TO HELD A TOWN
AND NATION .
NEXT .
♪
Hey everybody, hi mom...
streaming live with a tour
of my new place...
Knowing you can still
reach out.
... and now you've seen it.
Verizon.
Get mom a Lucid 2 by LG
for free.
>> LESS THAN A WEEK AFTER THE
BOMBINGS IN BOSTON.
36,000 RUNNERS HIT THE STREETS
OF LONDON FOR THAT CITY'S BIG
MARATHON.
SECURITY POLICE INCREASED 40
PERCENT FOR THE EVENT.
THAT MEANS MORE OFFICERS AND
SNIFFING DOGS ON HAND AND
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF
SPECTATORS EXPECTED TO LINE
THE ROUTE.
BRITISH OFFICIALS SAY THERE IS
NO CHANGE TO WANT THREAT LEVEL
BUT LONDON IS NOER TO TERROR
ATTACKS.
WITH US IS MIKE, THE DAILY
NATIONAL SPHORTS EDITOR.
I WONDER IF THEY WILL PULL
THIS THING OFF?
>> MARATHONERS ARE A TRIBE AND
SO WHEN SOMETHING AS HORRIBLE
OF WHAT HAPPENED IN BOSTON,
HAPPENED.
THEY WILL PUT MORE EMPHASIS
AND MORE SECURITY.
BUT PEOPLE WANTING TO RUN AND
SHOW SUPPORT FOR THE PEOPLE OF
BOSTON AND MARATHONERINGS.
>> DID THEY HAVE CANCELLATIONS
>> I AM SURE PEOPLE GOT COLD
FEET.
BUT IN TERPS OF PEOPLE WANTING
TO SHOW SUPPORT THEY ARE
WANTING TO DO IT.
>> THEY ARE READY FOR THIS.
>> THE INCREASED PRESENCE .
POLICE OFFICER AND HEART AND
SOUL OF THE PEOPLE RUNNING THE
MARATON.
>> TWO OF THE BOSTON SPORTS
TEAMS .
THEY ARE HONORING THE MARATHON
BOMBING VICTIMS IN THE CITY
TODAY.
AT THE SOX GAME PLAYERS AND
FANS SANG THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
♪
♪ BANNER YET WAVE.
♪ ORCH LAND OF THE FREE.
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE BRAVE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I ON THE STREETS LAST NIGHT
AS THE PARTYING BEGAN MIKE,
AND THEIR RESILIENCE IS
IMPRESSIVE.
>> IT IS IMPRESSIVE AND YOU
SAW THE FIRST NIGHT AND THE
GARDEN GAME WITH THE BRUINS.
BUILDING UP AND SPINGING THE
ANTHEM AND THE RED SOX GAME
AND THE CROWD GETTING INTO IT
SINGING THE ANTHEM AND THEN
NEAL DIAMOND SINGING SWEET
CARROLLINE AND THE SONG AT
YANKEES STADIUM AND A SHOW OF
SUPPORT.
BOSTON REALLY BRINGING ITSAN
THEM.
>> RED SOX ANTHEM BEING SUN IN
YANKEES STADIUM ON ENEMY
GROUND.
IT A GREAT SHOW OF SUPPORT BY
THE YANKEES FANNINGS.
>> A SIMILAR THING HAPPENED IN
FEN WAY.
FOR FOLKS IN NEW YORK.
IT IS FUNNY HOW THESE TWO
CITIES LOATHE EACH OTHER TEAMS
HAVE SO MUCH IN COMMON.
>> AND EVEN SAW IN MADISON
SQUARE GARDEN.
CARMELO ANTHONY AND PAUL
PIERCE SAYING BEFORE THE START
OF THE GAME.
THERE BOOS WHEN PAUL STARTED
TO SPEAK BUT NOT WAS DROWNED
OUT WITH CHEERS IT ALL BOILS
DOWN WE ARE IN THIS TOGETHER.
>> AND.
KNICKS.
THE CELTICS HAVE THE VETERAN
PLAYERS AND HAVE GARNET AND
DOC RIVERS AND KNICKINGS RIGHT
BEHIND THE HEAT.
THEY WILL HAVE THEIR HANDS
FULL WITH THE CELTICS THIS GO
AROUND.
>> AMERICA'S TEAM BLACKOUT
HAPPENED IN BROOKLYN.
>> AMERICA'S TEAM TO YOU.
>> GO NETS.
THANK YOU, MIKE.
THIS TIME THE POLICE HAD
CORNERED THE SECOND SUSPECT
AND UNFOLDING LIVE DURING THE
FOX REPORT.
AN UPDATE ON THE 24 HOURS
SINCE THEN.
FROM THE SUSPECT'S MEDICAL
CONDITION AND TO WHERE THE
INVESTIGATION GOES FROM HERE.
THAT'S NEXT.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
FROM THE WAY THE BRISTLES MOVE
TO THE WAY THEY CLEAN,
ONCE YOU TRY AN ORAL-B
DEEP SWEEP POWER BRUSH,
YOU'LL NEVER GO BACK
TO A REGULAR MANUAL BRUSH.
ITS THREE CLEANING ZONES
WITH DYNAMIC POWER BRISTLES
REACH BETWEEN TEETH
WITH MORE BRUSH MOVEMENTS
TO REMOVE
UP TO 100% MORE PLAQUE
THAN A REGULAR MANUAL BRUSH.
AND EVEN 76% MORE PLAQUE
THAN SONICARE FLEXCARE
IN HARD TO REACH AREAS.
ORAL-B DEEP SWEEP 5000
POWER BRUSH.
LIFE OPENS UP WHEN YOU DO.
ARE PROVEN TO BE
EFFECTIVE PAIN RELIEVERS.
Tylenol WORKS BY BLOCKING
PAIN SIGNALS TO YOUR BRAIN.
Bayer Advanced Aspirin
BLOCKS PAIN AT THE SITE.
TRY THE POWER
OF Bayer
Advanced Aspirin.
TO YOUR TABLE
FOR A LIMITED TIME!
IT'S OUR SEAFOOD DINNER FOR TWO
FOR JUST 25 DOLLARS!
A HANDCRAFTED SEAFOOD FEAST
MADE TO SHARE.
FIRST YOU EACH GET SALAD
AND UNLIMITED
CHEDDAR BAY BISCUITS.
THEN CHOOSE TWO
FROM A WIDE VARIETY
OF CHEF-INSPIRED TRéES
LIKE OUR NEW
HONEY GARLIC CRISPY SHRIMP
OR NEW
SEAFOOD LOVER'S LINGUI.
ROUND OUT YOUR SEAFOOD DINNER
WITH YOUR CHOICE
OF EITHER AN APPETIZER
OR DESSERT TO SHARE!
DON'T MISS OUR SEAFOOD DINNER
FOR TWO, JUST $25
AT RED LOBSTER,
WHERE WE SEA FOOD DIFFERENT.
♪
[ Male Announcer ] THIS IS A
STUNNING WORK OF TECHNOLOGY.
♪
THIS IS THE 2013 LEXUS ES
AND THE FIRST-EVER ES HYBRID.
THIS IS
THE PURSUIT OF PERFECTION.
CHARGINGS FOR THE SURVIVING
BOSTON SUSPECT COULD COME
TONIGHT.
THAT IS THE LATEST FROM THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
RIGHT NOW SPECIAL
INTERROGATION TEAMS ARE IN THE
HOSPITAL TO QUESTION THE
SUSPECT.
HE IS STILL UNCONSCIOUS AND IN
SERIOUS CONDITION.
MOMENTS AGO, WE GOT A NEW
PICTURE OF THE BOAT IN WHICH
THE SUSPECT WAS HIDING IT
SPLATTERED WITH BLOOD AND
FILLED WITH BULLET HOLES.
JENNIFER DAVIS IS WRAPPING UP
THE SCENE TONIGHT.
>> SHEP, CITY STREETS AND
ASKED WALKS AND PARKS
BUSTLING.
THEY ARE SHOWING WHAT IT MEANS
TO BE BOSTON STRONG .
THE LATEST WORD IS THAT THE
SUSPECT REMAIN HOSPITAL IN
SERIOUS AND STABLE CONDITION
STILL UNABLE TO COMMUNICATE
BEFORE THE MANHUNT ENDED WHEN
HE WAS DISCOVERED BLOOD
YEHIDING OUT IN WATERTOWN.
HE HAS NOT BEEN CHARGED AND WE
ARE WAITING FOR MORE ON THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT ON HOW THEY
PLAN TO PROCEED AMID
CONTROVERSY AND HOW THEY THINK
IT SHOULD PROCEED AND STILL NO
WORD.
AT THE SAME TIME CRIME SCENE
IN THE MARATHON FINISH LINE
AND IN WATTWATTCONTINUE TO BE
PROCESSED FOR EVIDENCE AND
INVESTIGATORS ARE LOOKING FOR
A MOTIVE AND BETTER
UNDERSTANDING OF THE BROTHERS
WORKING ALONE OR NOT AND WHEN
THEY BECAME RADICALIZED.
>>S THANK YOU.
>> AND ON THIS DAY IN 1999 TWO
SENIOR NECESSARY TRENCH COATS
KILLED 12 STUDENTS AND A
TEACHER THE ATTACKERS WERE 17
YEAR OLD ERIC HARRIS AND
KLEBOLD.
>> AND THE THERE ANOTHER
SENIOR ARRESTED IN THE HIGH
SCHOOL AFTER HE THREATEN TOD
FINISH THE JOB.
SCHOOL SHOOTINGS HAVE NOT GONE
AWAY.
IN 2007 THE GUNMEN TOOK THE
LIVES OF 32 PEOPLE IN VIRGINIA
TECH .
LAST YEAR 26 KIMED IN SANDY
HOOK.
BUT THE GRUESOME DAY IN
COLUMBINE I WILL NEVER FORGET
14 YEARS AGO TODAY .
NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS THISFOR
SATURDAY APRIL 20TH.
I AM SHEPHERD SMITH.
OUR THANK TOGS OUR FRIENDS IN
WXTX