LACK AT THAT FINALLY PUTS
HIS HANDS UP.
THAT WAS GOOD.
THANKS FOR INVITING US INTO
YOUR HOME TONIGHT.
THAT IS IT FOR THIS
"SPECIAL REPORT."
FAIR, BALANCED AND STILL
UNAFRAID.
>> Shepard: THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT.
TONIGHT, THE JODI ARIAS
JURY WORKING ON A LIFE OR
DEATH DECISION.
THE JURORS SAY THEY HAVE
ANOTHER QUESTION ABOUT THE
CASE.
PLUS, WHEN IS IT OKAY FOR
OUR GOVERNMENT TO KILL OUR
PEOPLE?
PRESIDENT OBAMA LAYING OUT
HIS POLICY.
>> TECHNOLOGY RAISES
PROFOUND QUESTIONS.
>> DRONES HAVE BECOME A
MAJOR PART OF COUNTER
TERRORISM.
FROM THOUSANDS OF MILES
AWAY OPERATORS CAN PULL THE
TRIGGER AND TAKE OUT A
TARGET.
BUT WHAT ARE THE ACTUAL
RULES FOR KILLING ENEMY OR
KILLING AMERICANS?
>> THE TARGETING OF ANY
AMERICAN RAISES
CONSTITUTIONAL ISSUES THAT
ARE NOT PRESENT IN OTHER
STRIKES.
>> TONIGHT, PRESIDENT OBAMA
ON OUR MACHINES OF WAR.
ATTACK ON THE STREETS OF
LONDON.
TWO MEN ACCUSED OF HACKING
A SOLDIER TO DEATH WITH
BUTCHER KNIVES AND A
MACHETE.
NOW YOU WILL MEET THE HERO
MOTHER WHO CONFRONTED THE
SUSPECTS SECONDS AFTER IT
ALL WENT DOWN.
>> I OKAY OBVIOUSLY A BIT
EXCITED.
>> Trace: PLUS REPORTS THAT
SECURITY FORCES HAD
INVESTIGATED THESE GUYS IN
THE PAST.
AND AN 80-YEAR-OLD MAN
BECOME THE OLDEST TO REACH
THE TOP OF THE WORLD BUT
SOMEBODY ELSE COULD BREAK
HIS RECORD WITHIN DAYS.
TONIGHT BATTLE ATOP MOUNT
EVERY REST.
>> Shepard: BUT FIRST FROM
FOX THIS THURSDAY NIGHT THE
PRESIDENT IS RULING OUT THE
DRONING OF AMERICANS IN
AMERICA ONCE AND FOREALL.
AND SPELLING OUT THE RULES
FOR DRONE STRIKES TO TAKE
OUT TERRORIST SUSPECTS
INCLUDING U.S. CITIZENS
OVERSEAS.
PRESIDENT OBAMA ALSO
CALLING FOR NEW STEPS TO
SHUT DOWN THE PRISON AT
GUANTANAMO BAY AT LAST AND
BRING SOME DETAINEES HERE
TO THE UNITED STATES.
>> GIVEN MY
ADMINISTRATION'S RELENTLESS
PURSUIT OF AL QAEDA'S
LEADERSHIP, THERE IS NO
JUSTIFICATION BEYOND
POLITICS FOR CONGRESS TO
PREVENT US FROM CLOSING A
FACILITY THAT SHOULD HAVE
NEVER BEEN OPENED.
>> THE JUSTIFICATION FOR
CLOSING GITMO IS THAT WE
DESTROYED THE AL QAEDA
LEADERSHIP RELENTLESS IN
OUR PURSUIT OF TERRORISTS.
THAT IS NOT A GOOD
JUSTIFICATION BECAUSE THAT
IS NOT TRUE.
THE REASON WE HAVEN'T
CLOSED GUANTANAMO BAY IS WE
DON'T HAVE A PLAN TO CLOSE
IT.
YOU NEED A PLAN.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT ALSO
HEARD REACTION TO HIS PLANS
DURING HIS SPEECH AT THE
NATIONAL DEFENSE UNIVERSITY
IN WASHINGTON.
I HAD HENRY IS ON FOX TOP
STORY LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE TONIGHT.
ED HE IS TALKING ABOUT, I
GUESS, IN ESSENCE SCALING
BACK THE WAR ON TERROR?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HE IS NOT EVEN REALLY USING
THE PHRASE WAR ON TERROR
ANYMORE.
SAYS THAT WHAT WE CALLED
THE WAR ON TERROR IT
BECOMES SELF-DEFEATING IN
HIS WORDS TO CONSTANTLY BE
ON A WAR FOOTING.
HE BELIEVES WE HAVE GOT TO
CHANGE OUR TOOLS, GOT TO
COME UP WITH A BETTER LEGAL
FRAMEWORK TO EXPLAIN TO THE
PUBLIC EXACTLY HOW WE'RE
USING THESE TOOLS TO FIND
TERROR.
SPECIFICALLY, HE IS
STARTING WITH TRYING TO
FINALLY MAKE GOOD ON THAT
FAILED PROMISE FROM HIS
FIRST WEEK IN OFFICE HERE
TO CLOSE THE U.S. MILITARY
PRISON AT GUANTANAMO BAY.
YOU MENTIONED THAT HE HAD
GOT SOME DIRECT FEEDBACK ON
THAT.
IT CAME FROM A HECKLER AT
CODE PINK WHO LET THE
PRESIDENT HAVE IT ABOUT
THAT HUNGER STRIKE THAT'S
GOING ON AT GUANTANAMO
RIGHT NOW.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> I'M ABOUT.
>> YOU ARE COMMANDER AND
CHIEF.
>> LET ME.
>> YOU CAN CLOSE GAHANNA
TAN TODAY.
>> THANK YOU.
YOU SHOULD LET ME FINISH MY
SENTENCE.
TODAY.
I ONCE AGAIN CALL ON
CONGRESS TO LIFT THE
RESTRICTIONS ON DETAINEE
TRANSFERS TO GITMO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> I HAVE ASKED THE
DEPARTMENT OF DEFENSE TO
DESIGNATE A SITE IN THE
UNITED STATES WHERE WE CAN
HOLD MILITARY COMMISSIONS.
>> REPUBLICANS LIKE JOHN
MCCAIN TONIGHT SAYING HE
WILL WORK WITH THE
PRESIDENT TO TRY TO MAKE
THAT HAPPEN.
BUT THAT HE BELIEVES THE
PRESIDENT STILL HASN'T
GIVEN A CLEAR PLAN ABOUT
HOW TO FOLLOW UP ON ALL OF
THAT.
AND THAT'S THE REAL REASON
WHY CONGRESS HASN'T MOVED
ON IT, SHEP.
>> Shepard: ED, WE GOT A
LOT OF DETAIL BRAND NEW
DETAIL ON THE DRONE
PROGRAM.
>> AND UNPRECEDENTED AMOUNT
OF DETAIL THE PRESIDENT
LAYING OUT AND ADMITTING
THAT THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
HAS SKILLED AT LEAST FOUR
AMERICANS SINCE 2009.
OVERSEAS.
ONE OF ONLY ONE OF THEM
ANWAR AL AWLAKI WAS
ACTUALLY TARGETED.
THE OTHER THREE WERE TAKEN
OUT AS PART OF OTHER
OPERATIONS.
NOT DIRECTLY TARGETED.
THE PRESIDENT BASICALLY
SAID THAT HE WANTS TO LAY
OUT A LEGAL FRAMEWORK TO
MAKE SURE THAT WE LIMIT
CIVILIAN CASUALTIES WHEN WE
USE THE DRONES.
REPUBLICANS ARE SAYING THEY
WANT TO SEE MORE DETAILS ON
THAT AS WELL.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> BEFORE ANY STRIKE IS
TAKEN, THERE MUST BE NEAR
CERTAINTY THAT NO CIVILIANS
WILL BE KILLED OR INJURED.
THE HIGHEST STANDARD WE CAN
SET.
>> WHAT I THINK CONGRESS
MUST DEMAND OF THE
ADMINISTRATION IS THE LEGAL
RATIONALE.
PROMPT NOTIFICATIONS WHEN
THERE IS A LETHAL ACTION OR
CAPTURE SITUATION OUTSIDE
OF AFGHANISTAN.
>> TO ADDRESS SOME OF THOSE
CONCERNS, THE PRESIDENT
SAYING IS HE LARGELY MOVING
KEY PARTS OF THE DRONE
PROGRAM FROM THE CIA'S
CONTROL TO THE PENTAGON'S
CONTROL.
HE THINKS THAT WILL BE A
BIT MORE TRANSPARENT, SHEP.
>> Shepard: ED, THE
PRESIDENT SAYS HE ALSO
BELIEVES THAT JOURNALISTS
SHOULD NOT FACE LEGAL
ACTION FOR DOING THEIR JOBS
IF THEY END UP IN THE
MIDDLE OF LEAK
INVESTIGATIONS.
TONIGHT THE PRESIDENT SAYS
IS DOING SOMETHING ABOUT IT
THAT IS COMING UP IN DETAIL
INSIDE FOX REPORT.
BUT, FIRST, POLICE HAVE NOT
ARRESTED MORE PEOPLE AFTER
THAT BRUTAL KNIFE ATTACK ON
THE STREETS OF LONDON.
ONE THAT LEFT A SOLDIER
DEAD AND BEHEADED IN THE
STREET.
AND NOW A WOMAN WHO
CONFRONTED THE TWO MEN
ACCUSED OF HACKING THAT
SOLDIER SAYS SHE WAS JUST
TRYING TO KEEP THEM CALM.
AND STOP THEM FROM HURTING
ANYBODY ELSE.
AT LEAST ONE OF THE MEN WAS
STILL CARRYING BUTCHER
KNIVES.
HIS HANDS DRIPPING WITH
BLOOD AFTER WITNESSES SAY
HE AND ANOTHER MAN CARVED
UP AN OFF DUTY BRITISH
SOLDIER.
HE THEN STARTED RANTING
ABOUT THE BRITISH
GOVERNMENT AND ITS TROOPS
IN FOREIGN COUNTRIES.
HOW THIS ATTACK IS PAY BACK
FOR THE DEATHS OF MUSLIMS.
THE WOMAN WHO WENT WITH UP
TO THE MEN IS A SCOUT
LEADER AND A MOTHER AND SHE
SAYS SHE WAS MORE WORRIED
ABOUT OTHERS THAN HER OWN
SAFETY.
>> WERE YOU NOT SCARED FOR
YOURSELF IN THAT SITUATION?
>> NO.
>> WHY NOT?
>> BETTER ME THAN A CHILD.
BECAUSE, UNFORTUNATELY MORE
MOTHERS WITH CHILDREN
STOPPING AROUND.
MORE AND MORE IMPORTANT.
I TALKED TO HIM AND THEN I
ASKED HIM WHAT HE WANTED.
>> REASONING WITH AN
APPARENT MAD MAN.
IT WORKED UNTIL POLICE
ARRIVED AND SHOT AND
WOUNDED BOTH MEN.
AND JUST HOURS AGO WORD OF
BRAND NEW ARRESTS TWO MORE
PEOPLE ARE IN CUSTODY AS
FOX REPORTS LIVE TONIGHT.
AGREEING PALKOT IS LIVE FOR
US IN LONDON THIS EVENING.
GREG, WHAT DO WE KNOW ABOUT
THESE TWO NEW SUSPECTS?
>> YEAH SHEP, THERE ARE
MORE DEVELOPMENTS ON WHAT
POLICE TONIGHT ARE CALLING
A FAST9Bfñ÷ MOVING
INVESTIGATION.
THESE TWO PEOPLE ARE UNDER
ARREST FOR SUSPICION OF
CONSPIRACY TO MURDER THE
APPARENT RESULT OF HOUSE
SEARCHES TODAY.
AND THAT AN APPARENT RESULT
OF THE SUSPECTED KILLERS
ALREADY BEING ON THE RADAR
OF SECURITY SERVICES HERE.
THE TWO ARE SAID TO BE
BRITISH BORN OF NIGERIAN
DISSENT WITH ASSOCIATIONS
WITH RADICAL ISLAM.
ONE OF THE SUSPECTS WE ARE
TOLD THOUGHT TO BE FAMILIAR
AROUND THE COMMUNITY.
SPOUTING ISLAMIC RHETORIC
AND RAISING QUESTIONS HERE
ABOUT WHY AUTHORITIES
DIDN'T HALL THEM IN
EARLIER.
THEY ARE NOW TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHETHER THERE
WAS A JIHADI NETWORK
BACKING UP THE SUSPECTED
KILLERS OR WHETHER THEY
ACTED ON THEIR OWN.
REGARD ALSO, BOTH ARE IN
THE HOSPITAL RIGHT NOW AND
ARE BEING GUNNED DOWN
POLICE UNDER ARREST.
U.K. PRIME MINISTER DAVID
CAMMERON IS SAYING THAT
THERE IS RESOLVE AND
RESOLUTION IN THE FACE OF
TERROR.
FINALLY SHEP, MINISTRY OF
DEFENSE HERE NAMING THE
VICTIM OF THIS ROAR RISK
ACT.
IS HE LEE RIGBY.
HE HOLDS THE RANK AND
POSITION OF DRUMMER IN THE
CEREMONIAL PART OF HIS JOB.
HE IS ALSO SAID TO BE A
GOOD MACHINE GUNNER.
HE WAS.
HE WAS IN AFGHANISTAN.
HE WAS IN COMBAT AND HE WAS
A FATHER OF A 2-YEAR-OLD
SON.
HE IS SAID -- IT IS SAID HE
WILL BE MISSED AND THAT'S
WHAT THE MINISTRY OF
DEFENSE IS SAYING TONIGHT.
>> Shepard: GREG PALKOT IN
LONDON TONIGHT.
THANKS.
THE VICTIM'S FAMILY
RELEASED A STATEMENT WHICH
READS IN PART.
LEE WAS LOVELY.
HE WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR
ANYBODY.
HE ALWAYS LOOK AFTER HIS
SISTERS AND ALWAYS
PROTECTED THEM.
IT CONTINUED:  ALL HE
WANTED TO DO FROM WHEN HE
WAS A LITTLE BOY WAS BEING
IN
BE IN THE ARMY.
LEE RIGBY WAS BUT 25 YEARS
OLD.
OUR 401(K)'S TOOK A BEATING
THIS MORNING BUT BY THE
AFTERNOON TRADERS WERE ABLE
TO MAKE UP SOME BUT NOT ALL
OF THE GROUND THEY LOST.
STOCKS FIRST WENT NEGATIVE
AFTER A SURPRISINGLY WEAK
REPORT ON THE CHINESE
FACTORY OUTPUT.
BUT HERE IN THE UNITED
STATES GOVERNMENT REPORTS
SHOW THAT SALES OF NEW
HOMES SPIKED AGAIN LAST
MONTH TO THEIR SECOND
HIGHEST LEVEL SINCE BEFORE
THE RECESSION BEGAN IN
2008.
WHAT'S MORE, FEWER
AMERICANS CLAIMED FIRST
TIME CLAIM FOR JOBLESS
BENEFITS LAST WEEK.
DOWN TO 340,000, A LEVEL
THAT ANALYSTS SUGGEST SOLID
JOB GROWTH.
SO BY THE END OF THE
TRADING SESSION THE DOW WAS
OFF BUT 13 AND NASDAQ DOWN
4.
THE S&P 500 LOST 5.
DEAD LOCK DRAMA AS WE AWAIT
THE JURY'S DECISION IN THE
JODI ARIAS CASE.
WHAT HAPPENS IF THE JURORS
CANNOT AGREE ABOUT WHETHER
JODI ARIAS SHOULD LIVE OR
DIE FOR HER CRIME?
PLUS THE BOY SCOUTS MAKE
HISTORY NOW WITH A DECISION
ABOUT INCLUDING OPENLY GAY
SCOUTS.
BUT WHAT ABOUT SCOUT
MASTERS?
THAT'S AHEAD FROM THE
JOURNALISTS OF FOX NEWS ON
THIS THURSDAY FOX REPORT.
HOW LONG BEFORE HE GOES  TO COLLEGE?
[ Woman ]  ...BECAME A REAL QUESTION.
ARE WE READY  TO PAY FOR COLLEGE?
[ Woman ]  SO THEY CAME TO SEE ME
AND WE TALKED ABOUT  WAYS TO MANAGE
THEIR MONEY  AND SAVE FOR COLLEGE
THAT FIT THEIR SITUATION.  SO WHEN
LITTLE DAVID --  WELL, NOT-SO-LITTLE
DAVID  WAS READY TO GO TO COLLEGE,
HIS PARENTS WERE READY, TOO.  WE DID
IT.    [ Female Announcer ]    LET'S
TALK ABOUT SMARTER WAYS    TO MANAGE
AND SAVE YOUR MONEY.    WHEN PEOPLE
TALK,    GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.    WELLS
FARGO.    TOGETHER WE'LL GO FAR.
PEOPLE JOIN ANGIE'S LIST    FOR ALL
KINDS OF REASONS.  I GO TO ANGIE'S
LIST  TO GAUGE WHETHER OR NOT
THE PROJECTS WILL BE DONE  IN A TIMELY
FASHION
AND WITHIN BUDGET.
ANGIE'S LIST MEMBERS
CAN TELL YOU WHICH PROVIDER  IS THE
BEST IN TOWN.
YOU'LL FIND REVIEWS    ON EVERYTHING
FROM HOME REPAIR TO HEALTHCARE.
NOW THAT WE'RE EXPECTING  I LIKE THE
FACT
THAT I CAN GO ONTO ANGIE'S LIST  AND
LOOK FOR PEDIATRICIANS.
THE SERVICE PROVIDERS  THAT I'VE FOUND
ON ANGIE'S LIST
ACTUALLY HAVE BLOWN ME AWAY.
JOIN TODAY AND FIND OUT
WHY OVER 1 MILLION MEMBERS    COUNT
ON ANGIE'S LIST.
ANGIE'S LIST --    REVIEWS YOU CAN
TRUST.
>> Shepard: FOX YOU ARE
JEST.
BOY SCOUTS OF AMERICA
APPROVED A PLAN THAT WILL
END THE PLAN OF OPENLY GAY
BOYS IN THE SCOUTS.
A RESTRICTION THAT HAD BEEN
IN PLACE THROUGHOUT THE
103--YEAR-OLD
ORGANIZATION'S HISTORY.
1400 MEMBERS OF THE GROUP'S
NATIONAL COUNCIL GATHERED
IN TEXAS TO VOTE ON THIS
PROPOSAL.
THE REVERSAL DOES NOT
REMOVE THE BAN ON GAY ADULT
LEADERS THREE DAYS OF
DELIBERATION AND THE JURY
HAS NOT DECIDED WHETHE"K  EI-   JODI
ARIAS LIVES OR DIE.
IN THE LAST HOUR WE LEARNED
WHETHER ASKED ANOTHER
QUESTION.
15 HOURS FOUR DAYS TO
CONVICT JODI ARIAS OF
HEARDED IN THE FIRST DEGREE
FOR SHOOTING EX-BOYFRIEND
IN THE HEAD.
STABBING HIM 27 TIMES AND
SOLICITING HIM IN THE
THROAT.
KEEP IN MIND JODI ARIAS
LARGELY CHAINED HER TUNE
EARLIER THIS WEEK IN HER
SPEECH TO THE JURY.
SHE SAID THAT SHE NO LONGER
WANTED THE DEATH PENALTY
AND PROMISED TO BRING ON
POSITIVE CHANGE FROM PRISON
BY TEACHING INMATES HOW TO
READ AND SPEAK SPANISH,
EVEN STARTING A NEW
RECYCLING PROGRAM AMONG
OTHER THINGS.
TRACE GALLAGHER LIVE IN OUR
WEST COAST NEWSROOM FOR US
THIS AFTERNOON.
ANY MORE MOVEMENT FROM THE
COURTHOUSE TRACE?
>> CERTAINLY THE MOST WE
HAVE SEEN ALLSñ DAY SHEP.
THE COURT REPORTER GOT
SUMMONSED TO COURT ALONG
WITH THE HEAD OF SECURITY
AND THE FAMILY OF TRAVIS
ALEXANDER BEGAN STREAMING
IN.
WE THOUGHT IT WAS JUST THE
JURY QUESTION YOU TALKED
ABOUT.
THEY ARE STILL IN AROUND
AROUND THE COURTROOM.
THERE COULD BE MORE GOING
ON HERE THAT WOULD HAVE
BEEN BY THE WAY, THE
SECOND COURT QUESTION FROM
THE DAY FROM THE JURY.
AND BECAUSE THEY ARE SEALED
THEY WON'T EXACTLY TELL US
WHAT THE JURY WANTS.
KEEP IN MIND THE JURY SO
FAR HAS DELIBERATED ABOUT
13 HOURS DURING THE PENALTY
PHASE.
THEY ONLY DELIBERATED 15
HOURS DURING THE GUILT OR
INNOCENCE PHASE.
AND BECAUSE ALL OF THE
MAJOR PLAYERS ARE ON SCENE,
IF THERE IS A VERDICT
SOMETIME IN THE NEXT 15 OR
20 MINUTES SHEP, IT IS
LIKELY IT WOULD BE READ
RELATIVELY QUICKLY.
>> Shepard: IF THERE IS NOT
A VERDICT, TRACE.
I'M HEARING THAT THIS JURY
MAY TAKE A LONG WEEKEND; IS
THAT RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
YOU COULD BE RIGHT SHEP.
NORMALLY THEY FINISH
DELIBERATIONS AT ABOUT 4:30
LOCAL TIME.
ABOUT 15 MINUTES FROM NOW.
NORMALLY THERE IS NO COURT
ON FRIDAY.
THEN, OF COURSE MONDAY IS
A HOLIDAY BUT NOW WE ARE
HEARING FROM THE COURT THEY
COULD GO AS LONGoT3 AS
WEDNESDAY BEFORE THEY
ACTUALLY COME BACK IN FOR
DELIBERATIONS.
FIVE DAYS.
A LONG WAIT FOR JODI ARIAS.
NOW, REMEMBER IF THEY ARE
HOPELESSLY DEADLOCKED, THE
COURT REALLY HAS JUST TWO
OPTIONS.
ONE, THEY CAN EITHER
IMPANEL A BRAND NEW JURY
AND RETRY PART OF THE
PENALTY PHASE OR, TWO,
PROSECUTORS COULD AGREE TO
WAIVE THE DEATH PENALTY AND
AGREE TO LIFE IN PRISON.
JODI ARIAS THINKS LIFE IN
PRISON WOULD BE LESS OF A
BURDEN ON THE LEGAL SYSTEM.
HERE SHE IS.
I DON'T THINK IT WILL GIVE
CLOSURE TO ANYONE.
IF I GET A DEATH VERDICT IT
WILL DRAG OAND ON AND ON IN
APPELLATE COURTS FOR YEARS
INSTEAD OF GETTING IT DONE
INSTEAD OF SENDING ME OFF
TO PRISON AND FORGETTING
ABOUT ME.
>> THE MEDIA HAS BEEN LET
INSIDE OF THE COURTROOM.
JODI ARIAS IS INSIDE OF THE
COURTROOM AS WELL AS ALL OF
THE ATTORNEYS.
WE DO DOO NOT KNOW IF THAT
IS PART OF THAT QUESTION WE
MENTIONED EARLIER BUT ALL
OF THE PLAYERS ARE NOW IN
THE COURTHOUSE.
WE AWAITING WORD FOR WHAT
IS GOING ON.
WE'RE GOING TO BE HERE
UNTIL THE JURY GOES HOME.   MOVEMENT,
WE
WILL JUMP BACK IN.
>> INDEED WE WILL.
TRACE GALLAGHER WE HAVE
LIVE COVERAGE WITHOUT
DOUBT.
THANK YOU.
A LOT OF FOLKS POINTED OUT
JODI ARIAS LOOKED PRETTY
GOOD DURING THE INTERVIEWS
EARLIER THIS WEEKS.
THE SELF-PROCLAIMED
TOUGHEST SHERIFF IN
AMERICA.
JOE ARPAIO SAYS THAT SOME
FOLKSED HIM IF HE PLAYED A
ROLE IN THAT HERE IS WHAT
HE TWEETED LATE YESTERDAY.
WE DID NOT BUY JODY MAKEUP.
WE WOULDN'T DO THAT.
THE MEDIA PROVIDED IT TO
HER.
AN EMOTIONAL DAY IN
OKLAHOMA.
AS THE PARENTS AT TOWER
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL MET WITH
THE TEACHERS WHO HELPED
SAVE THE LIVES OF MANY OF
THOSE CHILDREN.
AND JONATHAN HUNT WENT
INSIDE WHAT'S LEFT OF THE
SCHOOL TODAY TO SEE THE
DAMAGE FIRSTHAND.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AROUND AT
THE EXTENT OF THE
DESTRUCTION IN THIS SCHOOL
THE SHOCKING THING IS NOT
THAT SOME CHILDREN DID NOT
SURVIVE BUT THAT SO MANY
DID
THIS IS AMERICA.  WE DON'T LET FREQUENT
HEARTBURN  COME BETWEEN US  AND WHAT
WE LOVE.  SO IF YOU'RE ONE OF THEM
PEOPLE  WHO GETS HEARTBURN  AND THEN
TREATS DAY AFR DAY...  BLOCK THE ACID
WITH PRILOSEC OTC  AND DON'T GET HEARTBURN
IN THE FIRST PLACE!    [ Male Announcer
]    E PILL EACHMORNING.    24 HOURS.
ZERO HEARTBUR
ARE YOU STILL SLEEPING?
JUST WANTED TO CHECK AND MAKE  SURE
THAT WE WERE ON SCHEDULE.
THE FIRST TECHNOLOGY  OF ITS KIND...
MOM AND DAD, I HAVE GREAT NEWS.
IS NOW PROVIDING  ANSWERS FAMILIES
NEED.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
WHERE IS FLO?  ANYBODY KNOW WHERE
FLO IS?  ARE YOU FLO?
YES.  IS THIS THE THING  YOU GAVE
MY HUSBAND?
WELL, YEAH, YES.  THE "NAME YOUR PRICE"
TOOL.
YOU TELL US THE PRICE  YOU WANT TO
PAY,
AND WE GIVE YOU A RANGE  OF OPTIONS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
CAREFUL, THOUGH -- THAT KIND  OF POWER
CAN GO TO YOUR HEAD.
THAT EXPLAINS  A LOT.
YO, BUDDY!
I GOT THIS.
GIMME ONE, GIMME ONE  GIMME ONE!
THE POWER OF    THE "NAME YOUR PRICE"
TOOL.
ONLY FROM PROGRESSIVE.
>> Shepard: INSULT TO
INJURY POWERFUL SEVERE
THUNDERSTORMS HAS SLOWED
THE RECOVERY NEXT AT 5:30
MOORE, OKLAHOMA AS LOVED
ONES BEGAN BURRING THE DEAD
FROM THE DEADLY TORNADO IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
FUNERAL FOR A 9-YEAR-OLD
GIRL.
SHE WAS AMONG SEVERAL
CHILDREN KILLED WHEN THE
TWISTER SLAMMED DIRECTLY
INTO PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
LEVELING NEARLY THE ENTIRE
PLACE.
PARENTS, STUDENTS AND
TEACHERS FROM PLAZA
ELEMENTARY TODAY REENUNITED
AT ANOTHER LOCAL SCHOOL.
MEMBER AMOTHER WHO WAS
THERE EXPLAINED HOW ONE OF
THOSE TEACHERS SAVED HER
DAUGHTER'S LIFE.
>> I AM NEVER GOING TO HAVE
ANYTHING, YOU KNOW ANY
WORDS TO, YOU KNOW TO
REPAY HER FOR WHAT SHE DID.
SHE, YOU KNOW, SHE THREW
HERSELF ON MY DAUGHTER TO
PROTECT HER AND I'M NEVER
GOING TO HAVE ANYTHING TO
REPAY HER.
>> "THE FOX REPORT'S"
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
EARLIER GOT A FIRST
EXTENSIVE LOOK AT WHAT'S
LEFT INSIDE THAT SCHOOL.
SHE IS LIVE ON THE SCHOOL
GROUNDS FOR US THIS
EVENING.
JONATHAN?
>> SHEP, IT IS A STUNNING
VISION OF UTTER DESTRUCTION
AND EVERYWHERE THERE ARE
POIGNANT REMINDERS THAT
THIS WAS A PLACE THAT
CHILDREN WENT TO BE SAFE
AND WENT TO LEARN.
WE SAW LAYING ON THE FLOOR
A MAP OF THE UNITED STATES.
WE SAW CHILDREN'S BOOKS
SCATTERED AMONG THE RUBBLE.
WE ALSO SAW SOME BOOKS
STILL UNTOUCHED, STANDING
ON A BOOK SHELF THAT WAS IN
CON CON GREWOUSLY UPRIGHT.
WE SAW SCHOOLWORK STILL ON
THEIR DESKS, TRAGICALLY, OF
COURSE SEVEN CHILDREN DIED
HERE AT PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY MIRACULOUSLY
MANY MORE SURVIVED.
>> THIS SEVERE WEATHER
FRONT WALL OF THE SCHOOL
WAS.
>> THIS WAS WHERE THE FRONT
HALL OF THE SCHOOL WAS.
CLASSROOMS ON EACH SIDE.
THESE CLASSROOMS ARE NO
LONGER HERE.
THESE CLASSROOMS ARE.
THIS IS WHERE SOME STUDENTS
WERE SENT.
THIS IS A SAFE AREA IN THE
HALLWAY.
THERE WERE STUDENTS IN THE
HALLWAY THEY TAKE THEIR
CROUCHING DOWN POSITION.
THE KIDS IN THIS HALLWAY
ALL SURVIVED?
>> YES THE KITCHEN AREA
BACK THERE WHERE THE ROOF
IS CAVED IN THIS IS
ACTUALLY THE GYM AREA OVER
THERE THAT WAS 35-FOOT TALL
BUILDING THE GYMNASIUM.
THE ROOF BASICALLY
DEFINITELY AN AREA THAT WE
YOU KNOW, WANT TO AVOID AS
FAR AS THAT'S NOT A SAFE
AREA.
>> SOME OF THE  Gñ KIDS WERE IN
THERE?
>> YES, SOME OF THE KIDS
THAT WERE OUT HERE WERE IN
A CLASSROOM IN THE FAR BACK
SIDE.
>> DID ANY OF THE KIDS DIE
IN THAT GYM?
>> THE PEOPLE WHO DID NOT
SURVIVE HERE WERE ON THAT
SIDE OF THE SCHOOL.
>> SO THIS IS A FIRST
GRADERS IN THIS AREA
JEREMY.
>> FIRST GRADE AND
KINDERGARTEN IN THIS AREA.
THIS IS A HALLWAY WHERE
THEY TOOK SHELTER.
>> THIS IS, AGAIN, ONE OF
THE HALLWAYS.
YOU HAVE GOT THE LITTLE
FIRST GRADERS THAT COME OUT
AND LITERALLY TAUGHT TO GO
DOWN LIKE, THIS COVER THEIR
HEADS AND JUST CROUCH
AGAINST THE WALL?
>> CORRECT.
WE HAVE TORNADO DRILLS
REGULARLY IN OUR SCHOOLS.
THERE ARE CERTAIN SAFE
AREAS UNFORTUNATELY THIS
WAS A STORM AND WE HAVE HAD
ONE OTHER STORM LIKE THIS
THAT THE THE WEATHER MAN
EVEN ON THE TELEVISION WILL
SAY IF YOU ARE NOT
UNDERGROUND THERE IS A VERY
LIKELY CHANCE YOU WON'T
SURVIVE THIS STORM.
WE HE ONLY HAD 16 MINUTES.
THERE IS NO WAY TO EMPTY A
SCHOOL WITH ALMOST 500
PEOPLE IN IT OUT IN 16
MINUTES.
THINGS THAT THEY ARE
WORKING ON THAT DAY WHAT
THEY WANTED TO BE THEIR
FAVORITE THINGS FIVE THINGS
THEY LEARNED.
RIGHT BEFORE THEIR DAY WAS
OBVIOUSLY CHANGED A LOT.
>> LIVES CHANGED FOREVER.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: JONATHAN HUNT
AT PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
AND MOORE.
WE RECEIVED NEW VIDEO OF
THE VIDEO OF WHAT BRIAR
WOOD ELEMENTARY LOOKS LIKE
TODAY.
ABOUT A MILE AND A HALF
AWAY FROM PLAZA TOWERS AND
ALSO IN THE TORNADO'S PATH.
JOHN ROBERTS TOURED WHAT'S
LEFT OF BRIAR WOOD
ELEMENTARY AND TOMORROW HE
WILL TELL US THE STORY OF
THE TEACHER WHO GOT HURT
WHILE SAVING THE STUDENTS'
LIVES.
THERE IS BREAKING NEWS NOW
ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
WE HAVE A VERDICT IN THE
CASE OF THE MURDER JODI
ARIAS.
THE JURY HAS NOW DECIDED
WHETHER JODY -- WILL
RECOMMEND THAT JODI ARIAS
LIVES OR DIES.
THERE HAS BEEN A LOT GOING
ON IN THAT COURTROOM TODAY.
AT ONE POINT AS YOU KNOW
THE JURORS SAID WE CAN'T
COME UP WITH A DECISION.
THE JUDGE SENT THEM BACK.
WE KNEW THAT THEY WERE
CONVENING PEOPLE IN THE
COURTROOM NOW.
RELATIVES OF THE VICTIM
HAVE BEEN THERE AND MANY OF
THE COURT WATCHERS AS WELL.
EVERYONE IS IN THE
COURTROOM NOW AND THERE IS
A VERDICT.
SO OUR LIVE COVERAGE BEGINS
NOW OF THE JODI ARIAS
VERDICT.
AS YOU KNOW.
WE HAVE HAD VERY LITTLE
OPPORTUNITY TO HEAR
SPECIFICS THIS AFTERNOON.
BUT WE NOW KNOW THAT THE
VERDICT IS IN.
WE DON'T YET KNOW WHAT IT
IS.
BUT WE'RE WAITING TO FIND
OUT WHAT THAT VERDICT IS
AND, OF COURSE LIVE
COVERAGE.
TRACE GALLAGHER IS WITH US
FROM LOS ANGELES.
TRACE, THE THINKING WAS
THAT IF THEY DIDN'T GET A
VERDICT TODAY THAT THEY
PROBABLY WOULD TAKE A LONG
WEEKEND.
IT SOUNDS LIKE THE VERDICT
IS IN AND WE WILL KNOW
WHAT, MINUTES FROM NOW OR
WHAT?
DO WE KNOW?
>> WELL, SHEP, I MEAN NOT
SO FAST, BECAUSE THE JUDGE
SAID FIRST WE UNDERSTAND
THE JURY THAT YOU HAVE A
VERDICT.
AND, IN FACT WHAT THEY ARE
SAYING NOW IS THE JUDGE
COULD VERY WELL BE
DEADLOCKED.
NOW, OUR FEED IS KIND OF
BREAKING UP.
CAN YOU SEE JODI ARIAS
RIGHT THERE.
BUT IT SEEMS TO ME LIKE THE
JURY HAS NOT REACHED A
UNANIMOUS DECISION, SHEP
SO THE JURY REMAINS
DEADLOCKED.
AND WE WENT OVER THE
OPTIONS BEFORE THE COURT.
AND WHAT THEY'RE SAYING IS
IN ESSENCE THE JUDGE HAS
NOW SET A FURTHER DATE FOR
THEM, JULY 18TH IS THE DATE
FOR WHAT TO HAPPEN?
>> FOR THE RETRIAL.
SO THIS IS WHAT IS GOING TO
HAPPEN NOW.
WE TALKED ABOUT OPTION ONE
AND JULY 18TH HAS NOW BEEN
SET FOR A RETRIAL.
WHAT THEY WILL DO BETWEEN
NOW AND JULY 18TH, SHEP,
THEY WILL IMPANEL A BRAND
NEW JURY.
THIS JURY WILL BE EXCUSED.
THEY WILL IMPANEL A BRAND
NEW JURY AND THAT NEW JURY
WILL THEN RETRY PART OF THE
PENALTY PHASE.
NOT THE ENTIRE PENALTY
PHASE.
BUT PART OF IT BECAUSE THE
AGRA VARIETY HAS ALREADY
BEEN MET.
WHAT THE NEW JURY WILL DO
IS RETRY THE TAIL END OF
THE PENALTY PHASE.
THE IMPACT STATEMENTS FROM
THE FAMILY WILL BE READ
AGAIN AND THIS TIME JODI
ARIAS, IF SHE WANTS TO HAVE
SOMEBODY TESTIFY ON HER
BEHALF THAT CAN ALSO HAPPEN
DURING THE RETRY OF THE
PENALTY PHASE.
SO THE SECOND CHOICE THE
PROSECUTORS HAD WAS TO WAVE
THE DEATH PENALTY ALL
TOGETHER.
AND AGREE TO LIFE IN
PRISON.
CLEARLY THE PROSECUTION DID
NOT WANT TO DO THAT BECAUSE
THE JUDGE HAS AGREED TO SAY
LOOK WE ARE GOING TO GO
WITH A BRAND NEW JURY.
THEY WILL CULL THAT JURY
FROM THE SAME JURY THE
ORIGINAL MARICOPA COUNTY.
WE HAVE TALKED AD NAUSEAM
ABOUT THE COVERAGE THIS
TRIAL HAS GOTTEN IS THERE
ANY JURY JURY THAT COULDN'T
BE SKEWED BY THE COVERAGE.
THAT'S THE GO INTO THE JURY
SELECTION.
THOSE JUST JOINING US.
THIS IS HUGE NEWS.
THE JURY WAS DEADLOCKED.
THE JUDGE COULD HAVE SENT
THEM BACK AGAIN TO KEEP ON
DELIBERATING.
BUT THEY CAME BACK SAYING,
LOOK, WE ARE HOPELESSLY
DEAD LOCKED.
WE DON'T KNOW IF THE EXACT
COUNT IF IT WAS 6 TO 6 OR 8
TO 4.
THEY ARE DEADLOCKED.
THE JUDGE WILL NOW LET THE
JURY GO AND THEY WILL
IMPANEL A BRAND NEW JURY,
SHEP.
WE DON'T KNOW WHEN THAT
WILL HAPPEN.
BUT, FOR NOW, JODI ARIAS
GOES BACK TO THE MARICOPA
COUNTY JAIL AND SHE WILL
AWAIT A BRAND NEW PENALTY
PHASE OF HER TRIAL TO SEE
IF SHE LIVES OR DIES.
THE PROSECUTION WANTS TO
SEE THIS THROUGH TO THE
END.
THEY ARE NOT ABOUT TO WAIVE
THE DEATH PENALTY IN A CASE
WHERE SHE STABBED HER
BOYFRIEND 27 TIMES, SLASHED
HIS THROAT AND SHOT HIM IN
THE HEAD.
IT IS HUGE NEWS.
STILL WAITING FOR MORE
INFORMATION FROM THE JUDGE
AS IT COMES INTO THIS US,
SHEP.
WE WILL KEEP YOU UP TO
DATE.
>> Shepard: WE'RE NOT GOING
TO STOP HERE, TRACE.
WE ARE WAITING TO SEE IF
ANY OF THE PLAYERS FROM THE
COURTHOUSE COME OUT AND
TALK.
WE HAVE LIVE COVERAGE OF
THAT, OF COURSE, ANYTHING
FROM LAWYERS ON EITHER
SIDE?
ANYTHING FROM THESE JURORS
WHO HAVE NOW BEEN
DISMISSED?
TRACE, IT'S POSSIBLE WE
MIGHT HEAR FROM THEM
RIGHT?
>> WE MIGHT VERY WELL,
SHEP.
BECAUSE THEY HAD SAID THE
JURORS AFTER THIS WOULD
SPEAK.
WE JUST GOT WORD THAT THREE
FEMALE JURORS AS THEY WERE
LEAVING THE COURT PARDON
ME, WERE CRYING.
SO THREE FEMALE JURORS WERE
CRYING AS THEY LEFT THE
COURT.
KEEP IN MIND, I MEAN, THIS
IS A JURY THAT HAS WORKED
FOR THE BETTER PART OF
FOUR FOUR AND A HALF
MONTHS ON THIS CASE.
IT HAS BEEN A HUGE PART OF
THEIR LIVES.
WHEN THEY'RE EXCUSED.
UNABLE TO SEE THIS THROUGH,
IT'S GOT TO BE EXTREMELY
EMOTIONAL FOR THEM.
AGAIN, WE DON'T KNOW THE
BREAKDOWN, SHEP.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT THE JURY
MAKEUP WAS AND HOW MANY
WERE IN FAVOR OF LIFE AND
IN FAVOR OF DEATH.
AS LEGAL EXPERTS WOULD TELL
YOU, IT IS A LOT HARDER FOR
TO SWAY A JUROR WHO IS IN
FAVOR OF LIFE IN PRISON TO
ACTUALLY GO TO THE DEATH
PENALTY THAN THE CONVERSE.
TO SWITCH SOMEBODY WHO IS
IN FAVOR OF THE DEATH
PENALTY TO GO TOWARD LIFE
IN PRISON.
BUT APPARENTLY THESE JURORS
WERE VERY ADAMANT ABOUT
THEIR VIEWS BECAUSE THEY
SAID AFTER THREE HOURS OF
DELIBERATIONS YESTERDAY,
THEY CAME IN THEY TOLD THE
JUDGE THEY WERE DEADLOCKED.
SHE SAID GO BACK AND TRY
AGAIN.
NOW, SHE COULD HAVE DONE
THIS AGAIN AND AGAIN.
SHE COULD HAVE SENT THE
JURY BACK IN TO THE JURY
ROOM TO KEEP DELIBERATING.
FIVE SIX, SEVEN, 10 TIMES,
WHO KNOWS?
IT'S UP TO THE JUDGE.
CLEARLY, SHE GOT
INFORMATION THAT THEY WERE
DEADLOCKED AND SHE DECIDED
THE BEST AND MOST
EXPEDITIOUS WAY TO APPROACH
THIS WOULD BE TO IMPANEL A
BRAND NEW JURY.
IMAGINE WHAT THAT MEANS.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN IT I
MEAN, WE HAVE COVERED A
BUNCH OF TRIALS AND I HAVE
NEVER SEEN A BRAND NEW JURY
COME IN AND TAKE OVER TO
DECIDE WHETHER SOMEONE
LIVES OR DIES.
AND THEY WILL NOT TRY THE
BEGINNING OF THIS TRIAL.
SO THIS BRAND NEW JURY WILL
GET BROUGHT UP TO SPEED AND
THEN ONLY HEAR THE EVIDENCE
THAT WAS DELIVERED IN THE
PENALTY PHASE.
IT MIGHT BE -- IT MIGHT BE
KIND OF AN EXTRACTED
PENALTY PHASE IF YOU WILL
BUT IT WILL STILL ONLY BE
THE TAIL END OF THAT
PENALTY PHASE THAT GOES
PAST THE AGGRAVATING
FACTORS.
THE JURY UP TO NOW THAT WAS
IN THIS CASE FROM THE
BEGINNING HAS AGREED THAT
SHE IS GUILTY AND HAS
AGREED THAT WERE
AGGRAVATING FACTORS.
NOW THE SECOND JURY, THEY
WILL BE CHARGED WITH THE
TASK OF DECIDING WHETHER OR
NOT JODI ARIAS LIVES OR
DIES.
THE JURY SELECTION ALONE
COULD BE VERY LONG AND VERY
TEDIOUS.
JULY 18TH IS WHEN THAT WILL
ALL BEGIN.
SO FOR ALMOST TWO MONTHS
JODI ARIAS GOES BACK TO THE
MARICOPA COUNTY JAIL, SHEP.
>> Shepard: I CAN'T EVEN
BELIEVE THIS, TRACE.
THINK OF ALL THAT HAS
HAPPENED OUTSIDE THAT
COURTHOUSE THAT EVERYBODY
IN AMERICA HAS HAD ACCESS
TO.
AWESOME SPEECHES BY JODI
ARIAS, THE WORD NOW THAT
THE MEDIA HAVE GIVEN HER
MAKEUP AND SHE HAS GONE
THROUGH ALL OF THIS HOW SHE
FEELS AND WHAT SHE WANTS TO
DO IN PRISON AND ALL OF
THIS SIDE STUFF THAT NO
JUROR WAS SUPPOSED TO EVER
HEAR.
ESPECIALLY NOT THOSE MAKING
A LIFE OR DEATH DECISION
ABOUT HER.
NOW ALL OF THAT HAS BEEN
AVAILABLE TO EVERYONE.
THEY HAVE TO START OVER.
I HAVE NEAFER HEARD OF
THIS.
I OHIO NEVER HEARD OF THIS.
>> IMAGINE WE HAD THREE OF
THE ORIGINAL JURORS WERE
KICKED OFF THE JURY.
SO THEY HAD THREE OF THE
ALTERNATES THAT WERE IN
PLACE WHEN THIS FINAL JURY
MADE THE DECISION WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT MAYBE 15, 20
MINUTES AGO.
SO NOW YOU HAVE THIS JURY
POOL AND JURY SELECTION WAS
TEDIOUS TO BEGIN WITH.
AND NOW YOU HAVE THIS JURY
POOL THAT OF COURSE, THE
MOTIONS ARE GOING TO BE
FILED BITE THE DEFENSE
SAYING THERE IS NO WAY THAT
YOU ARE GOING TO BE ABLE TO
FIND A FAIR JURY IN
MARICOPA COUNTY WHICH OF
COURSE IS THE AREA
SURROUNDING THE GREATER
PHOENIX AREA.
THERE IS NO WAY YOU ARE
GOING TO BE ABLE TO FIND A
FAIR JURY IN THIS
JURISDICTION.
THEY WILL CLEARLY ASK FOR A
CHANGE OF VENUE.
IMAGINE THAT IMAGINE JODI
ARIAS GETTING A NEW TRIAL
AND A CHANGE OF VENUE IN A
DIFFERENT COUNTY IN
ARIZONA.
THOSE ARE THE FACTS THAT
WE'RE LOOKING AT HERE.
WE'RE WAITING FOR MORE
INFORMATION BECAUSE IT'S
ALL NEW TO US?
WE THOUGHT THIS WAS A JURY
QUESTION.
IT TURNS OUT THIS WAS THE
JURY VERDICT EVEN THE JUDGE
MY UNDERSTANDING YOU HAVE A
VERDICT SHE GOT THE
ENVELOPE AND THE VERDICT
WAS WE ARE DEADLOCKED.
>> Shepard: WHATEVER
STATEMENTS COME FROM THE
COURTHOUSE AND LEGAL
ANALYSIS AFTER THIS.
INSPECTION TESTS,
AND BEFORE SEVERAL THOUSAND  TENNESSEANS
DISCOVERED NEW JOBS  ON VOLKSWAGEN
DRIVE,
THEIR CFO AND OUR BANKER  MET FOR
LUNCH.
TOGETHER, WE WORKED  WITH A TEAM THAT
HELPED FINANCE CONSTRUCTION  OF THE
WORLD'S FIRST
LEED PLATINUM  AUTO MANUFACTURING
PLANT.
THAT'S THE IMPACT  OF GLOBAL CONNECTIONS.
THAT'S BANK OF AMERICA.
♪ ♪    [ Male Announcer ]    CLEARLY
THIS ISN'T    ONE OF THOSE    SPEED-EATING
CONTESTS.    THAT'S    A HEBREW NATIONAL
HOT DOG.    A KOSHER HOT DOG.    THAT
MEANS WE'RE EXTRA CHOOSY    ABOUT
THE CUTS OF BEEF    THAT MEET    OUR
HIGHER KOSHER STANDARDS.    AND ONLY
A GOOD, OLD-FASHIONED    SLOW-MOTN
BITE    IS GONNA CAPTURE    ALL THAT
KOSHER DELIGHT.    AND WHEN YOUR HOT
DOG'S KOSHER    THAT'S A HOT DOG YOU
CAN TRUST.    HEBREW NATIONAL.  COPD
MAKES IT HARD TO BREATHE...  BUT WITH
ADVAIR,  I'M BREATHING BETTER.  SO
NOW I CAN HELP MAKE THIS  A GREAT
BLOCK PARTY.  ♪ ♪    [ Male Announce
]    ADVAIR IS CLINICALLY PROVEN
TO HELP SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE    LUNG
FUNCTION.    UNLIKE MOST COPD MEDICATIONS,
ADVAIR CONTAINS    BOTH AN ANTI-INFLAMMATORY
AND A LONG-ACTING    BRONCHODILATOR
WORKING TOGETHER    TO HELP IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION ALL DAY.    ADVAIR
WON'T REPLACE    FAST-ACTING INHALERS
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS    AND SHOULD
NOT BUSED    MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
PEOPLE WITH COPD TAKING ADVAIR
MAY HAVE    A HIGHER CHANCE OF PNEUMONIA.
ADVAIR MAY INCRSE    YOUR RISK OF
OSTEOPOROSIS     SOME EYE PRLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR    IF YOU HAVE A
HEART CONDITION    OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING ADVAIR.  ASK YOUR DOCTOR
F INCLUDING ADVAIR COULD HELP  IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION.    [ Male Announcer
]    ADVAIR DISKUS    FLUTICASONE
PROPIONATE AND    SALMETEROL INHALATION
POWDER.    GET YOUR FIRST PRESCRIPTION
FREEILLS    AT ADVAIRCOPD.COM.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF BREAKING NEWS
ON THE FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
THE JURY IN THE THE JODI
ARIAS MURDER CASE ON THE
PENALTY PHASE OF IT IT ALL
DECIDING WHETHER SHE WILL
LIVE OR DIE FOR HER CRIME
HAS DEAD LOCKED.
AND AS TRACE GALLAGHER
REPORTS.
THERE WILL BE ANOTHER JURY
INPANELED.
THAT WILL HAPPEN IN JULY
BEGINNING OF IMPANELING
THAT JURY.
THAT JURY WILL BE TASKED
DECIDING WHETHER JODI ARIAS
SHOULD LIVE OR DIE.
INCREDIBLE SET OF
CIRCUMSTANCES.
UPPER RIGHT HAND OF YOUR
JURORS COMING OUT OF THE
COURTHOUSE.
IF THE JURORS DECIDE TO
SPEAK AND SOME MAY, THEY
WILL COME TO THAT PODIUM
AND SPEAK.
IF THE LAWYERS FOR EITHER
SIDE, THE DEFENSE OR THE
PROSECUTORS WANT TO SPEAK,
THEY WILL DO SO THERE,
BECAUSE THE GAG ORDER IS
LIFTED.
THINK OF THIS THIS PROCESS
HAS BEEN GOING ON FOR THE
BETTER PARTB
LIFE.
ON AND ON AND ON GAG ORDER.
ALL OF A SUDDEN WE GET DOWN
TO THE PENALTY PHASE.
THEY HAVE DECIDED -- THE
JURY HAS DECIDED YES, THIS
WAS SPECIAL CIRCUMSTANCES,
OR WHATEVER THEY CALL IT IN
ARIZONA.
YES SHE IS ELIGIBLE TO GET
THE DEATH PENALTY.
THEN THEY BEGIN THIS DEATH
PENALTY PHASE.
AND DURING THE DEATH
PENALTY PHASE, THE JUDGE
FOR THE FIRST TIME LIFTED
THE GAG ORDER.
SO JODI ARIAS HAS BEEN OUT
THERE SPOUTING HER STUFF
THE MURDERER THAT SHE IS.
DON'T FORGET WHEN YOU WATCH
THIS WOMAN STAND UP THERE
AND TALK ABOUT THE
GREATNESS SHE IS GOING TO
BE NOT COURTHOUSE.
DON'T FORGET WHAT SHE DID
TO THIS MAN.
DON'T FORGET SHE SLIT HIS
THROAT FROM EAR TO EAR AND
SHOT HIM IN THE HEAD AND
STABBED HIM 27 TIMES.
DO YOU KNOW HOW CLOSE YOU
ARE TO SOMEONE WHEN YOU ARE
STAB THEM.
CLOSE ENOUGH TO WHERE THE
BLOOD IS SPURTING ALL OVER
YOU.
TO WHERE HE IS DYING IN
YOUR OWN ARMS.
THAT'S WHAT SHE DID TO THIS
MAN.
AND NOW SHE HAS BEEN UP
THERE SPOUTING ABOUT HOW
SHE IS GOING TO MAKE THINGS
BETTER AND SHE JUST DOESN'T
WANT TO CAUSE ANYONE ANY
PAIN.
WELL, THE JURY POOL ALL OF
A SUDDEN HAS BEEN HEARING
THAT THE JUDGE LIFTED THE
GAG ORDER.
HERE IS HOW THIS WENT DOWN
IN COURT.
>> STATE OF ARIZONA WE THE
JURY DULY IMPANELED AND
SWORN ABOVE ENTITLED ACTION
UPON OUR OATH UNANIMOUSLY
FIND HAVING CONSIDERED ALL
OF THE FACTS AND
CIRCUMSTANCES THAT THE
DEFENDANT SHOULD BE
SENTENCED NO UNANIMOUS
AGREEMENT, SIGNED
FOREPERSON.
IS THIS YOUR TRUE VERDICT
THIS SAY YOU ONE AND ALL?
>> YES.
>> Shepard: NOT MUCH OF A
REACTION THERE RIGHT?
CONTINUING TO WATCH.
I GUESS THEY TOOK IT DOWN.
ANYWAY, SO NOW WE WAIT FOR
THE JURORS TO COME OUT AND
SPEAK.
AGAIN, THE JUDGE LIFTED THE
GAG ORDER.
SO WE HAVE HEARD CHAPTER
AND VERSE FROM JODI ARIAS
THE MURDERER, SHE TALKS
ABOUT HOW THINGS ARE GOING
TO BE GREAT IN PRISON.
SHE IS GOING TO TEACH
PEOPLE HOW TO SPEAK
SPANISH.
SHE IS GOING TO START A
RECYCLING PROGRAM.
SHE HAS BEEN SPEAKING TO HE
A POTENTIAL IT NEXT JURY
AND FOR HER, THIS WORKED
OUT ABSOLUTELY PERFECTLY.
THE JUDGE WHO ALLOWED HER
TO SPEAK ON THE STAND TO
TAKE THE STAND FOR 17 DAYS
THEN LATER LIFTED THE GAG
ORDER AND LET THE REPORTERS
RIGHT IN THERE SO THAT JODI
ARIAS COULD SPOUT AWAY
ABOUT ALL THE GREAT THINGS
SHE IS GOING TO DO NOW, NOW
THAT SHE HAS MURDERED HER
EXLOVER.
ARTHUR AIDALA, "STUDIO B"
CONTRIBUTOR FOX NEWS
ANALYST HERE IN STUDIO WITH
US TONIGHT.
FIRST OF ALL, I HAVE NEVER
IN ALL MY BORN DAYS HEARD
OF A -- IMPANELING OF A NEW
JURY TO TAKE OVER A PENALTY
PHASE.
>> I HAVE NEVER HEARD OF IT
EITHER.
IT'S VERY UNIQUE TO ARIZONA
AS IS THE JURORS ASKING THE
DEFENDANT QUESTIONS AS THEY
DID.
SHEPARD, LET'S JUST BACK UP
FOR A SECOND WHAT YOU JUST
SHOWED.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN A VERDICT
READ LIKE THAT.
>> Shepard: NORMALLY.
>> NORMALLY A NOTE COMES
OUT AND SAYS WE CAN'T REACH
A VERDICT.
WE CAN'T REACH A UNANIMOUS
VERDICT.
>> Shepard: THE JUDGE JUST
SAYS YOU ARE DEADLOCKED.
THANK YOU LADIES AND
GENTLEMEN FOR YOUR TIME
PEACE, GOD BE WITH YOU.
>> THE CLERK JUST READ THE
VERDICT IT TOOK YEARS OFF
OF PEOPLE'S LIVES.
YOU THOUGHT THERE WAS GOING
TO BE WE FIND UNANIMOUSLY
DEATH, WE FIND UNANIMOUSLY
LIFE IN PRISON.
INSTEAD WE FIND UNANIMOUSLY
NO UNANIMOUS DECISION.
THAT WAS SOLVE 00 WALL THE
WAY THAT WAS READ.
FIRST MY UNDERSTANDING IT
WAS A QUESTION.
>> Shepard: OUR
UNDERSTANDING AS WELL.
>> ALL THE STUD SUDDEN YOU
GET THIS NOTE SHOWS
SOMEWHAT OF A LACK OF
PROFESSIONALISM AND
SOMEWHAT OF A LACK OF A
JUDGE NOT REALLY BEING IN
CONTROL OF A COURTROOM AND
ESPECIALLY IN A NATIONAL
PLATFORM LIKE THIS.
SO NOW AFTER EVERYONE GOT
YEARS TAKEN OFF THEIR LIFE
WITH THAT VERDICT BEING
READ THEY HAVE TO GO BACK
TO THE DRAWING BOARD.
THE POOR FAMILY OF THE HE
DECEASED.
THEY HAVE NO CLOSURE.
THEY ARE GANGLING LIKE
PUPPETS.
WAIT UNTIL JULY A NEW JURY
A NEW PROCESS.
THE DEFENSE ATTORNEYS WHO
ARE ABSOLUTELY EXHAUSTED
PROBABLY TRYING TO GET OFF
THE CASE AGAIN, SHEPARD,
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
>> Shepard: TRIED AGAIN AND
AGAIN AND AGAIN TO GET OFF
THIS CASE.
>> PROBABLY TRY TO GET OFF
AGAIN.
I WILL BE VERY SURPRISED IF
IN JULY THEY ACTUALLY ARE
IMPANELING A JURY.
>> Shepard: YOU KNOW THEY
ARE GOING TO SEEK A CHANGE
OF VENUE JUST AS TRACE
SAYS.
>> OF COURSE.
IF THE JUDGE LET'S THE
LAWYERS OFF THE CASE AND
PUTS NEW LAWYERS ON.
THEY WILL SAY, YOUR HONOR
THIS CASE HAS BEEN GOING ON
FOR YEARS, WE NEED TIME TO
GET UP TO SPEED.
THIS SAGINAW IS NOT GOING
TO END ANY TIME SOON.
>> Shepard: SHANE TO ME HOW
THIS JUDGE HAS HAD A GAG
ORDER ON THIS CASE FROM THE
VERY BEGINNING.
AND WHEN WE GET DOWN TO THE
MOST IMPORTANT THING, THE
GOVERNMENT IS GOING TO KILL
YOU OR WE ARE GOING TO LOCK
YOU UP FOR THE REST OF YOUR
LAYOFF.
THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS
THE GOVERNMENT CAN EVER
DECIDE, THE PEOPLE ARE
HAVING TO DECIDE WHAT THE
GOVERNMENT IS ABOUT TO DO
TO A CITIZEN OF THE UNITED
STATES SHE LIFTS THE GAG
ORDER?
WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT?
>> THE ONLY RATIONALIZATION
I COULD THINK OF IS THIS IS
A WOMAN WHO IS LITERALLY
FIGHTING FOR HER LIFE
LITERALLY FIGHTING FOR HER
LIFE.
SHE HAS HAD HER FIRST
AMENDMENT PRIVILEGES TAKEN
AWAY FROM HER THROUGHOUT
THE COURSE OF THE TRIAL.
SHE IS NOT ALLOWED TO SPEAK
FREELY THE WAY EVERYONE
ELSE IS.
AND I MEAN, I'M GUESSING,
SHEPAR BUT THE JUDGE
PROBABLY SAID HEY, SHE HAS
GOT A COUPLE OF DAYS LEFT.
SHE WANTS TO GIVE HERSELF
SOME INTERVIEWS.
CHIEF JOE SET HER UP.
>> Shepard: JOE ARPAIO.
THE MEANEST OF THE MEANEST
OF THE MEANEST SUPPOSEDLY.
HE ARRANGED IT AND ALLOWED
IT TO HAPPEN.
SHE NEVER LOOKED SO GOOD.
MAKEUP AND LIPSTICK AND ALL
OF THAT STUFF.
AND SHE HAS NOW MADE HER
CASE WHICH IS OUT THERE
NATIONALLY.
WHATEVER NEW JURORS THERE
ARE I'M SURE HAVE HEARD IT.
IF THEY HAVEN'T THEY WILL
BE GOING LING IT RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: THIS WOMAN WHO
STOOD UP ON THAT STAND AND
FOR DAYS ACCUSED HER
EXLOVER OF ABUSING HER.
AFTER SHE MURDERED HIM IN
COLD BLOOD, ACCUSED HIM OF
ABUSIVING HER.
THAT'S WHAT THIS FAMILY --
AND THERE WAS NOT A SEN
CONTINUE LA OF EVIDENCE TO
SUPPORT THAT ACCUSATION.
NOTHING.
THE WHOLE WAY.
WHICH SHE WAS UP THERE
ALLOWED TO ASSASSINATE HIM
AGAIN AND NOW THERE IS NO
VERDICT?
AND NOW THEY HAVE TO GO
THROUGH ALL OF THIS AGAIN?
UPPER RIGHT-HAND PORTION OF
YOUR SCREEN THAT'S
WHERE -- OR NOW ON THE
LEFT-HAND SIDE OF YOUR
SCREEN THAT'S WHERE WE ARE
WAITING TO HEAR FROM THE
JURORS IF THEY WISH TO
SPEAK, THEY MAY.
WE WILL BE ABLE TO HEAR
FROM THE LAWYERS.
WE'RE TOLD WE HAVE A COUPLE
OF MINUTES.
WE HAVE A QUICK BREAK AND
OUR LIVE COVERAGE CONTINUESC, F
RIGHT AFTER THIS.
S...  THE CAPITAL ONE PURCHASE ERASER.
I CAN REDEEM THE DOUBLE MILES  I EARNED
WITH MY VENTURE CARD  TO ERASE RECENT
TRAVEL PURCHASES.  D WITH A FEW CLICKS
THIS MISSION NEVER HAPPENED.  UH,
WHAT'S THIS BUTTON DO?  [ electricity
zaps ]  ♪ ♪  YOU REQUESTED BACKUP?
YES.  YES I DID.  WHAT'S IN  YOUR
WALLET?
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE TO SEVERE  RHEUMATOID
ARTHRITIS, LIKE ME,  AND YOU'RE TALKING
TO  YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST
ABOUT TRYING OR  ADDING A BIOLOGIC.
THIS IS HUMIRA, ADALIMUMAB.
THIS IS HUMIRA WORKING  TO HELP RELIEVE
MY PAIN.
THIS IS HUMIRA HELPING ME  THROUGH
THE TWISTS AND TURNS.
THIS IS HUMIRA HELPING  TO PROTECT
MY JOINTS
FROM FURTHER DAMAGE.
DOCTORS HAVE BEEN PRESCRIBING  HUMIRA
FOR OVER TEN YEARS.
HUMIRA WORKS BY TARGETING  AND HELPING
TO BLOCK
A SPECIFIC SOURCE  OF INFLAMMATION
THAT CONTRIBUTES TO RA SYMPTOMS.
FOR MANY ADULTS, HUMIRA IS  PROVEN
TO HELP RELIEVE PAIN
AND STOP FURTHER JOINT DAMAGE.
HUMIRA CAN LOWER YOUR ABILITY  TO
FIGHT INFECTIONS,
INCLUDING TUBERCULOSIS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS,
SUCH AS INFECTIONS, LYMPHOMA  OR OTHER
TYPES OF CANCER
HAVE HAPPENED.
BLOOD, LIVER AND  NERVOUS SYSTEM PROBLEMS,
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
AND NEW OR WORSENING  HEART FAILURE
HAVE OCCURD.
BEFORE STARTING HUMIRA , YOUR  DOCTOR
SHOULD TEST YOU FOR TB.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU LIVE  IN OR
HAVE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL  INFECTIONS ARE
COMMON.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU  HAVE HAD
TB, HEPATITIS B
ARE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,  OR HAVE
SYMPTOMS SUCH AS FEVER
FATIGUE, COUGH, OR SORES.
YOU SHOULD NOT START HUMIRA IF  YOU
HAVE ANY KIND OF INFECTION.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF  HUMIRA CAN WORK
FOR YOU.
THIS IS HUMIRA AT WORK.
You thought this beach couldn't  get
any more tempting...
... you thought  wrong.
Get up to 50% off  Memorial Day hotels.
Final Days.
Book now with Travelocity.
>> Shepard: 14 MINUTES
BEFORE 5:00 IN PHOENIX,
ARIZONA.
AND THE UNTHINKABLE HAS
HAPPENED.
THE JURY HAS COME BACK WITH
NO DECISION ON LIFE OR
DEATH FOR JODI ARIAS.
AND THAT NO DECISION MEANS
A WHOLE NEW JURY WILL BE
IMPANELED IN JULY AND HE
THEY WILL GO THROUGH THIS
PENALTY PHASE ALL OVER
AGAIN.
WILL THEY BE ABLE TO DO IT
IN MARICOPA COUNTY?
WILL THEY BE GRANTED A
CHANGE OF VENUE AS MOST
LEGAL ANALYSTS HAVE SAID
PRIOR TO THIS THAT MOST
LIKELY THEY WILL BE?
WILL THE DEFENSE LAWYERS
ASK TO BE TAKEN OFF THE
CASE AGAIN?
MOST LIKELY.
AND WHAT OF THE PROSECUTORS
HERE?
ARTHUR AIDALA IS WITH US
HERE IN STUDIO.
FOX NEWS LEGAL ANALYST
"STUDIO B" LEGAL HE
CONTRIBUTOR.
IT'S JUST -- THIS IS JUST A
DISASTER.
>> IT IS A DISASTER.
AND IT'S NOT FAIR.
WHEN A JURY CAN'T REACH A
UNANIMOUS DECISION DE FACTO
IT'S LIFE WITHOUT PAROLE.
>> Shepard: THAT'S WHAT WE
DO HERE?
>> WHAT HAPPENS HERE IS IF
THIS NEXT JURY DOESN'T DO
IT THE JUDGE HAS A CHOICE
BETWEEN LIFE WITHOUT PAROLE
OR NATURAL LIFE.
I HAVEN'T DONE THE RESEARCH
TO TELL WHAT THE DIFFERENCE
IS LIFE WITHOUT PAROLE OR
NATURAL LIFE.
>> Shepard: TRACE HAS
SOMETHING ON THIS, TRACE?
>> WHY YOU ARE TALKING TO
ARTY, VERY IMPORTANT TO
POINT OUT NOW WE ARE TOLD
THERE IS A LITTLE BIT OF
WRIGGLE ROOM HERE FOR
PROSECUTORS.
WE ALWAYS SAID THERE WAS
OPTION TWO IN THIS.
OPTION ONE IS IMPANELING
BRAND NEW JURY AND GOING
OVER PART OF THE PENALTY
PHASE.
OPTION 2 IS IF PROSECUTOR
DECIDED THEY WANTED TO
WAIVE THE DEATH PENALTY AND
AGREE TO LIFE IN PRISON.
NOW, THERE HAS BEEN A
STATUS HEARING THAT HAS
BEEN SET FOR JUNE 20TH,
WHICH MEANS THAT THEY WILL
MEET WITH PROSECUTORS AND
THEY WILL DISCUSS GOING
FORWARD.
NOW, IT SEEMS LIKE A LONG
SHOT BECAUSE THESE
PROSECUTORS HAVE BEEN
ADAMANT ABOUT GOING FOR THE
DEATH PENALTY IT STILL
LEAVES A GREAT PERIOD FOR
THEM 27 DAYS WHERE THEY CAN
FIGURE OUT IF THIS WILL
WORK IF THEY CAN FIGURE OUT
A CHANGE OF VENUE, IF THEY
CAN FIGURE OUT HOW TO GET A
JURY AND THE PROSECUTORS
COULD IN THEORY SAY YOU
KNOW WHAT?
WE ARE GOING TO AGREE TO
GIVE HER LIFE IN PRISON AND
THEN CUT A DEAL WITH THE
DEFENSE ATTORNEYS AND SAY
HERE IS THE DEAL.
YOU TAKE LIFE IN PRISON
WITHOUT THE POSSIBILITY OF
PAROLE WHICH YOU IS REALLY
IMPORTANT BECAUSE RIGHT NOW
ARIZONA DOESN'T HAVE A
MECHANISM THAT GIVES LIFE
IN PRISON ANY TYPE OR ANY
CHANCE OF PAROLE BUT SOME
DAY DOWN THE LINE, 20 YEARS
FROM NOW.
IF THAT LAW IS PASSED THAT
GIVES THEM THAT.
SHE WOULD HAVE TO WAIVE
THAT IN OTHER WORDS THE
DEAL WOULD BE SHE WOULD
ACCEPT LIFE IN PRISON
WITHOUT ANY POSSIBILITY OF
PAROLE OR THEY ARE GOING
FORWARD WITH THE DEATH
PENALTY.
THAT'S JUST ONE THEORY.
BUT PROSECUTORS HAVE SAID
FROM DAY ONE THEY BELIEVE
THIS IS A DEATH PENALTY
CASE AND FOR THEM TO QUIT
IN THE MIDDLE OF IT SEEMS
HIGHLY UNLIKELY, BUT THERE
IS THAT LITTLE BIT OF
LEEWAY THEY HAVE NOW, SHEP
BUT IT LOOKS VERY MUCH LIKE
THEY WILL IMPANEL A BRAND
NEW DEATH PENALTY JURY.
>> Shepard: TRACE, I'M SO
HOPEFUL THAT ONE OF THESE
JURORS OR A GROUP OF THESE
JURORS WILL COME OUT.
WE WERE TOLD EARLIER THAT
THREE OF THE JURORS WERE
SEEN CRYING.
I BELIEVE YOU REPORTED
THAT.
RIGHT, TRACE?
>> YEAH, THREE OF THE WOMEN
WERE CRYING AS THEY LEFT
THE COURT.
REMEMBER YOU HAVE GOT THE
ALEXANDER FAMILY, THEY ARE
AN EMOTIONAL WRECK RIGHT
NOW.
THEY HAVE BEEN PULLED
ASIDE.
CAN YOU IMAGINE?
YOU GO THROUGH FOUR AND A
HALF MONTHS OF THIS.
YOU ARE EXPECTING THIS TO
HAPPEN.
AND YOU GET THE VERDICT IS
NO VERDICT.
VERY EMOTIONALLY DRAINING
SHEP.
>> Shepard: YOU KNOW, THERE
IS SOMEBODY ELSE TO WHOM
THEY CAN TURN ON THIS,
ARTHUR.
>> IF I'M THE PROSECUTOR,
AFTER WHAT THIS DECEASED
FAMILY HAS BEEN THROUGH.
AND WE HAVE HEARD THEIR
HEART WRENCHING CRIES, THEY
SHOULD BE MAKING THAT
DECISION.
YOU WANT TO GO THROUGH THIS
AGAIN?
DO YOU WANT TO HAVE THIS
OPEN-ENDED PART OF YOUR
LIFE FOR WEEKS AND MONTHS
AND WHO KNOWS HOW MUCH
LONGER OR DO YOU WANT TO
JUST SAY PUT HER IN JAIL
FOREVER?
>> Shepard: THAT WITH A WOO
BE AN INTERESTING TURN OF
EVENTS.
WE ARE WAITING TO HEAR FROM
LAWYERS IN THE CASE.
IN ADDITION JURORS.
LIVE COVERAGE CONTINUE
ITING AFTER THIS.
Many choose us because we have  the
largest 4GLTE network.
Others, because of our  reputation
for reliability.
Or maybe it's because  we've received
JD Power
and Associates' customer service
award 4X in a row.
In the end  there are countless reasons.
But one choi.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS
COVERAGE CONTINUES.
NEW RIGHT NOW, WE HAVE JUST
GOTTEN A STATEMENT FROM THE
PROSECUTOR'S OFFICE.
THE MARICOPA COUNTY'S
ATTORNEYS OFFICE AND IT
READS AS FOLLOWS:  QUOTE WE
APPRECIATE THE JURY'S
VERDICT IN THE GUILT AND
AGGRAVATION PHASES OF THE
TRIAL.
NOW WE WILL ASSET BASED
UPON AVAILABLE INFORMATION
WHAT THE NEXT STEPS WILL
BE.
AS OF THIS POINT IN TIME
THE COURT HAS SET A STATUS
CONFERENCE FOR JUNE THE
20TH, AND WE WILL PROCEED
WITH THE INTENT TO RETRY
THE PENALTY PHASE BECAUSE
FOR PURPOSES OF A JURY
DETERMINATION OR
PUNISHMENT, THIS IS STILL A
PENDING MATTER, THERE WILL
BE NO FURTHER COMMENT.
YOU GOT TO WONDER IF THOSE
PROSECUTORS WON'T GO TRAVIS
ALEXANDER'S FAMILY, LET'S
TALK.
YOU HAVE HAD THE MOST
UNBELIEVABLY BAD SERIES OF
EVENTS HAPPEN TO YOU THAT
ARE EVEN IMAGINABLE.
FIRST, HE DIES IN THIS WAY.
THEN SHE SHOW BOATS IN THIS
WAY.
ACCUSES HIM OF ABUSING HER
IN THE WAY SHE DID.
SHE HAS BEEN ON EVERY
TELEVISION IN AMERICA
SPOUTING HER CRAP SO
PROSECUTORS COULD CALL IN
THE FAMILY OF TRAVIS
ALEXANDER AND GO, YOU HAVE
BEEN THROUGH ENOUGH.
IF YOU WANT US TO CONTINUE
WITH THE DEATH PENALTY
CASE, WE WILL.
IF YOU HAVE HAD ENOUGH, WE
WON'T.
IT'S UP TO YOU.
I DON'T KNOW WHY THEY
WOULDN'T ARTHUR.
YOU ARE THE ONE WHO BROUGHT
IT UP.
I WOULDN'T KNOW WHY THEY
WOULDN'T DO THAT.
>> DON'T FORGET THE
PROSECUTORS WORK FOR THE
PEOPLE RIGHT?
THEY WORK FOR EVERYONE.
BUT THEY WORK FOR THOSE
PARTICULAR CITIZENS AS
WELL.
>> Shepard: THE PROSECUTORS
ARE SUPPOSED TO PROTECTED
PUBLIC FROM DANGEROUS
PEOPLE AND PUNISH THOSE.
SHE IS NOT GOING TO HURT
NOBODY NO MORE.
LET'S LEAVE IT UP TO THE
FAMILY, WHY NOT?
>> I AGREE WITH YOU.
IT SHOWS YOU, SHEPARD ON
HOW SPLIT PEOPLE ARE ABOUT
THE DEATH PENALTY.
THEY REACH THE VERDICT OF
HER GUILT RELATIVELY
QUICKLY.
>> Shepard: YOU BET.
REACHED THE VERDICT ON IT
BEING A HEINOUS CRIME,
CRUEL CRIME QUICKLY.
ON THIS A JURY THAT LIVES
AND BREATHES.
>> Shepard: LISTEN TO THIS.
WE HAVE BEEN WAITING TO
HEAR FROM THE JURORS
RIGHT?
THAT WAS THE HOPE THESE
JURORS WHO DEADLOCKED ON
THIS MOST IMPORTANT PHASE
OF IT ALL.
FROM THE FOX NEWS PRODUCER
JEN IN PHOENIX THE PUBLIC
INFORMATION OFFICER TELLS
US THAT EACH AND EVERY
JUROR HAS DECLINED TO SPEAK
TO US AT THIS POINT.
AND THEIR NAMES ARE UNDER
SEAL.
DON'T EVEN THINK THAT THE
MEMBERS OF THE MEDIA DON'T
KNOW WHO THEY ARE.
THEY DO.
IF YOU YOU HAVE BEEN
THROUGH ALL OF THIS, WHY
WOULDN'T YOU SPEAK?
SOME OF THEM DON'T WANT TO.
I GUARANTEE YOU IT'S
COMING.
THERE WILL BE BOOKS.
THERE IS A GRAVE TRAIN
HERE.
THERE IS A CABLE TELEVISION
NETWORK THAT HAS REINCENTED
ITSELF AROUND THIS THING.
IT'S COMING.
WE MIGHT NOT HEAR AT THIS
MOMENT.
BUT WE WILL HEAR.
WE WILL HEAR PLENTY AND
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
[ Woman ]  ...BECAME A REAL QUESTION.
ARE WE READY  TO PAY FOR COLLEGE?
[ Woman ]  SO THEY CAME TO SEE ME
AND WE TALKED ABOUT  WAYS TO MANAGE
THEIR MONEY  AND SAVE FOR COLLEGE
THAT FIT THEIR SITUATION.  SO WHEN
LITTLE DAVID --  WELL, NOT-SO-LITTLE
DAVID  WAS READY TO GO TO COLLEGE,
HIS PARENTS WERE READY, TOO.  WE DID
IT.    [ Female Announcer ]    LET'S
TALK ABOUT SMARTER WAYS    TO MANAGE
AND SAVE YOUR MONEY.    WHEN PEOPLE
TALK,    GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.    WELLS
FARGO.    TOGETHER WE'LL GO FAR.
I'M PHYLLIS  AND I HAVE DIABETIC NERVE
PAIN.  WHEN I FIRST FELT  THE DIABETIC
NERVE PAIN,  OF COURSE  I HAD NO IDEA
WHAT IT WAS.  I FELT LIKE  MY FEET
WERE GOING TO SLEEP.  IT PROGRESSED
FROM THERE  TO BURNING  LIKE I WAS
WALKING  ON HOT COALS...  TO LIKE
1,000 BEES  THAT WERE JUST STINGING
MY FEET.  I HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DOCTOR...  HE FOUND LYRICA
FOR ME.    [ Female Announcer ] IT'S
KNOWN    THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED    TO TREAT
DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.    LYRICA IS
NOT FOR EVERYONE.    IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIO    OR SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS    OR ACTIONS.    TELL YOUR
DOCTOR T AWAY    IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRON    OR UNUSUAL
CHAES    IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.    OR
SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,    RASH,
HIVES, BLISTERS,    CHANGES IN EYESIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,    MUSCLE
PAIN WITH FEVER    TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.    COMMON
SIDE EFFES ARE    DIZZINESS, SLEESS,
WEIGHT GAIN AND SWELLING    OF HANDS,
LEGS AND FEET.    DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKI LYRICA.    DON'T DRIVE
OR USE MACHINERY    UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.    THOSE WHO
HAVE HAD A DRUG    OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY    TO MISUSE LYRICA.
HAVING LESS PAIN --  IT'S A WONDERFUL
FEELING.    [ Female Announcer ] ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT    FOR DIABETIC
NERVE PAIN.    TO HEAR MORE OF PHYLLIS'S
STORY, VISIT LYRICA.COM.
WELCOME TO THE NEW BUFFALO...  WHERE
NEW YORK STATE IS  INVESTING ONE BILLION
DOLLARS TO ATTRACT  AND GROW BUSINESS.
WHERE COMPANIES LIKE  GEICO ARE INVESTING
IN TECHNOLOGY & FINANCE.
WELCOME TO THE STATE WHERE  CUTTING
TAXES FOR BUSINESS...
IS OUR BUSINESS.
WELCOME TO THE NEW BUFFALO.
NEW YORK STATE IS THROWING  OUT THE
OLD RULE BOOK
TO GIVE YOUR  BUSINESS A NEW EDGE,
THE EDGE YOU CAN ONLY  GET IN NEW
YORK STATE.
TO GROW OUR START YOUR  BUSINESS,
VISIT THENEWNY.COM
WE HAD NEVER  USED A CONTRACTOR BEFORE
AND DIDN'T KNOW WHERE TO START.
AT ANGIE'S LIST,    YOU'LL FIND REVIEWS
ON EVERYTHING    FROM HOME REPAIR
TO HEALTHCARE
WRITTEN BY PEOPLE    JUST LIKE YOU.
NO COMPANY CAN PAY  TO BE ON ANGIE'S
LIST,
SO YOU CAN TRUST  WHAT YOU'RE READING.
ANGIE'S LIST IS LIKE HAVING  THOUSANDS
OF CLOSE NEIGHBORS
WHERE I CAN GO ASK  FOR PERSONAL RECOMMENDATIONS.
THAT'S THE IDEA.
BEFORE YOU HAVE ANY WORK DONE,
CHECK ANGIE'S LIST.
FROM ROOFERS TO PLUMBERS    TO DENTISTS
AND MORE
ANGIE'S LIST --    REVIEWS YOU CAN
TRUST.
I LOVE YOU, ANGIE.  SORRY, HONEY.
JODI ARIAS JURY DEATH ARE
LIFE IN HER CASE.
DEATH PENALTY VERDICT HUNG
JURIES FIVE TIMES.
FOUR OF THEM WERE RETRIED.
OF THOSE FOUR, THREE
RESULTED IN THE DEATH
PENALTY IN THE RETRIAL.
WILL THEY HAVE ANOTHER
PENALTY PHASE?
WILL THEY IMPANEL ANOTHER
JURY BEGINNING IN JULY OR
MIGHT THEY MAKE ANOTHER
DECISION IN JUNE?
WE SHALL SEE.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THE FACTOR BEGINS RIGHT
NOW.
BILL BILLION THE O'REILLY
FACTOR IS ON.
TONIGHT:
>> TODAY, USAMA BIN LADEN
IS DEAD.
THERE HAVE BEEN NO LARGE
SCALE ATTACKS ON THE UNITED
STATES.
AND OUR HOMELAND IS MORE
SECURE.
>> Bill: PRESIDENT OBAMA
TRYING TO REASSERT HIS
AUTHORITY IN THE WAKE OF
THE SCANDALS.
WITH A MAJOR FOREIGN POLICY
ADDRESS.
>> THE DECISIONS THAT WE
ARE MAKING NOW WILL DEFINE
THE TYPE OF NATION AND
WORLD THAT WE LEAVE TO OUR
CHILDREN.
>> Bill: WE WILL ANALYZE
THE PRESIDENT'S DILEMMA.
>> BY LAW WE SWEAR -- UNTIL
YOU LEAVE US ALONE.
>> ISLAM IS NOT A RELIGION
OF PEACE.
ISLAM IS -- WE HAVE HAD
ENOUGH.
>> Bill: THERE L. THERE BE
STREET BATTLES IN LONDON
BETWEEN MUSLIMS AND THOSE