PICTURES OF THIS LIVE IN THE
NEXT LITTLE WHILE.
SO WE'RE WAITING THAT HERE ON
FOX NEWS AND WILL BRING IT TO
YOU WHEN IT HAPPENS.
IT'S BEEN A BUSY HOUR.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
MORE NEWS NOW.
HERE'S SHEP.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST, 3:00 IN PUERTO RICO
WHERE HURRICANE MARIA HAS BEEN
PUNISHING THAT ISLAND WITH
POWERFUL WINDS.
>> WE'VE BEEN SEEING STRONG
WINDS WELL OVER 100 MILES FOR
TWO HOURS HERE, STRONG ENOUGH TO
CAUSE VISIBLE DESTRUCTION.
WE'VE SEEN TREES SNAPPED, PARTS
OF WELL-MADE STRUCTURES
COLLAPSE.
>> Shepard: AS STEVE CAN ATTEST,
IT'S A CATASTROPHIC STORM.
ONE OF THE STRONGEST TO EVER HIT
AMERICAN SOIL AND THE
DESTRUCTION COULD BE WIDESPREAD.
WE'RE TRACKING THE HURRICANE.
PLUS, IN MEXICO CITY, CRIES OF
ANGUISH AT THE SITE OF A SCHOOL
COLLAPSED IN THE EARTHQUAKE.
PARENTS STILL WAITING TO FIND
OUT WHAT HAPPENED TO THEIR KIDS.
RESCUERS WORKING THROUGH THE
NIGHT, SEARCHING FOR SURVIVORS.
WE'LL GO THERE LIVE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SET TO MEET WITH
THE BRITISH PRIME MINISTER.
THE LEADER OF OUR STRONGEST
ALLY.
WE'RE EXPECTING THAT IN THIS
HOUR.
LET'S GET TO IT.
WE'RE TRACKING TWO DEADLY
NATURAL DISASTERS.
THE DANGEROUS HURRICANE MAKING
ITS WAY ACROSS THE CARIBBEAN AND
THE EARTHQUAKE IN MEXICO.
WE'LL GO LIVE TO MEXICO CITY IN
JUST A MOMENT.
BUT HURRICANE MARIA HAS KILLED
ANYBODY PEOPLE ACROSS THE
CARIBBEAN.
TODAY IT MADE LANDFALL AS ONE OF
THE STRONGEST TO HIT PUERTO RICO
AND ST. CROIX.
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR SAYS
PUERTO RICANS HAVE NOT
EXPERIENCED AN EVENT OF THIS
MAGNITUDE IN THEIR MODERN
HISTORY.
HERE'S A LOOK AT THE STORM FROM
SPACE AS THE CORE MOVES OVER
PUERTO RICO.
THE HURRICANE MADE LANDFALL AS A
CATEGORY FOUR.
THE STORM ON THE SOUTHEAST COAST
OF THE ISLAND WITH SUSTAINED
WINDS OF 155 MILES AN HOUR.
THE NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER
WARNING OF LIFE THREATENING
WINDS AND STORM SURGE AND RAIN
OVER PUERTO RICO IN ST. CROIX
TODAY.
WATER LEVELS COULD RISE UP TO
NINE FEET ON PUERTO RICO WITH
LARGE AND DESTRUCTIVE WAVES.
THE DANGEROUS WINDS ARE EXPECTED
TO CONTINUE FOR 24 HOURS.
PUERTO RICAN OFFICIALS SAY
DOZENS OF COMMUNITIES WILL HAVE
TO BE REBUILD.
THEY SAY THE STORM COULD
"DECIMATE" THE ISLAND'S POWER
COMPANY.
IN ONE NEIGHBORHOOD ON PUERTO
RICO'S NORTHERN COAST, THE MAYOR
SAID FOUR OUT OF FIVE HOMES ARE
DESTROYED.
THE STORM HAS SNAPPED PALM
TREES, PEELED OFF ROOFTOPS.
PEOPLE IN THE CAPITOL OF
SAN JUAN ARE REPORTING
WIDESPREAD FLOODING.
SOME IN HIGH RISE APARTMENTS.
ONE WOMAN THAT LIVES IN SAN JUAN
TOLD THE "MIAMI HERALD" THAT HER
HOUSE WAS TREMBLING.
THE RAIN HORIZONTAL AND ALL THE
TREES ON THE GROUND.
SHE SAID THE WINDS ARE LIKE
SOMETHING OUT OF A HORROR MOVIE.
WE'RE ALSO GETTING A LOOK AT THE
DEVASTATION ON THE SMALL ISLAND
OF DOMINIC DiNATALE --
DOMINIQUE.
THE STORM HIT AND BLEW AWAY THE
MAYOR'S ROOF.
HERE'S A LOOK AT THE DAMAGE IN
ST. CROIX, ONE OF THE U.S.
VIRGIN ISLANDS.
THE HURRICANE SIDE SWIPED THE
ISLAND.
KNOCKING OVER TREES, TOPPLING
POWER LINES AND CAUSING SEVERE
FLOODING.
OFFICIALS IN ST. CROIX WARNED
PEOPLE TO STAY AWAKE MOST OF THE
NIGHT AND KEEP THEIR SHOES ON IN
CASE THEY NEEDED TO RUN.
FORECASTERS SAY HURRICANE FORCE
WINDS EXTEND 60 MILES FROM THE
EYE OF MARIA.
THEY SAY THE CENTER OF THE STORM
IS EXPECTED TO CROSS OVER THE
COAST OF THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
TONIGHT BEFORE MOVING TO THE
TURKS AND CAICOS AND THE
BAHAMAS.
I WANT TO GET STRAIGHT TO STEVE
HARRIGAN WHO IS LIVE IN SAN JUAN
FOR US THIS AFTERNOON.
STEVE, LOOKS LIKE THINGS HAVE
CALMED DOWN.
WHAT DOES IT LOOK LIKE NOW?
>> SHEPARD, THE WIND HAS CALMED
CONSIDERABLY, UNDER 50 MILES PER
HOUR THAT MEANS THE POLICE AND
FIRST RESPONDERS CAN GO OUT.
EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK HERE, IT'S A
WET MISS AND IT'S NOT GETTING
BETTER SOON.
WHERE I'M STANDING NOW, CHUNKS
OF BUILDINGS, SATELLITE DISHES,
BALCONIES, PIECES OF WALL, HOLES
IN BUILDINGS.
THAT WAS 145 MILES PER HOUR
WINDS EARLIER THIS MORNING.
WE JUST MOVED AROUND TO A
NEIGHBORHOOD.
IF YOUR HOUSE IS MADE OF WOOD
WITH A METAL ROOF, JUST GONE.
SOME HOUSES WE SAW ON THE STREET
GONE.
TO MOVE AROUND HERE, IT'S
STREAMLY DIFFICULT.
IF YOU'RE AN AVERAGE CITIZEN IN
PUERTO RICO RIGHT NOW, YOU MIGHT
NOT HAVE A ROOF.
YOU PROBABLY HAVE STRUCTURAL
DAMAGE WHEREVER YOU LIVE AND YOU
DEFINITELY DO NOT HAVE
ELECTRICITY.
A SITUATION THAT COULD LAST FOR
WEEKS OR MONTHS, SHEPARD.
>> GOING FORWARD, FLOODS AND
MUDSLIDES.
>> IT'S NOT OVER YET.
THE WINDS WERE DRAMATIC AND
POSSIBLY DEADLY.
WE DON'T KNOW THE RESULTS YET.
WE SAW POWER CREWS OUT ON FOOT
BECAUSE YOU CAN'T GET ANYWHERE.
THERE'S SO MANY DOWNED POWER
LINES AND DOWNED BRANCHES.
THEY WERE WALKING TO TRY TO
ASSESS THE DAMAGE.
AS FAR AS THE MUDSLIDES GO,
ESPECIALLY IN THE CENTRAL
MOUNTAINOUS PART OF THE COUNTRY
THAT IS LIKELY WHEN YOU GET
10-15 INCHES OF RAIN.
FEMA HAS PREPOSITIONED HERE.
WE'LL SEARCH AND RESCUE AND A
LOT OF RECOVERY.
>> Shepard: THANKS, STEVE.
LET'S GET TO RICK REICHMUTH IN
THE EXTREME WEATHER CENTER, THIS
IS AWFUL.
>> A HORRIBLE FORM.
MAKING LANDFALL 6:15 A.M.
MAYBE A LITTLE BRIGHT NEWS,
ANOTHER GOING OVER LAND DURING
THE DAYLIGHT HOURS.
ALMOST EVERY RECORD IN PUERTO
RICO AT RECORD FLOOD STAGE.
ALL OF THEM GOING UP INCREDIBLY
FAST.
UNFORTUNATELY, CUTTING A CROSS
DIAGONALLY ACROSS THE ISLAND.
EVERYBODY FEELING THE IMPACTS OF
THIS STORM, THIS IS THE FUTURE
RADAR.
THE RUSSIA ARE THE HURRICANE
FORCE WINDS STAYING TO THE NORTH
OF THE NORTH SIDE OF THE IDEA OF
THE D.R.
HOPEFULLY TO THE EAST OF TURKS
AND CAICOS THAT GOT DEVASTATED
BY IRMA A COUPLE WEEKS AGO.
THEN IT CONTINUES TO PULL TO THE
NORTH.
MOST OF THE MODELS MAKE THIS
NORTH WARD TURN HERE.
THIS IS GOOD NEWS FOR THE
SOUTHEASTERN PART OF THE U.S.
WHICH WE THOUGHT WOULD HAVE A
DISTRICT IMPACT, THIS IS
FOLLOWING A SIMILAR TRAJECTORY
AS TO WHAT THE HURRICANE JOSE
HAS DONE.
PULLING TO THE MID-ATLANTIC AND
AROUND PARTS OF THE NORTHEAST.
WE'LL BE ADDING IMPACTS ACROSS
PARTS OF THE NORTHEAST WEDNESDAY
AND THURSDAY AS THE STORM PULLS
OFF TO THE NORTH.
THAT SAID, TOO EARLY TO SAY WHAT
THE IMPACTS ARE.
DO WE HAVE A DISTRICT HIT
SOMEWHERE?
MAYBE ON THE OUTER BANKS?
IT'S A POSSIBILITY.
SOMEWHERE FARTHER IN FROM NEW
YORK CITY UP AROUND PARTS OF THE
NORTHEAST, TOO EARLY TO SAY WHAT
WE DO KNOW, ENVIRONMENTAL
CONDITIONS ARE LESS FAVORABLE
FOR A STRONG HURRICANE.
THE WATER TEMPERATURES COME DOWN
AS WELL.
ALL GUIDANCES HAVE A WEAKER
STORM.
BUT TUESDAY, A STORM OFF THE
SHORE OF THE MID-ATLANTIC, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT A SEASON, RICK.
CAN YOU IMAGINE LIVING THROUGH
THIS THING?
NO LIGHTS, NO WAY TO GET HELP,
NO IDEA WHETHER YOUR HOME WILL
STAND UP OR FALL DOWN AROUND
YOU.
WE'LL SPEAK WITH A WOMAN RIDING
OUT THE STORM, HIDING IN HER
CLOSET.
THAT'S COMING UP FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK ON THIS WEDNESDAY
AFTERNOON.
Ugh. Heartburn.
Sorry Ma'am.
No burning here.
Try Alka-Seltzer
Heartburn relief
gummies.
They don't taste
chalky and work fast.
MMMM. Incredible.
Can I try?
She doesn't
have heartburn.
Alka-Seltzer heartburn
relief gummies.
Enjoy the relief.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
>> Shepard: MORE ON HURRICANE
MARIA AS IT BATTERS PUERTO RICO.
OFFICIALS SAY THE EXTREMELY
DANGEROUS STORM KNOCKED OUT
POWER TO THE ENTIRE ISLAND.
BLEW OUT WINDOWS IN SAN JUAN.
LET'S TURN TO JENNIFER GONZALEZ
COLON NOW.
SHE'S PUERTO RICO'S RESIDENT
COMMISSIONER.
THE ISLAND'S REPRESENTATIVE IN
CONGRESS AND RIDING OUT THE
STORM IN A CLOSET EAST OF
SAN JUAN.
HOW ARE YOU?
>> RIGHT NOW, I'M FINE.
WAITING UNTIL THE WINDS GETS
OVER THE ISLAND.
WE ARE STILL HAVING WINDS MORE
THAN 60 MILES PER HOUR.
SO OFFICIALS ARE ASKING PEOPLE
TO REMAIN AT THEIR HOMES BECAUSE
IT'S NOT SAFE YET TO GET OUT OF
THE HOUSES.
THERE'S A LOT OF FLOODING IN
MANY AREAS.
WE RECEIVED BETWEEN 12 TO 35
INCHES OF RAIN DURING THIS DAY.
THE WINDS BEGAN AT 1:00 A.M. IN
THE MORNING.
WE'RE STILL HAVING THE SEVERE
CONDITIONS AND SEVERE WINDS
ACROSS THE ISLAND.
ONE OF THE MAIN ISSUES IS THAT
THE RIVERS OVERFLOWED THEIR
BANKS.
SO IT'S REALLY SCARY.
WE NEVER HAD THIS KIND OF
HURRICANE BEFORE.
OF COURSE, THE WHOLE ISLAND IS
WITHOUT POWER.
>> Shepard: HOW ARE YOU TALKING
TO US?
>> I HAVE EXTRA BATTERIES FOR MY
CELL PHONE BECAUSE IT'S THE ONLY
WAY TO HAVE COMMUNICATION.
ACTUALLY, A LOT OF COMMUNICATION
TOWERS WENT DOWN AND ARE OFF
LINE.
A LOT OF THE PEOPLE ON THE
ISLAND DO NOT HAVE COMMUNICATION
AT THIS TIME.
SO THAT'S MAYBE THE REASON SOME
PEOPLE THAT ARE IN THE STATES
ARE CALLING THEIR FAMILIES AND
PEOPLE AND FRIENDS IN PUERTO
RICO AND THEY'RE NOT ANSWERING,
BECAUSE OF THAT.
>> Shepard: REPRESENTATIVE
GONZALEZ COLON, THERE'S SO MANY
PUERTO RICANS, THERE'S SO MANY
CONCERNED ABOUT THE AREA OUTSIDE
OF THE CAPITOL.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW FROM THE
NEIGHBORHOODS?
WERE PEOPLE EVACUATED
EFFICIENTLY?
>> YES, STILL, A LOT OF PEOPLE
ARE STILL HERE BECAUSE OF THE
FLOODING AND THE RIVERS OUT OF
THEIR BANKS.
THIS IS THE MAIN PROBLEM WE HAVE
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S NOT SAFE TO GET OUT OF THE
HOUSES.
IN SAN JUAN, A LOT OF PEOPLE
LOST THEIR HOMES IN THE AREAS
HIT HARD.
A LOT OF PEOPLE LOST THEIR HOMES
BECAUSE OF THE HEAVY WINDS.
ESPECIALLY PEOPLE WITH WOODEN
HOUSES.
THOSE WOODEN HOUSES ARE ALMOST
GONE IN MANY AREAS OF THE
ISLAND.
I'M SPEAKING WITH YOU.
I'M STILL HAVING HEAVY WINDS IN
MY OWN HOUSE.
THE HOUSE JUST TREMBLED DURING
THIS SITUATION.
>> Shepard: CONGRESS WOMAN, FOR
OUR VIEWERS WATCHING ACROSS THE
48 AND AROUND THE WORLD THIS
AFTERNOON, WHAT CAN PEOPLE DO TO
HELP YOU AND THE PEOPLE OF
PUERTO RICO?
WHAT IS THE MOST URGENT NEED?
HOW CAN WE HELP?
>> THE MOST URGENT NEED IS
RESTORING THE POWER ON THE
ISLAND.
FOR THAT MATTER, I ASK DIRECTLY
VICE PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE LAST
NIGHT.
HE CALLED ME.
I ASKED HIM DIRECTLY AND SOME
OTHER CABINET MEMBERS TO SEND
ELECTRIC TEAMS TO THE ISLAND TO
HELP US RESTORE THE POWER GRID.
THE SECOND ONE, THE GOVERNOR OF
PUERTO RICO, HELP FOR THOSE
PEOPLE THAT LOST THEIR
BELONGINGS.
IT'S GOING TO TAKE A LONG TIME
TO RECOVER THE INFRASTRUCTURE OF
THE ISLAND.
ROADS, BRIDGES AND MANY
HOSPITALS HAVE BEEN HIT DIRECTLY
BY THIS HURRICANE.
YOU'LL HAVE THAT.
ALSO IN THE HOTELS AND METRO
AREA.
SO WE STILL DON'T KNOW THE FULL
EXTENT OF THE DAMAGE OF THIS
MONSTER HURRICANE LEFT US HERE.
>> Shepard: I KNOW THE GREATEST
FEARS ARE FOR THE VERY YOUNG AND
THE VERY OLD.
IT'S A GOOD TIME TO REMEMBER
THAT PUERTO RICANS ARE AMERICANS
JUST LIKE ALL OF US.
THEY DIE ON THE BATTLEFIELD AND
SALUTE THE SAME FLAG.
I KNOW THIS NATION AND THE
GENEROUS PEOPLE OF AMERICA WILL
RESPOND AS THEY ALWAYS DO.
ALL THE BEST, CONGRESSWOMAN.
WE'RE THINKING ABOUT YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
AS YOU SAID, THERE'S FOUR
MILLION AMERICAN CITIZENS HERE.
FIVE MILLION PUERTO RICANS IN
THE MAINLAND.
IT'S THE THIRD TIME IN LESS THAN
A MONTH THAT A HURRICANE
LANDFALL ON THE U.S. SOIL.
IN OUR CASE, TWICE.
IRMA AND WITH MARIA.
WE'VE BEEN MANAGING PEOPLE FROM
ST. THOMAS, THE U.S. VIRGIN
ISLANDS, THE BRITISH VIRGIN
ISLANDS, GIVING SHELTER TO THEM.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO NEED A LOT OF
HELP.
I WANT TO THANK VICE PRESIDENT
MIKE PENCE AND FEMA DIRECTOR FOR
THEIR CALLS AND THEIR DILIGENCE.
THEY'RE ALREADY ON THE ISLAND,
FEMA, WORKING WITH THE GOVERNOR,
WORKING WITH THE TEAMS.
WE MAY NEED A LOT OF HELP TO
HELP THE ISLAND RECOVER.
>> Shepard: WE'LL BE SPEAKING TO
BROCK LONG IN JUST A MOMENT FROM
FEMA.
THANKS, REPRESENTATIVE
GONZALEZ-COLON.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: A NINTH PATIENT HAS
DIED AFTER HURRICANE IRMA TURNED
A FLORIDA NURSING HOME INTO AN
OVEN.
THAT'S THE WORD OF POLICE FROM
HOLLYWOOD.
COPS THERE SAY THE LATEST VICTIM
HAD BEEN 93 YEARS OLD.
THIS COMES NEARLY A WEEK AFTER
RESCUERS FOUND ELDERLY PATIENTS
SWELTERING IN THAT FACILITY.
THE STORM KNOCKED OUT THE AIR
CONDITIONING.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE STAFF
DIDN'T CALL 911 FOR THREE DAYS.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE LAUNCHED A
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION NOW.
THE CENTER'S ADMINISTRATOR HAS
SAID THAT STAFFERS DILIGENTLY
PREPARED FOR THE IMPACT OF
HURRICANE IRMA.
YET WHEN THE AIR CONDITIONING
WENT OUT ON ELDERLY AND
INFIRMED, THEY DID NOT CALL 911
FOR THREE DAYS.
WE'RE WATCHING THE AFTERMATH OF
ANOTHER NATURAL DISASTER.
ONE THAT BROKE DURING THIS HOUR
YESTERDAY.
CREWS ARE DIGGING THROUGH THE
REMAINS OF A SCHOOL LOOKING FOR
ANYBODY THAT MAY HAVE SURVIVED
YESTERDAY'S DEVASTATING
EARTHQUAKE IN MEXICO.
PARENTS WAIT FOR WORD ON THEIR
CHILDREN.
AGONIZING HOURS GO BY.
FIREFIGHTERS, POLICE,
VOLUNTEERS, RESCUE DOGS WERE ON
SCENE.
WE'LL TAKE YOU THERE AFTER THIS.
(VO) Pro Plan Bright Mind
Adult 7+ promotes alertness and
mental sharpness in dogs
7 and older.
(Ray) The difference has been
incredible.
She is much more aware. She
wants to learn things.
(VO) Purina Pro Plan Bright
Mind. Nutrition that performs.
Hey you've gotta see this.
CNo.n.
Alright, see you down there.
Mmm, fine.
Okay, what do we got?
Okay, watch this.
Do the thing we talked about.
What do we say?
It's going to be great. Watch.
Remember what we
were just saying?
Go Irish!
See that? Yes!
I'm gonna just go back to
doing what I was doing.
Find your awesome with the
XFINITY X1 Voice Remote.
>> Shepard: EVEN BEFORE THIS
STORM, PUERTO RICO HAD A
CRUMBLING INFRASTRUCTURE AND
TENS OF BILLIONS IN DEBT.
THIS WILL COMPOUND THE PROBLEMS.
POWER LINES ALL OVER PUERTO
RICO.
TWO WEEKS AGO, HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDING WITHOUT ELECTRICITY.
NOW ALL OF PUERTO RICO IS
WITHOUT POWER RIGHT NOW.
THESE HURRICANES CAUSING MORE
PROBLEMS FOR AN ISLAND THAT HAS
SPENT YEARS IN FINANCIAL CRISIS.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THIS ONE
FOR US.
TRACE?
>> SHEP, THE ECONOMY IS
EXTREMELY DIRE.
PUERTO RICO IS A PUERTO RICO --
POOR ISLAND TO BEGIN WITH.
THEY HAVE BILLIONS IN UNFUNDED
PENSIONS TO TEACHERS AND
GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEES.
WHEN YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT AN
ISLAND WITH FIVE MILLION PEOPLE,
THAT IS ASTOUNDING.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF PUERTO
RICO'S BEST AND BRIGHTEST LEAVE
THE ISLAND EACH YEAR FOR BETTER
JOBS IN THE U.S.
THE GOOD NEWS IS THE STATE OF
EMERGENCY IN PUERTO RICO
DECLARED BY PRESIDENT TRUMP
COULD MEAN A LOT OF FEDERAL
DOLLARS FLOWING INTO THE ISLAND,
WHICH COULD BOOST THE ECONOMY AT
LEAST TEMPORARILY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE, THE STORMS
HAVE SHOWN HOW BAD SOME OF
PUERTO RICO'S INFRASTRUCTURE
PROBLEMS ARE.
>> RIGHT.
WE TALK ABOUT THE ISLAND BEING
WITHOUT POWER.
10% IS ALREADY WITHOUT POWER
FOLLOWING HURRICANE IRMA WHICH
DIDN'T HAVE A DIRECT HIT.
THE NUMBER 1 CLIENT IS THE WATER
COMPANY.
SO NO POWER MEANS NO WATER, NO
SEWER.
UNLIKE HERE IN THE U.S., THE
CELL PHONE PROVIDERS IN PUERTO
RICO RELY SOLELY ON THE PUBLIC
POWER GRID.
SO COMMUNICATIONS ARE ALSO VERY
LIMITED AND THE ISLAND'S POWER
AUTHORITY IS MASSIVELY IN DEBT.
SO TURNING THE LIGHTS BACK ON
COULD TAKE SEVERAL MONTHS.
WHEN IT COMES TO INFRASTRUCTURE,
IT GETS WORSE.
RETAINING WALLS AND BUILDINGS
ARE WEAK.
IN SOME CASES, THEY'RE DANGEROUS
BY YEARS OF DEFERRED MAINTENANCE
AND MEDICAL FACILITIES ARE
UNDERFUNDED AND COULD BE
OVERWHELMED BY THE STORM.
>> Shepard: THANKS, TRACE.
UPDATING THE TOP STORY.
THE FEDS FACING ANOTHER HUGE
CLEANUP.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THE HEAD OF
FEMA ABOUT RESPONSE AND WE'LL
WATCH FOR HURRICANE MARIA'S NEXT
MONTH.
FIRST, ANTHONY WIENER SOON TO
LEARN HIS SENTENCE FOR SEXTING
WITH A TEENAGE GIRL.
TODAY PROSECUTORS LAYING OUT HOW
LONG THEY WANT HIM IN PRISON.
DETAILS AHEAD.
>> A FOX REPORT NOW.
HEADLINES FROM THE FOX NEWS
DECK.
THE FIGHT TO LIBERATE RAQQA IN
SYRIA IS IN ITS FINAL STAGES.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM U.S.-BACKED
FIGHTERS THAT SAY THEY CONTROL
90% OF THE CAPITOL IN SYRIA.
THE U.S. HAS HUNDREDS OF TROOPS
ON THE GROUND FOR SUPPORT.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS URGING A
FORMER JUDGE TO SEND ANTHONY
WIENER TO PRISON FOR 27 MONTHS.
WIENER PLEADED GUILTY TO SENDING
OBSCENE TEXTS TO A 15-YEAR-OLD
GIRL.
HIS SENTENCING SET FOR MONDAY.
DEFENSE LAWYERS CLAIM THE TEEN
WAS THE AGGRESSOR AND MAY WANTED
TO HAVE GATHERED MATERIAL FOR A
BOOK.
WATCH THIS.
A SINKHOLE SWALLOWING A HOME
NEAR ORLANDO.
THE HOMEOWNER SAID IT WAS TIME
TO GET OUT OF DODGE WHEN SHE
HEARD THE HOUSE CREEKING AND
CRACKING AND NOTICED THE BATHTUB
SINKING INTO THE GROUND.
♪
So, I was at Mom and Dad's
and found this.
CD's, Baseball cards...
Your old magic set?
And this wrestling ticket...
Which you still owe me for.
Seriously?
$25?
I didn't even want to go.
Ahhh, your diary.
"Mom says it's totally
natural..."
$25 is nothing.
Abracadabra, Bro.
The Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
The fast, secure and simple way
to send money.
>> Shepard: AT LEAST 225 PEOPLE
CONFIRMED DEAD IN MEXICO AND
DOZENS OF HOMES DESTROYED AFTER
THE EARTHQUAKE THAT STRUCK 25
HOURS AGO.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO OFFICIALS ON
SCENE.
DRONE VIDEO SHOWS CREWS WORKING
AT A SCHOOL IN MEXICO.
ONE OF THE SEARCH AND RESCUE
MISSIONS ARE UNDERWAY RIGHT NOW.
VIDEO SHOWS RESCUERS PULLING
CHILDREN FROM WHAT REMAINS OF
THE SCHOOL.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
>> THERE YOU GO.
A LIVE LOOK AT THE SCHOOL WHERE
RESCUES ARE UNDERWAY RIGHT NOW.
THEY'RE LOOKING FOR ANYBODY ELSE
THAT MAY HAVE SURVIVED AND SEEM
TO BE ONE PERSON MAY BE ALIVE IN
THERE.
THE QUAKE HIT YESTERDAY SOUTH
AND EAST OF MEXICO CITY.
32 YEARS TO THE DAY AFTER A
DEVASTATING EARTHQUAKE HIT THE
COUNTRY AND KILLED SOME 10,000
PEOPLE.
SOME MORE PICTURES NOW IN THE
SLIDE SHOW THAT THIS FIRST
ONE -- THE FIRST PICTURE HERE
SHOWING SOMEBODY GIVING WATER TO
A MAN WHO IS TRAPPED UNDER A
COLLAPSED BUILDING.
AND HERE, A CAR CRUNCHED UNDER
PART OF THE COLLAPSED SCHOOL
WE'VE BEEN SHOWING YOU.
ANOTHER IMAGE SHOWS FIRST
RESPONDERS WORKING TO REMOVE A
MASSIVE PILE OF DEBRIS.
LOOK AT THAT PILE.
JUST INCREDIBLE THE WORK THEY'RE
DOING WITH SO MANY BUILDINGS
DAMAGED OR DESTROYED, THIS
FAMILY AND MANY OTHERS WERE
PREPARING TO SLEEP ON THE
STREETS LAST NIGHT AS THEY
WAITED FOR AFTER SHOCKS.
MANY RACED TO HELP RESCUERS.
HERE'S A STREET CLOWN THAT
SHOWED UP TO OFFER WHATEVER
ASSISTANCE HE COULD.
IN THIS INSTANCE, A WOMAN
HOLDING UP A SIGN FOR SILENCE SO
FIRST RESPONDERS CAN LISTEN FOR
THOSE BURIED UNDER THE CONCRETE
AND STEEL.
THERESA MAY MEETING WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE PRIME
MINISTER MAY FROM THE UNITED
KINGDOM AND HER REPRESENTATIVES
WHO ARE PEOPLE THAT WE KNOW VERY
WELL THROUGH RECENT TRADE
NEGOTIATIONS.
I HAVE TO SAY WE'LL BE DOING A
LOT OF TRADING WITH THE UNITED
KINGDOM.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO IT.
WE HAVE GOTTEN TO KNOW EACH
OTHER OVER THE LAST YEAR.
IT'S A REAL HONOR TO HAVE YOU
HERE.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
GOOD TO BE HERE.
AS YOU SAY, WE'VE HAD MANY
DISCUSSIONS BETWEEN
REPRESENTATIVES AND OURSELVES ON
A WHOLE VARIETY OF ISSUES,
INCLUDING TRADE WHICH THERE BE
IMPORTANT FOR US AND OTHER
ISSUES, FOREIGN POLICY ISSUES,
SECURITY AND DEFENSE
RELATIONSHIP, WHICH IS THE
CLOSEST THAT WE HAVE.
GREAT THAT THAT CONTINUES.
>> THANKS VERY MUCH FOR BEING
HERE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: PLEASANTRIES BUT NO
QUESTIONS ANSWERED TODAY.
LIVE PICTURES FROM MEXICO CITY
WHERE STREET RESCUES ARE
UNDERWAY, A SPLIT SCREEN HERE ON
THE RIGHT.
YOU CAN SEE THE STREETS OF THE
CITY AND ON THE LEFT IS THE SPOT
WHERE THEY'RE SEARCHING FOR ANY
POSSIBLE SURVIVORS FROM THE
SCHOOL THAT COLLAPSED THERE.
OUR CORRESPONDENT, JONATHAN HUNT
IS IN MEXICO CITY NEAR A
COLLAPSED BUILDING WHERE WE'RE
HEARING THERE MAY BE PEOPLE
TRAPPED THERE AS WELL, JONATHAN?
>> YEAH, SHEP.
WE JUST ARRIVED IN MEXICO CITY
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO.
WE APOLOGIZE FOR THE
COMMUNICATIONS.
WE'RE GETTING YOU A PICTURE AT
THIS POINT.
LET ME PAINT THE PICTURE FOR
YOU.
I'M STANDING IN FRONT OF WHAT
WAS A FIVE-STORY APARTMENT
BUILDING.
EACH STORY OF THE BUILDING
PANCAKED DOWN ON TO EACH OTHER
RIGHT NOW.
SO IT NOW STANDS WHAT WOULD HAVE
BEEN ABOUT TWO STORIES HIGH.
ALTHOUGH FIVE CRUSHED INTO EACH
OTHER.
WE'RE TOLD THERE WAS LIKE 40
APARTMENTS IN THAT BUILDING.
RESCUERS ARE SWARMING AROUND IT
RIGHT NOW TRYING TO FIND ANYBODY
THAT STILL MAY BE ALIVE IN THE
RUBBLE.
THEY'VE BEEN BRINGING OUT A
NUMBER OF BODIES TO THE BODIES
OF TWO CHILDREN FOR INSTANCE
BROUGHT OUT A SHORT TIME AGO.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
HERE.
A LOT OF OFFICIAL REFUGEE
WORKERS OBVIOUSLY.
I HAVE TO SAY ONE OF THE
STRIKING THINGS WHEN YOU ARRIVE
IN MEXICO CITY IS THE NUMBER OF
VOLUNTEERS, THE NUMBER OF
ORDINARY MEXICAN CITIZENS
RUSHING TO HELP.
WE DROVE HERE FROM THE AIRPORT,
SHEP, IN THE LAST FEW MINUTES.
LITERALLY HUNDREDS OF PICKUPS,
MOTOR BIKES GETTING ALONG AS
FAST AS THEY CAN.
THOSE PICKUP TRUCKS OF MOTOR
BIKES LOADED WITH PEOPLE JUST
WANTING TO HELP.
THEY'RE CARRYING SHOVELS,
ANYTHING THAT MAY BE OF USE AS
THEY TRY TO PERFORM THE RESCUES
AROUND THIS CITY RIGHT NOW.
WE'RE IN THE SOUTHERN PART OF
THE CITY, WHICH IS WARDS WHERE
THE SCHOOL IS THAT YOU'RE
TALKING ABOUT.
THAT IS ONE OF THE MOST INTENSE
SCENES BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY
CHILDREN STILL UNACCOUNTED FOR.
THAT DIGGING WILL GO ON
OBVIOUSLY UNTIL THEY HAVE
ACCOUNTED FOR EVERYBODY WHO MAY
HAVE BEEN IN THAT SCHOOL.
THE SAME WITH THE BUILDING I'M
STANDING IN FRONT OF RIGHT NOW.
THE SAME WITH ALL OF THE 40 OR
SO BUILDINGS THAT COLLAPSED HERE
IN MEXICO CITY.
PRESIDE
THE PRESIDENT HAS DECLARED
THREE DAYS OF MOURNING.
IT'S RIGHT NOW A RESCUE
OPERATION.
THE FOCUS IS FINDING PEOPLE
UNDER THIS RUBBLE WHO MAY STILL
BE ALIVE.
WE'RE TOLD, AS YOU LOOK AT THE
PICTURES OF THE SCHOOL, THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL AND THE
SOUTHERN PART OF MEXICO CITY,
THAT THEY FOUND ONE YOUNG GIRL
ALIVE.
THEY'RE DOING THEIR BEST TO GET
TO HER.
OBVIOUSLY IT IS A VERY, VERY
DIFFICULT OPERATION.
A VERY DANGEROUS OPERATION.
WHEN RESCUE WORKERS GO IN TO
PERFORM THE OPERATIONS AS WE SAW
A FEW YEARS AGO IN HAITI,
THEY'RE PUTTING THEIR LIVES AT
RISK.
ONE WRONG MOVE, ONE WRONG PIECE
OF CONCRETE OR ONE PIECE OF
TIMBER MOVES AND MORE OF THE
BUILDING CAN COME DOWN
ENDANGERING THE LIVES OF THE
RESCUE WORKERS.
IT'S A TENSE, DIFFICULT
OPERATION, SHEP.
>> Shepard: JONATHAN HUNT IN
MEXICO CITY.
LIVE REPORTS THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
BACK TO CONTINUING COVERAGE OF
HURRICANE MARIA PUMMELLING
PUERTO RICO AND ST. CROIX AND
OTHERS.
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT NOW DEALING
WITH ITS THIRD NATURAL DISASTER
IN LESS THAN A MONTH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS APPROVED AN
EMERGENCY DECLARATION FOR PUERTO
RICO AND THE VIRGIN ISLANDS.
THE MONSTER STORM COULD COST
BILLIONS IN DAMAGE ACROSS THE
CARIBBEAN.
THAT'S ON TOP OF THE DEVASTATION
THAT HURRICANE IRMA HAS JUST
LEFT BEHIND.
LET'S GO TO BROCK LONG NOW FROM
FEMA WHO BRIEFED PRESIDENT TRUMP
BY PHONE ON HURRICANE MARIA.
SIR, NICE TO SPEAK WITH YOU.
HOW IS THE BRIEFING?
>> THE PRESIDENT REMAINS VERY
ENGAGED AND HIS MESSAGE IS TAKE
CARE OF PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHAT WE'RE DOING.
WE KEPT 3,200 STAFF ON THE U.S.
VIRGIN ISLANDS AND PUERTO RICO.
THAT IS INCIDENT MANAGEMENT
TEAMS TO MEDICAL TEAMS TO SEARCH
AND RESCUE TEAMS.
THEY'RE STARTING TO DEPLOY OUT
AS THE STORM -- ELEMENTS OF THE
STORM PASS THROUGH.
AND THEN WE'RE PREPARED TO OPEN
UP AIRPORTS AND THE SHIPPING
PORTS TO CONTINUE WITH MORE
TEAMS AND COMMODITIES COMING IN
UP.
>> Shepard: WHAT KIND OF REPORTS
SPECIFICALLY ARE YOU GETTING
FROM THE TEAMS FANNING OUT?
>> SO IN THE VIRGIN ISLANDS AS
THE SYSTEM PASSED TO THE SOUTH
OF THE ISLANDS LAST NIGHT, THE
WINDS EXPANDED AND THEY
BASICALLY -- THEY HAD UP TO
ABOUT 137 MILES PER HOUR WINDS.
SO THEY HAVE A LOT OF ROOF
DAMAGE.
THEY DO HAVE DAMAGE TO THEIR
CRITICAL INFRASTRUCTURE.
THE POWER IS OFF.
THEY EXPERIENCED SOME DAMAGE TO
HOSPITALS, WHICH WERE ALREADY
WORKING WITH THE GOVERNOR TO
ALLEVIATE SOME OF THOSE IMPACTS.
PUERTO RICO UNFORTUNATELY,
THEY'RE UNDER FLASH FLOOD
WARNINGS IN THE COMMONWEALTH.
THEY HAVE 100% OF THE POWER OFF.
VIRGIN ISLANDS AND PUERTO RICO
HAVE FRAGILE POWER SYSTEMS.
THE GOAL IS LIFE SAFETY, LIFE
SUSTAINING MISSIONS BY GETTING
COMMODITIES IN.
FIRST TO PUSH OUT DEBRIS TO OPEN
THE ROADS AND PROVIDE EMERGENCY
POWER TO THE INFRASTRUCTURE TO
GET IT BACK UP AND TRY TO
RESTORE ROUTINE.
>> Shepard: LOOKING ACROSS THE
EXPAND OF ALL THAT YOUR
DEPARTMENT IS DEALING WITH, IT'S
HARD TO FATHOM HOW DIFFICULT IT
MUST BE TO GET THROUGH THIS.
YOU HAVE TO BE STRETCHED THIN
RIGHT NOW.
>> YEAH.
I WOULDN'T SAY WE'RE STRETCHED
THIN.
THESE GUYS BACK HERE ARE
INCREDIBLY DEDICATED.
THEY'VE BEEN RUNNING FOR 30 DAYS
AT THIS POINT.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO MEET THE
DEMANDS.
WE SIGNED UP FOR THIS JOB AND
DEDICATED TO HELPING THE
GOVERNORS ACHIEVE THEIR RESPONSE
GOALS AND HELP PEOPLE.
>> Shepard: FOR PEOPLE AT HOME
SAYING I WANT TO HELP BUT NOT
SURE HOW TO DO IT, WHAT DO YOU
TELL THEM?
>> RIGHT NOW THE BEST WAY IS TO
GO TO NVOAD.ORG.
THAT WILL GIVE YOU BASICALLY A
WHOLE LIST OF OPTIONS TO
VOLUNTEER AND DONATE.
THEN ONCE WE WORK WITH THE
GOVERNORS, THERE WILL BE OTHER
OPPORTUNITIES TO SUPPORT
VOLUNTEER AND DONATIONS TO EACH
ONE OF THE TERRITORIES.
>> Shepard: WE'RE WITH YOU.
CAN'T THANK YOU ENOUGH.
FEMA ADMINISTRATOR BROCK LONG.
TALK TO YOU SOON.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
HE THINKS HE HAS A GOOD SHOT AT
BROKERING PEACE IN THE MIDDLE
EAST.
THE PRESIDENT MET WITH THE
PALESTINIAN LEADER TODAY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID HE MADE UP
HIS MIND ABOUT THE IRAN NUCLEAR
DEAL ONE DAY AFTER CALLING IT AN
EMBARRASSMENT.
SO WHAT IS THE DECISION?
BY THE WAY, THE IRANIAN
PRESIDENT HAS SHOT BACK.
THAT IS NEXT.
I work
overtime when
I can get it.
I need
my blood sugar
to stay
in control.
So I asked
about Tresiba®.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
Tresiba®
is a once-daily,
long-acting
insulin
that lasts even
longer than
24 hours.
I need to cut my A1C.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
Tresiba® works
like my body's insulin.
Releases slow
and steady.
Providing
powerful
A1C reduction.
My week?
Hectic.
My weekends?
My time.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
I can take Tresiba®
any time of day.
So if I sleep in,
and delay my dose,
I take it as soon as I can,
as long as there's at least
8 hours between doses.
Once in use,
Tresiba® lasts
8 weeks,
with or without
refrigeration,
twice as long
as the Lantus® Pen.
(announcer)
Tresiba® is used
to control high blood sugar
in adults with diabetes.
Don't use Tresiba® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during
episodes of low blood sugar,
or if you are allergic
to any of its ingredients.
Don't share needles
or insulin pens.
Don't reuse needles.
The most common side effect
is low blood sugar,
which may cause dizziness,
sweating, confusion
and headache.
Check your blood sugar.
Low blood sugar can be serious
and may be life-threatening.
Injection site reactions
may occur.
Tell your prescriber
about all medicines you take
and all your medical conditions.
Taking TZDs with insulins
like Tresiba®
may cause serious side
effects like heart failure.
Your insulin dose shouldn't
be changed
without
asking your prescriber.
Get medical help right away
if you have trouble breathing,
fast heartbeat,
extreme drowsiness,
swelling of your face,
tongue or throat,
dizziness or confusion.
Ask your health care provider
if you're Tresiba® ready.
Covered by most insurance
and Medicare plans.
♪ Tresiba® ready ♪
Pcountries thatk
mewe traveled,t
what is your
nationality and
I would always
answer Hispanic.
So when I got my Ancestry DNA
results it was a shocker.
I'm everything.
I'm from all nations.
I would look at forms
now and wonder
what do I mark?
Because I'm everything.
And I marked other.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
>> Shepard: LIVE IN MEXICO CITY.
SOUTHERN PART OF THE CITY.
SO MANY BUILDINGS THAT HAVE A
COLLAPSED ACROSS THE GREAT CITY.
THIS SCHOOL IS OF URGENT
CONCERN.
MORE THAN 30 KIDS AND TEACHERS
FOR THAT MATTER ARE UNACCOUNTED
FOR.
25 CONFIRMED DEAD.
NOW THE RACE TO FIND SOMEONE
ALIVE.
THEY RESCUED ONE GIRL TODAY.
WE DON'T KNOW THE PARTICULARS OF
HER CONDITION.
WE KNOW THAT SHE'S ALIVE AND WE
KNOW THEY BELIEVE THEY'RE
HEARING SOUNDS INSIDE.
THEY'RE DOING EVERYTHING THEY
CAN TO GET IN THERE AND SAVE
ANYBODY POSSIBLE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE'S MADE A
DECISION ON WHETHER TO PULL THE
UNITED STATES OUT OF THE
HISTORIC NUCLEAR DEAL WITH IRAN.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT DECISION
IS HIS TO KNOW FOR NOW.
>> HAVE YOU DECIDED TO STAY OR
LEAVE?
>> I HAVE DECIDED.
>> WHAT IS YOUR DECISION?
>> I'LL LET YOU KNOW.
>> Shepard: HE WILL LET US KNOW.
HE MADE A COMMENT WITH A MEETING
WITH MAHMOUD ABBAS.
THE PRESIDENT'S COMMENT ON THE
IRAN DEAL AFTER HE CALLED IT AN
EMBARRASSMENT DURING A SPEECH TO
THE UNITED NATIONS GENERAL
ASSEMBLY.
THE PRESIDENT OF IRAN TOOK A
SHOT BACK.
>> IT WILL BE A PERIOD OF
DISAGREEMENT IN THE WORLD OF
POLITICS.
THE WORLD WILL HAVE LOST A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY.
BUT SUCH UNFORTUNATE BEHAVIOR
WILL NEVER IMPEDE IRAN'S COURSE
OF PROGRESS AND ADVANCEMENT.
>> Shepard: ROGUE NEWCOMERS TO
THE WORLD OF POLITICS.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JOHN ROBERTS IS
HERE.
THAT'S TO BE EXPECTED.
>> THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
DISCUSSIONS AROUND THE JCP,
JOINT COMPREHENSIVE PLAN OF
ACTION.
THE CONVERSATIONS ARE CAN THE
DEAL BE REOPENED.
THE UNITED STATES IS ONE OF SIX
SIGNATORS TO THE DEAL.
IF YOU CAN'T GET A BETTER DEAL,
IS THE PRESIDENT BETTER TO PULL
OUT.
AS A CANDIDATE, THE PRESIDENT
SAID HE WAS GOING TO SCRAP THE
DEAL.
BUT THE PRESIDENT HAS
RECERTIFIED THAT IRAN IS
COMPLYING WITH THE DEAL AS
ANOTHER DEADLINE COMES UP AS
SOME ARE SAYING THE PRESIDENT
WILL CONSIDER THE DECISION.
THE WHITE HOUSE'S VIEW OF THE
DEAL, IT ONLY DEALS WITH IRAN
AND THE NUCLEAR PROGRAM AND
DOESN'T DEAL WITH THE SUPPORT
FOR TERROR, BASHAR AL-ASSAD.
YESTERDAY HE SAID AT THE U.N.,
THE IRANIAN RESPOND TODAY BY
SAYING THE FOLLOWING.
>> IGNORANT, ABSURD AND HATEFUL
RHETORIC FILLED WITH
RIDICULOUSLY BASELESS
ALLEGATIONS.
>> ABSURD HATEFUL RHETORIC.
WE REPORT, YOU DECIDE.
THE PRESIDENT HAS TAKEN SOME
OTHER STEPS WITH REGARDS TO IRAN
OUTSIDE OF THE FRAME WORK OF THE
NUCLEAR AGREEMENT UNILATERALLY
IMPOSED SANCTIONS.
IF HE DECIDED TO STAY IN THE
IRAN NUCLEAR DEAL, THE WHITE
HOUSE COULD TAKE MORE STEPS TO
REIGN IN IRAN'S BAD BEHAVIOR.
GOOD LUCK WITH THAT.
>> AND THEY TALKED ABOUT THE
MIDEAST PEACE DEAL.
>> THE PRESIDENT MET WITH
MAHMOUD ABBAS AND THE KING OF
JORDAN.
HE MET WITH THE ISRAELI PRIME
MINISTER.
THE PRESIDENT HAS A LOT INVESTED
IN THIS.
HIS SON-IN-LAW, JARED KUSHNER IS
THE POINT PERSON ON THIS.
THEY HAVE MADE A NUMBER OF
VISITS TO THE REGION.
WE TALKED ABOUT THIS YESTERDAY.
THE PRESIDENT HOLDING OUT HOPE
THAT SOMETHING MAY BE POSSIBLE.
LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID THIS
MORNING.
>> WE'RE AT A VERY IMPORTANT
JUNCTURE.
A SMALL PERIOD OF TIME AND WE'RE
GOING TO SEE WHAT WE CAN DO.
SO MANY PEOPLE HAVE TALKED ABOUT
IT AND IT'S NEVER HAPPENED.
WE'RE FIGHTING VERY HARD.
>> HE'S OPTIMISTIC.
SHOULD WE GO THROUGH THE LIST OF
PRESIDENTS THAT WERE HOPEFUL AND
CAME AWAY WITH NOTHING.
>> Shepard: IT'S A LONG ONE.
>> IT IS.
>> Shepard: MICHAEL CROWLEY FROM
POLITCO.
GOOD TO SEE YOU, MICHAEL.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT IS THE
REPORTING WHERE WE ARE IN THIS.
PULLING OUT HAS ENORMOUS
CHALLENGES.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
SOME CRITICS OF THE DEAL, SOME
THAT OPPOSED IT AT THE TIME THAT
IT WAS SEALED WITH SEVERAL
COUNTRIES AS JOHN POINTED OUT,
EVEN SOME OPPONENTS OF DOING
THAT NOW SAY IT'S TOO LATE.
THE COST OF UNDOING THIS DEAL
ARE MUCH GREATER THAN TO OPPOSED
THE DEAL.
IRAN GOT A LOT OF FINANCIAL
BENEFITS.
AS SOON AS THE DEAL WAS STRUCK
IN JULY 2015, IRAN GOT BILLIONS
OF IMMEDIATE PAY-OFF.
THERE'S NO WAY YOU CAN CLAW THAT
BACK.
IN FACT, CIA DIRECTOR MIKE
POMPEO SPOKE TO BRET BAIER.
BRET SAID YOU WERE A STRONG
CRITIC.
AND POMPEO SAID THINGS LOOK
DIFFERENT NOW BEING ON THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE DESK AND THE
ENVIRONMENT HAS CHANGED.
THE DEAL IS SIGNED.
IRAN GOT THE BENEFITS.
THOSE THAT DIDN'T LIKE THE DEAL
ARE CAUTIOUS ABOUT BLOWING IT UP
RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: WILL THERE REAL
INDICATORS THAT THEY'RE CHEATING
OR IS THE CONSENSUS THAT THINGS
ARE GOING AS WELL AS COULD BE
EXPECTED?
>> YOU KNOW, I GUESS WHAT YOUR
DEFINITION OF CHEATING IS.
THE INTERNATIONAL A COMIC ENERGY
AGENCY INSPECTORS THAT HAVE BEEN
GOING TO IRAN AND HAVE THIS VERY
SPECIFIC CHECKLIST OF TECHNICAL
METRICS SAY THAT IRAN IS NOT
CHEATING.
THEY'RE IN COMPLIANCE.
THERE WAS ONE INCIDENT IRAN GOT
A LITTLE ABOVE THE AMOUNT OF
HEAVY WATER THEY WERE SUPPOSED
TO HAVE ON HAND.
IF YOU TALK THE PEOPLE THAT
ARE -- FOLLOW THIS CLOSELY, THEY
SAY IT'S NOT THAT BIG OF A DEAL.
THE IAEA SAYS THEY'RE IN
COMPLIANCE.
THERE'S A GROUP OF PEOPLE, TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS,
CONSERVATIVE, ISRAELI OFFICIALS
SAY IT'S THE WRONG WAY TO THINK
ABOUT IT.
THAT IT'S BROADER THAN THIS.
IRANIAN BEHAVIOR YOU HAVE TO
LOOK AT.
ARE THEY BECOMING MORE OF A
CIVILIZED NATION THAT OBEYS THE
SORT OF RULES OF THE ROAD
INTERNATIONALLY.
THE ANSWER TO THAT IS NO.
THE DEAL SORT OF OBLIGATED IRAN
TO BEHAVE BETTER IN THEIR
NEIGHBORHOOD AND THEREFORE
THEY'RE NOT HONORING WHAT SOME
TRUMP OFFICIALS HAVE CALLED THE
SPIRIT OF THE DEAL.
THE FRIENDS THAT SERVED UNDER
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID THE DEAL
HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH IRANIAN
BEHAVIOR, THE METRICS, THE
RESEARCH, THE URANIUM ON HAND.
THAT'S THE OPINION RIGHT NOW.
>> MICHAEL CROWLEY FORE POLITCO.
THANK YOU.
>> THANKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THE TOP REPUBLICAN
IN THE UNITED STATES SENATE SAYS
HE PLANS TO MOVE AHEAD WITH THE
LATEST GOP HEALTHCARE PLAN.
BUT HE CAN LOSE ONLY ONE MORE
REPUBLICAN VOTE AND STILL PASS
THE BILL.
TODAY THE FORMER PRESIDENT
BARACK OBAMA WEIGHED IN ON THIS
MATTER.
ON THE BATTLE OVER HIS OWN
HEALTHCARE LAW.
WE'LL GO LIVE TO CAPITOL HILL
AND WE'RE CONTINUING TO WATCH IN
MEXICO CITY WHERE THE SEARCH IS
ON FOR SURVIVORS A DAY AFTER THE
QUAKE HIT WITH SO MANY WONDERING
WITH BUILDINGS COLLAPSED ALL
OVER THE COUNTRY, HOW HIGH THE
DEATH TOLL MAY BE.
stimate.
I just snapped a photo
and got an estimate in 24 hours.
My insurance company
definitely doesn't have that...
You can leave worry behind when
Liberty Stands With You™
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
>> Shepard: THE SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER MITCH McCONNELL INTENDS
TO BREAK THE LATEST GOP
HEALTHCARE BILL TO THE SENATE
FLOOR TO A VOTE NEXT WEEK.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM HIS
SPOKESMAN.
WHEN RAND PAUL ALREADY PLEDGING
TO VOTE NO AND WITH NO SUPPORT
FROM DEMOCRATS AT ALL, THE GOP
CAN AFFORD TO LOSE BY ONE MORE
VOTE.
AND THERE ARE PEOPLE ON THE
FENCE.
THE CHIEF CONGRESSIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MIKE EMANUEL WITH
THE NEWS.
HI, MIKE.
>> PLANS TO VOTE NEXT WEEK ARE
DESIGNED TO TURN UP THE PRESSURE
ON UNDECIDED REPUBLICANS.
>> IT'S BEEN THE MOST FUN THING
I'VE WORKED ON, THE MOST
CHALLENGING THING I'VE WORKED ON
AND WE'RE A POINT TO TAKE THE
BILL UP NEXT WEEK.
TO MY REPUBLICAN COLLEAGUES, IF
YOU HAVE A BETTER IDEA, NOW IS
THE TIME.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE IT UP
NEXT WEEK?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE'RE GOING TO THE FLOOR WITH A
REPEAL AND REPLACE PROPOSAL THAT
IS FEDERALISM.
EVERYBODY GETS TO LOOK AT IT,
STUDY IT.
>> A LOT OF FOCUS ON THREE
REPUBLICAN SENATORS THAT KILLED
HEALTHCARE REFORM IN JULY.
SUSAN COLLINS, JOHN McCAIN AND
ALASKA'S LISA MURKOWSKI.
>> THE INITIAL ANALYSIS ON THE
IMPACT OF THE STATE OF MAINE OF
THEIR BILL IS THAT IT WOULD
RESULT TO MAINE RECEIVING A
BILLION DOLLARS LESS IN FEDERAL
FUNDING FOR HEALTHCARE OVER THE
NEXT DECADE.
>> MEETINGS CONTINUE ON CAPITOL
HILL TRYING TO ADDRESS THE
CONCERNS OF GOP SENATORS
SCHLEPP?
>> Shepard: THERE WAS A
BIPARTISAN EFFORT TO TRY TO
IMPROVE OBAMACARE.
WHAT HAPPENED TO THAT?
>> IT FELL APART LAST NIGHT.
YOU HAD SENATOR LAMAR ALEXANDER
AND PATTY MURRAY TRYING TO WORK
ON A BIPARTISAN FIX BY THE END
OF THE MONTH.
TOP DEMOCRATS ARE EXPRESSING
DISAPPOINTMENT.
>> IT'S UNFORTUNATE.
WE HAD A CHANCE TO DO SOMETHING
IMPORTANT, HISTORIC, BIPARTISAN
THAT WOULD HAVE BUILT ON THE
HEALTHCARE SYSTEM THAT WE HAVE
IN THIS COUNTRY.
NOW WE'RE MOVING TO ANOTHER
PARTISAN APPROACH.
NO CBO SCORE, NO HEARINGS.
GETTING READY TO REPEAT WHAT WE
DID A FEW MONTHS AGO.
>> FORMER PRESIDENT OBAMA
WEIGHED IN THIS AFTERNOON
CALLING THE LATEST ATTEMPT TO
SCRAP OBAMACARE AGGRAVATING.
>> ALL OF THIS IS BEING DONE
WITHOUT ANY ECONOMIC OR
ACTIONARY OR PLAIN COMMON SENSE
RATIONALE.
IT FRUSTRATES.
IT'S CERTAINLY FRUSTRATING TO
HAVE TO MOBILIZE EVERY COUPLE
MONTHS TO KEEP OUR LEADERS FROM
INFLICTING REAL HUMAN SUFFERING
ON OUR CONSTITUENTS.
>> IT'S NOT ENTIRELY CLEAR IF
REPUBLICANS WILL GET TO 50 YES
VOTES, SHEP.
>> Shepard: MIKE EMANUEL AT THE
ROTUNDA ON THE HILL.
THANK YOU.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
If yand constipation,ling
and you're overwhelmed
by everything you've tried--
all those laxatives,
daily probiotics,
endless fiber--
it could be wearing on you.
Tell your doctor
what you've tried,
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults
with IBS
with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help relieve
your belly pain
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.
Do not give LINZESS
to children less than six
and it should not be given
to children
six to less than eighteen.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS
if you have a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop
unusual or severe
stomach pain,
especially with
bloody or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe,
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor
right away.
Other side effects
include gas,
stomach-area pain
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
ExpeStandard.e Lexus RX
with Advance Safety...
Lease the 2017 RX 350 for
$399 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing at
your Lexus dealer.
>> Shepard: WE'VE BEEN WATCHING
ALMOST CONSTANTLY AS THEY WORK
FEVERISHLY TO SAVE ANYBODY
BURRED IN THAT SCHOOL IN
SOUTHERN MEXICO CITY.
WE'LL HAVE UPDATES THROUGHOUT
THE AFTERNOON.
WE'VE BEEN WATCHING THE DOW
TODAY AFTER THE FEDS MADE A
DECISION TO KEEP THE RATES
STEADY BUT A HIKE BY THE END OF
THE YEAR.
THE DOLLAR STRONG OUT OF THE
GATE.
CAVUTO STARTS NOW.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT.
MARIA IS A MONSTER.
CONTINUES TO BASH PUERTO RICO.
HERE'S WHAT WE KNOW RIGHT NOW.
THE HURRICANE CATEGORY THREE
STORM WITH WINDS IN EXCESS OF
115 MILES AN HOUR.
ALL OF PUERTO RICO, ALL 3.5
MILLION RESIDENTS ARE WITHOUT
POWER.
A FISHING VILLAGE NEAR SAN JUAN
IS WIPED OUT.
THE GOVERNOR OF PUERTO RICO IS
ASKING THE PRESIDENT TO DECLARE
THE ISLAND A DISASTER ZONE TO
PAVE THE WAY FOR FEDERAL
FUNDING.
STEVE HARRIGAN HAS MORE.
IT LOOKS LIKE A MESS.
>> IT IS A BETTER