SOVEREIGNTY OF CHINA, A
REPRESSIVE REGIME EVER
SINCE 1997.
>> Bret: THAT IS IT FOR THE
PANEL.
THANKS FOR WATCHING
"SPECIAL REPORT," FAIR,
BALANCED AND UNAFRAID.
>> Shepard: THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT.
TONIGHT, RED LINE CROSSED.
THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT DID
USE CHEMICAL WEAPONS
AGAINST OPPOSITION
FIGHTERS.
NOW, THE WHITE HOUSE
CONSIDERING A MILITARY
MOVE.
PLUS, IT COULD HAVE
PREVENTED THE ATTACKS OF
9/11.
THE FBI DIRECTOR ON THE
SECRET SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAM.
HE SAYS TRACKING PHONE
RECORDS COULD HAVE HELPED
THEM FIND ONE OF THE
HIJACKERS.
>> THAT'S SAFE HOUSE HAD A
TELEPHONE NUMBER BUT THEY
COULD NOT KNOW WHO WAS
CALLING INTO THAT
PARTICULAR SAFE HOUSE.
>> Shepard: BUT SOME
LAWMAKERS ARE NOT
CONVINCED.
>> I AM NOT PERSUADED THAT
THAT THAT MAKES IT OKAY TO
COLLECT EVERY CALL.
>> Shepard: WHAT ABOUT THE
GUY WHO LEAKED EVERYTHING.
>> HE IS THE SUBJECT OF AN
ONGOING CRIMINAL
INVESTIGATION.
>> Shepard: TONIGHT,
SURVEILLANCE, SECURITY, AND
A WHOLE LOT OF SECRETS.
>> Shepard: SHE WAS PERHAPS
DAYS FROM DEATH WHEN THE
CALL CAME IN.
THEY HAD FOUND A LUNG DONOR
AND THE TRANSPLANT WAS GOOD
TO GO.
>> THE SURGERY WAS VERY
VERY SUCCESSFUL.
>> Shepard: TONIGHT, AN
UPDATE ON THE BRAVE GIRL
WHO IS FINALLY BREATHING A
BIT EASIER.
[WHOO!
>> Shepard: BUT FIRST FROM
FOX THIS THURSDAY NIGHT.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS U.S.
INTELLIGENCE HAS HIGH
CONFIDENCE THAT THE SYRIAN
PRESIDENT BASHAR ASSAD HAS
USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS IN
THAT COUNTRY'S CIVIL WAR.
A SENIOR U.S. OFFICIAL SAYS
THE COUNTRY WILL NOW
PROVIDE MILITARY SUPPORT TO
SOME REBEL FIGHTERS.
ANALYSTS POINT OUT THAT
DOES NOT NECESSARILY MEAN
WEAPONS.
AND THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS
PRESIDENT OBAMA HAS NOT YET
MADE A DECISION ABOUT
ENFORCING A NO-FLY ZONE
OVER SYRIA.
A FULL NO-FLY ZONE WOULD
COST AN ESTIMATED
$50 MILLION A DAY:  THE
UNITED NATIONS NOW REPORTS
MORE THAN 90,000 PEOPLE
HAVE DIED SINCE THE
UPRISING BEGAN IN SYRIA
MORE THAN TWO YEARS AGO.
BUT THE PRESIDENT SAID THE
USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS
WOULD BE A GAME CHANGER.
>> A RED LINE FOR US IS WE
START SEEING A WHOLE BUNCH
OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS MOVING
AROUND OR BEING UTILIZED.
THAT WOULD CHANGE MY
CALCULUS.
>> Shepard: TONIGHT, THE
WHITE HOUSE SAYS THAT
CALCULUS HAS CHANGED.
NOW THE U.S. WILL TALK TO
CONGRESS AND U.S. ALLIES
ABOUT AMERICA'S NEXT MOVE.
LIVE AT THE WHITE HOUSE ON
FOX TOP STORY.
ED, WE ARE TO BELIEVE AFTER
TWO YEARS OF A CIVIL WAR
THERE IS NO PLAN FOR WHAT
TO DO NEXT.
>> SHEP THAT IS WHAT IS SO
CONFUSING ABOUT THIS
ANNOUNCEMENT FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
ONE OF THEIR TOP AIDES HERE
BEN RHODES ANNOUNCED JUST A
SHORT TIME AGO THAT THIS
DOES CHANGE THE CALCULUS
THIS USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
IT IS A GAME CHANGER.
CROSS THE RED LIGHT
WHATEVER WORDS YOU WANT TO
USE THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
USED BEFORE BUT THEN NOT
DIRECTLY SAY THAT THE U.S.
IS GOING TO HARM ARM THE
SYRIAN RENELS.
NOT CLEAR WHAT ACTION WILL
BE TAKEN.
WILL THE U.S. HELP ONE OF
OUR ALLIES ARM THEM SO WE
ARE NOT DIRECTLY ARMING
THEM.
THAT'S ONE OF THE QUESTIONS
WE HAVE TO ANSWER IN THE
DAYS AHEAD.
ANNOUNCEMENT FALLS SHORT OF
PRESIDENT'S CRITICS NOT
JUST ON THE RIGHT LIKE JOHN
MCCAIN BUT BILL CLINTON WHO
WE ARE LEARNING TODAY ON
TUESDAY NIGHT AT A PRIVATE
EVENT WITH JOHN MCCAIN
CRITICIZED THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION POLICY
SUGGESTING IT WAS TOO SLOW
THOUGH JAY CARNEY TODAY
TRIED TO BRUSH OFF THAT
CRITICISM.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO HAVE
EXPERTISE IN THE MATTER
BOTH OUTSIDE OF GOVERNMENT
AND IN CONGRESS AND INSIDE
OF GOVERNMENT HAVE
PERSPECTIVES TO ADD.
AND OPINIONS TO CONTRIBUTE.
AND AANALYSIS TO PROVIDE.
AND THE PRESIDENT WELCOMES
ALL OF THAT.
IN THE END, OF COURSE, HE
AND HIS TEAM HAVE TO MAKE
THE DECISIONS THAT THEY
BELIEVE ARE IN THE BEST
INTEREST OF THE UNITED
STATES AND THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE.
>> SO STILL WAITING ON
WHETHER IT WILL BE U.S.
MILITARY ACTION.
THAT DECISION BUT THE
DECISION ON WHETHER
CHEMICAL WEAPONS HAVE BEEN
USED, THAT HAS BEEN
DECIDED, SPECIFICALLY THE
ADMINISTRATION SAYING
TONIGHT THEY HAVE DIRECT
EVIDENCE THAT THE REGIME,
THE SYRIAN REGIME USED
SYRIAN GAS.
THAT IS A SPECIFIC KIND OF
CHEMICAL WEAPON AND THAT IT
KILLED ABOUT 150 PEOPLE.
IMPORTANT, BUT LET'S
REMEMBER AS YOU HAVE NOTED
THAT'S A SMALL NUMBER OF
PEOPLE THAT WERE KILLED
COMPARED TO THE OVER WELL
OVER 90,000 THE U.N. SAID
HAS NOW BEEN SLAUGHTERED IN
THIS CONFLICT.
150 IMPORTANT TO NOTE THAT
BUT STILL, YOU KNOW, JUST A
SMALL DROP IN THE BUCKET IN
THIS BROADER CONFLICT
SHEP.
>> Shepard: IT WAS THE
PRESIDENT WHO SAID THAT'S
THE RED LINE.
WHEN ARE WE GOING TO HEAR
FROM THE PRESIDENT.
>> WELL, THAT'S WHAT WE ARE
STILL WAITING ON.
AND REPUBLICAN SAXBY
CHAMBLISS IS SAYING TONIGHT
LOOK, THIS IS NOT REALLY
MAJOR NEWS THAT THE
ADMINISTRATION IS NOW
SAYING CHEMICAL WEAPONS
WERE USED.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT MANY
HAVE SUSPECTED FOR A LONG
TIME.
WHAT HE SPECIFICALLY WANTS
SAXBY CHAMBLISS IS A NO-FLY
ZONE.
THE ADMINISTRATION TONIGHT
RULED THAT OUT AT LEAST FOR
NOW AND THAT'S NOT MAKING
CHAMBLISS HAPPY.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> WE NOW KNOW THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS HAVE BEEN USED FOR
ALMOST A YEAR BY THE SYRIAN
REGIME.
WE HAVE DONE NOTHING.
SO I THINK IT'S TIME THAT
WE ACT IN A VERY SERIOUS
WAY.
IF A NO-FLY ZONE IS WHAT
THEY DECIDED TO DO, THEN
I'M SURE OUR MILITARY IS
TAKING RIGHT PREPARATIONS
FOR CARRYING OUT A
SUCCESSFUL OPERATION AND I
WILL SUPPORT THAT.
>> SO WHEN WILL WE HEAR
FROM THE PRESIDENT?
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS ARE
SAYING TO US TONIGHT THAT
HE HAS THE G 8 SUBMIT IN
NORTHERN IRELAND NEXT WEEK.
MEETING WITH ALLIES LIKE
THE FRENCH THE BRITISH AND
OTHERS.
CONSULTING WITH THEM BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS AND PUBLICLY
TELLING THE WORLD WHAT THE
ARE THE NEXT STEPS.
>> Shepard: OPTIONS HAVE
BEEN DESCRIBED AS
POTENTIALLY ALL BAD.
MIGHT U.S. INTERVENTION
MAKE THINGS WORSE WOULD THE
RUSSIANS JOIN IN ON THE
SIDE OF THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT?
COULD THE CONFLICT EXPAND
ACROSS THE REGION?
JONATHAN HUNT'S REPORT ON
THIS GROWING CRISIS JUST
AHEAD.
FIRST THOUGH THE FEDS MIGHT
HAVE BEEN ABLE TO PREVENT
THE ATTACKS OF 9/11 IF THEY
HAD BEEN COLLECTING
MILLIONS OF PHONE RECORDS
BACK THEN LIKE THEY ARE
NOW.
THAT'S WHAT THE FBI
DIRECTOR ROBERT MUELLER
TOLD CONGRESS TED.
-- TODAY.
HE SAID THEY COULD HAVE
LINKED THE PHONE NUMBER
YEMEN TO ONE OF THE
HIJACKERS BEFORE 9/11.
>> THE OPPORTUNITY WAS NOT
THERE IF WE HAD THAT
PROGRAM THAT OPPORTUNITY
WOULD HAVE BEEN THERE.
>> I'M NOT PERSUADED THAT
THAT MAKES IT OKAY TO
COLLECT EVERY -- EVERY
CALL -- IT'S MY FEAR THAT
WE ARE ON THE VERGE OF
BECOMING A SURVEILLANCE
STATE.
>> Shepard: IT WAS A
BRUISING DAY FOR SECRETARY
MULTI-CULTURAL.
ED SNOWDEN THE FORMER NSA
CONTRACTOR WHO SAYS HE
EXPOSED THE SURVEILLANCE.
HE IS HIDING THOUGHT HONG
KONG AN THREATENING TO
REVEAL WHAT HE SAYS ARE
MORE GOVERNMENT SECRETS.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE WITH
THIS PART OF THE STORY LIVE
FROM D.C. NEWSROOM.
>> ASKED WHETHER ED SNOWDEN
WAS A SPY OR HAD DEFECTED
TO CHINA THE HOUSE
LEADERSHIP LEFT THE DOOR
OPEN.
>> HE HAS ALREADY DONE
SERIOUS HARM.
IS HE ALSO STATING THINGS
THAT ARE JUST CAN DID CANDIDLY
NOT CORRECT.
AND CLEARLY THERE IS --
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE SURE
THAT THERE IS A THOROUGH
SCRUB OF WHAT HE IS
HIS CHINA CONNECTIONS ARE.
IT SEEMS UNUSUAL THAT HE
WOULD BE IN CHINA AND
ASKING FOR PROTECTION OF
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT
GIVING PRESS CONFERENCES TO
CHINESE MEDIA THE CHAIRMAN
OF THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE SAID HE WAS PART
OF THE CHINESE THAT HE
SHOULDN'T HAVE BEEN.
SOURCE TELLS FOX NEWS THAT
STONE'S ELECTRONIC TRAIL
HAS BEEN TRACED TO THE
DOCUMENTS HE ACCESSED AND
THE SYSTEMS.
THE "L.A. TIMES" IS
REPORTING TONIGHT THAT THE
29-YEAR-OLD USED A THUMB
DRIVE TO STORE THE
CLASSIFIED DOCUMENTS.
THUMB DRIVES ARE SUPPOSED
TO BE BANNED ON THESE
SECURE NETWORKS, SHEP.
THEN.
>> Shepard: THERE IS SOME
DEBATE NOW, CATHERINE IT
WOULD SEEM HOW MUCH THIS
SURVEILLANCE WHICH MANY
ARGUE IS UNCONSTITUTIONAL
ON THE FACE OF IT MIGHT
HAVE HELPED WITH.
>> WELL AFTER THE NSA
DIRECTOR TESTIFIED THAT
QUOTE.
DOZENS OF TERRORIST EVENTS
WERE DISRUPTED, DEMOCRATIC
SENATORS RON WHY DEN AND
MARK URDAHL EARLY CRITICS
OF THESE PROGRAMS SAYING
QUOTE:
THE HOUSE IS BACKING UP
ALEXANDER WHO CLAIMS
CONTROVERSIAL DATA
COLLECTION PROGRAMS ARE
PROVIDING PRIMARY
INVESTIGATIVE LEADS.
>> THESE PROGRAMS
AUTHORIZED BY CONGRESS
OVERSEEN BY CONGRESS AND
FEDERAL JUDGES OVERSEEN
WITH INTERNAL CHECKS AND
BALANCES WITHIN THE
EXECUTIVE BRANCH WERE
FOUND TO BE DIRECTLY
EFFECTIVE IN THWARTING
TERRORIST ATTACKS.
>> BUT CRITICS SAY THE
INITIAL CREDIT CRITICAL
NEEDS OF THE NEW YORK CITY
SUBWAY KILLER ZHIZI AND
HEADLEE CAME FROM OVERSEA
AGENCY AND PROGRAMS WERE
SECONDARY.
THEY CONFIRMED THE TIPS.
ALSO AHEAD THE SENATE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
SENATOR DIANNE FEINSTEIN
SAYS A LIST OF PLOTS
DISRUPTED BY THE NSA MAY BE
DECLASSIFIED AS EARLY AS
MONDAY.
ASKED WHETHER A COURT ORDER
IS NEEDED FOR INVESTIGATORS
TO SWIM THROUGH OR SIFT
THROUGH THE PHONE RECORDS
OF MILLIONS OF AMERICANS,
FEINSTEIN SAID NO.
ADDING, YOU JUST NEED COURT
APPROVAL IF YOU WANT TO GET
TO THAT CONTENT, SHEP.
>> Shepard: ALL RIGHT.
CATHERINE, LAWMAKERS HAD
LOTS OF OTHERS QUESTIONS
FOR THE FBI DIRECTOR TODAY.
AS I MENTIONED IT WAS
BRUISING.
QUESTIONS ABOUT THE IRS
INVESTIGATION.
AND WHY THE FEDS CALLED THE
FOX NEWS CORRESPONDENT A
POSSIBLE CRIMINAL.
THAT'S NEXT FROM THE
JOURNALISTS OF FOX NEWS.
ON THIS THURSDAY FOX
REPORT.
DID MY RESEARCH.
MY DOCTOR AND I WENT WITH AXIRON
THE ONLY UNDERARM LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN OR
ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO ARE OR
WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID CONTACT
WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEECTED SIGNS OF PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS AND MEDITIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD INCLUDE
INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER; WORSENING PROSTATE
SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT; ANKLE, FEET
OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARG OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING AND INCREASE
IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT E ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
For all those who sleep
too hot or too cool, and struggle
to sleep comfortably together
now there's a solution.
Introducing Sleep Number DualTemp,the
revolutionary
temperature-balancing layer
with Active Air technology that
works on any mattress, including yours.
Whether you sleep hot or cool,
Sleep Number Dual Temp allows each
of you to
select your ideal temperature.
And it's only at one of our over
400 Sleep Number stores nation wide.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
>> JUST BECAUSE WE CALL
SOMEBODY A POSSIBLE
CRIMINAL DOES NOT MEAN WE
PLAN TO PROSECUTE THE
PERSON.
THAT TODAY FROM THE FBI
DIRECTOR ROBERT MUELLER
TESTIFYING ON CAPITOL HILL
SEARCH REQUEST THAT
REFERRED TO FOX NEWS
CORRESPONDENT JAMES ROSEN
AS A QUOTE POTENTIAL
COCONSPIRATOR IN A LEAK
INVESTIGATION.
DIRECTOR MULTI-CULTURAL
SAID AS FAR AS HE KNOWS
JAMES ROSEN WAS NEVER A
SUSPECT.
>>
>> WHEN YOU AUTHORIZE A
SEARCH WARRANT FOR A TARGET
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION
ISN'T THE PROSECUTION OF
THAT TARGET AN OBJECTIVE?
>> I WOULD SAY NO.
QUITE OFTEN IN SWARNTSZ,
THERE ARE AFFIDAVITS SEARCH
WARRANTS.
PERSON MENTIONED AS HAVING
CULPABILITY.
NO DISCUSSION OR
ANTICIPATION OF
PROSECUTION.
>> Shepard: WHICH IS QUITE
CONVENIENT.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS
JOURNALISTS SHOULD NOT FACE
LEGAL ACTION FOR DOING
THEIR JOBS.
AND THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
ERIC HOLDER HAS MET WITH
NEWS EXECUTIVES TO TALK
ABOUT CHANGING THE
GUIDELINES FOR
INVESTIGATIONS THAT INVOLVE
THE MEDIA MIKE EMANUEL IS
LIVE FOR US ON CAPITOL
HILL.
I GUESS THEY ASKED HIM
TODAY ABOUT THE IRS
INVESTIGATION AS WELL.
>> SHEP, THAT'S BECAUSE
THERE IS A CRIMINAL
INVESTIGATION LOOKING INTO
THE TARGETING OF THOSE
CONSERVATIVE ORGANIZATIONS
BY THE IRS.
SO SOME LEADING LAWMAKERS
WERE LOOKING FOR SOME
ANSWERS FROM THE FBI
DIRECTOR.
>> CAN YOU TELL ME SOME
BASICS?
CAN YOU TELL ME HOW MANY
AGENTS AND INVESTIGATORS
YOU HAVE ASSIGNED TO THE
CASE?
>> MAY BE ABLE TO DO THAT
BUT I HAVE TO GET BACK TO
YOU.
>> YOU CAN TELL ME HOT LEAD
INVESTIGATOR IS.
>> OFF THE TOP OF MY HEAD
NO.
>> THIS IS THE MOST
IMPORTANT ISSUE IN FRONT OF
THE COUNTRY THE LAST SIX
WEEKS YOU DON'T KNOW WHO IS
LEADING UP THE CASE, HOT
LEAD INVESTIGATOR IS.
>> NO, AT THIS JUNCTURE NO
I DO NOT KNOW WHO.
>> MULTI-CULTURAL ADMITTED
NOT HAD A UPDATE ON THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> THAT'S INTERESTING.
TERRORIST ATTACK ON OUTPOST
ON BENGHAZI.
I GUESS THE QUESTION WAS
HOW ABOUT SOME ARRESTS?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND THE POINT WAS CLEARLY
MADE THAT CONGRESS WANTS
THE TERRORISTS HELD
ACCOUNTABLE.
THE FBI DIRECTOR EXPLAINED
SOME THE "NEWSWEEK"
CHALLENGES WITH THIS
INVESTIGATION.
>> THERE IS NO GOVERNMENT
TO HELP US IN LIBYA.
WE DON'T HAVE COLLEAGUES WE
CAN GO TO AND SO IT IS
UNIQUE.
>> BUT YOU ACCESS TO THE
SITE AND ABILITY TO GET
INTO BENGHAZI IF ABSOLUTELY
NECESSARY EITHER YOU OR
AGENTS ON OUR BEHALF?
>> IF ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY
BUT AS T. IS A VERY HOSTILE
TERRITORY AS CAN YOU
UNDERSTAND.
>> THE CONCERN BEING IF THE
BENGHAZI INVESTIGATION NINE
MONTHS LATER HAS STALLED
SHEP.
>> Shepard: MIKE EMANUEL IN
D.C. TONIGHT.
WELL, THIS WAS DIRECTOR
MULTI-CULTURAL'S LAST
SCHEDULED APPEARANCE BEFORE
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY
COMMITTEE.
IS HE SCHEDULED TO LEAVE
THE FBI THIS SEPTEMBER
AFTER 12 YEARS ON THE JOB.
PRESIDENT OBAMA HAS
NOMINATED JAMES COLME TO
TAKE OVER.
HE WAS THE NUMBER TWO
OFFICIAL AT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT UNDER FORMER
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH.
DOZENS OF WORKERS ARE HURT
AND AT LEAST ONE IS DEAD
AFTER AN EXTREMELY LARGE
AND POWERFUL BLAST AT A
CHEMICAL PLANT IN
LOUISIANA.
HAPPENED THIS MORNING.
STARTED A FIRE THERE.
AND THAT BLAST WAS SO
STRONG THAT ONE MAN SAYS
THE GROUND SHOOK AT HIS
HOME SEVERAL MILES AWAY.
HE SAID IT FELT LIKE A
THREE SECOND EARTHQUAKE.
IT HAPPENED IN AN
INDUSTRIAL AREA ABOUT
20 MILES SOUTHEAST OF BATON
ROUGE.
SEVEN FIRE DEPARTMENTS
RESPONDED TO THE SCENE.
AND CREWS JUST STARTED
CLEARING OUT WORKERS AS
FAST AS THEY COULD.
>> THE LATEST NUMBERS ARE
THAT 73 INDIVIDUALS FROM
THE PLANT SITE HAVE BEEN
TAKEN TO A VARIETY OF LOCAL
HOSPITALS.
AS OF NOW WE BELIEVE THAT
EVERY WORKER HAS BEEN
ACCOUNTED FOR.
>> Shepard: GOVERNOR JINDAL
SAID THAT 10 WORKERS STAYED
BEHIND IN A SAFE ROOM AS HE
DESCRIBED IT TO TRY TO SHUT
DOWN THE PLANT'S
OPERATIONS.
THE FACILITY MAKES
PETROLEUM PRODUCTS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY
DON'T YET KNOW WHAT CAUSED
THE EXPLOSION.
THEY ALSO SAY THEY HAVE
BEEN MONITORING THE AIR
QUALITY AND SO FAR IT SEEMS
FINE.
>> A 10-YEAR-OLD GIRL NOW
RECOVERING AFTER LUNG
TRANSPLANT SURGERY.
JUST AHEAD WHAT SARAH'S
FAMILY SAYS ABOUT HER
FUTURE AND WHY SHE STILL
HAS SOME MAJOR OBSTACLES TO
OVERCOME.
BREAKING RIGHT NOW, A
SHERIFF SAYS REMAINS OF TWO
PEOPLE FOUND IN AN AREA
BURNED BY THE WILDFIRE IN
COLORADO SPRINGS, I'M JUST
LEARNING OF THIS.
APPARENTLY THE WILDFIRE HAS
NOW CLAIMED TWO HUMAN
VICTIMS.
THAT'S COMING.
--         WE CHIP AWAY.
AT REDEFINING CAPABILITY.
F WHATEVER DAYS MAY COME.
LIKE BEACH DAYS...
RAINY DAYS...
EVEN VACATION DAYS.
MADE WITH PRIDE.
CRAFTED WITH PASSION.
THIS IS THE NEW 2014   JEEP GRAND
CHEROKEE.
IT IS THE BEST        OF WHAT WE'RE
MADE OF.
WELL-QUALIFIED LESSEES
CAN LEASE THE 2014       GRAND CHEROKEE
REDO 4X4
FOR $359 A MONTH.
>> Shepard: THERE IS
BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
COLORADO.
DEVASTATING AND HISTORIC
WILDFIRE THERE.
THEY JUST TURNED DEADLY.
THE SHERIFF JUST CONFIRMED
THAT TEAMS HAVE FOUND THE
REMAINS OF AT LEAST TWO
PEOPLE IN AN AREA THAT THE
WILDFIRE BURNED NEAR
COLORADO SPRINGS.
ALICIA ACUNA IS THERE RIGHT
AT THE EDGE OF THE
EVACUATION ZONE.
ALICIA?
>> SHEPARD, AND NOW THE
SHERIFF SAYS THIS BECOMES A
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION.
THE CORONER IS NOW ON SCENE
AND WILL TRY TO MAKE AN
IDENTIFICATION.
HERE IS WHAT THE SHERIFF
TOLD US WAS HAPPENING WITH
THESE TWO PEOPLE WHOSE
REMAINS WERE FOUND.
THEY BELIEVED THAT THESE
TWO PEOPLE WERE PACKING UP
AT THE TIME AND TRYING TO
GET OUT OF THE FIRE ZONE.
AND THE REASON THEY SAY
THAT IS THAT ONE OF THESE
FOLK WAS ON THE PHONE WITH
SOMEONE ELSE DISCIPLINING
WHAT THEY WERE DOING.
AND THE PERSON ON THE OTHER
LINE SAID THAT THEY COULD
HEAR A POPPING IN THE
BACKGROUND AND THEN THEY
DIDN'T HEAR ANYTHING ELSE.
SUPPOSEDLY THESE FOLKS ARE
TRYING TO GET OUT OF THIS
AREA.
NOW, WHAT THE SHERIFF
DESCRIBED THIS AREA IT WAS
INTENSELY HOT PLACE WITHIN
THE FIRE, SO THE FIRE IS
ITSELF HOT.
THIS WAS INAT THE BUS
STOPLY HOT AREA.
HE SAID THIS WAS AN AREA
WHERE THE TREES WERE
CROWNING.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS THAT THE
FIRE WAS THEN TRAVELING
VERY QUICKLY ON THE TOPS OF
THE TREES.
SO IF YOU IMAGINE TRYING TO
GET OUT OF THAT AREA, IT
CAN BE ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE IF
YOU ARE DOING THAT TOO
LATE.
IN TERMS OF A FIRE FIGHT,
THEY ARE SAYING IT'S ONLY
5% CONTAINED BUT THEY ARE
DOING THE BEST THEY CAN TO
TAKE ADVANTAGE OF CLOUD
COVER AND SOME THE COOLING
TEMPERATURES AT THIS TIME.
BUT, YES, THIS HAS
DEFINITELY TAKEN A DEADLY
TURN.
AND IT'S VERY DANGEROUS.
THEY HAVE EVACUATED MORE
THAN 38,000 PEOPLE AT THIS
TIME.
AND SO MANY HOMES STILL
HAVE BEEN DESTROYED
SHEPARD?
>> Shepard: UPDATES AS
WARRANTED BACK TO IT ALICIA
ACUNA, THANKS.
A POPULAR NASCAR DRIVER IS
DEAD TONIGHT AFTER HIS CAR
SLAMMED INTO A WALL DURING
A RASSMENTS HIS NAME IS
JASON LEVY LER.
NASCAR FANDZ KNEW HIM AS
LEFT TURN.
IT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT
SPRINT CAR EVENT IN JERSEY.
BASICALLY WE ARE TOLD MINOR
LEAGUES FOR RACING.
EMERGENCY CREWS HAD TO CUT
THE DRIVER FROM THE WRECK.
HE LATER WAS PRONOUNCED
DEAD AT THE HOSPITAL.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT CAUSED.
THIS HE WAS A TWO-TIME
WINNER ON THE NASCAR
NATIONWIDE SERIES.
FELLOW DRIVER TONY STEWART
TODAY CALLED HIM A GREAT
RACER AND AN EVEN BETTER
FRIEND.
AND IN A STATEMENT NASCAR
OFFICIALS SAY HE WAS A
FIERCE COMPETITOR AND THAT
THE RACING WORLD WILL
GREATLY MISS HIM.
MUCH MORE AHEAD ON THE NEW
WHITE HOUSE RESPONSE TO THE
SYRIAN REGIME UNLEASHING
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
WE WILL LOOK AT HOW OUR
MILITARY SUPPORT FOR REBEL
GROUPS HAS WORKED OUT IN
THE PAST.
PLUS THE SUPREME COURT'S
IMPORTANT RULINGS ON YOUR
GENES.
NOT THE ONES YOU WEAR.
AND WHETHER U.S. COMPANIES
CAN PATENT THEM.
PATENT PARTS OF YOUR BODY.
ONE CANCER CAUSING GENE AT
THE CENTER OF THIS CASE LED
ANGELINA JOLIE TO SEEK
SURGERY.
GUESS WHICH TROUBLED
CREWSSHIP IS READY TO SET
SAIL AGAIN?
THE CARNIVAL TRIUMPH BACK
IN PORT.
DON'T YOU WANT TO TAKE HER
OUT FOR A SPIN?
[Old English accent] I DOTH DECLARE
THAT THOU HAVE BROUGHT OVERMANY DISCOUNTS
TO THINE CUSTOMERS!
[Old Engli accent] SAFE DRIVER,
MULTI-CAR, PAID IN FULL --
A MOST FULSOME BOUNTY INDEED LORD
JAMIE.
THOU COMETH AND WE THY SAVETH!
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
WE DOTH OFFER SO MANY DISCOUNTS,
WE HAVE SOME TO SPARE.
OH, YOU HAVE ANY OF THOSE HOMEOWNERS
DISCOUNTS?
HERE WE GO.
THANK YOU.
HE TOOK MY SHIELD, MY LADY.
THESE ARE TROUBLING TIMES IN THE KINGDOM.
MORE DISCOUNTS THAN WE  KNOWETH WHAT
TO DO WITH.
NOW THAT'S PROGRESSIVE.
IT STARTS WITH LITTLE THINGS.  TINY
CHANGES IN THE BRAIN.  LITTLE THINGS
ANYONE CAN DO.
IT STEALS YOUR MEMORIES.  YOUR INDEPENDENCE.
ENSURES SUPPORT  A BREAKTHROUGH.
AND SOONER THAN YOU'D LIKE.
SOONER THAN YOU'D THINK.
YOU DIE FROM  ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
WE CURE ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
EVERY LITTLE CLICK, CALL  OR DONATION
ADDS UP  TO SOMETHING BIG.
AT OD,
WHATEVER BUSINESS YOU'RE IN, THAT'S
THE BUSINESS WE'RE IN.
WITH PREMIUM SERVICE LIKE ONE OF THE
BEST ON-TIME DELIVERY
RECORDS AND A LOW CLAIMS RATIO
WE DO WHATEVER IT TAKES TO MAKE YOUR
BUSINESS OUR BUSINESS.
OD. HELPING THE WORLD KEEP PROMISES.
[ Female Announcer ] DOCTORS    TRUST
CALCIUM PLUS VITAMIN D    TO SUPPORT
STRONG BONES.    AND THE BRAND
MOST RECOMMENDED BY...  MY DOCTOR.
MY GYNECOLOGIST.  MY PHARMACIST.
Citracal.  Citracal.    [ Female Announcer
]    YOU TRUST YOUR DOCTOR.    DOCTORS
TRUST Citracal.
>> Shepard: AT LEAST THREE
PEOPLE ARE DEAD AND MORE
THAN 150 OTHERS HURT AS TWO
COMMUTER TRAINS COLLIDE IN
A CAPITAL CITY.
IT AND THAT TOPS OUR NEWS
AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
>> ARGENTINA, OFFICIALS SAY
ONE OF THOSE DOUBLE-DECKER
TRAINS SLAMMED INTO ANOTHER
THAT HAD STOPPED BETWEEN
TWO STATIONS IN BUENAS AIR
WAS.
NO WORD ON WHY THAT TRAIN
WAS SITTING BETWEEN
STATIONS OR WHY THE OTHER
ONE FAILED TO STOP BEFORE
IMPACT.
AUTHORITIES RUSHED TO THE
SCENE TO PULL SURVIVORS
FROM THE WRECKAGE.
ANOTHER TRAIN CRASHED LAST
YEAR ON THE SAME LINE
KILLING SOME 50 PEOPLE AND
HURTING 700 MORE.
BOLIVIA.
VIOLENCE FILLED THE STREETS
OF A CENTRAL CITY AS
SUPPORTERS OF A FORMER
MAYOR BATTLED POLITICAL
RIVALS.
THE DEMONSTRATORS ARMED
WITH BATS AND FLARES
DEMANDED THE CURRENT MAYOR
STEP DOWN.
RIOT POLICE MADE SEVERAL
ARRESTS.
THE CITY HAS HAD FOUR
MAYORS IN THE PAST YEAR.
CHINA RESCUERS SAVED
DOZENS OF VILLAGERS FROM
HEAVY FLOODING IN THE
NORTHWEST.
STATE MEDIA REPORTS THE
RISING WATER SUBMERGED
ROADS AND CUT OFF SEVERAL
ROADS IN ONE TOWN.
PULLED EVERYBODY TO SAFETY.
NOBODY HURT.
BELGIUM.
WHAT ORGANIZERS CALL THE
WORLD'S LARGEST SAND
SCULPTURE FESTIVAL SET TO
OPEN IN A COASTAL CITY.
PROFESSIONAL ARTISTS USED
20 TONS OF SAND TO CREATE
THE DESIGNS WHICH INCLUDE
DEPICTIONS OF THE MONA
LISA, THE BEATLES, AND THE
MASSIVE ELVIS PRESLEY AND
THAT'S A WRAP ON THIS FOX
TRIP AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
>>
>> Shepard: THE BRAVEST
CREWS PASSENGERS IN THE
HISTORY OF THE WORLD SET
PASSAGE ON THE CARNIVAL
TRIUMPH.
IT LEFT GALVESTON, TEXAS A
SHORT TIME AGO.
THE THING THEY CALLED THE
CRUISE FROM HELL BACK IN
FEBRUARY.
ENGINE POWER KNOCKED OUT
POWER AND LEFT IT STRANDED
IN THE GULF OF MEXICO FOR
DAYS.
THAT LEFT THE THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE ON BOARD WITHOUT
WORKING TOILETS AND IN SOME
CASES EATING COLD ONION
SANDWICHES.
ONE PASSENGER DESCRIBED IT
AS FLOATING CESSPOOL.
WHAT DID IT COST TO GET THE
THING READY TO SALE -- SAIL
AGAIN CARNIVAL SAYS
$115 BILLION.
THE CRUISE BOOKED SOLID
SOMEHOW.
ENYOI NOW.
WOW, I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR TIME FOR THE TOP OF
THE NEWS.
AND THE SYRIAN REGIME OF
THAT MAN HAS USED CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ON OPPOSITION
FIREFIGHTERS -- FIGHTERS
INCLUDING NERVE GAS SAR
WRITTEN.
IT REPORTS U.S.
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
ESTIMATES 150 PEOPLE HAVE
DIED IN SUCH ATTACKS INSIDE
SYRIA.
IT SAYS THAT DATA IS LIKELY
INCOMPLETE.
THE WHITE HOUSE WILL
PROVIDE MILITARY SUPPORT IN
SYRIA.
NO DETAILS.
DOESN'T NECESSARILY MEAN
ARMING THE REBELS.
KEEP IN MIND THE UNITED
NATIONS REPORTS NEARLY
93,000 PEOPLE HAVE DIED
SINCE THE FIGHTING IS SYRIA
BEGAN.
THAT INCLUDES THOUSANDS OF
CHILDREN.
AND OFFICIALS SAY THE
NUMBER IS A CONSERVATIVE
ESTIMATE.
"THE FOX REPORT'S"
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
IS WITH US NOW.
THIS HAS APPARENTLY CHANGED
THE PRESIDENT'S CALCULUS.
>> IT HAS BEEN A LONG TIME
COMING IN THE EYES OF MANY
SHEP.
ALTHOUGH THE DEPUTY
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISOR
BEN RHODES SAID IN A
CONFERENCE CALL TONIGHT
QUOTE:  THERE HAS BEEN AN
URGENCY FOR TWO YEARS.
MR. RHODES ALSO SAID THAT
ESTABLISHING A PIPELINE OF
AIDE TO THE REBELS IS NOT
AN HAS NOT BEEN SIMPLE.
AND THERE HAS ALSO BEEN THE
DIFFICULTY OF IDENTIFYING
THE MODERATE REBEL GROUPS
LISTEN.
IT'S BEEN IMPORTANT TO WORK
THROUGH THEM WHILE AIMING
TO ISOLATE THE MORE
EXTREMIST ELEMENTS OF THE
OPPOSITION SUCH AS AL
NASRA.
WE HAVE THOSE RELATIONSHIPS
AND PIPELINE FLOWING.
WE HAVE SEEN MATERIAL GET
INTO SYRIA INCLUDING TO THE
FMC.
>> THE FMC IS THE SUPREME
MILITARY COUNCIL.
IT'S A 30 MEMBER BODY
ELECTED BY REBEL COMMANDERS
LAST DECEMBER.
AND IF YOU ARE WONDERING
JUST HOW MANY GROUPS ARE
FIGHTING IN SYRIA, THAT --
THOSE REBEL COMMANDERS
NUMBERED SOME 260, SHEP.
REPRESENTING IN EFFECT 260
DIFFERENT REBEL GROUPS.
>> SO THE WHITE HOUSE IS
CONSIDERING MILITARY
SUPPORT.
HELP ME OUT WHAT DOES IT
MEAN?
>> IT CLEARLY LEAVES OPEN
RIGHT NOW A HUGE RANGE OF
OPTIONS.
THIS IS THIS IS HOW FAR THE
SECURITY ADVISOR WAS
WILLING TO GO.
LISTEN.
>> THAT INCLUDES MILITARY
SUPPORT.
I CANNOT DETAIL FOR YOU ALL
OF THE TYPES OF THAT
SUPPORT.
FOR A VARIETY OF REASONS.
BUT, AGAIN SUFFICE IT TO
SAY, THIS IS GOING TO BE
DIFFERENT IN BOTH SCOPE AND
SCALE THE REBELS HAVE BEEN
ASKING FOR MORE
SURFACE-TO-AIR MISSILES.
THOSE ARE THE KIND OF
MISSILES THAT THE PROVIDING
TO THE SOVIET INVASION IN
AFGHANISTAN IN THE 1980S
AND WERE CREDITED WITH
CHANGING THE COURSE OF THAT
CONFLICT ANOTHER OPTION
WOULD BE ESTABLISHING THE
KIND OF NO-FLY ZONE THAT
NATO ENFORCED OVER THE
SKIES OF LIBYA.
ABOUT APPARENTLY ACCORDING
TO OFFICIALS AT THE WHITE
HOUSE AND BEYOND, THERE ARE
NO DECISIONS YET.
THE PRESIDENT WILL AMONG
THE WORLD LEADERS ATTENDING
WILL BE PRESIDENT PUTIN OF
RUSSIA.
HE MAY HAVE SOME VERY
STRONG THOUGHTS ON ANY
PROPOSALS TO DEEPEN U.S.
MILITARY INVOLVEMENT IN HIS
ALLY SYRIA.
SHEP?
>> YEAH, IS HIS INDUSTRY
WOULD SUGGEST.
JONATHAN HUNT WOULD IN.
TWO IMPORTANT ANNOUNCEMENTS
FROM THE THE PRIME MINISTER
OF TURKEY TODAY WHICH
STRIKE DIFFERENT TONES
AFTER VIOLENT AND DEADLY
PROTESTS STARTING UNFOLDING
THERE.
FIRST THE PRIME MINISTER
DELIVERED WHAT HE CALLED A
FINAL WARNING.
TELLING ALL THOSE
DEMONSTRATORS THAT HE AND
OTHER LEADERS HAVE RUN OUT
OF PATIENCE.
THOSE ACTIVISTS THOUGH ARE
STILL CAMPING OUT IN TAX
TAKSIM SQUARE.
THE SENATOR ISTANBUL.
TURKISH STATE MEDIA
REPORTED PARK INTO A MALL.
THAT PLAN FIRST SET OFF ALL
THESE DEMONSTRATIONS.
AT LEAST FIVE PEOPLE
REPORTED DEAD INCLUDING AN
OFFICER SINCE THE PROTEST
BEGAN.
THOUSANDS OF OTHER PEOPLE
SAID TO BE HURT.
DRUG COMPANIES CANNOT
PATENT OUR GENES.
IT'S A BIG LANDMARK
DECISION TODAY FROM THE
UNITED STATES SUPREME
COURT.
THE CASE INVOLVED A COMPANY
THAT PATENTED TWO GENES
WHICH ARE LINKED TO A
WOMAN'S RISK TO DEVELOPING
BREAST CANCER OR OVARIAN
CANCER.
THE ACTRESS ANGELINE NO
JOLIE SAID SHE HAD A DOUBLE
MASTECTOMY AFTER LEARNING
SHE CARRIED ONE OF THOSE
GENES.
AFTER TODAY'S RULING THE
DECIDED GENES ARE PART OF
NATURE.
BECAUSE SCIENTISTS FOUND
THEM DOES NOT MEAN THEY
CREATED THEM OR OWN THEM
SHANNON BREAM COVERS THE
COURT FOR US, SHE IS LIVE
IN WASHINGTON.
SHANNON.
>> MEDICAL RESEARCHERS SAY
WHEN IT COMES TO GENETIC
TESTING TODAY'S OPINION
WILL MAKE A WORLD OF
DIFFERENCE.
THE PLAINTIFFS HAVE ARGUED
THAT THE COMPANY EXCLUSIVE
HOLD ON THE GENE PATENTS
MADE TESTING INCREDIBLY
EXPENSIVE OUT OF REACH FOR
MOST PEOPLE AND PREVENTED
OTHER COMPANIES FROM
DEVELOPING LOWER COST
OPTIONS.
TODAY JUSTICE CLARENCE
THOMPSON WROTE WE WROTE
THAT A NATURALLY OCCURRING
D.N.A. SEGMENT IS A PROCESS
OF NATURE AND NOT PATENT
ELIGIBLE NEARLY BECAUSE
IT'S BEEN ISOLATED.
>> THE SUPREME COURT SENDS
A REALLY IMPORTANT MESSAGE
THAT OUR GENES, PARTS OF
OUR HUMAN BODY CANNOT BE
PATENTED.
THE INFORMATION ABOUT OUR
GENES IS TOO IMPORTANT TO
ALLOW ONE COMPANY TO
CONTROL ALL OF ITS USES.
>> THE JUSTICES DID
HOWEVER HOLD THAT
SYNTHETIC COPIES OF D.N.A.
CREATED IN A LAB ARE NOT
NATURALLY OCCURRING.
SO THEY CAN BE PATENTED.
MYRIAD SAID IT IS HAPPY THE
COURT UPHELD THE PATENTS ON
SYNTHETIC MATERIAL AND IT
REMAINS FOCUSED ON SAVING
AND IMPROVING PEOPLE'S
LIVES.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: SHANNON, STILL
WAITING FOR RULINGS ON
OTHER ISSUES INCLUDING
CASES DEALING WITH SAME SEX
MARRIAGE, AFFIRMATIVE
ACTION AND VOTING RIGHTS.
DECISIONS ARE EXPECTED
WITHIN A MATTER OF WEEKS.
WALL STREET CAME BACK IN A
HUGE WAY TODAY AFTER A
THREE-DAY LOSING STREAK
THE LONGEST OF THE YEAR.
THE DOW CLOSED UP AROUND
180 POINTS.
THE NASDAQ UP IN HIGHER
PERCENTAGE AND THE S&P TOO.
ALL OF THIS AFTER THE
GOVERNMENT RELEASED
POSITIVE REPORTS ON HIRING.
AND RETAIL SALES.
LUNG TRANSPLANT SURGERY WAS
VERY VERY SUCCESSFUL.
FOR THE 10-YEAR-OLD GIRL
NAMED SARAH.
IN HER BATTLE AGAINST THE
DEADLY DISEASE CYSTIC
FIBROSIS, SHE HAS A LEG UP.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM HER
RELATIVES.
YOU WILL HEAR FROM THEM
ABOUT HER NEXT STEPS IN
TREATMENT AND THEIR
OPTIMISTIC OUTLOOK.
PLUS LOOK AT THIS.
THE SAME STORM SYSTEM THAT
HAMMERED THE MIDWEST WITH
RAIN AND HAIL AND FUNNEL
CLOUDS YESTERDAY HAS
BROUGHT SWATTER SPOUTS TO
THE EAST COAST.
WORD OF A TORNADO ON THE
GROUND NEAR WASHINGTON,
D.C.
A LIVE REPORT FROM THE FOX
EXTREME WEATHER CENTER ALL
AHEAD AS FOX REPORTS LIVE
TONIGHT.
OK, I AM COMING.  [ Susan ] I HATE
THAT THE REASON  WE'RE ALWAYS STOPPING
IS BECAUSE I HAVE TO GO  TO THE BATHROOM.
AND WHEN WE'RE SITTING  IN TRAFFIC
I WORRY I'LL HAVE AN ACCIDENT.
BE RIGHT BACK.
SO TODAY, I'M FINALLY  GOING TO TALK
TO MY DOCTOR  ABOUT OVERACTIVE BLADDER
SYMPTOMS.    [ Female Announcer ]
KNOW THAT GOTTA GO FEELING?    ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT    PRESCRIPTION
TOVIAZ.    ONE TOVIAZ PILL A DAY
SIGNIFICANTLY REDUCES   SUDDEN URGES
AND ACCIDENTS    FOR 24 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE CERTAIN    STOMACH PROBLEMS
OR GLAUCOMA    OR CANNOT EMPTY YOUR
BLADDER,    YOU SHOULD NOT TAKE TOVIAZ.
GET EMERGENCY MEDICAL HELP    RIGHT
AWAY    IF YOUR FACE, LIPS,    THROAT
OR TONGUE SWELLS.    TOVIAZ CAN CAUSE
BLURRED    VISION, DIZZINESS, DROWSINESS,
AND DREASED SWEATING.    DO NOT DRIVE,
OPERATE MACHINERY    OR DO UNSAFE
TASKS    UNTIL YOU KNOW HOW TOVIAZ
AFFECTS YOU.    THE MOST COMMON SIDE
EFFECTS    ARE DRY MOUTH AND CONSTIPATION.
[ Susan ]  TODAY, I'M VISITING MY
SON  WITHOUT VISITING  EVERY SINGLE
BATHROOM.    [ Female Announcer ]
TODAY, TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR    ABOUT
TOVIAZ.
For all those who sleep
too hot or too cool, and struggle
to sleep comfortably together
now there's a solution.
Introducing Sleep Number DualTemp,the
revolutionary
temperature-balancing layer
with Active Air technology that
works on any mattress, including yours.
Whether you sleep hot or cool,
Sleep Number Dual Temp allows each
of you to
select your ideal temperature.
And it's only at one of our over
400 Sleep Number stores nation wide.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
>> Shepard: TONIGHT WE'RE
MONITORING THE RECOVERY OF
A LITTLE GIRL WHO GOT A
LUNG TRANSPLANT AND THAT
GIRL'S FAMILY NOW SAYS ARE
A YESTERDAY'S SUCCESSFUL
SURGERY SHE COULD BE
RUNNING THE HALLS IN A
MATTER OF SWEEX.
INCREDIBLE REALLY.
JUST YESTERDAY, 10-YEAR-OLD
SARAH WAS IN A COMA AND
VERY CLOSE TO DEATH
ACCORDING TO HER FAMILY.
THEN A RELATIVE GOT THE
NEWS THEY HAD PRAYED THEY
WOULD HEAR.
A SET OF LUNGS WAS
AVAILABLE.
IT COULD SAVE HER LIFE.
DOCTORS PERFORMED A SIX
HOUR TRANSPLANT SURGERY AND
HER AUNT SAYS SARAH COULD
BE BREATHING ON HER OWN.
>> NOW SHE IS INTUBATED.
SHE HAS BEEN SINCE
SATURDAY.
THEY WILL PROBABLY TAKE
THAT TUBE OUT IN THE NEXT
48 HOURS.
AND SO WE EXPECT HER TO GET
HER FIRST BREATH PRETTY
QUICK HERE.
IT HAPPENS PRETTY FAST.
THEY HAVE GOT THOSE GET
THOSE LUNGS WORKING AS FAST
AS THEY CAN.
>> SARAH HAS CYSTIC
FIBROSIS A GENETIC DISEASE.
TRANSPLANT WAS FRANKLY HER
ONLY HOPE.
THE RULES SAY YOU HAVE TO
BE 12 YEARS OLD TO GET ON
THE TRANSPLANT LIST.
SINCE THERE ARE SO FUEL
CHILD DONORS SARAH'S
PARENTS GOT TO THE JUDGE
AND THE JUDGE BENT THE
RULES SO SHE COULD GET AN
ADULT ORGAN.
THAT LIKELY SAVED THE
LITTLE GIRL'S LIFE.
THE GIRL IS NOT OUT OF
DANGER.
FAR FROM IT.
MORE WITH SOME HURDLES
AHEAD.
>> THERE ARE SHEP.
THE BIGGEST HURDLE IS THE
POSSIBILITY THAT HER BODY
MIGHT REJECT THE DONOR LUNG
AND THAT'S WHY SHE IS ON
MEDICATION TO PREVENT THAT
BUT THIS REALLY WILL BE A
LIFE-LONG PROBLEM FOR
SARAH.
WE SPOKE TO A LUNG
TRANSPLANT SURGEON WHO SAYS
OVER THE YEARS DOCTORS HAVE
GOTTEN VERY GOOD AT
REPLACING VITAL ORGANS BUT
HE ALSO CAUTIONED THAT IN
THESE TYPES OF SURGERIES
SOMETHING ALWAYS COMES UP.
LISTEN.
>> SWELLING OF THE LUNG.
LUNG BEING SLIGHTLY TOO BIG
OR TOO SMALL IN THIS CASE
IT MAY BE A LOWER LOBE
THAT'S PUT IN.
SO THERE HAVE A VARIETY OF
THINGS THAT CAN HAPPEN WITH
THE WAY THAT THE LUNGS ARE
SOWN IN.
THAT'S GETTING TO BE LESS
AND LESS COMMON IT DOES
HAPPEN ESPECIALLY SWHU A
ADVISE MISMATCH LUNG LIKE
THIS.
THAT DOCTOR SAYS WHEN THEY
PULL OUT THE BREATHING TUBE
HE BELIEVES E. BELIEVES
SARAH WILL TAKE FIRST DEEP
BREATH IN A VERY LONG TIME.
SHEP?
>> ANYTHING FROM HEALTH AND
HUMAN SERVICES?
>> YEAH.
THEY DID COMMENT BUT IT WAS
VERY SHORT AND IT DID NOT
MENTION SARAH'S CASE AT
ALL.
IT READS AND I'M QUOTING
HERE.
OUR HEARTS GO OUT TO THE
FAMILIES CARING FOR LOVED
ONES WHO ARE RECEIVING
TRANSPLANTS OR WHO REMAIN
ON THE TRANSPLANT WAITING
LIST.
THIS SERVES AS A REMINDER
ABOUT THE IMPORTANCE OF
ORGAN DONATION.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO REMEMBER
IF THIS WERE UP TO HEALTH
AND HUMAN SERVICES SARAH
WOULD NOT HAVE GOTTEN NEW
LUNGS.
HER FAMILY SAYS THIS IS A
VERY GOOD EXAMPLE FOR OTHER
FAMILIES TO KEEP ON
FIGHTING.
LISTEN.
NEVER LOSE HOPE AND NEVER
GIVE UP.
BE AGGRESSIVE AND LEARN AS
MUCH AS YOU CAN AND MAKE
SURE YOU ARE ON THE RIGHT
LIST AND YOUR DOCTORS ARE
ADVOCATING WITH YOU WITH
THE LUNG REVIEW BOARD
BECAUSE NOW THERE IS A
PROCESS IN PLACE TO DO THAT
HOPEFULLY IT'S NOT TOO
DIFFICULT.
>> Trace: OF COURSE AT
LEAST THE NEXT YEAR KIDS
UNDER 12 WILL BE ELIGIBLE
TO BE ON THAT ADULT DONOR
LIST.
SHEP?
>> CYSTIC FIBROSIS
FOUNDATION REPORTS THAT 150
TO 200 PEOPLE GET LUNG
TRANSPLANTS EACH YEAR AND
MORE THAN HALF OF THEM
SURVIVE FOR FIVE YEARS OR
MORE.
PATIENTS INCLUDING SARAH DO
NOT RUN THE RISK OF HAVING
THEIR NEW LUNGS CLOG UP
BECAUSE THE NEW LUNGS DON'T
CARRY THE DEFECTIVE CYSTIC
FIBROSIS GENE.
THE DISEASE CAN DAMAGE
OTHER PARTS OF THE BODY.
INCLUDING THE PANCREAS AND
THE GUY GEIVE SYSTEM.
IN FEDERAL FLORIDA, THE
JURY IN THE GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN TRIAL WILL STAY
IN ISOLATION AWAY FROM
FAMILY, FRIENDS AND ALL OF
US IN THE MEDIA FOR THE
ENTIRETY OF THE TRIAL.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM THE
JUDGE TODAY WHO PREDICTED
THE PROCEEDINGS WOULD LAST
ROUGHLY TWO TO FOUR WEEKS.
JURY SELECTION IS STILLWAY AND FRANKLY
IT IS
NOT GOING WELL.
ZIMMERMAN PLEADED NOT
GUILTY TO CHARGES OF MURDER
IN THE SECOND DEGREE FOR
THE SHOOTING THAT KILLED
THE UNARMED 17-YEAR-OLD
TRAVON MARTIN.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN SAYS HE
FIRED IN SELF-DEFENSE.
JURORS IN THE TRIAL OF THE
ACCUSED MOB BOSS WHITEY
BULGER TODAY SAW MUCH
YOUNGER VERSION OF THE
REPUTED BOSTON GANGSTER IT
CAME IN THE VIDEO FROM BACK
IN 1980 THAT APPARENTLY
SHOWS BULGER MEETING IN A
GARAGE WITH MEMBERS OF THE
WINTER HILL GANG OF THE
ITALIAN MAFIA.
PROSECUTORS SHOWED THAT
CLIP.
THEY ARE TRYING TO PROVE
THAT BULGER PLAYED A VITAL
ROLE IN THE GANG'S
RACKETEERING ACTIVITY.
HE IS ACCUSED OF TAKING
PART IN 19 MURDERS.
POLICE MAY HAVE CAUGHT A
SERIAL KILLER WITHOUT EVEN
REALIZING.
IT A MAN HAS CONFESSED TO
TWO DOZEN MURDERS.
HIS NAME IS JOSE MARTINEZ.
THE PRIME SUSPECT IN A
DOUBLE MURDER IN 2006.
THEY ARRESTED HIM IN
ARIZONA LAST MONTH AS HE
TRIED TO CROSS THE BORDER
INTO MEXICO.
AFTER INVESTIGATING, POLICE
EXTRADITED HIM TO IT
ALABAMA WHERE HE NOW FACES
CHARGES FOR ANOTHER MURDER
AND THAT'S WHERE
AUTHORITIES SAY HE ADMITTED
HE HAS KILLED SOME 30
PEOPLE ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
INCLUDING THOSE TWO IN
FLORIDA.
OKAY.
FOX WEATHER ALERT NOW.
SEVERE THUNDERSTORMS ARE
THREATENING THE
MID-ATLANTIC AND PARTS OF
THE SOUTHEAST.
DAMAGING WINDS, FLOODING,
POSSIBLE TORNADOES ALL IN
THE FIRST ALERT FORECAST.
THE SAME MASSIVE SYSTEM
HAMMERED THE MIDWEST
YESTERDAY.
IT REPORTEDLY PRODUCED MORE
THAN A DOZEN TWISTERS ALONG
WITH POWERFUL WINDS AND
HEAVY HAIL ACROSS SEVERAL
STATES.
THE STORM LEFT A PATH OF
DESTRUCTION IN PLACES
INCLUDING IOWA, OHIO, AND
NORTHERN ILLINOIS.
CUTTING OFF POWER TO TENS
OF THOUSANDS.
EARLIER TODAY, THE STORM
TRIGGERED WATER SPOUTS OVER
A RIVER IN MARYLAND AS
FOLKS IN D.C. AND BEYOND
BRACED FOR MORE SEVERE
WEATHER.
RICK REICHMUTH IN THE
EXTREME WEATHER CENTER.
AT ONE POINT THEY REPORTED
A TORNADO ON THE GROUND
NEAR D.C.
>> YEAH, THERE WAS.
JUST TO THE NORTH OF D.C.
TO THE SOUTH OF BALTIMORE.
THAT ACTIVITY IS GONE.
TAKE A LOOK THOUGH AT THE
LAST 24 HOURS OF THIS
STORM.
STARTED WITH THOSE BIG
THUNDERSTORMS LAST EVENING
AROUND FOX REPORT.
AND THEN IT BECAME THE
DERECHO THAT MOVED
OVERNIGHT.
CAN YOU SEE THIS BENDING
RIGHT THERE AND ALL OF THE
VERY STRONG WINDS EXITING
THE MID-ATLANTIC THIS
MORNING.
AND THEN A NEW LINE OF
STORMS DEVELOPING ACROSS
THE TENNESSEE VALLEY.
THAT'S THE ONE THAT NOW IS
BRINGING THE THREAT FOR
SOME SEVERE WEATHER --
SEVERE THUNDERSTORM WATCH
BOX.
STILL IN EFFECT UNTIL
AROUND 1:00 IN THE MORNING
HERE IS THAT LINE OF
THUNDERSTORMS MOVES ON
THROUGH.
AND THERE IS ONE TORNADO
WARNING HERE THAT WE'RE
WATCHING JUST TO THE NORTH
IN ATLANTA.
PLACES LIKE ROSEWELL AND
COBB COUNTY FULTON COUNTY
UNDER TORNADO WARNING THERE
NORTHERN SUBURBS.
ALSO WATCHING BIG STORMS
MOVE ACROSS AREAS OF THE
NORTHEAST TOWARDS THE NEW
YORK CITY AREA AND THIS
BATCH HERE IS ABOUT TO MOVE
OVER LONG ISLAND SO SOME
BIG FLOODING CONCERNS
CONTINUED THERE.
SOME SPOTS HAVE SEEN 3 TO A
INCHES OF RAIN ALREADY AND
MAYBE ANOTHER INCH OR SO OF
RAIN.
WE WILL SEE MORE RAIN AS
WELL ACROSS THE
MID-ATLANTIC BEFORE THIS
FINALLY GETS OUT OF HERE.
ABOUT 12 STATES SHEP HAVE
FLASH FLOODING GOING ON OR
FLOOD WATCHES OR WARNINGS
THAT IS DOWN FROM 15.
THAT'S THE GOOD NEWS.
ONCE THIS IS GONE, THIS
WEAK CERTAINLY IMPROVING.
SOUTHEAST BEEN SO HOT.
BRING RELIEF FOR
TEMPERATURES FOR THOSE
PEOPLE.
ALL RIGHT, RICK?
>> Shepard: THANK YOU SIR.
>> YOU BET.
>> HERMINE EXPLODED EARLIER
THIS AFTERNOON NORTH OF
DENVER.
OFFICIALS SUSPECT A NATURAL
GAS LINE CAUTIONED IT.
ONE WITNESS SAYS IT SHOOK
HER ENTIRE APARTMENT
COMPLEX.
DAMAGED TWO HOMES.
SPARKED FIRES.
A FIRE DEPARTMENT
SPOKESWOMAN SAYS PEOPLE IN
BOTH HOUSES HAD EVACUATED
BY THE TIME THE
FIREFIGHTERS GOT THERE
AUTHORITIES SET UP A
SHELTER AT A CHURCH NEARBY
FOR THE VICTIMS.
NOBODY THANKFULLY GOT HURT.
THE GOVERNMENT SURVEILLANCE
CONTROVERSY COULD MEAN BIG
BUSINESS FOR SOME TECH
ENTREPRENEURS.
WE'LL SHOW YOU HOW THE
FOLKS WHO MAKE APPS ARE
TRYING TO CASH IN ON
PROTECTING YOUR PRIVACY AND
ONE THAT JUST MIGHT WORK
OUT WELL FOR YOU.
PLUS, SOMETIMES IT'S BETTER
TO CALL IN THE EXPERTS.
HOW ONE GUY'S BATTLE
AGAINST BED BUGS UGH, PUT
HIM IN THE HOSPITAL.
lets you connect up to 25 devices
on one easy to manage plan.
That means your smartphone her Blackberry
his laptop Mark's smartphone...
But I'm still on vacation...
...stilln the plan. Nice!
So is his tablet, that guy's hotspot,
thentern's tablet.
The intern gets a tablet?
Everyone's devices.
His, hers, oh sorry...
all easier to manage on The Share
Everything Plan
for Small Business.
Connecting more so you can do more.
That's Powerful. Verizon.
Get the Blackberry Q10 for $199.99.
>> Shepard: THE PRESIDENT
SAYS NOBODY IS LISTENING TO
YOUR PHONE CALLS.
HE SAYS THE GOVERNMENT JUST
COLLECTS INFORMATION LIKE
WHO MILLIONS OF AMERICANS
CALL AND HOW LONG THEY
TALK.
BUT IF YOU DON'T WANT TO
TAKE ANY CHANCES, THERE IS
AN APP. FOR THAT.
DAVID LEE MILLER WITH THE
GOOD NEWS.
DAVID LEE?
>> SHEPARD THERE ARE, IN
FACT, MORE THAN A HALF A
DOZEN APPS AVAILABLE ONLINE
SUCH AS SEE CLIFT AND
SILENT CIRCLE THAT SAY THEY
WILL PROTECT YOUR PRIVACY.
THE NEXT TIME YOU USE YOUR
SMART PHONE.
THEY EACH ENCRYPT THE DATA
FROM YOUR PHONE MAKING IT
DIFFICULT IF NOT IMPOSSIBLE
FOR A THIRD PARTY TO LISTEN
IN OR LEARN WHO YOU ARE
CALLING.
SOME OF THE COMPANIES SAY
THEY ARE BASED OUTSIDE THE
U.S. IN ORDER TO BEING
SUBJECT TO U.S. PRIVACY
LAWS AND SUBPOENAS BUT ADD
THEY WILL DO THE RIGHT
THING IF PUBLIC SAFETY IS
AT RISK.
>> THIS IS AN APP. TO
RESTORE PRIVACY RIGHTS TO
THE AVERAGE PERSON.
WE ARE NOT HERE TO HELP
TERRORISTS JUST TO BE VERY
CLEAR.
SO IF A GOVERNMENT COMES TO
US AND SAYS WE NEED HELP,
YOU KNOW, WE WILL COOPERATE
WITH THEM TO THE FULL
EXTENT THAT WE CAN.
>> MOST OF THE INCRYPTION
SERVICES SAY ONCE A CALL IS
FINISHED ALL RELEVANT DATA
IS DESTROYED.
ACCORDING TO ONE PRIVACY
EXPERT THESE APPS DO A GOOD
JOB OF PROTECTING PRIVACY,
FORTUNATELY FOR LAW
ENFORCEMENT THEY NORTH
PERFECT.
>> I THINK WHAT A LOT OF
PEOPLE DON'T REALIZE IS FBI
AND INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES
HAVE A LOT OF CAPABILITY TO
HACK INTO COMPUTER SYSTEMS.
AND THEY CAN USE THAT
ABILITY RIGHT NOW TO
EAVESDROP ON PEOPLE EVEN IF
THEY'RE USING INCRYPTION.
>> SOME OF THESE PRIVACY
APPS DO MORE THAN ENCRYPT
PHONE CALLS.
THEY CAN BE USED FOR
TEXTING, EMAIL AND EVEN
VIDEO CONFERENCING.
SHEPARD?
>> Shepard: DAVID LEE.
THE FEDS ARE NOW ASKING
COMPANIES THAT MAKE MEDICAL
DEVICES TO IMPROVE
SECURITY.
TO GUARD THEIR PRODUCTS
FROM HACKERS.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY WANT TO
PROTECT CONFIDENTIAL
INFORMATION AND PREVENT
MALFUNCTIONS.
THE TOP PROSECUTORS IN NEW
YORK AND SAN FRANCISCO
MAKING A PUSH TO STOP SMART
PHONE THIEVES ACROSS THE
NATION.
THEY ANNOUNCED A NEW
INITIATIVE CALLED SECURE
OUR SMART PHONES.
WHICH THEY SAY WILL INVOLVE
LAW ENFORCEMENT AND
CONSUMER ADVOCATES FOR FOR
MORE THAN A DOZEN STATES.
HERE IS THE DEAL.
THEY SAY THEY WILL PRESSURE
SMART PHONE COMPANIES TO
END THE SECONDARY MARKET IN
STOLEN PHONES AND TO SEEK
THE INDUSTRY WIDE
INTRODUCTION OF A KILL
SWITCH THAT WOULD RENDER
STOLEN PHONES WORTHLESS FOR
GOOD.
SO A GUY SET HIS HOUSE ON
FIRE RIGHT WHILE BATTLING
BED BUGS IN NEW JERSEY,
OBVIOUSLY.
A COUNTY SPOKESWOMAN SAYS
THE GUY WAS TRYING TO GET
RID OF THE PESTS IN THE
SECOND FLOOR BEDROOM USING
A SPACE HEATER A HAIR
DRYER, AND A HEAT GUN.
THAT COMBINATION SPARKED
SOME FLAMES IT APPEARS.
ENVIRONMENTAL PROTECTION
AGENCY OFFICIALS SAY VERY
HIGH SUSTAINED HEAT CAN
KILL BUGS, BUT THEY SAY YOU
ALSO NEED SPECIAL EQUIPMENT
AND YOU SHOULD LEAVE IT TO
THE PROFESSIONALS.
NEWS FLASH.
HIGH HEAT ALSO CAUSE THINGS
TO BURN.
THE NFL IS STEPPING UP
SAFETY MEASURES BUT THIS
TIME IT'S FOCUSING ON THE
FANS.
COMING UP DETAILS ON A
SECURITY CRACKDOWN THAT
LIMITS WHAT YOU CAN BRING
TO THE STADIUM.
THE DETAILS AHEAD.
E THEM THE BASICS, YOU KNOW. I GOT
THIS.
[Thinking] IS IT THAT TIME?  THE SON
PICKS UP THE CHECK?
[Thinking] I'M STILL WORKING.  HE'S
RETIRED.
I HOPE HE'S SAVING.
I HOPE HE SAVED ENOUGH.
WHO MATTERS MOST TO YOU  SAYS THE
MOST ABOUT YOU.
AT MassMutual WE'RE OWNED  BY OUR
POLICYOWNERS,
AND THEY MATTER MOST TO US.
WHETHER YOU'RE JUST STARTING  YOUR
401(k)
OR YOU ARE READY  FOR RETIREMENT
WE'LL HELP YOU GET THERE.
Save big on great gifts
at Bass Pro Shops' Father's Day Sale.
Like World Wide Sportsman Boca Grande
Shorts for under $25.
And the Bass Pro Aluminum Fish Fryer
for under $30.
Plus check out our free Family Summer
Camp.
THE Kyocera Torque  LETS YOU HEAR
AND BE HEARD  EVEN IN STUPID LOUD
PLACES.  TO PROVE IT, WE SET UP  OUR
CALL CENTER RIGHT HERE...  [ chirp
]  ALL GOOD?  [ chirp ]  GETTY UP.
SERIOUSLY,  THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING!
[ cellphone rings ]  HELLO?  IT'S
A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.    [ Male
Announcer ] GET IT DONE  [ chirp ]
WITH THE ULTRAUGGED    ocera Torque
ONLY FROM Sprint   Direct Conct.
BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE    FOR YOUR
BUSINESS.
>> Shepard: GOING TO A
FOOTBALL GAME THIS YEAR
COULD BE A LOT LIKE GOING
TO AN AIRPORT.
MAYBE WORSE.
THE NFL REPORTS IT'S
LIMITING THE SIZE AND TYPE
OF BAGS THAT FANS CAN BRING
TO THE GAME STARTING THIS
SEASON.
OTHER THAN MEDICALLY
NECESSARY ITEMS, ONLY CLEAR
PLASTIC VINYL OR THICK
PLASTIC HANDBAGS WILL BE
ALLOWED BUT NOT BIG ONES,
BANNED ITEMS INCLUDE
COOLERS, BRIEFCASES,
BACKPACKS AND COMPUTER BAGS
AMONG OTHER THINGS.
BASICALLY DON'T BRING ANY
BAGS.
THE LEAGUE CLAIMS THIS WILL
HELP SECURITY AND SPEED UP
ENTRY TO THE STADIUMS.
FOR MY PURPOSES IT WILL
KEEP ME IN FRONT OF MY
TELEVISION SCREEN.
THANK YOU NFL.
COOL CRITTERS NOW.
FIVE CYBERRIAN TIGER CUBS
MAKING THEIR FIRST PUBLIC
APPEARANCE.
WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT THIS
IS A WILDLIFE PARK IN
CHINA.
THE CUBS NICKNAMED THE FIVE
SISTERS BECAUSE AS YOU
MIGHT EXPECT THEY ARE ALL
GIRLS.
GENIUSES.
QUITE RARE FOR FEMALE
QUINTUPLETS.
300 BABY ANIMALS WERE BORN
IN THAT PARK THIS YEAR FROM
MORE THAN 20 DIFFERENT
SPECIES INCLUDING THESE
RING TAILED LEMURS.
CONFIDENCE THAT SYRIA'S
LEADER HAS USED CHEMICAL
WEAPONS AGAINST HIS OWN
PEOPLE.
THE ONE OFFICIAL SAYS THE
U.S. WILL NOW PROVIDE
MILITARY SUPPORT TO THE
OPERATION.
WHAT KIND OF SUPPORT?
WE HAVE NO IDEA.
A SHERIFF IN COLORADO
CONFIRMS THE MOST
DESTRUCTIVE FIRE IN
COLORADO HISTORY HAS NOW
KILLED AT LEAST TWO PEOPLE.
THAT WILDFIRE HAS ALSO
DESTROYED HUNDREDS OF
HOMES.
AND INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY
ARE NOW TRYING TO DETERMINE
WHAT CAUSED AN ENORMOUS
EXPLOSION AT A CHEMICAL
PLANT IN LOUISIANA.
EMERGENCY CREWS SAY THE
BLAST RESULTED IN A FIRE
KILLED A WORKER AND HURT
MORE THAN 70 OTHERS.
AND ON THIS DAY IN THE YEAR
1805, THE EXPLORER MARY
WEATHER LEWIS REACHED THE
GREAT FALLS OF THE MISSOURI
RIVER CONFIRMING HIS
EXPEDITION WITH WILLIAM
CLARK WAS RIGHT ON TRACK
FROM THE MISSISSIPPI RIVER
TO THE PACIFIC OCEAN.
THE TEAM HAD SET OUT THE
PREVIOUS YEAR.
SOME NATIVE AMERICANS HAD
GIVEN THEM VALUABLE
DIRECTIONS TO THE ROCKIE
MOUNTAINS.
THEY TOLD LEWIS AND CLARK
THEY HAD HAD REACHED AN
IMPASSABLE WATER FALL WHEN
THEY NEARED THE ROCKIES.
THE PARTY CONTINUED UP THE
MISSOURI RIVER UNTIL IT
FORKED OFF WITH NO CLUE
WHERE TO GO, LEWIS AND A
FEW OTHERS WENT AHEAD OF
THE PACK IN HOPES OF
FINDING THAT GREAT WATER
FALL.
THEY CHOSE THE RIGHT PATH.
AND EXPLORERS MADE A VITAL
FIND ON THEIR WESTWARD
JOURNEY 208 YEARS AGO
TODAY.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS
FOR THIS THURSDAY JUNE THE
13TH, 2013.
THANK GOD IT'S NOT FRIDAY
THAT WOULD BE TOO MANY 13S.
PROBABLY WOULD HAVE CALLED
IN SICK FOR THAT O'REILLY
WOULD HAVE STEPPED IN AN
HOUR EARLY FOR ME.
BECAUSE THAT'S JUST THE
KIND OF GUY HE IS SHEP,
TAKE IT OFF.
>> I WILL DO IT FOR YOU.
AH.
>> Bill: THE O'REILLY
FACTOR IS ON.
TONIGHT:
>> YOU CAN'T HAVE 100%
SECURITY AND ALSO THEN HAVE
100% PRIVACY.
>> Bill: LAWSUIT LATEST
POLLING SHOWS PRESIDENT
OBAMA LOSING CREDIBILITY
AMONG THE PUBLIC.
DOES HE HAVE A STRATEGY TO
TURN THINGS AROUND AMONG
ALL CONTROVERSIES.
CHARLES KRAUTHAMMER ON
THAT.
>> PAT BUCHANAN AND OF
COURSE O'REILLY.
THESE GUYS ARE HARD RIGHT
WHIPPING GUYS.
THEY LOOK A LOT ALIKE.
BLACK EYE LOOK TO THEM.
>> Bill: SOUNDS VAGUELY
RACIST, DOESN'T IT AS THE
FAR LEFT BECOMES OBAMA
IDOLATRY FALLING APART
LASHING OUT.
WE HAVE ANALYSIS.
>> EWE HAVE ROUGH DAYS FOR
THE FIRST TIME I HAVE FOUND
SOMEONE I'M ABLE