THOSE
PEOPLE WHO ARE INJURED AND
SENDING OUR DEEPEST
CONDOLENCES AND SYMPATHIES.
THOSE PEOPLE WHO WERE HURT
AND WISHING WELL OUR MEN
AND WOMEN OF LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
I HAVE ABSOLUTELY FULL
FAITH AND CONFIDENCE.
>> Bret: MASSACHUSETTS.
FAIR, BALANCED AND
UNAFRAID.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF BREAKING NEWS.
TERROR ATTACK AT THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
A WHITE HOUSE SPOKESMAN
SAYS THE EXPLOSIONS IN
BOSTON ARE QUOTE:  CLEARLY
AN ACT OF TERROR.
NOW, FROM THAT SAME
SPOKESMAN TO LEARN WHETHER
THE PERPETRATORS ARE
DOMESTIC OR FOREIGN AND
WHETHER THOSE PERPETRATORS
ARE MEMBERS OF A TERRORIST
ORGANIZATION.
TO THOSE QUESTIONS AT THIS
MOMENT WE HAVE NO ANSWERS.
RIGHT NOW AWAITING ANOTHER
BRIEFING FROM OFFICIALS IN
BOSTON WITH THE LATEST
INFORMATION.
IT'S SCHEDULED TO BEGIN AT
THIS MOMENT.
WE WILL TAKE YOU THERE WHEN
IT DOES.
HERE'S WHAT WE KNOW RIGHT
NOW.
AT LEAST TWO PEOPLE ARE
CONFIRMED DEAD, 70 HURT
AFTER TWO BOMBS EXPLODED AT
THE FINISH LINE OF THE
BOSTON MARATHON.
ONE WITNESS SAYS HE WATCHED
A TRASH CAN EXPLODE.
HERE IS VIDEO OF THE FIRST
WOMAN AND AND -- BOMB AND
MOMENTS OF CHAOS THAT
FOLLOWED.
[EXPLOSION]
SCREAMING]
>> Shepard: AND ANOTHER
CAMERA CAPTURED THE SCENE
MOMENTS RIGHT AFTER THE
FIRST BLAST ALONG WITH THE
SECOND EXPLOSION.
BOTH BLASTS CAME JUST
BEFORE 3:00 BOSTON TIME.
THE LAST RUNNERS FINISHED
TIME IN THE MARATHON IS
LISTED OFFICIALLY AT
2:57 P.M.
THEN THE SECOND ONE WENT
OFF, JUST DOWN THE STREET
FROM THE FIRST ONE.
POLICE SAY ABOUT 100 YARDS
AWAY.
IT DETONATED APPROXIMATELY
12 TO 14 SECONDS AFTER THE
FIRST.
PEOPLE WHO WERE THERE SAY
THEY HAD NO IDEA EXACTLY
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
>> WE WERE COMING DOWN
BOYLSTON STREET AND
LITERALLY I HEARD A CANNON
GO OFF.
I SAW A WHOLE BUNCH OF
SMOKE.
IT KNOCKED ME TO THE
GROUND, AND THEN, YOU KNOW,
EVERYBODY STARTED RUNNING.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN
EVERYONE, ALL THE RUNNERS
STARTED SAYING RUN.
AND SO ALL OF A SUDDEN
PEOPLE WERE RUNNING AT US.
>> YOU START LOOKING AT ALL
THE INJURIES AND YOU SEE
PEOPLE COMING OUT WITH NO
LEGS.
PEOPLE WERE NO ARMS.
PEOPLE, FACES AND BODIES
COVERED IN BLOOD.
>> Shepard: A SOURCE TELLS
FOX NEWS THAT INVESTIGATORS
IN BOSTON ARE NOW GUARDING
A MAN THEY HAVE CALLED A
PERSON OF INTEREST.
GUARDING THIS PERSON AT A
HOSPITAL.
WE DO NOT KNOW WHICH ONE.
WE'RE TOLD THAT PERSON HAS
SEVERE BURNS BUT
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY
CANNOT DETERMINE WITH
CERTAINTY WHETHER HE WAS A
VICTIM OR AN ATTACKER.
AGAIN, AT THIS MOMENT, A
PERSON OF INTEREST IN A
HOSPITAL.
AND POLICE SAY NOBODY HAS
BEEN IDENTIFIED AS A
SUSPECT.
IN THE LAST HOUR, PRESIDENT
OBAMA SAID THE COUNTRY WILL
FIND OUT WHO DID THIS.
AND HOLD THEM ACCOUNTABLE.
HERE IS ANOTHER ANGLE OF
THE FIRST EXPLOSION.
CAN YOU SEE ONE RUN ARER
FALL AS THE SMOKE FILLED
INTO THE AIR.
BOSTON POLICE SAY THERE WAS
ALSO A FIRE AT JFK LIBRARY
IN THE DOOR CHESTER
NEIGHBORHOOD.
POLICE NOW SAY AS OF THIS
MOMENT THERE IS NO EVIDENCE
TO CONNECT IT TO THE
BOMBINGS.
THEY THINK IT WAS A FIRE,
UNRELATED.
THEY ARE STILL
INVESTIGATING.
NOBODY WAS HURT THAT -- IN
THAT FIRE.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE MAP OF
THE AREA NOW SO YOU CAN GET
A SENSE OF WHAT HAPPENED.
THE BLASTS 200 FEET APART.
TWIN EXPLOSIONS ON
PATRIOT'S DAY IN BOSTON
WHEN PEOPLE WERE RUNNING
THE MARATHON, FAMILIES AND
FRIENDS CHEERING THEM ON.
THOUSANDS PACKING THE
STREETS ON A HOLIDAY THERE.
AND IN AN INSTANT
EVERYTHING CHANGED.
"THE FOX REPORT'S"
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
WAS ON AIR WITH US WHEN
THIS HAPPENED AND HAS THE
LATEST INFORMATION FROM OUR
NEWSROOM.
JONATHAN?
>> SHEP, FIRST THE TIMING
OF THIS.
THE LAST RUNNERS ACTUALLY
WERE RECORDED CROSSING THE
FINISH LINE AT 2:57 EASTERN
TIME THAT GIVES YOU A
PRETTY ACCURATE PICTURE OF
EXACTLY WHEN THOSE TWO
EXPLOSIONS RIPPED THROUGH
THE SCENE.
ONE FIRST, THEN ANOTHER.
ABOUT 14 SECONDS APART BY
OUR COUNT AS WE LISTENED TO
THE EXPLOSIONS ON THE VIDEO
THAT YOU SAW.
NOW, IT APPEARS ACCORDING
TO ALL THE EXPERTS THAT
THEY WERE ON SOME SORT OF
TIMER DEVICE.
NOW IT COULD HAVE BEEN A
TIMER ATTACHED TO EACH OF
THOSE EXPLOSIVE DEVICES BUT
MORE LIKELY, ACCORDING TO
THE EXPERTS I SPOKEN TO
THEY WERE REMOTELY
DETONATED, POSSIBLY USING
CELL PHONES.
THAT IS WHY WE WERE TOLD AT
THE TIME THAT CELL PHONE
TRAFFIC HAD BEEN SHUTDOWN.
ALTHOUGH A COUPLE OF THE
CELL PHONE COMPANIES SAID
THAT THEY WERE NOT
REQUESTED TO DO SO.
BUT IT APPEARED TO A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT CELL PHONES HAD
BEEN BLOCKED.
THERE WAS NOT A LOT OF
STRUCTURAL DAMAGE.
THESE WERE NOT HUGE DEVICES
IN THAT SENSE.
BUT THEY WERE CLEARLY ABLE
TO DO A LOT OF DAMAGE TO
THE PEOPLE MANY OF THEM
GATHERED THERE.
THIS WAS THE FOUR HOUR MARK
OF THE MARATHON.
THAT'S A TYPICALLY BUSY
TIME AT THE FINISH LINE,
AND THERE WERE A LOT OF
PEOPLE STILL CROWDED AROUND
THE FINISH LINE.
SPECTATORS AND THOSE WHO
HAD ALREADY COMPLETED THE
RACE AND WERE SIMPLY
WAITING FOR FRIENDS OR
RELATIVES TO COME IN.
WE HAVE HAD SOME WORD THAT
THE BOMBS MAY HAVE BEEN
PACKED WITH BALL BEARINGS.
THAT IS ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT DOES A GREAT DEAL OF
DAMAGE TO HUMAN FLESH.
THAT WOULD BE WHY WE ARE
HEARING THE REPORTS OF
HORRIFIC INJURIES,
INCLUDING MANY PEOPLE
LOSING THEIR LIMBS.
SO NOW THE INVESTIGATION
BEGINS.
THERE ARE THREE BASIC
QUESTIONS HERE.
WHO DID IT, HOW THEY DID
IT WHY THEY DID IT.
BUT WHAT WE KNOW FOR SURE,
SHEP, AS YOU LOOK AT THE
SCENE OF THE EXPLOSIONS
AGAIN IS TWO EXPLOSIONS,
TWO PEOPLE DEAD, MORE THAN
100 WOUNDED.
AMONG THEM, CHILDREN WHO
HAD BEEN TAKEN BY THEIR
PARENTS TO SEE A SUPPORTING
EVENT ON THIS HOLIDAY IN
BOSTON SHEP.
>> Shepard: JONATHAN WHDH
TELEVISION, CHANNEL 7, THE
NBC STATION IN BOSTON IS
REPORTING THAT AMONG THE
TWO CONFIRMED DEAD IS AN
8-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
WE CAN'T INDEPENDENTLY
CONFIRM THIS AND WE HAVEN'T
LEARNED TOO MUCH ABOUT THE
REST OF THE VICTIMS.
>> YEAH.
WE CAN'T INDEPENDENTLY
CONFIRM THAT, SHEP.
WE HAD HEARD THAT REPORT.
WE ARE ALSO SEEING REPORTS
FROM SOME OF THE LOCAL
MEDIA THERE.
THAT THE CHILDREN'S
HOSPITAL IN BOSTON
CURRENTLY HAS SEVEN
PATIENTS IT IS TREATING
FROM THIS.
WE DON'T KNOW THE EXTENT OF
THEIR INJURIES.
THERE ARE REPORTS OF
CHILDREN AT SOME OF THE
OTHER HOSPITALS INVOLVED
HERE.
AS I SAY A TOTAL, WE ARE
TOLD, OF SOMETHING LIKE 105
PEOPLE TAKEN TO THE LOCAL
HOSPITALS AS A RESULT OF
THIS WHICH JUST SHOWS YOU
THE FORCE OF THOSE
EXPLOSIONS AND WHATEVER
SHRAPNEL THEY WERE PACKED
WITH RIPPING THROUGH
EVERYBODY WHO WAS CROWDED
IN THAT AREA AT THAT TIME.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: I DON'T KNOW
THAN, I MENTIONED AT THE
TOP OF THIS NEWSCAST WE ARE
WAITING FOR A BRIEFING FROM
OFFICIALS IN BOSTON.
AS YOU CAN SEE THAT'S THE
PODIUM WHERE THEY WILL BE
SPEAKING.
IT WAS SCHEDULED TO BEGIN
AT 7:00.
SO JUST ABOUT SEVEN MINUTES
AGO NOW.
AND WE ARE EXPECTING THAT
SHOULD BEGIN SHORTLY.
IN THE MEANTIME, JONATHAN,
THE OBVIOUS BECAME CLEAR
THIS AFTERNOON WHEN THESE
WERE SEPARATE EXPLOSIONS
WHEN WE KNEW THEY WERE
DEVICES THAT THIS WAS WHAT
AUTHORITIES IN THE WHITE
HOUSE IS NOW CALLING A
TERROR ATTACK.
THE QUESTION IS, WHO AND
WITH WHAT MOTIVE AS YOU
JUST SAID.
WE DON'T YET HAVE ANSWERS
TO ANY OF THAT.
BUT SPECULATION HAS BEEN
RAMPANT BUT NOTHING FIRM AT
ALL.
>> NO, ABSOLUTELY NOTHING
FIRM WHATSOEVER.
AND THERE ARE THESE REPORTS
THAT A PERSON OF INTEREST
MAY BE BEING GUARDED BY THE
BOSTON POLICE DEPARTMENT IN
ONE OF THE HOSPITALS.
WE DO NOT HAVE INDEPENDENT
CONFIRMATION OF WHO THIS
PERSON MIGHT BE.
OR EVEN WHETHER IT IS A MAN
OR A WOMAN AT THIS POINT.
BUT, OBVIOUSLY THE
INVESTIGATION ALREADY IN
HIGH GEAR.
EVERY LAW ENFORCEMENT
AGENCY INVOLVED RIGHT NOW.
THEY ARE LOOKING FOR
ANSWERS.
WHAT THEY WILL BE DOING
FIRST IS LOOKING AT THE
EXPLOSIVE DEVICES.
THEY WILL BE TAKING THEM
APART, SEEING HOW THEY WERE
PUT TOGETHER, WITH WHAT
MATERIALS THEY WERE PUT
TOGETHER.
THAT WILL GIVE
INVESTIGATORS A LOT OF
CLUES.
REMEMBER, WHEN THEY LOOK AT
THESE THINGS, THEY TEND TO
SEE WHAT THEY CALL A
SIGNATURE OF A BOMB MAKER.
THAT WILL LEAD THEM IN ONE
DIRECTION.
WE'LL FIND OUT IN GOOD
TIME SHEP.
>> Shepard: JONATHAN, THANK
YOU.
WE WILL BE BACK TO YOU AS
NEWS WARRANTS.
CATHERINE HERITAGE WORKS
INTELLIGENCE FOR US AND
LIVE IN OUR D.C. BUREAU.
IT'S MY STANDING THERE ARE
NO CREDIBLE CLAIMS OF
RESPONSIBILITY HERE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE HAVE BEEN IN TOUCH WITH
VARIOUS GROUPS SHEP.
THEY MAKE IT THEIR BUSINESS
TO MONITOR THESE EXTREMIST
WEB SITES AND SO FAR THERE
HAS BEEN NO CLAIM OF
RESPONSIBILITY FOR WHAT'S
HAPPENED IN BOSTON.
JONATHAN, THOUGH, IS
TOUCHING ON AN IMPORTANT
POINT BECAUSE THE FORENSIC
INFORMATION, THIS BOSTON
MARATHON IS NOW A CRIME
SCENE.
AND I'M TOLD THE FBI
FOCUSES VERY MUCH ON TAKING
THE RESIDUE FROM THESE
DEVICES, IDENTIFYING THE
EXPLOSIVES, THEN FINDING
THE ORIGIN OF THOSE
EXPLOSIVES AND THEN LOOKING
FOR THAT BOMB MAKER'S
SIGNATURE.
EACH ONE OF THESE BOMB
MAKERS MAKES THESE DEVICES
IN A CERTAIN WAY.
THE TYPE OF DETONATOR.
AND THEN SPECIFICALLY
WHETHER THERE WAS SHRAPNEL.
A SHORT TIME AGO WE HEARD
FROM THE HEAD OF THE HOUSE
HOMELAND SECURITY COMMITTEE
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN MIKE
MCCALL WHO CONFIRMED THAT
HE IS GETTING REPORTS THAT
THE DEVICES CONTAINED BALL
BEARINGS, SO SHRAPNEL.
THAT IS A CRITICAL MARKER
HERE.
THE OTHER THING I WOULD
DRAW YOUR ATTENTION TO IS
THE FACT THAT THE
EXPLOSIONS WERE NEARLY
SIMULTANEOUS AND ABOUT 50
TO 100 YARDS APART.
WHAT HAS THE INTENTION OF
AT LEAST ONE SOURCE WHO IS
FOLLOWING THE INVESTIGATION
IS THAT IT IS A STANDARD
PRACTICE TO HAVE THAT
INITIAL EXPLOSION WITH THE
IDEA THAT YOU WILL DRIVE
THE PUBLIC TOWARDS THE
SECONDARY SITE WHICH IS, IN
FACT, A LARGER DEVICE SO
THAT CAN MAXIMIZE THE
CASUALTIES IN AN EVENT LIKE
THIS.
THIS IS WHY PEOPLE ARE
DISCUSSING THIS AS AN ACT
OF TERRORISM FIRST
PRIVATELY AND NOW MORE
PUBLICLY WITH
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS.
A FINAL POINT WE JUST HAD
CONFIRMATION IN THE LAST
FEW MINUTES THAT THE FBI
AS WELL AS THE NCTC, THIS
IS THE NATIONAL COUNTER
TERRORISM CENTER, THIS IS
THE GROUP THAT WAS CREATED
AFTER 9/11 TO MONITOR
THREATS AGAINST THE UNITED
STATES WILL BE BRIEFING
MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE AS
EARLY AS TOMORROW.
SO WHAT THAT TIMING TELLS
YOU, SHEP FROM MY
EXPERIENCE, IS THAT THIS
THING IS REALLY ON FIRE,
THIS IS A PRESSING ACTIVE
INVESTIGATION.
IF THEIR GONNA HAVE
HEARINGS ON THE HILL AS
EARLY AS TOMORROW MORNING
SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE, JUST
FOR CLARITY, IS IT PROPER
TO SAY THAT IN THE EARLY
GOING, FROM YOUR REPORTING
WE DON'T KNOW WHETHER THIS
WAS SOME SORT OF TERRORIST
ORGANIZATION --
>> -- THAT'S CORRECT.
>> Shepard: WEATHER --
WHETHER IT WAS ONE PERSON
WITH A BEEF WITH A LOCAL
ISSUE IN BOSTON.
FRANKLY AT THIS MOMENT WE
KNOW THERE WAS AN ACT OF
TERROR BECAUSE WE CAN LOOK
IT UP IN THE DICTIONARY AND
THIS FITS THE DEFINITION
BUT WE DON'T KNOW WHETHER
QUOTE TERRORISTS WERE
INVOLVED.
>> THE DEFINITION OF
TERRORISM IS AN ACT OF
VIOLENCE TO PROMOTE A
POLITICAL END.
WHAT IS NOT CLEAR IS THAT
IS IT AN INDIVIDUAL?
IS IT A SMALL CELL OF
INDIVIDUALS?
ARE THEY DOMESTIC?
OR IS THERE AN
INTERNATIONAL COMPONENT?
BUT WHEN YOU HAVE
SIMULTANEOUS ATTACKS THEY
MEET THAT THRESHOLD
DEFINITION OF TERRORISM.
SO YOU ARE CORRECT.
>> Shepard: EARLIER,
CATHERINE, AS THIS WAS
BREAKING.
WE TALKED ABOUT WHETHER
THERE HAD BEEN UNUSUAL
SIGNS OF SPECIFIC QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHETHER THE BOSTON
MARATHON MIGHT BE A TARGET.
AT THE TIME, THE ANSWER WAS
NO, THERE HADN'T BEEN.
IS THAT STILL THE CASE?
>> THAT IS STILL THE CASE.
I HAVE SPOKEN TO A HALF
DOZEN PEOPLE SHEPARD WHO
WORK THIS ISSUE ON CAPITOL
HILL OR THEY ARE IN FEDERAL
LAW ENFORCEMENT AND THE
SENSE I HAD FROM EVERY
CONVERSATION IS THAT THERE
WAS NOTHING SPECIFIC OR
CREDIBLE AT LEAST INITIALLY
THEY WERE SAYING TO ME THAT
THERE WAS A THREAT TO THE
BOSTON MARATHON.
HOWEVER, ONE OF THE THINGS
THAT'S HAPPENING RIGHT NOW
IS THEY ARE GOING BACK TO
THAT THREAD INFORMATION TO
SEE IF SOMETHING HAD BEEN
MISSED.
BUT, AGAIN, YOU HAVE THE
SENSE THAT PEOPLE WERE
SOMEWHAT BLINDSIDED BY WHAT
HAPPENED IN BOSTON TODAY
SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: ALL RIGHT,
CATHERINE.
WHEN YOU SAY BLINDSIDED,
SOMETIMES WHEN THEY ARE
BLINDSIDED, THAT COULD MEAN
THAT THIS ISN'T SOME BIG
GRAND -- THIS COULD BE A
COUPLE OF FOLKS OR A PERSON
WITH A BACKPACK OR TWO.
>> UM-HUH.
I DON'T WANT TO GET INTO
BECAUSE WE DON'T HAVE THIS
INFORMATION YET WHETHER WE
KNOW THE INDIVIDUAL OR
INDIVIDUAL'S ASSOCIATION.
BUT TO SPEAK MORE BROADLY
ONE WITH OF THE ISSUES THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY HAS
BEEN WRESTLING WITH,
ESPECIALLY IN THE LAST TWO
TO THREE YEARS IS THE
EMERGENCE OF WHAT THEY CALL
THE INDIVIDUAL ACTOR OR
SMALL CELLS.
THE PROBLEM WITH THAT IS
THAT IT IS VERY HARD TO
INTERCEPT COMMUNICATIONS.
THEY DON'T NECESSARILY USE
THE TRADITIONAL METHODS OF
TALKING TO EACH OTHER
WHICH HAS ALLOWED US TO
INTERCEPT OR TO BLOCK THESES OF EVENTS
IN THE
PAST.
SO, I DON'T WANT TO GO DOWN
ONE ROAD AS TO A SPECIFIC
GROUP.
BUT THIS HAS BEEN SEEN AS
THE EMERGING THREAT.
THE INDIVIDUAL OR SMALL
CELL WHICH IS VERY HARD TO
INFILTRATE BY LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
IN THIS CASE THE FBI
SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE
HERRIDGE, OUR INTELLIGENCE
CORRESPONDENT LIVE IN
WASHINGTON.
WE WILL BE BACK TO HER AS
EVENTS WARRANT.
ON THE LEFT-HAND SIDE OF
YOUR SCREEN THE WESTIN
HOTEL ADVERTISEMENT THERE
IS ACTUALLY THE SCENE OF A
NEWS CONFERENCE WHICH WILL
HAPPEN CLEARLY AT THE
WESTIN AT COPLY PLACE IN
BOSTON WHICH FRANKLY ISN'T
FAR FROM THE SPOT WHERE ALL
OF THIS HAPPENED.
AUTHORITIES WERE TO BRIEF
US 13 MINUTES AGO.
THAT'S BEEN DISPLAYED FOR A
FEW MINUTES.
ALL I CAN TELL YOU IS WE
WILL TAKE YOU THERE WHEN IT
STARTS.
JOE DEFAZZIO WAS WORKING ON
COMMUNICATIONS AT THE RACE
AND WAS WORKING ON IT WHEN
THE EXPLOSION HAPPENED
THERE WAS ONE AS WE
REPORTED AND ANOTHER WHAT
APPEARED TO HIM TO BE THE
SAME INTENSITY.
SIR, IT'S NICE TO SPEAK
WITH YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> HI, SHEPARD, HOW ARE
YOU?
>> Shepard: I'M DOING
PRETTY WELL.
I'M CURIOUS THOUGH ABOUT
WHAT THAT SCENE WAS LIKE IN
THE SECONDS BETWEEN AND IN
THE SECONDS AFTER THE
SECOND.
>> OH, IT WAS JUST -- THIS
IS A UNIQUE BOSTON EVENT
MARATHON, RED SOX GAME UP
THE STREET.
AND WENT FROM A GREAT I DO
HORRIFIC DAY IN MOMENTS TO
BE HONEST WITH YOU.
I WAS 20 YARDS AWAY FROM
WHERE THE FIRST EXPLOSION
WENT OFF WAITING FOR
FRIENDS OF MINE.
LOOKING FOR THEM.
YOU HEARD THE FIRST
EXPLOSION.
IT SOUNDED LIKE A CANNON
WENT OFF.
I THOUGHT MAYBE, YOU KNOW,
BEING PATRIOT'S DAY I
THOUGHT MAYBE SOMEONE FIRED
A MUSKET AND I SAW THE
PLUME OF SMOKE AND I KNEW
SOMETHING WAS UP.
I THOUGHT MAYBE IT'S A GAS
EXPLOSION AND THEN MAYBE, I
DON'T KNOW, 10 TO 12
SECONDS LATER THE OTHER
EXPLOSION HAPPENED.
I KNEW -- YOU KNOW, I KNEW
IT WASN'T -- I KIND OF HAD
AN IDEA IT WAS A TERRORIST
ACT AT THAT POINT.
>> Shepard: JOE, WE WERE IN
THE MIDDLE OF "STUDIO B"
WHEN THIS HAPPENED THIS
AFTERNOON AND THE FIRST
VIDEO CAME IN.
WE SAW THE KIND OF PICTURES
THAT PEOPLE CAN FIND ON THE
INTERNET NOW.
BUT TO WHICH WE ARE NOT
GOING TO SUBJECT FAMILIES
AT FAMILY HOUR.
BUT I READ WITH INTEREST
YOUR DESCRIPTION OF WHAT
YOU WERE SEEING, THE
SPECIFICS THEREOF OF THOSE
WOUNDED.
IT SEEMS TO ME TO ELIMINATE
THAT FROM OUR REPORTING NOW
THOUGH WE WON'T SHOW THE
PICTURES WOULD DO
DISSERVICE TO THE FACTS.
I WONDER IF YOU WOULD TELL
US WHAT YOU WITNESSED.
>> WELL, WHEN THE INCIDENT
HAPPENED, YOU KNOW, A CREW
OF US WORKING AND I WAS THE
ONLY ONE THAT WAS OUTSIDE.
I RACED BACK TOWARDS THE
PUBLIC LIBRARY WHERE WE HAD
ALL OUR EQUIPMENT TO MAKE
SURE THAT THE GUYS WERE
OKAY.
AND THE POLICE RUSHING US
OUT OF THE LIBRARY BECAUSE
THEY THOUGHT THERE MIGHT BE
A DEVICE INSIDE THE
LIBRARY.
AND I LOOKED ACROSS THE
STREET AT THAT POINT AND IT
WAS JUST -- THE SIDEWALK
WAS, AGAIN WAS LIKE A SEA
OF BLOOD.
AND, I HUNG AROUND FOR A
FEW MOMENTS TO SEE IF I
COULD DO ANYTHING.
AND THE PROBLEM WAS HE --
THEY COULDN'T GET ANY
VEHICLES IN THERE BECAUSE
IT WAS COMPLETELY BLOCKED
OFF AS IT USUALLY IS
BECAUSE OF THE MASS OF
RUNNERS.
>> Shepard: THAT'S WHY WE
SAW SOME PEOPLE BEING
WHEELED AROUND IN
WHEELCHAIRS WITHOUT
AMBULANCES.
>> CORRECT.
THE RECOVERY TENT, WHICH
WAS, YOU KNOW, ABOUT MAYBE
100 YARDS DOWN THE ROAD,
YOU KNOW, USED AS A
RECOVERY TENT AND BEING
USED AS ALMOST A MAKESHIFT
HOSPITAL AND THEY COULDN'T
GET VEHICLES IN THERE.
SO IN ORDER TO TRANSPORT
PEOPLE THAT WAS INJURED TO
GET THEM OUT OF THE AREA
THEY HAD TO, EXACTLY USE
THE WHEELCHAIR THAT THEY
USUALLY USE FOR RUNNERS
THAT ARE SUFFERING FROM
FATIGUE OR WHATEVER I MEAN,
YOU KNOW, JUST HORRIFIC
INJURIES.
MOST OF THEM WERE LOWER
BODY INJURIES TO BE HONEST
WITH YOU I DON'T KNOW WHAT
SHRAPNEL WAS THERE BUT IT
WAS AN UGLY SCENE.
>> YOU KNOW, IT WAS OUR
SENSE IN WATCHING THIS THAT
THERE WERE A LOT OF PEOPLE
TRYING TO RISE ABOVE AND
GIVE A HAND THERE AT THE
TIME.
IT WAS REMARKABLE TO WATCH.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I DID
THAT IT WAS ALMOST LIKE AN
OUT-OF-BODY EXPERIENCE.
STUFF HAPPENS ALL OVER THE
WORLD AND YOU DON'T EXPECT
IT TO HAPPEN IN A CITY LIKE
BOSTON.
BUT IT CAN.
A GUY CAN JUST WALK DOWN
THE STREET AND PUT A
BACKPACK AND TRASH BARREL
AND BEFORE YOU KNOW IT AN
ENTIRE REGION IS JUST
BROUGHT TO GRIPS.
IT'S PRETTY SAD.
>> IT WAS CONFIRMED TO ADD
TO YOUR POINT WHAT WE HAVE
KNOWN TO THIS MOMENT IF YOU
GET ON TO GET ON A SUBWAY
IN BOSTON OR YOU ARE ON A
BUSY STREET CORNER YOU KNOW
SECURITY IS TIGHT AND THEY
ARE DOING WHAT THEY CAN DO.
IF SOMEBODY WANTS TO GET ON
THE SIX TRAIN IN NEW YORK
CITY WITH A BACKPACK ON
THEY CAN ALL DOO THAT WE
HAVE BEEN THANKFUL ALL
THESE YEARS SINCE THE
TERRORIST ATTACK ON OUR
NATION BEEN THANKFUL IT
HASN'T HAPPENED.
TODAY IT HAS.
WE KNEW IT COULD AND NOW IT
HAS.
>> NO QUESTION.
IT'S BEEN 12 YEARS AND I
THINK WE ALL LET OUR GUARD
DOWN TO A CERTAIN EXTENT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW, -- COUPLE
YEARS NOW DOING WHAT I
WORK FOR AND THERE IS A
HIGH POLICE PRESENCE THERE.
IT JUST DOESN'T MATTER.
IF DOESN'T NOTICE THAT
PERSON DOING WHAT THEY ARE
DOING, YOU KNOW, IT'S
ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE, LIKE
FINDING A NEEDLE IN THE HAY
STACK.
>> Shepard: JOE DIFAZIO
WORKS
WORKS IN WAKEFIELD
MASSACHUSETTS.
JUST A FEW FEET FROM THE
EXPLOSION WHEN IT HAPPENED.
HELLO TO YOUR FAMILY AND
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Shepard: WFXT BOSTON.
FOX 25 IS OUR LOCAL STATION
THERE, THEIR REPORTER
CRYSTAL HAINES IS AT THE
BEACON HILLS SECTION OF
BOSTON WITH MORE.
CRYSTAL, WHAT DO WE KNOW,
IF ANYTHING MORE ABOUT THE
POSSIBLE VICTIMS HERE?
>> WELL, WE ARE GETTING A
LOT OF UNCONFIRMED REPORTS.
WE DO KNOW AT LAST COUNT WE
ARE AT ROUGHLY 98 PEOPLE
RATHER THAT WERE ACTUALLY
INJURED, TWO KILLED.
OF THE TWO KILLED THE
"BOSTON GLOBE" IS REPORTING
ONE OF THEM IS AN
8-YEAR-OLD LITTLE BOY.
CERTAINLY VERY SAD
SITUATION HERE HISTORIC
EVENT IN BOSTON.
>> Shepard: LOOKING AT THE
AREA BEHIND YOU ON THIS
LIVE SHOT, I KNOW A LITTLE
BIT OF THAT AREA, NOT WELL.
BUT THIS TIME OF NIGHT
NORMALLY, THERE WOULD BE A
LOT OF PEOPLE OUT
ESPECIALLY ON PATRIOT'S
DAY.
THE MAYOR ASKED EVERYBODY
TO STAY HOME IT KIND OF
LOOKS LIKE WITH THIS
SNAPSHOT THEY HAVE DONE
THAT.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
YOU KNOW, MARATHON MONDAY
IN THE CITY OF BOSTON.
IT'S PACKED WITH PEOPLE,
WHETHER THEY ARE FROM OUT
OF TOWN, FROM IN TOWN.
THAT'S TRUE.
WE ARE HEARING ABOUT THE
15-BLOCK AREA AROUND COP
COP-LEY PLACE.
SHUT DOWN.
WE ARE HEARING UP TO 24
HOURS.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WHEN THEY
HEARD THIS EXPLOSION, WHEN
THEY WERE NEAR THIS
EXPLOSION, THEY PANICKED.
THEY DROPPED EVERYTHING IN
THEIR ARMS AND RAN TO
SAFETY.
AND NOW BOSTON POLICE,
FEDERAL OFFICIALS AND STATE
OFFICIALS, THEY ARE
ACTUALLY INSPECTING THOSE
PACKAGES TO MAKE SURE THEY
ARE NOT SUSPICIOUS.
>> Shepard: CRYSTAL HAINES
FOR FOX 25.
CRYSTAL THANKS VERY MUCH.
FIRST RESPONDERS SCRAMBLED
TO GET TO THE SCENE OF THIS
HORROR.
AS THEY DID, IMAGINE
THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE AROUND THE FINISH
LIBRARY AT THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
THE BARRICADES ARE UP.
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT TO MOVE
AROUND AT ALL.
SECURITY IS EXTREMELY
TIGHT.
THERE IS NO WAY REALLY TO
GET VEHICLES IN AND OUT OF
THERE, AT LEAST IN THE
EARLY GOING.
SO THEY ENDED UP USING
WHEELCHAIRS.
BUT PEOPLE BEGAN MAKING
PHONE CALLS AND CALLING 911
DESCRIBING WHAT THEY ARE
SEEING AND ASKING FOR HELP.
AND WE'LL HAVE THAT FOR YOU
IN JUST A MOMENT.
ABOUT AN HOUR AGO THE
PRESIDENT SPOKE OF THIS
TRAGEDY AND THE
INVESTIGATION.
LISTEN.
>> WE STILL DO NOT KNOW WHO
DID THIS OR WHY.
AND PEOPLE SHOULDN'T JUMP
TO CONCLUSIONS BEFORE WE
HAVE ALL THE FACTS.
BUT, MAKE NO MISTAKE, WE
WILL GET TO THE BOTTOM OF
THIS.
AND WE WILL FIND OUT WHO
DID THIS.
WE'LL FIND OUT WHY THEY DID
THIS.
ANY RESPONSIBLE
INDIVIDUALS, ANY
RESPONSIBLE GROUPS WILL
FEEL THE FULL WEIGHT OF
JUSTICE.
TODAY IS A HOLIDAY IN
MASSACHUSETTS.
PATRIOT'S DAY.
IT'S A DAY THAT CELEBRATES
THE FREE AND FIERCELY
INDEPENDENT SPIRIT THAT
THIS GREAT AMERICAN CITY OF
BOSTON HAS REFLECTED FROM
THE EARLIEST DAYS OF OUR
NATION.
DRAWS THE WORLD TO BOSTON
STREETS IN THE SPIRIT OF
FRIENDLY COMPETITION.
BOSTON IS A TOUGH AND
RESILIENT TOWN.
SO ARE ITS PEOPLE.
I'M EXTREMELY CONFIDENT
THAT BOSTONIANS WILL PULL
TOGETHER, TAKE CARE OF EACH
OTHER, AND MOVE FORWARD AS
ONE PROUD CITY AND AS THEY
DO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE WILL
BE WITH THEM EVERY SINGLE
STEP OF THE WAY.
>> Shepard: THE WHITE HOUSE
SAYS THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN
IN TOUCH WITH FEDERAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS AND
LEADERS IN MASSACHUSETTS
OVER THE PAST FEW HOURS.
ED HENRY IS OUR CHIEF WHITE
HOUSE CORRESPONDENT AND IS
LIVE FOR US THERE TONIGHT.
ED?
>> YES.
QUEENK SHEP.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS WHEN YOU
HEARD THE IT THE SPEAKING
THERE VOWING THAT JUSTICE
WILL BE BROUGHT TO THIS
INVESTIGATION AS IT IT
UNFOLDS THERE HE DID NOT
USE AND THAT IS THE WORLD
THAI.
THE WHITEHOUSE TONIGHT DOES
BELIEVE THIS IS THAT I
REMEMBER WHEN MULTIPLE
GITIONS GO OFF THAT'S AN    AN
ACT OF TERRORISM.
THE PRESIDENT DELIBERATELY
DID NOT USE THAT WORD IN
HIS REMARKS IN THE PRESS
BRIEFING ROOM BECAUSE HE
DOES NOT WANT TO GET AHEAD
OF THE FACTS.
THEY REALIZE INSIDE THE
WHITE HOUSE I'M TOLD BY
AIDES THEY MAY FACE
CRITICISM ESPECIALLY
DANCING AROUND THE WAR
TERROR AND THAT BENGHAZI
INVESTIGATION LAST
SEPTEMBER BECAUSE YOU HAVE
LAWMAKERS AND THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN PARTY LIKE
DIANNE FEINSTEIN OUT SAYING
THIS IS TERRORISM.
SHE IS USING THAT WORD.
THEY SAY INSIDE THE WHITE
HOUSE, LOOK, THEY STILL
DON'T KNOW IN THESE EARLY
STAGES WHETHER IT WAS A
FOREIGN GROUP OR SOMEONE
LIKE AL QAEDA BEHIND THIS
OR WHETHER IT IS TERRORISM.
IT WAS TERRORISM
NONETHELESS.
WHAT WE KNOW THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF HAS BEEN DOING TO
STAY ON TOP OF THIS
INVESTIGATION WAS HE WAS ON
THE PHONE EARLIER WITH
WHITE HOUSE DIRECTOR ROBERT
MURIEL.
THE WHITE HOUSE PUT OUT A
PHOTO OF THAT YOU SEE NEW
PLAYERS.
ROBERT McDID YOU KNOWNA.
LISA MONACO IS THE
PRESIDENT'S NEW HOMELAND
SECURITY VOFER.
LET'S REMEMBER THERE IS A
WHOLE NEW NATIONAL SECURITY
TEAM HERE AT THE SECOND
TERM DEFENSE SECRETARY
HAGEL.
SECRETARY OF STATE KERRY.
JOHN BRENNAN WAS THE
HOMELAND SECURITY ADVISOR.
NOW THE CIA DIRECTOR.
THEY ARE ALL BEING TESTED
TONIGHT.
NOT JUST OVER THIS
INVESTIGATION THE WHITE
HOUSE COULD BE A TARGET.
THAT IS WHY DON'T WE HAVE
PICTURES AS WELL OF YELLOW
TAPE THAT WAS PUT EARLIER
AROUND THE PERIMETER OF THE
WHITE HOUSE TO EXPAND THE
PERIMETER BEYOND THAT
NORMAL FENCE THAT'S OUT
THERE TO MAKE SURE TOURS
AND OTHERS DON'T GET ANY
CLOSER TO THE WHITE HOUSE.
THEY JUST SORT OF MADE A
LARGER PERIMETER OF WHYER
CIRCUMFERENCE AS YOU CAN
SEE.
THERE ARE UNIFORMED SECRET
SERVICE OFFICERS WHO HAVE
BEEN OUT THERE.
I LOOKED OVER AND THEY ARE
STILL OUT THERE SEVERAL
HOURS AFTER THESE
EXPLOSIONS GOING OFF IN
BOSTON.
JUST AS PRECAUTIONARY
MEASURES BUT THEY ARE ON
HIGHER GUARD.
>> PRECAUTIONARY MEASURES
HERE IN NEW YORK CITY AS
WELL.
IS IT YOUR SENSE THAT THIS
THIS NIGHT IS JUST
BEGINNING THERE.
>> YES.
>> Shepard: WE WILL HEAR
MORE FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
ITSELF?
>> I DON'T THINK WE WILL
HEAR FROM WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS PUBLICLY.
YOU ARE RIGHT THAT IT'S
DOUBTFUL THE PRESIDENT
WOULD COME OUT A SECOND
TIME UNLESS THERE WAS SOME
DRAMATIC DEVELOPMENT.
I THINK THEY ARE CONTENT
TONIGHT TO LETTED
INVESTIGATION GO FORWARD.
LET PEOPLE AROUND BOSTON
AND THE WORLD TO GRIEVE
TONIGHT.
WE HEARD THE PRESIDENT SAY
THAT THE ENTIRE NATION IS
PRAYING TONIGHT FOR BOSTON.
THAT IS FOR SURE,
OBVIOUSLY.
BUT IN TERMS OF WHAT IS
HAPPENING HERE, YES THEY
WILL BE TELLING ME THE
QUARTERBACK OF THIS
INVESTIGATION COORDINATING
IT INSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE
AGAINST COORDINATING THE
FACT THAT YOU HAVE GOT THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT AND THE
FBI INVOLVED AND THE
DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND
SECURITY ON THE FEDERAL
LEVEL NOT TO MENTION THE
FACT THAT YOU HAVE HAVE
FEDERAL AND STATE LAW
ENFORCEMENT AS WELL.
THIS IS A MASSIVE
INVESTIGATION.
AND THE LAST THING THE
WHITE HOUSE WANTS TO DO IS
INTERFERE WITH THAT THEY
WANT TO COORDINATE AS WELL
AS THEY CAN TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THIS NUMBER ONE
AND, NUMBER TWO, GET PEOPLE
IN BOSTON AS MUCH RELIEF
AND HELP FEDERAL
ASSISTANCE AS THEY CAN
SHEP.
>> Shepard: ED HENRY AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
ED, WE'LL COME BACK TO YOU
AS UPDATES WARRANT
THROUGHOUT THE NIGHT.
WE NOW KNOW MEMBERS OF THE
MILITARY ARE NOW INVOLVED
IN THIS INVESTIGATION.
THIS IS BREAKING NOW.
JONATHAN HUNT WITH THIS
INFORMATION FROM THE
NEWSROOM.
>> THE NAVY SENDING ONE OF
ITS BOMB DISPOSAL UNITS TO
ASSIST LOCAL AUTHORITIES IN
BOSTON.
IT'S EXPROPOSAL ORDINANCE
GOBLE TEAM NEWPORT RHODE
ISLAND.
THEY ARE ON THEIR WAY.
WHAT WE ARE HEARING FROM
BOSTON THEY WANT TO NOW GO
THE ENTIRE LENGTH OF THE
MARATHON ROUTE 26.2 MILES
TO CHECK OUT EVERY SINGLE
PACKAGE THAT HAS BEEN LEFT
ON THE SECRETS AROUND
BOSTON.
WE HAVE ALREADY BEEN TOLD
THAT THEY MAY HAVE FOUND
SEVERAL UNEXPLODED DEVICES
A COUPLE OF THOSE, ONE
REPORT SAYS THREE
UNEXPLODED DEVICES HAVE
BEEN FOUND.
NOW, IF THAT IS TRUE
OBVIOUSLY, THAT WILL BE A
TREASURE TROVE OF
INFORMATION FOR
INVESTIGATORS.
BUT THERE ARE GOING TO BE
SO MANY REPORTS OF SO MANY
SUSPICIOUS DEVICES IN THE
HOURS AND PERHAPS DAYS TO
COME THAT THE LOCAL
AUTHORITIES NEED ALL THE
HELP THEY CAN GET SO THE
U.S. NAVY AS I SAY NOW
SENDING A BOMB DISPOSAL
UNIT TO BOSTON TO HELP
LOCAL AUTHORITIES THERE.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: JONATHAN, THE
OFFICIAL NUMBERS ARE AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE SCREEN AND
HAVE BEEN THROUGHOUT THE
AFTERNOON AND EVENING.
THOUGH THE FINE NEWS
ORGANIZATION IN BOSTON AND
ASSOCIATED PRESS ARE WELL
AHEAD OF THIS.
THE A.P. HAS 100.
BOSTON.COM OR THE BOSTON
HERALD -- I MEAN THE
"BOSTON GLOBE," I'M SORRY
IS AT 115 WITH TWO DEAD.
I'M NOT SURE WE'RE POSITIVE
YET OF EXACTLY HOW MANY
INJURED AND OTHERWISE WE
HAVE.
BUT I'M NOT SURE IT'S
COMPLETELY RELEVANT AT THE
MOMENT ANYWAY.
>> NO.
IT SEEMS TO BE WE ARE IN
THE REGION OF 100 INJURED
IN THIS.
I THINK THAT'S PROBABLY THE
SAFEST WAY TO PUT IT RIGHT
NOW, SHEP.
ONCE YOU GET TO THE LOWER
END OF INJURIES, NOT EVERY
ONE ACCOUNTED BY SOME
ORGANIZATION.
THAT'S WHY YOU MIGHT GET
SOME DISCREPANCY 98 AND
SEEING UP TO 115,000.
IN TERMS OF THE DEAD, WE
HAVE TWO CONFIRMED AND THE
TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE NEWS
TONIGHT THAT WE ARE GETTING
IS THAT ONE OF THOSE
CONFIRMED DEAD IS AN
8-YEAR-OLD BOY SHEP.
WE HAVE ALSO HEARD THAT THE
YOUNGEST VICTIM INJURED IN
THIS WAS A 3-YEAR-OLD.
JUST KIDS WHO AS I WAS
SAYING EARLIER WERE TAKEN
BY THEIR PARENTS TO SEE
WHAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE A
JOYFUL SPORTING EVENT ON A
HOLIDAY IN BOSTON.
A BEAUTIFUL DAY IN BOSTON
AND THIS AS YOU SEE THERE
WAS THE TRAGIC SCENE THAT
WE ENDED UP WITH.
CHILDREN ABOUT HALF A DOZEN
WE ARE HEARING AT THE
MOMENT AMONGS INJURED AS I
SAY ONE 8-YEAR-OLD BOY
CONFIRMED DEAD TONIGHT
SHEP.
>> Shepard: JONATHAN, THANK
YOU.
WE WILL BE BACK TO YOU
SHORTLY.
TO CLEAR UP SOME OF WHAT
HAPPENED TODAY AND GIVE YOU
COMPLEX.
THESE HAPPENED A FEW
SECONDS APART AND THEN A
LITTLE MORE THAN 1 HOUR AND
20 MINUTES LATER THERE WAS
THIS FIRE AND SOMETHING
THAT WENT BOOM AT THE JFK
LIBRARY IN THE DOOR CHESTER
SECTION.
WE HAVE MORE CLARITY ON
THAT NOW.
WE HAVE MORE SPECIFICS.
FIRST OF ALL EVERYBODY WAS
FINE THERE.
THE FIRE STARTED ACTUALLY
JUST AFTER 3:00 P.M.
SO JUST MINUTES LATER
FRANKLY.
IN THE VICINITY OF H HAVE
BUILDING OPENED IN 2011
THAT HOUSES OFFICES IN THE
CLASSROOM AND THE REST.
THERE WAS A FIRE.
PEOPLE THERE SOUNDED LIKE
AN EXPLOSION SO WE REPORTED
THIS AS AN EVENT AND NOT
KNOWING WHETHER WE COULD
TIE THE TWO TOGETHER.
AUTHORITIES INITIALLY CAME
OUT AND SAID NO DEFINITELY
NOT TIE TIED TOGETHER BUT
NOW THEY ARE INVESTIGATING
THAT FOR NOW THIS IS AN
ISOLATED EVENT.
IT'S HALF PAST 7:00 IN
BOSTON.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS FOX NEWS CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF THE ATTACK ON
BEAN TOWN.
WE ARE STILL AWAITING THE
NEWS CONFERENCE FROM
OFFICIALS THERE WITH AN
UPDATE ON THE INVESTIGATION
OF THE AFTERMATH OF TODAY'S
TWIN EXPLOSION.
THAT NEWS CONFERENCE WAS
SCHEDULED TO BEGIN A HALF
HOUR AGO.
OFFICIALS HAVE POSTPONED
IT.
WE ARE EXPECTING IT WILL
COME FROM ANY TIME OF
COURSE WE HAVE LIVE
COVERAGE.
TWO PEOPLE CONFIRMED DEAD
AND REPORTS ON THE NUMBER
ISSUED CONTINUE.
SOMEWHERE AROUND 100 PEOPLE
AFTER TWO EXPLOSIONS AT THE
FINISH LINE OF THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
THE WHITE HOUSE, OF COURSE
HAS CALLED THIS AN ACT OF
TERROR.
A SENIOR OFFICIAL SAYS WE
STILL DO NOT KNOW WHETHER
THOSE RESPONSIBLE ARE
FOREIGNERS OR FROM HERE IN
THE UNITED STATES.
WHETHER THEY ARE MEMBERS OF
THE TERRORIST ORGANIZATION
OR LONE WOLVES.
THEY FRANKLY AT THIS MOMENT
DO NOT KNOW WITH ANY
CERTAINTY.
MOLLY LINE, OUR NEW ENGLAND
BASED, BOSTON BASED
CORRESPONDENT AT THE SCENE
OF THE CRIME NOW.
MOLLY, WHAT ARE YOU SEEING
THERE?
>> SHEP, WE'RE IN COLUMBUS
AVENUE.
THIS IS A MAJOR THOROUGH
FARE HERE IN BOSTON HERE IN
THE CITY.
YOU CAN SEE AMBULANCES LINE
UP ALL THE WAY DOWN THIS
STREET.
WE ARE REALLY JUST AROUND
THE CORNER FROM WHERE THESE
EXPLOSIONS OCCURRED ON
BOYLSTON STREET THAT WHAT
SHOULD HAVE BEEN A JOYFUL
END.
THE ELITE RUNNERS HAD
FINISHED WITH THEIR RUN AND
THESE WERE REALLY THE
CHARITY RUNNERS THE FAMILY
MEMBERS, STILL TREMENDOUS
AMOUNT OF RUNNERS HAD YET
TO CROSS THE FINISH LINE
WHEN THESE EXPLOSIONS
OCCURRED SOME 5,000 BEAM
YET TO FINISH THE RACE.
THE FINISH LINE WAS REALLY
PACKED WITH FAMILY MEMBERS
KIDS, PEOPLE WAITING FOR
THEIR LOVED ONES TO CROSS
THE FINISH LINE.
OVER 100 PEOPLE INJURED AT
LEAST TWO SERIOUSLY.
TWO PEOPLE KILLED.
SOME OF THE INJURIES BEING
REPORTED BY LOCAL HOSPITALS
INCLUDE AMPUTATIONS OF ARMS
AND LEGS AND LIMBS.
SHRAPNEL WOUNDS.
A LOFTD WOUNDS TO EARDRUMS.
PEOPLE COMPLAINING ABOUT
BEING UNABLE HEAR AFTER
THIS INCIDENT.
PRETTY SIGNIFICANT INJURY
HERE IN THE STREETS OF
BOSTON TODAY FROM THIS
EVENT.
AND THE HOSPITALS IN THE
AREA ARE STILL TRYING TO
WRAP THEIR ARMS AROUND THIS
AND WE ARE GETTING
DIFFERENT NUMBERS FROM
DIFFERENT HOSPITALS AS TO
JUST HOW SERIOUS THE
INJURIES ARE.
YET TO HEAR ANYMORE AS FAR
AS FATALITIES ARE
CONCERNED.
WE'RE STILL WAITING ON THAT
THROUGHOUT THE DAY AS WE
EXPECT A LOT OF PEOPLE WILL
BE IN SURGERY AS WE ARE
WAITING TO HEAR MORE ABOUT
THEIR INJURIES.
WE'RE STILL WAITING ON
YACHT DATE FROM
INVESTIGATION AS TO MORE
INFORMATION.
THINGS ARE STILL LOCKED
DOWN HERE.
BLOCKS IN ALL DIRECTION
AROUND THIS SCENE.
THAT'S WHERE IT IS EXPECTED
TO STAY.
THE STREETS ARE EXPECTED TO
BE COMPLETELY BLOCKED OFF.
IT'S QUIETED DOWN
CONSIDERABLY.
WE ARE STILL SEEING PEOPLE,
MARATHON RUNNERS IN THE
AREA, JUST A FEW.
THE BOSTON COMMON WHICH IS
VERY CLOSE ALSO TO WHERE
THE RACE ENDS HERE IN
BOSTON.
IT'S BEING USED AS STAGING
GROUND.
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT OF
MILITARY PERSONNEL STAGED
OVER THERE.
AND REALLY THE STREETS ARE
JUST BEGINNING TO CLEAR.
PEOPLE ARE BEGINNING TO
HEAD FOR THE AIRPORT AND
WORKING ON GETTING HOME TO
THEIR VARIOUS RESIDENCES.
HOTELS IN THE AREA REMAIN
LOCKED COUNSEL AND THE
PEOPLE HERE IN BOSTON, THE
AUTHORITIES, THE MAYOR AND
GOVERNOR ASKING PEOPLE TO
STAY INSIDE TONIGHT.
TO ESSENTIALLY STAY OFF THE
STREETS.
THIS IS BEING LOOKED AT AS
AN ONGOING EVENT AND
AUTHORITIES WANT TO ENSURE
THAT EVERYONE IS SAFE AND
THEY DON'T WANT ANYBODY OUT
ON THE STREETS IF THERE
CONTINUES TO BE GLARNG.
>> Shepard: GOING THROUGH
VIDEO FROM SURVEILLANCE
CAMERAS TRYING TO FIND
CLUES ANYBODY THEY CAN SEE
ON THOSE VIDEO HE VIDEOS
NEEDS TO BE TALKED TO.
HAVE THEY SECRETARY OF
DEFENSE ANYTHING BEBB?
R. THAT?
>> THEY SAID THERE ARE
POLICE OFFICERS HEADED TO
ALL VARIOUS HOSPITALS ALL
ACROSS THE CITY OF BOSTON.
NOT JUST FOR SAFETY SAKE
BECAUSE THEY WANT TO ENSURE
THAT ALL OF THE VICTIMS ARE
SAFE, BUT THEY WANT TO TALK
TO PEOPLE THAT WERE
WITNESSES.
PEOPLE THAT WERE RIGHT
THERE WHEN THIS OCCURRED TO
SEE WHAT THEY SAW AND TO
TRY TO GATHERING
INFORMATION.
WHILE MANY TRAUMATIC EVENT
MANY PEOPLE SERIOUSLY
INJURED BUT ASK WHAT
WITNESSES SAW.
SO THERE ARE INVESTIGATORS
OUT AT ALL THESE VARIOUS
HOSPITALS TRYING TO GLEAN
INFORMATION FROM FOLKS WHAT
THEY CAN.
UNDERSTAND WHETHERABLY A LOT OF
PEOPLE IN SHOCK RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: MOLLY LINE, OUR
BOSTON CORRESPONDENT LIVE
FROM BOSTON.
WE HAVE BEEN SEEING VIDEO
OF THE EXPLOSION GIVING US
TIME LINE HOW THIS WENT
DOWN.
FIRST YOU WILL SEE THE
FIRST EXPLOSION RIGHT BY
THE GRANDSTANDS AT THE
FINISH LINE AND THE BLAST
KNOCKING PEOPLE ASIDE AND
BLOWING THE FLAGS AND THERE
IT IS FROM ANOTHER ANGLE.
AND THEN 12 TO 14 SECONDS
LATER, YOU'LL BE ABLE TO
SEE THE SMOKE IN THE
DISTANCE.
OFFICIALS SAY THAT THIS IS
BETWEEN THE TWO BLASTS WAS
ABOUT THE LENGTH OF A
FOOTBALL FIELD.
WE'RE ALSO GETTING THE
DISPATCH RECORDINGS FROM
THE SCENE.
THE POLICE DISPATCH AS THE
FIRST DESCRIBE THE HORROR.
>> UNITS STAY OFF THE AIR.
JUST MAKE YOUR WAY OVER
THERE ALL UNITS STAY OFF
THE AIR AND MAKE YOUR WAY
OVER THERE.
>> OKAY.
COPY THAT.
>> I ONLY WANT TO HEAR FROM
THE 984.
I ONLY WANT TO HEAR FROM.
[MULTIPLE PEOPLE TALKING.
>> THIS IS WHAT I NEED.
I WANT ALL ROADS CLEARED IN
OR OUT.
OKAY?
I WANT THAT ROAD --
>> OKAY.
MULTIPLE PEOPLE DOWN HERE,
OKAY?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE CAUSE
IS.
STAND BY.
>> HAVE THE BOMB SQUAD CALL
ME IMMEDIATELY 5449,
IMMEDIATELY.
>> BOMB SQUAD MONITORING.
>> WE HAVE UNATTENDED
BACKPACK AT BOYLSTON AND WE
NEED TO SET UP A PERIMETER
TO GET PEOPLE AWAY FROM IT.
>> WE ARE GOING TO GET THE
VICTIMS OUT.
WE WILL CONDUCT A SWEEP
WITH MAKE SURE THERE ARE NO
OTHER DEVICES ON THE
STREET.
WE WILL GET PEOPLE OUT OF
THE RESTAURANTS AND BARS.
>> Shepard: THAT IS HOW IT
ALL WENT DOWN WITH THE
FINAL WORD OF EXACTLY HOW
THINGS WERE GOING TO
PROCEED.
HANG WITH ME.
THOSE RECORDINGS WERE FROM
POLICE DISPATCH CHANNELS
AND WHEN IT FIRST BECAME
CLEAR THAT RESPONDERS WERE
DEALING WITH AN ACT OF
TERROR.
THEY HAD BEEN THROUGH
NUMEROUS DRILLS TO THEY
TELL US TO PREPARE FOR THIS
SORT OF THING.
SO FOR THOSE FIRST
RESPONDERS AND THE REST,
THIS WAS PART OF A ROUTINE
THAT HAS COME THROUGH THE
DRILLS.
WE SPOKE WITH PEOPLE AT
HOSPITALS TODAY WITH
DOCTORS AND ADMINISTRATORS
AT HOSPITALS AS SOME OF THE
FINEST HOSPITALS IN THE
NATION OBVIOUSLY BEGAN TO
TAKE THE INJURED.
DOCTORS SPOKE WITH US LIVE
THIS AFTERNOON ON
TELEVISION EXPLAINING WE
KNEW WHAT WOULD GO DOWN.
WE EXPECTED THESE SORTS OF
THINGS.
WE WERE READY FOR THIS.
IN FACT, AT MASS GENERAL.
BOSTON'S MASS GENERAL
HOSPITAL THEY SAID THEY
WERE READY FOR MORE WOUNDED
THAT THE OPERATING ROOMS
WERE KEPT OPEN THAT THIS
WENT ACCORDING TO PLAN FROM
THE TERROR DRILLS THAT HAD
TAKEN PLACE IN THE WAKE OF
THE ATTACKS ON OUR COUNTRY
AND OTHERWISE.
FOR THE BOSTON MARATHON
THEY HAD PREPARED WELL WITH
THE HOSPITALS AND EMERGENCY
MANAGERS.
THEY GOT PEOPLE TO THOSE
HOSPITALS WHICH WE HOPE
WILL RESULT IN VERY FEW
NUMBERS OF LOSS OF LIFE.
OF COURSE, IF IT'S SOMEONE
YOU KNOW, THE NUMBER IS
ALREADY WAY TOO HIGH.
OF COURSE, THE DEADLY
TERROR ATTACK THERE IN
BOSTON IS RAISING CONCERNS
ABOUT SECURITY ACROSS THE
NATION.
AND LOCAL AUTHORITIES ARE
PREPARING AND HAVE ALREADY
BEGUN TO RAISE SECURITY.
WILY IS A FORMER DIRECTOR
FOR THE NATIONAL THREATS ON
THE NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
HE IS THE PRESIDENT UNDER
PRESIDENT CLINTON AND
GEORGE W. BUSH AND HE IS
WITH US NOW ON THE PHONE.
LEE, FOLKS LIKE YOU ARE
BUSY RIGHT NOW.
>> YES, GOOD EVENING SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHERE ARE WE IN
THE PROCESS?
>> WELL, OBVIOUSLY THE
FIRST STEP IS TO CARE FOR
THE INJURED AND TO CARE FOR
THEIR FAMILIES OF THE
CASUALTY TODAY.
AND THE SECOND STEP IS TO
TURN TOWARDS THE
INVESTIGATION AND FIGURE
OUT WHO IS RESPONSIBLE.
>> Shepard: IT'S MY
STANDING FROM SECURITY
TYPES THAT THERE ARE
SIGNATURES THAT THEY WILL
KNOW QUICKLY IF THEY DON'T
ALREADY WHETHER THIS IS
SOME ORGANIZED GROUP WHO
DOES THIS FOR A LIVING OR
SOMETHING HIS.
>> RIGHT.
I MEAN, I THINK HA THERE IS
SOME INDICATIONS THAT THERE
IS PROBABLY MORE THAN ONE I
HAD INDIVIDUAL BECAUSE OF
MULTIPLICITY OF GUYS THE
FACT THAT THEY HAD TO BE
PLACED AT DIFFERENT
LOCATIONS THAT REQUIRED
SOME COORDINATION.
WHO ARE THEY?
ARE THEY PURELY DOMESTIC?
ARE THEY DOE MESS STWIK
INTERNATIONAL COMPONENT?
OR IS IT SOMETHING ELSE?
ORGANIZED INTERNATIONAL
ATTACK?
I THINK THE CHANCES OF THAT
LAST POSSIBILITY ARE
PROBABLY PRETTY SLIM AND IT
PROBABLY ONE OF TWO FLAVORS
OF DOMESTIC ATTACK.
PURELY DOMESTIC SUCH AS THE
OLYMPICS IN 1996 OR EVEN
OKLAHOMA CITY IN 1995.
OR DOMESTIC WITH AN
INTERNATIONAL COMPONENT IE
SOMEBODY WHO IS BORN HERE
AND LIVED HERE AND
RADICALIZED ABROAD.
>> Shepard: LEE, I WONDER
IF IT'S POSSIBLE TO HAVE
SOME NUT JOB WHO JUST
WANTED TO CAUSE A BIG SHOW?
I DON'T THINK WE HAVE ANY
CLARITY IN THIS MATTER.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ANOTHER MATTER TO POINT OUT
IT'S A LOCAL HOLIDAY IN
MASSACHUSETTS AND CERTAIN
PARTS OF NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS DAY.
THAT HOLIDAY COMMON RATES
THE BATTLES OF LEXINGTON
AND CONQUERORS FIRST
REVOLUTIONARY WAR 1775.
IT'S POSSIBLE, ALTHOUGH
THIS IS OBVIOUSLY
SPECULATION THAT IT IS --
HARD TO KNOW BUT IT IS
THAT -- IT DOES HAVE
SIGNIFICANCE IN THE REGION
IN BOSTON.
>> Shepard: REALLY, WHEN WE
WENT THROUGH THE TRIAL, I
COVERED THE OKLAHOMA CITY
BOMBING AND THEN THE TRIAL
OF TIMOTHY MCVEIGH WHICH
FOLLOWED, AND THERE IS NO
QUESTION THAT THE REASON
THAT THAT HAPPENED AT THAT
TIME HAD SOMETHING TO DO
WITH THE ATTACKS AT WACO
AND BEYOND.
TO SUGGEST THAT WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT THIS DATE, IT
IS JUST IN A VACUUM WITHOUT
HISTORICAL CONTEXT IS
REALLY TO MISS THE FACTS
HERE.
IN THE PAST THAT HAS
HAPPENED.
IT'S NOT TO SAY IT HAS
HAPPENED AT THIS TIME BUT
IN THE PAST IT HAS.
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
OBVIOUSLY THE TARGET, THE
BOSTON MARATHON IS A
SIGNIFICANT EVENT FOR
BOSTON AND IT IS AN
INTERNATIONAL EVENT IN THE
SENSE THAT IT DRAWS
INTERNATIONAL COMPETITORS
AND VERY IMPORTANT RACE.
BUT IT IS NOT A TARGET OF
NATIONAL OR INTERNATIONAL
SIGNIFICANCE SUCH AS A --
THE WORLD TRADE CENTER OR
EVEN THE OLYMPIC GAMES.
>> Shepard: RIGHT.
IF I MIGHT GO ONE FARTHER
I'M NOT SUGGESTING THIS IS
THE REASON FOR ANYTHING.
ONE REASON WE KNOW ABOUT
THE BOSTON MARATHON IS
THERE WILL BE CAMERAS
EVERYWHERE.
ONE THING WE KNOW ABOUT
NEWS EVENTS IS TO MAKE THEM
HAVE IMPACT YOU NEED TO
HAVE VIDEO OF IT HAPPENING.
AS IT SO HAPPENS OR BY
DESIGN, ONE OR THE OTHER
THESE EXPLOSIONS HAPPENED
AS CAMERAS WERE RUNNING ON
THE SIDELINES AND AS
CHOPPERS FLEW IN THE AIR.
>> RIGHT.
RIGHT.
CLEARLY IT WAS A
WELL-PLANNED ATTACK, AS I
SAID, MORE LIKELY THAN NOT.
I WANT TO CONTINUE WITH
THESE PICTURES.
BECAUSE IT'S IMPORTANT TO
REMEMBER.
IF YOU ARE PLANNING AN
EVENT OF ANY KIND, YOU HAVE
SOME SORT OF GOAL IN MIND.
PLANNING AN EVENT WHICH
WAS A BOMBING AND YOU WANT
TO SEE WHAT HAPPENED, THEN
YOU WOULD DO THAT THEN YOU
WILL BE POSITIVE THERE WERE
CAMERAS THERE TO RECORD IT,
RIGHT?
THAT'S NOT A MATTER OF
SPECULATION.
THAT'S WHAT YOU DO.
AND TODAY TO HAVE IT AT
THE FINISH LINE OF THE
BOSTON MARATHON.
WHOEVER PUT THOSE BOMBS
THERE WAS -- COULD SAY WITH
GREAT CERTAINTY THAT THERE
WOULD BE CAMERAS ON THIS
EVENT.
AND THAT IT WOULD BE VERY
QUICK AND EASY TO GET LIVE
COVERAGE AFTERWARDS AND
THAT THERE WOULD BE A
RECORD OF WHAT YOU DID THAT
WOULD LAST FOR GENERATIONS
BEYOND ANY OF US.
THIS PICTURE RIGHT NOW IS
FOREVER WHAT HAPPENED ON --
IN BOSTON ON PATRIOTS DAY
IN 2013.
BECAUSE THE CAMERAS WERE
THERE AND RECORDED IT
HAPPEN.
WERE I TELLING YOU ABOUT IT
NOW, AND EXPLAINING TO YOU
THAT THERE WERE MASS
CASUALTIES AND THE SCENE
WAS CHAOTIC WOULD NOT HAVE
NEARLY THE IMPACT ON THE
COLLECTIVE PSYCHE THAT THIS
VIDEO DOES.
IT FOR THE PEOPLE WHO WERE
THERE BUT NOT FOR THE REST
OF US.
IF THERE HADN'T BEEN VIDEO
OF THE WORLD TRADE CENTER
ATTACK AS A SEPARATE AND
NOT RELATED IN ANYWAY WE
WOULD ALL HAVE DIFFERENT
COLLECTIVE MEMORIES.
WE KNOW WHAT THEY'RE AND
THEY CAME FROM THE
TELEVISION IMAGES.
THIS IS WHAT WE WILL
REMEMBER FROM HERE.
WHOEVER PLANTED THOSE
BOMBS, WITHOUT ANY QUESTION
KNEW THAT ON THE PHONE WITH
US NOW THE RUNNER DEMI
CLARK, SHE WAS RUNNING THE
MARATHON, SAYS SHE WAS JUST
CROSSING THE FINISH LINE AS
THE BOMB BLAST ROCKED THE
STREET.
DEMI, HOW ARE YOU?
ARE YOU SAFE?
>> YES WE'RE AT OUR HOTEL
IN BOSTON RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: SO YOU ARE
CROSSING THE FINISH LINE.
AND, AS YOU DID WAS PART
OF YOUR THINKING THAT MAYBE
THIS IS PART OF A PATRIOTS
DAY CELEBRATION OR BECAUSE
YOU HAD CROSSED IT WAS
CLEARLY BEHIND YOU, WHAT
WAS YOUR THINKING?
>> HONESTLY, IT WAS.
I THINK -- I LITERALLY HIT
THE FINISH LINE AS IT
HAPPENED AND LOOKED AT AN
OFFICIAL WHO WAS FACING
THAT WAY AND HE HAD THIS
LOOK OF HORROR ON HIS FACE.
AND SO I KNEW IT WASN'T
RIGHT.
IT JUST KIND OF EXPLODED
ALL OUR EARDRUMS, TOO.
SO IT JUST WASN'T RIGHT.
WE KNEW IT WASN'T RIGHT.
>> Shepard: HUH.
AND AFTER THAT HAPPENED,
THE MOMENTS AFTER THE FIRST
BLAST, WHAT DID YOU DO AND
WHERE WERE YOU WHEN THE
SECOND HIT?
>> I WAS LOOKING TO THE
LEFT AND SAW JUST CARNAGE.
I MEAN SOMETHING OUT OF A
WAR ZONE.
IT WAS PEOPLE UP AGAINST
FENCES.
BLOOD EVERYWHERE.
RUN ARERS DOWN TO MY LEFT.
AND GLASS AND THEN THE
OTHER EXPLOSION WENT OF
OFF.
MY FAMILY WAS IN THE
BLEACHER SECTION.
MY THREE OUTCOME DAUGHTERS
AND MY HUSBAND.
I IMMEDIATELY THOUGHT OH MY
GOODNESS ANOTHER ONE COULD
GO OFF.
HOW DO I GET THEM OUT OF
HERE AS SOON AS POSSIBLE?
>> Shepard: AND THEN
ANOTHER ONE DID?
>> YES.
AND AWAY FROM US BUT
IMMEDIATELY I JUST THOUGHT
YOU KNOW, I THINK IT WAS
MOTHER'S INSTINCT IS WHAT
CAN I DO TO GET MY KIDS OUT
OF HERE BECAUSE THEY ARE
SEVEN AND NINE AND DON'T
KNOW WHAT TO DO AND THE
SITUATION LIKE THIS.
>> Shepard: WHAT DID YOU
DO?
>> I TRIED MY BEST TO GET
TO THEM.
MY HUSBAND 6'4", 240.
I SAW HIM WITH ONE CHILD
UNDER EACH ARM.
I HAD JUST SEEN THEM.
SO I KNEW HOW TO SIGHTED
THEM FROM THE FINISH.
HE WAS MAKING HIS WAY TO
ME.
OFFICIALS WERE TRYING
NECESSARILY TO KEEP US OFF
THE COURSE.
SO I JUST KIND OF SAID I
HAVE GOT TO GO TO MY FAMILY
AND JUST WAS IN TEARS.
ABSOLUTE TEARS.
>> Shepard: I'M GLAD YOU
ARE ALL SAFE.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: WE'RE WAITING
FOR THE NEWS CONFERENCE TO
BEGIN AND WE'LL TAKE YOU TO
THAT LIVE AFTER THIS.
It's Monday.  A brand new start.
Your chance to rise and shine.  With
CenturyLink as your  trusted technology
partner  you can do just that.  With
our visionary   cloud infrastructure
global broadband network and  custom
communications solutions,  your business
is more   reliable - secure - agile.
And with responsive,  dedicated support,
we help you shine  every day of the
week.
ALL STATIONS COME OVER TO  MISSION
A FOR A FINAL GO.  THIS IS FOR REAL
THIS TIME.
STEP SEVEN POINT  TWO ONE TWO.
RIFY AND LOCK.
COMMAND IS LOCKED.
FIVE SECONDS.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
STANDING BY FOR CAPTURE.
THE MOST INNOVATIVE  SOFTWARE ON THE
PLANET...
DRAGON IS CAPTURED.
IS CONNECTING TODAY'S LEADING  COMPANIES
TO PLACES BEYOND IT.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
WE KNOW ALL YOUR INVESTMENTS  MAY
NOT BE WITH FIDELITY  BUT WE CAN STILL
HELP YOU SEE  YOUR BIG PICTURE.
WITH THE FIDELITY  GUIDED PORTFOLIO
SUMMARY
YOU CHOOSE  WHICH ACCOUNTS TO TRACK
AND USE FIDELITY'S ANALYTICS  TO SPOT
TRENDS
GAIN INSIGHTS, AND FIGURE OUT  WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO NEXT.
ALL IN ONE PLACE.
I'M MEREDITH STODDARD
AND I HELPED CREATE
THE FIDELITY GUIDED  PORTFOLIO SUMMARY.
IT'S ONE MORE INNOVATIVE REASON
SERIOUS INVESTORS
ARE CHOOSING FIDELITY.
NOW GET 200 FREE TRADES    WHEN YOU
OPEN AN ACCOUNT.
COPD MAKES IT HARD TO BREATHE...
BUT WITH ADVAIR,  I'M BREATHING BETTER.
SO NOW I CAN HELP MAKE THIS  A GREAT
BLOCK PARTY.  ♪ ♪    [ Male Announce
]    ADVAIR IS CLINICALLY PROVEN
TO HELP SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE    LUNG
FUNCTION.    UNLIKE MOST COPD MEDICATIONS,
ADVAIR CONTAINS    BOTH AN ANTI-INFLAMMATORY
AND A LONG-ACTING    BRONCHODILATOR
WORKING TOGETHER    TO HELP IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION ALL DAY.    ADVAIR
WON'T REPLACE    FAST-ACTING INHALERS
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS    AND SHOULD
NOT BUSED    MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
PEOPLE WITH COPD TAKING ADVAIR
MAY HAVE    A HIGHER CHANCE OF PNEUMONIA.
ADVAIR MAY INCRSE    YOUR RISK OF
OSTEOPOROSIS     SOME EYE PRLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR    IF YOU HAVE A
HEART CONDITION    OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING ADVAIR.  ASK YOUR DOCTOR
IF INCLUDING ADVAIR COULD HELP  IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION.    [ Male Announcer
]    ADVAIR DISKUS    FLUTICASONE
PROPIONATE AND    SALMETEROL INHALATION
POWDER.    GET YOUR FIRST PRESCRIPTION
FREE    AND SAVE ON REFILLS    AT
ADVAIRCOPD.COM.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF THE BOMBING
BOSTON MAYOR THOB.
SPOT WE ARE WAITING FOR THE
NEWS CONFERENCE.
WE HAVE AN IDEA NOW WHY
THIS HAS BEEN POSTPONED.
IT WAS SUPPOSED TO BEGIN AT
7 EASTERN.
IT STILL HASN'T HAPPENED.
THE FBI IS NOW INVOLVED.
THIS WILL BE A JOINT NEWS
CONFERENCE AIM THE AGENCIES
INVOLVED.
THE FBI LENDING ASSISTANCE
AS THE FBI PUTS IT.
THIS NEWS CONFERENCE NOW
SCHEDULED FOR 8:30 P.M.
EASTERN DAYLIGHT TIME.
WE'LL HAVE LIVE COVERAGE,
OF COURSE, DURING A LIVE
EDITION OF THE O'REILLY
FACTOR.
WE WILL BE LIVE THROUGHOUT
THE NIGHT OBVIOUSLY SO THAT
WE CAN COVER EVENTS AS
WARRANTED.
SO THAT NEWS CONFERENCE NOW
JUST ABOUT WHAT, 42
MINUTES AWAY.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE BEGUN
THE PAIN-STAKING WORK OF
FINDING EVIDENCE IN TODAY'S
ATTACK.
IN CASE LIKE, THIS
AUTHORITIES TYPICALLY
SEARCH THE SCENE FOR
SHRAPNEL, ANYTHING THAT CAN
PROVIDE A CLUE TO WHAT
SORTS OF EXPLOSIVE DEVICES
EXPLODED.
SOME INSIGHT FROM STEVE
WOLF A PYROTECHNIC    ENGINEER
WHO JOINS US LIVE.
STEVE, FROM WHAT'S LEFT AT
THE SCENE AFTER SOMETHING
EXPLODES, YOU CAN LEARN A
LOT ABOUT WHAT'S FIRST
THERE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SHEP.
YOU CAN REALLY LEARN
TREMENDOUS AMOUNT.
BUT IT'S A VERY PAINSTAKING
PROCESS.
MUCH LIKE PUTTING AN
AIRPLANE BACK TOGETHER
AFTER IT CRASHES.
ALL OF THE PIECE GOES
SOMEWHERE.
IT'S JUST A MATTER OF
FINDING THEM.
LOCATING THEM, IDENTIFYING
THEM, AND TR
THEM BACK TOGETHER.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE TRYING
TO FIND OUT WHETHER THE
DEVICE CONTAINS OWN
SHRAPNEL.
AS IN THE CASE OF A PIPE
BOMB OR WHETHER THEY USED
SOMETHING ELSE AS SHRAPNEL
AND SIMPLY PRO-FINDED --
PROVIDED EXPLOSIVE AS
PROPELLANT.
>> Shepard: GOT A NUMBER OF
REPORTS FROM EYEWITNESSES
WHO HAD BEEN RIGHT THERE
WHEN ONE OF THE EXPLOSIONS
HAPPENED.
ONE PARTICULAR MAN SAID I
REACHED INTO MY POCKET, HE
SAID HE DIDN'T EVEN KNOW
WHY AND FOUND WHAT LOOKED
LIKE SHOTGUN PELLETS IN HIS
POCKET.
IMMEDIATELY, YOU KNOW THAT
IS SOME SORT OF SHRAPNEL.
YOU DON'T KNOW EXACTLY WHAT
IT IS, BUT YOU KNOW THEN
SOMEBODY SET A BOMB.
>> YEAH.
IT'S NOT VERY LIKELY THAT
SOMEONE FOUND A PILE OF
SHRAPNEL THERE AND STUCK A
BOMB IN IT.
CERTAINLY IN THIS CASE IT
SOUNDS LIKE THE SHRAPNEL
WAS ALL INCLUDED.
THE THING WITH THESE BOMBS
THOUGH IS THAT THERE IS SO
MUCH ENERGY CONTAINED IN
SUCH A TINY AMOUNT OF
CHEMICAL THAT YOU CAN DO
TREMENDOUS DAMAGE WITH
SOMETHING, YOU KNOW,
ESSENTIALLY THE SIZE OF A
TENNIS BALL.
>> Shepard: AND NOW A
MATTER TO PUT IT ALL BACK
TOGETHER.
THANK YOU.
I NEED TO GET --
>> -- OF COURSE.
FINDING OUT WHAT IT WAS
ISN'T REALLY THE GOAL.
THE GOAL IS FINDING OUT WHO
DID IT AND WHY.
>> Shepard: AND FROM
FINDING OUT WHAT IT WAS YOU
CAN FIND OUT THE SIGNATURE
OF SOME GROUPS, AT LEAST
THAT'S WHAT THEY HAVE TOLD
US FROM THE FBI TODAY.
WE HAVE TO HIT A QUICK
COMMERCIAL BREAK.
WE'RE GOING TO COME BACK
WITH CONTINUING COVERAGE
FROM BOSTON AND THE
O'REILLY FACTOR JUST
MINUTES AWAY.
LIVE TONIGHT AND BREAKING
NEWS COVERAGE.
Using supercomputing  and mobile technology
over our secure network,
Verizon innovators  are building a
world of
medical treatment data  in the cloud.
So doctors can make  a more informed
diagnosis
from anywhere, in seconds
rather than months.
Because the world's  biggest challenges
deserve even  bigger solutions.
Powerful answers.
Verizon.
IM.
>> IDENTITY THEFT WAS A HUGE
HUGE PROBLEM FOR ME AND IT'S
GONE AWAY BECAUSE OF LIFELOCK.
>> Announcer: WHILE NO ONE CAN
STOP ALL IDENTITY THEFT,
IF CRIMINALS DO STEAL
YOUR INFORMATION, LIFELOCK
WILL HELP FIX IT, WITH OUR
$1 MILLION SERVICE GUARANTEE.
DON'T WAIT UNTIL YOU BECOME
THE NEXT VICTIM.
YOU HAVE SO MUCH TO PROTECT
AND NOTHING TO LOSE WHEN YOU
CALL LIFELOCK NOW TO GET TWO
FULL MONTHS OF IDENTITY THEFT
PROTECTION RISK FREE.
THAT'S RIGHT, 60 DAYS RISK-FREE.
USE PROMO CODE: GETHELP.
IF YOU'RE NOT COMPLETELY
SATISFIED, NOTIFY LIFELOCK
AND YOU WON'T PAY A CENT.
ORDER NOW AND ALSO GET THIS
SHREDDER TO KEEP YOUR DOCUMENTS
OUT OF THE WRONG HANDS--
A $29 DOLLAR VALUE, FREE.
GET PROTECTED NOW.
CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
OR GO TO LIFELOCK.COM TO TRY
LIFELOCK PROTECTION RISK FREE
FOR A FULL 60 DAYS.
USE PROMO CODE: GETHELP.
PLUS GET THIS DOCUMENT SHREDDER
FREE-- BUT ONLY IF YOU
ACT RIGHT NOW.
CALL THE NUMBER ON YOUR SCREEN
NOW!
>> Shepard: 6 MINUTES
BEFORE 8:00 IN BOSTON LIFE
COVERAGE CONTINUES.
BILL HEMMER IS WITH US NOW
LIVE FROM BOSTON HILLS
BEACON NEIGHBORHOOD LIVE
FROM THE SCENE.
BILL?
>> GOOD EVENING.
RIGHT NEAR COPLEY SQUARE.
INCIDENT TODAY AT 2:AUTO
LOCAL FULL-TIME.
WE'RE NOW FIVE HOURS BEYOND
THAT SHEPARD, AND THE SCENE
TONIGHT NEITHER FINISH LINE
WHERE WE JUST CAME FROM IS
STUNNING.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS AND
THOUSANDS OF YELLOW BAGS.
THESE ARE BAGS OF PERSONAL
POSSESSIONS THAT BELONG TO
EACH OF THE THEY'RE NONE
RUNNERS.
WHAT THEY WILL DO AT THESE
RACES AND S. PREPOSITION
THEIR PERSONAL BELONGINGS
SO WHEN THEY FINISH THE
RACE THEY HAVE SOMETHING IT
TO RETURN TO.
SOMETHING TO PUT ON A
CHANGE OF CLOTHES.
THERE ARE THOUSANDS
STRANDED WITHOUT THOSE
POSSESSIONS TONIGHT.
THEY TRICKLE IN ONE AFTER
ANOTHER.
BUT THIS IS SOMETHING THAT
CLEARLY WILL NOT BE TAKEN
CARE OF TONIGHT SHEPARD.
I TALKED TO ONE YOUNG MAN
WHO CAME IN FROM ST. LOUIS
MISSOURI.
HE WAS A QUARTER MILE
BEHIND THE FINISH LINE,
FINISHING HIMSELF WHEN THE
EXPLOSION OCCURRED BUT HE
NEVER HEARD THE EXPLOSION.
HE SAID THERE WERE
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE ON BOTH
SIDES OF THE STREETS AND
THEIR CHEERING WAS SO LOUD
IT DROWNED OUT THE SOUND OF
THE EXPLOSION A QUARTER
MILE DOWN THE ROAD.
WHAT HE DESCRIBED IS IS THE
ENTIRE RACE JUST STOPPED IN
FRONT OF HIM AND HE STOPPED
TOO AND THEY WERE TOLD THE
RACE WILL NOT GO ON ANY
LONGER.
A QUARTER OF A MILE FROM
THE FINISH.
TONIGHT, I ASKED HIM WHAT
HE THOUGHT ABOUT THE NEWS
AFTER IT WENT OUT
THROUGHOUT THE CITY AND
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND HE
TALKED ABOUT HIS OWN
8-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER WHO
WANTED TO BE HERE AT THE
FINISH LINE TO SEE HER
FATHER FINISH.
SHE IS HOME AND SAFE
TONIGHT IN ST. LOUIS
MISSOURI.
THERE ARE SO MANY STORIES
JUST LIKE, THIS SHEPARD
TONIGHT HERE IN BOSTON.
>> Bill: BILL HEMMER LIVE
FOR US.
WE WILL CHECK BACK.
IN FIRST, THIS HAS CREATED
INCREASED SECURITY OR
BROUGHT ABOUT INCREASED
SECURITY AT CITIES ACROSS
THE COUNTRY.
IN FACT, CITIES WORLDWIDE
ARE ON ALERT.
LONDON, LOS ANGELES, NEW
YORK AND OTHERS ALL
ADJUSTING SECURITY
PROCEDURES.
OUR SENIOR CORRESPONDENT
ERIC SHAWN LIVE IN NEW YORK
CITY IN TIMES SQUARE.
ERIC?
>> YEAH, SHEPARD.
WE ARE IN TIMES SQUARE.
IT WAS JUST THREE YEARS AGO
YOU MAY RECALL WAS THE
TARGET ITSELF OF A
TERRORIST ATTACK.
A CAR BOMB THAT THANKFULLY
FIZZLED AND DID NOT GO OFF.
AS YOU CAN SEE THE POLICE
OF NEW YORK CITY ARE ON
HEIGHTENED ALERT.
THEY HAVE TAKEN PRECAUTIONS
THAT HAVE BEEN IN PLACE
SINCE 9/11.
INCREASED SECURITY AT
HOTELS, PROMINENT LOANINGS,
THE NEW YORK CITY SUBWAY
SYSTEM.
THE NEW YORK CITY HAVING
GONE THROUGH THIS BEFORE
NOT JUST 9/11 BUT BACK IN
1993, THE BOMBING OF THE
WORLD TRADE CENTER THAT
KILLED SIX PEOPLE.
AND, SHEPARD THE NEW YORK
CITY MARATHON HAPPENED TO
HAVE BEEN CANCELLED LAST
NOVEMBER BECAUSE OF
HURRICANE SANDY.
BUT THOSE HERE TONIGHT HAVE
THEIR THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS
WITH OUR FELLOW COMPATRIOTS
IN BOSTON BECAUSE OF WHAT
HAPPENED THERE.
>> Shepard: HEIGHTENED
SECURITY IN OTHER MAJOR
CITIES AS WELL.
YES, THAT'S RIGHT.
NOT JUST LONDON BUT ACROSS
THE COUNTRY AND WASHINGTON,
D.C. THE WHITE HOUSE HAS A
PERIMETER, THE SECRET
SERVICE EXPANDED THAT
PERIMETER FURTHER OUT JUST
OUT OF AN ABUNDANCE OF
CAUTION.
MAYORS ACROSS THE COUNTRY
SAYING SEATTLE DENVER
ILLINOIS POLICE DEPARTMENTS
ON HEIGHTENED ALERT.
NO SPECIFIC THREATS IN
THOSE CITIES.
OF COURSE, THE COMMON THEME
FROM CITY HALLS IS THAT WE
ARE ALL IN THIS TOGETHER.
IF YOU SEE SOMETHING, SAY
SOMETHING, SHEP.
>> Shepard: ERIC SHAWN LIVE
NEW YORK CITY'S TIMES
SQUARE.
THANK YOU.
CONTINUING COVERAGE AHEAD
OF THE O'REILLY FACTOR FROM
NEW YORK TONIGHT IN 60
SECONDS.
>> Shepard: ONE MINUTE
BEFORE THE TOP OF THE HOUR.
RECAPPING THE NEWS AS WE
HAVE A IT FROM BOSTON THIS
AFTERNOON.
THE EXPLOSIONS HAPPENED IN
THE MOMENTS BEFORE 3:00
P.M.
THE LAST MARATHON RUNNER
RECORDED TO HAVE CROSSED
THE FINISH LINE AT 2:57.
THEN ONE EXPLOSION AND 12
TO 14 SECONDS LATER ANOTHER
EXPLOSION AND NOW WE KNOW
TWO PEOPLE ARE CONFIRMED
DEAD SOMEWHERE AROUND 100
ARE INJURED.
BOSTON HOSPITALS TOOK IN
INJURED THIS AFTERNOON AND
AT LATEST WORD A NUMBER OF
PATIENTS WERE LISTED IN
CRITICAL.
THE INVESTIGATION HAS
BEGUN.
THERE IS A PERSON OF
INTEREST BEING WATCHED IN
ONE OF THOSE HOSPITALS
ACCORDING TO THE REPORTING
OF FOX NEWS.
THAT PERSON IS NOT A
SUSPECT.
MAY BE A VICTIM, MAY BE A
PERSON OF INTEREST.
FOR THE MOMENT AUTHORITIES
SAY THEY ARE WATCHING THIS
PERSON WHO IS BEING
TREATE