JOINING US.
ARTHEL: WE KNOW YOU HAVE CHOICES
AND ARE THANKFUL YOU SPEND YOUR
TIME WITH US ON THE FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
THE FOX NEWS REPORT IS UP NEXT.
LAURA INGLE IS IN FOR HARRIS
FAULKNER.
>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
FACING CHALLENGES AT HOME AND
ABROAD AS IT RAMPS UP THE SEARCH
FOR THE NEXT FBI DIRECTOR AND
RESPONSE ON THE LATEST NORTH
KOREAN MISSILE LAUNCH.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS RESPONDING TO
THE LATEST PROVOCATION FROM
NORTH KOREA.
IT CAME JUST A DAY AFTER A
SENIOR NORTH KOREAN DIPLOMAT
SAID THEY WOULD ENGAGE IN TALK
WITH THE U.S.
MEANWHILE, THE ADMINISTRATION
WASTING NO TIME ON THE SEARCH
FOR A NEW FBI DIRECTOR.
THEY ARE WEIGHING IN ON MORE
THAN A DOZEN CANDIDATES AND
INTERVIEWING AT LEAST EIGHT OF
THEM THIS WEEKEND.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID WE COULD
HAVE AN APPOINTMENT BY FRIDAY
BEFORE HEADING ON HIS FIRST
FOREIGN TRIP AS PRESIDENT.
THIS IS HAPPENING AS THE
ADMINISTRATION IS TRYING TO PUT
OUT A FIRE STORM AFTER JAMES
COMAY'S OUSTING.
WHITE HOUSE COUNSELOR KELLYANNE
CONWAY SAID THAT IS NOT THE CA
CASE.
>> INDEPENDENT OF THAT, HIS
DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL WHO
OVERSEES THE FBI, THAT'S HIS
JOB, HE CAME TO THAT CONCLUSION
ON HIS OWN AND MADE THE
RECOMMENDATION.
NOW, I WOULD ALSO POINT OUT THAT
EVERYONE IS SAYING JAMES COMEY
WAS INVESTIGATING.
NO, HE WASN'T.
THE FBI WAS INVESTIGATING AND
THEY WILL CONTINUE TO
INVESTIGATE.
LAURA: WE HAVE FOX TEAM COVERAGE
ON ALL OF THIS.
CAROLINE SHIVELY IS IN
WASHINGTON WITH THE LATEST ON
NORTH KOREA.
FIRST WE GO TO KEVIN ON THE
NORTH LAWN AND WE HAVE HEARD THE
PRESIDENT WOULD LIKE TO FILL THE
POST AT THE FBI BY FRIDAY.
WHAT IS THE HURRY?
>> I THINK A COUPLE OF THINGS.
THEY FEEL THIS IS A POSITION
THEY CAN FILL WITH RELATIVE EASE
AND FIND A VERY HIGHLY QUALIFIED
CANDIDATE.
IN FACT, YOU CAN MAKE A
PLAUSIBLE ARGUMENT THAT
WHITTLING DOWN THE FIELD IS
PROBABLY GOING TO BE THE MOST
DIFFICULT PART HAS AS I SHOW YOU
THE NAMES AND FACES WE'VE
ALREADY TALKED ABOUT, WE ARE
TALKING OF SOME OF THE MOST
HIGHLY QUALIFIED SPECIALISTS IN
THIS AREA.
BIG NAMES INCLUDE FRAN TOWNSEND,
MIKE ROGERS, HIMSELF A FORMER
FBI AGENT AND HE HAS ALSO BEEN
ENDORSED BY A GROUP OF FORMER
AND CURRENT FBI AGENTS.
FOR HIS PART, THE PRESIDENT
SPENT HIS SATURDAY DELIVERING
HIS VERY FIRST COMMENCEMENT
ADDRESS AT LIBERTY UNIVERSITY.
HE SAID THIS SHOULDN'T TAKE A
GREAT DEAL OF TIME TO WHITTLE
DOWN.
>> BEFORE YOU LEAVE BEFORE
SATURDAY'S DEPARTURE.
>> THESE ARE OUTSTANDING PEOPLE
WHO ARE VERY WELL KNOWN.
>> BEFORE THE TRIP NEXT WEEK?
>> EVEN THAT IS POSSIBLE.
>> SOURCES TELL FOX NEWS IT'S
UNLIKELY THE PRESIDENT WILL LOOK
FOR SOMEONE WHO COMES FROM A
SPECIFIC OR STRICTLY POLITICAL
BACKGROUND.
LIKELY HE WILL DRAW ON SOMEONE
WHO HAS EXPERIENCE FROM THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY
SPECIFICALLY AND MAYBE SOMEONE
WHO CAN SAY THEY'VE DONE A BIT
OF BOTH.
LAURA: SOME FROM CAPITOL HILL
ARE FLOATING THEIR OWN IDEAS
ABOUT WHO THEY THINK MIGHT BE A
GOOD PERSON TO LEAD THE FBI.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING.
>> YOU WANT SOMEONE WHO IS NOT
JUST HIGHLY QUALIFIED.
LAWMAKERS WILL TELL YOU YOU WANT
SOMEONE WHO IS NOT JUST
QUALIFIED, BUT PASSABLE AND THAT
MEANS APOLITICAL AS BEST YOU CAN
MANAGE THAT.
ONE NAME THAT'S BEEN TOSSED OUT,
IT'S COMPLETELY COUNTERINTUITIVE
BUT IT'S A NAME THAT PEOPLE ARE
TALKING ABOUT AND THAT IS
MERRICK GARLAND.
CHIEF JUDGE MERRICK GARLAND.
REMEMBER HIM, NOMINATED FOR THE
SUPREME COURT.
HE NEVER GOT AN UP OR DOWN VOTE.
THERE ARE SOME WHO FEEL HE WOULD
BE A GREAT COMPROMISE CANDIDATE.
>> THE OUTCOME OF INVESTIGATIONS
SHOULD NOT HAVE PARTISAN
AFFILIATION.
I THINK IN THIS INSTANCE THERE
ARE A LOT OF OPTIONS AVAILABLE.
MERRICK GARLAND WOULD BE A GOOD
OPTION GIVEN THAT HE COULD HAVE
SO MUCH SUPPORT FROM BOTH SIDES
OF THE AISLE.
>> I WOULD STRONGLY URGE THE
ADMINISTRATION TO PICK SOMEONE
WHO IS APOLITICAL.
ONE OF THE HEIGHTENED
RESPONSIBILITIES WE WILL HAVE IS
MAKING SURE THAT WHOEVER COMES
IN, THIS INVESTIGATION GOES ON
UNIMPEDED.
>> MAKE NO MISTAKE ABOUT IT,
GARLAND WOULD BE A VERY
LONGSHOT, BUT KEEP IN MIND THERE
ARE A NUMBER OF LAWMAKERS ON THE
HILL WHO FEEL THAT BECAUSE HE IS
APOLITICAL, HE WOULD BE ABLE TO
MAINTAIN THE INTEGRITY OF THE
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIAN
MEDDLING IN THE 2016 ELECTION
CAMPAIGN.
BY THE WAY, FOR THOSE OF YOU
KEEPING TRACK, IT ENDED SIX
MONTHS AGO.
LAURA: WE KNOW IT WILL BE AN
INTERESTING WEEK RIGHT WHERE YOU
ARE PAIRED NEW DETAILS ON THE
NORTH KOREAN MISSILE LAUNCH.
U.S. OFFICIALS TELLING FOX NEWS
THE REGIME APPEARS TO HAVE FIRED
WHAT IS KNOWN AS A CAYENNE 17
BALLISTIC MISSILE.
EXPERTS BELIEVE NORTH KOREA
WOULD USE THIS PARTICULAR
MISSILE TO TARGET SHIPS.
IT IS ALSO IMPORTANT TO POINT
OUT THIS WAS THE FIRST WEAPONS
TEST SINCE THE NEW SOUTH KOREAN
PRESIDENT TOOK OFFICE.
THE NORTH HAS CONDUCTED AT LEAST
TWO DOZEN TESTS OVER THE PAST
YEAR.
AT LEAST SEVEN OF THOSE FAILED.
THIS LATEST TEST APPEARS TO HAVE
SUNK THE IDEA OF THE U.S.
SPEAKING WITH NORTH KOREA.
NIKKI HALEY SAYS THE U.S. CANNOT
LET UP.
>> I THINK YOU HAVE TO GET INTO
KIM JONG-UN'S HEAD.
HE IS IN A STATE OF PARANOIA.
HE IS CONCERNED ABOUT ANYTHING
AND EVERYTHING AROUND HIM.
THIS WAS A MESSAGE TO SOUTH
KOREA AFTER THE ELECTION AND
WHAT WE WILL DO IS TIGHTEN THE
SCREWS.
HE FEELS IT.
WE WILL CONTINUE WHETHER IT
SANCTIONS, PRESS STATEMENTS,
ANYTHING WE HAVE TO DO.
LAURA: CAROLINE SHIVELY IS LIVE
IN WASHINGTON.
IF THIS IS A MEDIUM RANGE
MISSILE, WHAT DAMAGE CAN IT DO?
>> IT CAN DO SOME DEFINITE
DAMAGE.
WITHIN THE LAST HOUR, THE NEWS
AGENCY SAID THE AIM WAS TO
VERIFY THAT THE MISSILE COULD
CARRY A LARGE SCALE NUCLEAR
WARHEAD AND THEY ARE CALLING IT
A SUCCESS.
THERE IS WHAT U.S. OFFICIALS
SAY.
IT IS A SINGLE STAGE LIQUID
FUELED MISSILE, NOT THE SOLID
FUEL MISSILE THAT WAS TESTED
BACK IN FEBRUARY.
THAT CAUSED MORE CONCERN FOR
PENTAGON OFFICIALS.
IT WAS IN THE AIR FOR ROUGHLY 30
MINUTES AND TRAVELED ABOUT
430 MILES ACCORDING TO THE SOUTH
KOREAN MILITARY.
A MEDIUM RANGE MISSILE CAN GO
FURTHER BUT THIS HAD A VERY HIGH
TRAJECTORY.
THE U.S. OFFICIALS THAT IT
SPLASHED DOWN IN THE SEAS
60 MILES SOUTH OF RUSSIA AND 25.
IT COULD NOT HAVE REACHED THE
U.S. BUT THE STATEMENT, JUST OUT
FROM THE NORTH REAFFIRMS IT IS
ONE OF KIM JONG-UN'S MAIN GOALS
FOR HIS NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
DAN SULLIVAN OF ALASKA SAID HE
PLANS TO INTRODUCE LEGISLATION
NEXT WEEK THAT AUTHORIZES
GROUND-BASED INTERCEPTORS TO BE
LINED UP IN ALASKA AND
CALIFORNIA.
THAT IS A THIRD MORE THAN THE
U.S. HAS RIGHT NOW.
>> WE KNOW THE U.S. IS PUSHING
BACK ON NORTH KOREA.
WE'VE BEEN REPORTING.
WHAT ABOUT THE REST OF THE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY?
>> CHINA AND RUSSIA BOTH SAID
THEY WERE CONCERNED ABOUT THE
LAUNCH, BUT IT WAS A PRETTY
TEPID RESPONSE.
NOT THE U.S. THOUGH.
THEY SEEM TO BE PUSHING
COUNTRIES IN THE REGION TO GET
TOUGHER.
>> WHAT WE DO KNOW IS THE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY IS
CONCERNED.
IT'S NOT JUST US AGAINST THEM.
YOU WILL SEE THE ENTIRE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY ISOLATE
NORTH KOREA AND LET THEM KNOW
THIS IS NOT ACCEPTABLE.
>> THE UN SECURITY COUNCIL WILL
HOLD URGENT MEETINGS ON THE TEST
THIS TUESDAY.
THE U.S., JAPAN AND SOUTH KOREA
ALL ASKED FOR THE MEETING.
THEY HAVE ADOPTED TOUGH
SANCTIONS BUT THEY DON'T APPEAR
TO BE SLOWING KIM JONG-UN DOWN.
AMBASSADOR HALEY SAID MORE
SANCTIONS COULD BE ON THE WAY
AND THE POTENTIAL MEETING
BETWEEN KIM JONG-UN AND
PRESIDENT TRUMP, NOT HAPPENING.
>> HAVING A MISSILE TEST IS NOT
THE WAY TO SIT DOWN WITH THE
PRESIDENT.
HE ABSOLUTELY WON'T DO IT.
HE CAN SAY ALL THE CONDITIONS HE
WANTS.
UNTIL HE MEETS OUR CONDITIONS WE
AREN'T SITTING DOWN WITH HIM.
LAURA: YOU MENTION THE TIMING
JUST DAYS AFTER THE SOUTH KOREAN
PRESIDENT CAME INTO OFFICE.
IT ALSO COMES AS THE U.S. AND
JAPANESE NAVIES HAVE COME
TOGETHER FOR WARGAMES IN THE
SOUTH PACIFIC.
LAURA: WE HAVE A LOT TO TALK
ABOUT.
LET'S BRING IN KEVIN RUDD WHO
JOINS US BY PHONE.
HE IS THE FORMER PRIME MINISTER
OF AUSTRALIA AND PRESIDENT OF
THE ASIA POLICY INSTITUTE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
>> DO YOU THINK THE RESPONSE
FROM THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
GOING TO BE EFFECTIVE ENOUGH TO
CALM THE SITUATION DOWN?
HOW DO YOU THINK OUR ALLIES WILL
HELP HANDLE THIS WITH DIPLOMACY?
>> REMEMBER THE KEY OBJECTIVE IS
TO BRING ABOUT A CHANGE IN NORTH
KOREAN BEHAVIOR.
EVERYTHING ELSE IS A SOUND AND
LIGHT SHOW.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS WHAT CAN YOU
DO TO BRING ABOUT A CHANGE IN
BEHAVIOR.
THE OUTCOME OF THE MAR-A-LAGO
MEETING WAS FOR THE TWO SIDES TO
WORK ON A COMMON DIPLOMATIC
STRATEGY TO BRING ABOUT THAT
CHANGE IN NORTH KOREA.
SO FAR, WITHOUT RESULT AS YOU'VE
JUST DISCUSSED WITH THE MOST
RECENT MISSILE TEST, BUT FROM
CHINA'S PERSPECTIVE, THIS
MISSILE TEST BY THE NORTH KOREAN
IS THE LEAST WELCOMED
DEVELOPMENT.
IT SENDS A DIRECT SIGNAL TO THE
NEWLY ELECTED PRESIDENT OF SOUTH
KOREA LESS THAN A WEEK AGO THAT
THE NORTH KOREANS ARE IN A
BELLIGERENT MOOD.
FROM CHINA'S PERSPECTIVE IN
BEIJING, IT WAS A MAJOR GLOBAL
CONFERENCE HOSTED HERE YESTERDAY
ON A BIG INFRASTRUCTURE
CONFERENCE.
WHO UPSETS THE PARTY BUT THE GUY
NEXT DOOR.
HE DOESN'T DO A LOT IN TERMS OF
IMPROVING CHINA'S SENSE OF HUMOR
ABOUT WHAT THE NORTH KOREAN
LEADER IS UP TOO.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS BEEN
CALLING FOR EVEN STRONGER
SANCTIONS AND EVEN THOUGH THE
U.S. IS APPLYING PRESSURE, WE
HAVE NORTH KOREA WRITING A
LETTER TO THE CONGRESS
COMPLAINING ABOUT THESE
SANCTIONS.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL US?
>> THE BOTTOM LINE IS THE NORTH
KOREAN DIPLOMATIC BEHAVIOR HAS A
HISTORY OF BEING ALL OVER THE
PLACE.
SOMETIMES IT IS HARSH.
I DON'T THINK IT'S ANYTHING THAT
ANYONE IN THE UNITED STATES
SHOULD TAKE TERRIBLY SERIOUSLY.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS PEOPLE WATCH
THEIR BEHAVIOR AND THE MISSILE
TEST IS AN ACTION BY THE NORTH
KOREANS WHICH IS BY DEFINITION
BELLIGERENT.
LET'S NOT GET DISTRACTED FROM
THE CORE ACTION WHICH IS WHAT IS
THE UNITED STATES DOING WITH THE
CHINESE TO BRING ABOUT
SUBSTANTIAL CHANGE IN NORTH
KOREAN BEHAVIOR?
THE KEY TO THIS, IF THERE IS
FURTHER SANCTIONS AND WHETHER
THAT WOULD INCLUDE THE SUPPLY OF
OIL FROM CHINA TO NORTH KOREA.
THIS IS THE CORE POINT OF
LEVERAGE.
NORTH KOREA DEPENDS ON CHINA OIL
TO KEEP THEIR ECONOMY RUNNING.
THIS IS THE POINT AT WHICH CHINA
LEVERAGE WOULD BEGIN TO HAVE AN
IMPACT.
LAURA: I WANTED TO ASK YOU ABOUT
A REPORT THAT WAS OUT TODAY.
CONGRESS IS WEIGHING OPTIONS FOR
BOLSTERING SANCTIONS AGAINST
NORTH KOREA BY INCREASING THE
MISSILES ON THE WEST COAST.
THIS RECENT MISSILE CAME
60 MILES OFF RUSSIA.
>> THESE FALL INTO THREE
CATEGORIES.
SHORT RANGE WHICH CAN WORK FOR
THEM ACROSS THE PARALLEL WITH
SOUTH KOREA, MEDIUM RANGE WHICH
WOULD AFFECT JAPAN AND AMERICAN
DEPLOYMENTS IN GUAM, AND
LONG-RANGE MISSILES OR
INTERCONTINENTAL MISSILES WHICH
COULD REACH ALASKA AND THE U.S.
WEST COAST.
THE NORTH KOREANS HAVE BEEN
TESTING THE FIRST TWO SETS OF
CATEGORIES OF THAT AND THAT IN
OF ITSELF IS DESTABILIZING.
THE CORE QUESTION IS, I
UNDERSTAND THE DEBATE IN THE
U.S. THAT THERE ARE ANTIMISSILE
DEFENSE.
THAT IS A NORMAL REACTION TO
WHAT THE NORTH KOREANS ARE DOING
AND IRRATIONAL REASON BUT IF
THEY REQUIRE A LARGE NUMBER OF
MISSILES, AND THEY ALREADY HAVE
A LARGE NUMBER OF BOMBS, IF THEY
ARE ABLE TO MILITARIZE THOSE
NUCLEAR WEAPONS AND HAVE A LARGE
STOCK, THE DANGER FOR ALL OF US
IN THE UNITED STATES AND THE
U.S. ALLIES IN THE REGION IS
THAT THEY HAVE A LARGE NUMBER
AND THEY CAN OVERWHELM A MISSILE
DEFENSE SYSTEM SO THERE IS A
RACE AGAINST CAPABILITY AND THE
NUMBER OF MISSILES AS WELL.
LAURA: KEVIN RUDD IS RIGHT IN
THE MIDDLE OF EVERYTHING IN
CHINA.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US WITH
YOUR PERSPECTIVE.
>> THANK YOU.
LAURA: AND INTERNATIONAL EFFORT
TO TRACK DOWN HACKERS TARGETING
MORE THAN 100 COUNTRIES.
THE HIGHLY ORGANIZED CYBER CROOK
INFECTING COMPUTERS AROUND THE
GLOBE WITH RENT SOMEWHERE.
>> THIS IS A VERY SERIOUS
PROBLEM AND I THINK IT WILL
GROW.
LAURA: A COLD HARD LOOK AMID A
GROWING OPIOID CRISIS.
WHAT PARENTS OF VICTIMS ARE
DOING NOW TO HELP SAVE LIVES.
I've found a permanent
escape from monotony.
Together, we are
perfectly balanced,
our senses awake,
our hearts racing as one.
I know this is sudden,
but they say: If you
love something...
set it free.
See you around, Giulia
♪
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night,
so he got home safe.
Yeah, my dad says our
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Yet up 90% fall short in getting
key nutrients from food alone.
Let's do more.
Add One A Day Women's
complete with key
nutrients we may need.
Plus it supports
bone health
with calcium
and vitamin D.
One A Day Women's in
gummies and tablets.
♪
I'm Dr. Kelsey McNeely and some
day you might be
calling me an energy farmer.
♪
Energy lives here.
even if you're
trying your best.be
a daily struggle,
Along with diet
and exercise,
once-daily Toujeo® may help
you control your blood sugar.
Get into a daily groove.
♪ Let's groove tonight.
♪ Share the spice of life.
♪ Baby, slice it right.
From the makers of Lantus®,
♪ We're gonna groove tonight.
Toujeo® provides blood
sugar-lowering activity
for 24 hours and beyond,
proven blood sugar control
all day and all night,
and significant
A1C reduction.
Toujeo® is used to control
high blood sugar in adults
with diabetes.
It contains 3 times
as much insulin
in 1 milliliter as
standard insulin.
Don't use Toujeo® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during episodes
of low blood sugar
or if you're
allergic to insulin.
Get medical help right away
if you have a serious
allergic reaction
such as body rash
or trouble breathing.
Don't reuse needles
or share insulin pens.
The most common side
effect is low blood sugar,
which can be
life threatening.
It may cause shaking,
sweating, fast heartbeat,
and blurred vision.
Check your blood
sugar levels daily.
Injection site
reactions may occur.
Don't change your
dose of insulin
without talking
to your doctor.
Tell your doctor about
all your medicines
and medical conditions.
Check insulin label
each time you inject.
Taking TZDs with
insulins, like Toujeo®,
may cause heart failure
that can lead to death.
Find your rhythm and
keep on grooving.
♪ Let's groove tonight.
Ask your doctor about Toujeo®.
♪ Share the spice of life.
LAURA: PRESIDENT TRUMP
REPORTEDLY CALLING FOR AN
EMERGENCY MEETING FOLLOWING A
MASSIVE RANSOM WARE ATTACK THAT
AFFECTED DOZENS OF COUNTRY
WORLDWIDE.
IT'S A BELIEVED TO BE THE
BIGGEST ONLINE EXTORTION ATTACK
EVER RECORDED.
THE NSA AND FB FBI ARE WORKING O
FIND THE ATTACKER.
>> MANY OF THOSE WILL BE
BUSINESSES.
IT'S NOT A UK ONLY PROBLEM.
IT'S AN INTERNATIONAL PROBLEM.
LAURA: ALLISON BARBER HAS MORE
FROM OUR D.C. BUREAU.
>> THIS IS BELIEVED TO BE THE
LARGEST CYBER EXTORTION ATTACK
IN HISTORY IN A MY NOT BE OVER.
EXPERTS SAY THE ATTACK COULD
GROW WHEN PEOPLE HAD TO WORK
TOMORROW AND START LOGGING ONTO
THEIR COMPUTER.
>> THAT IS THE CONCERN, THAT
MONDAY WHEN EVERYONE RETURNS TO
THE OFFICE, THIS RANSOM WARE
ATTACK WILL BE EVEN LARGER.
>> THIS ALL BEGAN FRIDAY,
HITTING HOSPITALS IN ENGLAND,
REAL COMPANIES IN GERMANY AND
FEDEX.
HACKERS REPORTEDLY EXPLOITED
LOOPHOLES IN VERSION OF
MICROSOFT WINDOWS.
THEY CREATED A VIRUS CALLED WANT
TO CRY.
THEY LOCKED SYSTEMS AND
ENCRYPTED FILES AND DEMANDED
HUNDREDS OF DOLLARS IN EXCHANGE.
IT IMPACTED 150 COUNTRIES AND AT
LEAST 100,000 ORGANIZATIONS.
THE DIRECTOR SAID THE ATTACK IS
UNPRECEDENTED.
>> WE ARE RUNNING AROUND 200
GLOBAL OPERATIONS AGAINST
CYBERCRIME EACH YEAR.
THOUGH WE'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING
LIKE THIS.
WE'VE SEEN THE RISE OF RANSOM
WARE BECOMING THE PRINCIPAL
THREAT, BUT THIS IS SOMETHING WE
HAVEN'T SEEN BEFORE.
THE GLOBAL REACH IS
UNPRECEDENTED.
>> EXPERTS ARE URGING EVERYONE
TO INSTALL THE LATEST WINDOWS
UPDATE BECAUSE THERE IS A
SECURITY PATCH IN IT TO EXPOSED
THE LOOPHOLE.
MICROSOFT SAYS THEY ARE WORKING
WITH CUSTOMERS AND RELEASING
UPDATES FOR COMPUTERS RUNNING ON
OLDER SYSTEMS.
SECURITY EXPERTS TOLD THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS THE ATTACK
HAPPENED BECAUSE OF A PERFECT
STORM OF CONDITIONS INCLUDING
THE FACT THESE HACKERS USED A
WEAPON ICED EXPLOIT CREATED BY
THE NSA YEARS AGO IN LEAKED
ONLINE LAST MONTH.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS PLANNING FOR
AN EMERGENCY MEETING.
SOURCES ARE TELLING REUTERS THAT
TRUMP ORDERED HOMELAND SECURITY
ADVISOR TO HOLD THIS MEETING
FRIDAY NIGHT AND EVALUATE THE
ATTACK.
LAURA: THANK YOU SO MUCH.
FAMILY AND FRIENDS OF DRUG
OVERDOSE VICTIMS ARE TRYING TO
SOUND THE ALARM AND ERASE THE
SHAME OF DRUG ADDICTION AMID THE
OPIOID ADDICTION.
HOW MORE FAMILIES ARE SPEAKING
OPENLY AND HONESTLY ABOUT THE
HORRORS OF THIS DISEASE, HOPING
THAT IT WILL SAVE LIVES AND
PREVENT PAINFUL LOSSES
try doctor recommended Gaviscon.
It quickly neutralizes stomach
acid
and helps keep acid down for
hours.
Relieve heartburn with fast-
acting, long-lasting Gaviscon.
and helps keep acid down for
hours.
[FBI Agent] You're a brave man,
Your testimony will save lives.
Mr. Stevens?
This is your new name.
This is your new house.
And a perfectly inconspicuous
SUV.
You must become invisible.
[Hero] I'll take my
chances.
[Customer] Have you ever walkedp
into the paint store
feeling like you should really
know more than you know?
Satin versus semi-gloss, and...I
don't know!
[Team Member] Yes...I know the
feeling.
[Customer] That's how I feel
right now about all the
financing options for this
project I'm doing.
I feel like I should know more
than I know.
[Team Member] Don't sweat it.
We have this new tool--My Credit
Options Guide--
that gives you a customized
comparison like this,
which helps you discover which
credit options
might be right for you.
[Customer] Oh, this is better.
They should make one for paint.
[Team Member] Want to get
started?
[Customer] Sure.
Z286OZ ZWTZ
Y286OY YWTY
AtMore than one flavor, oruch
texture, or color.ing.
A good clean salad is so much
more than green.
And with Panera catering, more
for your event.
Panera. Food as it should be.
could be preventedrrent
with the right steps.
And take it from me,
every step counts.
A Bayer aspirin regimen
is one of those steps
in helping prevent
another stroke.
Be sure to talk
to your doctor
before you begin
an aspirin regimen.
LAURA: WHILE THE OPIOID EPIDEMIC
IS SPREADING IN AMERICA, A NEW
TREND IS RISING CALLED HONEST
OBITUARIES.
MORE AND MORE WHO HAVE LOST
LOVED ONES TO DRUG ADDICTION
HAVE WRITTEN HONEST OBITUARIES
TO EXPOSE HOW DAMAGING IT IS.
>> USING HEROIN ONCE IS ALL IT
TAKES TO GET HOOKED.
FROM THEN ON YOU ARE PLAYING
RUSSIAN ROULETTE.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED TO ANDREW.
LAURA: HERE IS A CLOSE LOOK AT
THE STORY.
HI BRIAN.
>> MOTHER'S DAY IS NOT AN EASY
DAY FOR EVERYONE.
FOR STEPHANIE OSWALD, THIS IS
HER FIRST WITHOUT HER SON
ANDREW.
DESPITE REHAB, HE DIED ALONE IN
HIS APARTMENT FROM A HEROINE
OVERDOSE.
IT'S NOT THE KIND OF THINGS
PARENTS WOULD USUALLY INCLUDE IN
THEIR CHILDHOO OBITUARY BUT STEE
DID.
>> ON JANUARY 27, 2017, OUR
BEAUTIFUL SON ANDREW DIED FROM A
HEROIN OVERDOSE.
HE WAS 23 YEARS OLD.
NO PARENT SHOULD EVER HAVE TO
BURY THEIR CHILD.
>> MORE PARENTS ARE USING STARK
CANDOR IN THEIR CHILD'S OBITUARY
ABOUT HEROIN ADDICTION TO REACH
OUT TO FAMILIES STRUGGLING IN
SILENCE, FEELING SHAME AND
EMBARRASSMENT.
>> PEOPLE HAVE TO STOP SEEING IT
AS A DIRTY LITTLE SECRET.
IT'S EVERYWHERE.
THE MORE PEOPLE WHO ARE HONEST
ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON OUT THERE,
THE MORE ATTENTION IT CAN GET.
>> ANDREWS ADDICTION BEGAN AFTER
BEING PRESCRIBED OXYCODONE AFTER
A CAR ACCIDENT.
STEPHANIE SAID SHE WAS HESITANT
AT FIRST ABOUT BEING SO PUBLIC.
>> SINCE HE HAD KEPT IT SUCH A
SECRET TO ALL OF HIS FRIENDS
HERE, I FEEL LIKE I OUTED HIM IN
A WAY.
IT WAS MOMENTARY, BUT I STILL
FELT THAT.
>> THE OBITUARY HAD AN IMPACT
IMMEDIATELY.
STRANGERS, OTHER PARENTS WHO
LOST KIDS TO ADDICTION CAME TO
HIS FUNERAL TO SUPPORT AND THANK
THE OSWALD FOR THEIR COURAGE.
>> I WON'T STOP TALKING.
IF I HAVE TO YELL I WILL.
WHATEVER IT TAKES, I'M GOING TO
KEEP MOVING THIS THING FORWARD.
>> INCREDIBLE COURAGE FROM
STEPHANIE.
HIS OBITUARY ALSO INCLUDED A
REMINDER THAT ADDICTION DOES NOT
DISCRIMINATE.
SHE REMEMBERS HER SON'S BIG
HEART AND LOVE OF MUSIC.
A TOUGH DAY FOR STEPHANIE, NO
DOUBT.
LAURA: THANK YOU FOR SHARING
THAT VERY IMPORTANT STORY.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
VOWING TO TIGHTEN THE SCREWS ON
NORTH KOREA AFTER THE LATEST
MISSILE TEST.
OUR SANCTIONS THE RIGHT PATH TO
TAKE?
PLUS, THE FIRING OF JAMES COMEY
REIGNITING DEMOCRATIC CALLS FOR
AN INDEPENDENT PROSECUTOR.
MOST REPUBLICANS ARE REFUSING TO
BUDGE.
WHAT ABOUT POLITICAL STANDOFF
AND WHAT THAT MEANS FOR BOTH
PARTIES.
>> THE PRESIDENT CONTINUES TO
INDICATE THEY ARE AFRAID OF
WHERE THE INVESTIGATION MAY
LEAD.
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID HE
WANTS THE INVESTIGATION TO GO
FORWARD
I love how USAA gives me
the peace of mind
and the security
just like the Marines did.
At one point, I did change
to a different company
with car insurance,
and I was not happy with the
customer service.
We have switched back over
and we feel like
we're back home now.
The process through USAA
is so effortless,
that you feel like
you're a part of the family.
I love that I can pass the
membership to my children,
and that they can be protected.
We're the Williams family,
and we're USAA
members for life.
Call USAA today
to talk about
your insurance needs.
What's going on? Oh hey!
♪
That's it?
Yeah.
♪
Everybody two seconds!
"Dear Sebastian,
after careful consideration of
your application, it is
with great pleasure that we
offer our congratulations
on your acceptance..."
Through the Tuition Assistance
Program,
every day McDonald's helps more
people go to college.
It's part of our commitment to
being America's Best First Job.
♪
What makesHeart healthysalad the
beCalifornia Walnuts.r?
The best simple
veggie dish ever?
Heart healthy
California Walnuts.
The best simple dinner ever?
Heart healthy
California Walnuts.
Great tasting, heart healthy
So simple.
Get the recipes at walnuts.org.
Whether it's connecting one of
Or bringing WiFi to 65,000 fans.
campuses.
Businesses count on
communication, and communication
counts on CenturyLink.
I count on my Dell Small
for tech advice.
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs and
I get back to business.
♪
LAURA: I AM LAURA INGLE IN FOR
HARRIS PARTNER AND THIS IS THE
FOX REPORT.
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR AND
TIME FOR THE TOP OF THE NEWS.
THE WHITE HOUSE CONDEMNING NORTH
KOREA'S LATEST MISSILE TESTS.
THEY REVEALED IT WAS THE FIRST
SUCCESSFUL TEST OF WHAT'S KNOWN
AS A KM 17 MISSILE.
THEY CALL IT MORE CONCERNING
THAN PREVIOUS LAUNCHES AND SAY
IT COULD BE USED TO TARGET
SHIPS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WEIGHING MORE
THAN A DOZEN CANDIDATES TO
REPLACE JAMES COMMANDS THE NEXT
DIRECTOR OF THE FBI.
THE ADMINISTRATION INTERVIEWED
AT LEAST EIGHT PEOPLE THIS
WEEKEND.
THE PRESIDENT SAID A DECISION
COULD COME BY FRIDAY.
THAT IS THE SAME DAY THE
PRESIDENT WILL HEAD TO SAUDI
ARABIA KICKING OFF HIS FIRST
FOREIGN TRIP AS
COMMANDER-IN-CHIEF.
HE WILL ALSO GO TO ISRAEL AND
ROME VISITING THE CENTERS OF
ISLAM AND CHRISTIANITY.
THE TRIP IS SEEN AS A MAJOR
FOREIGN-POLICY TEST FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
MR. GATES OFFERED THIS ADVICE.
>> I THINK OF WHEN IT COMES TO
THE ISSUES, I WOULD ADVISE HIM
TO STICK TO THE SCRIPT.
HE IS GOING TO HAVE SOME VERY
TOUGH CONVERSATIONS AND HE WILL
TALK ABOUT SOME VERY TOUGH AND
COMPLICATED ISSUES IN ALL OF THE
PLACES HE VISITS.
I THINK ANY TIME A PRESIDENT
DOES THINGS THAT ARE HUMANIZING,
I THINK IT'S GOOD.
LAURA: LET'S BRING IN EVAN SIG
FREED, AUTHOR OF GOP, GPS AND
DOUG, FORMER ADVISOR TO
PRESIDENT BILL WINTON AND A FOX
NEWS CONTRIBUTOR.
WELCOME.
WE WANT TO TALK ABOUT THIS
STAYING ON MESSAGE THING.
WE HEAR THIS ADVICE FROM GATES
BUT AS WE'VE SEEN FROM TIME TO
TIME, THE PRESIDENT HAS A
TENDENCY TO GO OFF SCRIPT.
LET'S ASSUME HE DOES STICK TO
THE TALKING POINTS.
DOUG, WHAT DOES HE NEED TO PROVE
AND HOW DOES HE DO THAT.
>> HE NEEDS TO PROVE HE IS AN
AUTHENTIC AND SERIOUS
REPRESENTATIVE OF THE UNITED
STATES AND OUR POSITIONS, THAT
HE CAN ARTICULATE OUR POSITION
IN THE MIDDLE EAST WITH THE
SAUDI'S AND THE ISRAELIS WHO ARE
WORKING TOGETHER, HE CAN
ARTICULATE IN EUROPE OUR
POSITION WITH THE G-7 AND NATO
AND MAKE IT CLEAR THAT HE IS
AUTHENTIC, CREDIBLE, AND
ASSERTIVE IN STANDING UP FOR OUR
INTERESTS AND OUR FOREIGN POLICY
POSITIONS.
LAURA: EVAN, ANY CONCERNS ON
YOUR PART OF HYMNS STICKING TO
THE SCRIPT.
>> HE DOES GO OFF SCRIPT
SOMETIMES BUT WHEN YOU LOOK AT
FOREIGN-POLICY, HE HAS DONE VERY
WELL.
THE ONLY TIME THAT WAS A CONCERN
WAS RIGHT AFTER HE WAS ELECTED
WHERE HE HAD THE CALL WITH
TAIWAN WHICH GREATLY INFURIATED
THE CHINESE.
WHEN HE HAS TO AVOID IS DOING
SOMETHING THAT CAN GIVE
PERCEPTION TO ANOTHER COUNTRY OR
ALLY THAT HE IS SMEARING THEM OR
UPSETTING THEM.
LAURA: CALL IS SO IMPORTANT WITH
ALL THIS.
DOUG, TAKING A LOOK AT THE LAST
TWO PRESIDENTS ON THEIR FIRST
FOREIGN TRIP, PRESIDENT OBAMA
WENT TO CANADA IN 2009 AND
GEORGE W. BUSH TOOK HIS FIRST
FOREIGN TRIP TO MEXICO IN
FEBRUARY 2001.
IT TOOK A FEW EXTRA MONTHS BUT
THE PRESIDENT IS JUMPING IN,
GOING OVERSEAS.
GOOD MOVE?
BAD MOVE?
>> I THINK IT'S TH
THERE IS A NEW AND EMERGING
ALLIANCE BETWEEN ISRAEL, SAUDI
AND THE EGYPTIANS AND THAT'S
IMPORTANT, AND FOR NATO WHICH
THE PRESIDENT HAS CALLED
OBSOLETE AND REVERSED HIMSELF,
HE HAS TO REASSURE THEM TO MAKE
IT CLEAR HE WILL STAND UP
AGAINST RUSSIA AGGRESSION WHICH
IS STRONG IN THE BALKANS AND
EVER PRESENT IN COUNTRIES LIKE
ESTONIA, LITHUANIA AND LATVIA.
>> HE IS JUMPING RIGHT IN GOING
OVERSEAS.
THIS IS A BIG TRIP.
>> HE HAS ALREADY ASSUAGED THE
NATO ALLIES WHEN HE MET WITH THE
SECRETARY GENERAL AT THE WHITE
HOUSE AND SAID WE ARE HERE AND
WE ARE A MEMBER AND WE WANT TO
BE WITH YOU ON THIS.
I THINK WHAT'S REALLY IMPORTANT
IN ADDITION TO SOLVING THE
PALESTINE CONFLICT IS THE G-7
AND NATO MEETINGS.
WITH NORTH KOREA'S AGGRESSION,
WE NEED TO HAVE ALL OF OUR
ALLIES ON THE SAME PAGE
ENCOUNTERING NORTH KOREA AND
STOPPING THEM FROM BAD BEHAVIOR
WHICH IS ENDANGERING ASIA AND
THE REST OF THE WORLD.
LAURA: ONE OF THE THINGS WE'VE
BEEN LOOKING AT WITH VISITING
POPE FRANCIS IS THE PRESIDENT'S
TRIP AND POPE FRANCIS VIEWS.
>> I THINK THIS IS A WORK IN
PROGRESS.
THE PRESIDENT AND THE POPE
COULDN'T HAVE TWO MORE DIVERGENT
VIEWS.
THAT BEING SAID, FOR THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
NOT TO HAVE A HARMONIOUS
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE POPE.
[INAUDIBLE]
>> WE CAN'T ENVISION THE BEING
COMBATIVE.
IT WILL BE A DECENT VISIT.
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT, ONE OF
HIS STRENGTHS, WHEN HE IS
ONE-ON-ONE WITH SOMEONE IN A
ROOM, HE IS MUCH BETTER THAN HE
IS IN A CROWD.
I THINK POPE FRANCIS, THE TWO OF
THEM KNOW THEY WILL DISAGREE BUT
I THINK THEY WILL FIND COMMON
GROUND.
I THINK THEY CAN WORK TOGETHER
AND HAVE A CONSTRUCTIVE DIALOGUE
SO THEY CAN WORK TOGETHER IN THE
FUTURE TO TACKLE THE MAJOR
PROBLEMS OF THE WORLD AND HAVE
AN EFFECTIVE RELATIONSHIP.
LAURA: THIS VISIT KICKS OFF ON
FRIDAY.
I WANT TO TALK ABOUT THE FIRING
OF JAMES COMEY AND THE FBI.
THERE HAS BEEN A LOT OF
COMPARISON TO NIXON AND
WATERGATE.
WE WANT TO BRING IN BOB FROM FOX
NEWS SUNDAY TALKING ABOUT THAT.
>> THIS IS NOT WATERGATE.
THERE IS NO EVIDENCE THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP, AT THIS POINT
WAS SOMEHOW INVOLVED IN
COLLUSION.
IN THE CASE OF NIXON, HE HAD HIS
FORMER WHITE HOUSE COUNSEL, JOHN
DEAN, TESTIFY FOR FOUR DAYS THAT
THE PRESIDENT CORRUPTLY AND
ILLEGALLY LED THE OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
YOU HAVE NOTHING COMPARABLE.
LAURA: DOUG, DO YOU AGREE?
>> I THINK WITH THE EARLY STAGES
OF THE RUSSIA, TRUMP POTENTIAL
COLLUSION ISSUE, THERE ARE LOTS
OF QUESTIONS ABOUT WHAT GENERAL
FLYNN DID OR DIDN'T DO, WHO PAUL
MANAFORT WAS WORKING WITH.
WE JUST DON'T KNOW.
THE REASON I THINK THE FIRING OF
JAMES COMEY WAS SO UNFORTUNATE,
WE WERE BEGINNING THE
INVESTIGATION.
MORE FUNDS WERE REQUESTED,
SUBPOENAS HAD GONE OUT FOR
GENERAL FLYNN'S PAPERS.
I THINK IT IS A MUCH EARLIER
STAGE OF THE INVESTIGATION THAN
THE POINT WOODWARD WAS TALKING
ABOUT WITH WATERGATE.
TIME WILL TELL, LAURA.
LAURA: EVAN, HOW DO YOU SEE IT?
THIS IS A BIG POINT PEOPLE ARE
MAKING AND GOING BACK IN TIME TO
MAKE THIS COMPARISON.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE MAKING
THE COMPARISON.
I DON'T THINK IT'S FAIR AT THIS
POINT.
IT'S WAY TOO EARLY IN THE GAME.
LET'S LOOK AT WHAT HAS HAPPENED.
THE PRESIDENT IS, AS JAMES COMEY
ADMITTED ON WEDNESDAY, WITHIN
HIS RIGHT TO FIRE THE FBI
DIRECTOR AT ANY POINT IN TIME.
THE SUBSEQUENT MESSAGE FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE HAS GOTTEN THE
PRESIDENT INTO HOT WATER BECAUSE
ON TUESDAY NIGHT HIS AIDES WENT
ON TV AND SAID IT'S TIME FOR THE
RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION TO STOP
AND ON THURSDAY, HE SAID THE
RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION PLAYED A
PART IN THAT.
NOW, IF THE PRESIDENT, I DON'T
SEE ANYTHING HAPPENING TO THE
PRESIDENT FOR SAYING THAT.
HOWEVER, IF JAMES COMEY WERE TO
GO OUT AND SAY YES, THE
PRESIDENT TRIED TO OBSTRUCT
JUSTICE AND INTERFERE, THAT'S A
MAJOR PROBLEM.
AT THE SAME TIME WE ARE ALSO
SEEING REPUBLICANS AND THE
COUNTRY AS A WHOLE SHOWS VERY
LITTLE ATTENTION BEING PAID TO
THIS IN COMPARISON.
LAURA: THE MILLION-DOLLAR
QUESTION, HE IS GOING TO PICK A
NEW PERSON.
WHAT KIND OF PERSON SHOULD HE
PICK?
WHO WILL HEAT PICK?
>> TWO VERY DIFFERENT QUESTIONS.
I THINK HE SHOULD PICK SOMEONE
OF INDEPENDENCE, NO TIES TO
POLITICS, SOMEONE LIKE RAY
KELLY, MIKE LEE OF UTAH
SUGGESTED MERRICK GARLAND, THE
JUDGE NOMINATED BY THE DEMOCRA
DEMOCRATS, SOME OF THE LIKE THAT
WOULD BE IDEAL.
MY PREDICTION HE WILL PICK JOHN
CORNYN, THE TEXAS SENATOR WHO
HAS BEEN A LOYAL DEFENDER OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP THROUGH THE
WHOLE INVESTIGATION.
>> DOUG JUST BIT ON THE MERRICK
HARLAND BAIT BECAUSE AS
REPUBLICANS WE WOULD ABSOLUTELY
SUPPORT THAT.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS SOMEONE WHO
CAN PASS 100 - 0.
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE BEING
MENTIONED ARE ALL VERY QUALIFIED
AND CAPABLE.
I AGREE WITH DOUG THAT JOHN
CORNYN WOULD BE A FANTASTIC
PICK.
HE HAS THE RESPECT OF THE SENATE
ON BOTH SIDES OF THE AISLE AND
HE UNDERSTANDS LAW-ENFORCEMENT
AS WELL AS HOW TO WORK WITH
CAPITOL HILL AND OTHERS.
LAURA: THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
BEING HERE.
ALWAYS INTERESTING.
IT WILL BE A VERY BIG WEEK.
WE WANT TO REMIND YOU TO TURN IN
LATER FOR JUDGE JEANINE'S
CONVERSATION WITH TRUMP WHERE HE
ADDRESSES HIS REMARKS ABOUT
ENDING LIVE WHITE HOUSE PRESS
BRIEFINGS.
>> WHEN WE HAVE THOSE PRESS
CONFERENCES, I ACTUALLY SAID WE
SHOULDN'T HAVE THEM BECAUSE
SARAH HUCKABEE --
>> FOR A HUNDRED YEARS WE BEEN
DOING THEM.
>> BUT THERE'S NEVER BEEN ACTION
LIKE THIS.
THIS IS CRAZY.
THERE ARE HIGHER RATINGS ON
THOSE PRESS CONFERENCES --
>> WOULD YOU SERIOUSLY CONSIDER
STOPPING THOSE PRESS
CONFERENCES.
>> WE WOULD DO IT IN A DIFFERENT
WAY.
A PIECE OF TAPE OR WITH A
PERFECTLY ACCURATE BEAUTIFUL
ANSWER.
>> IN WRITING?
>> THEY ARE ASKED A HUNDRED
QUESTIONS OR 50 QUESTIONS OR 20
QUESTIONS.
IF THEY GET ONE OUT OF 50 AND
IT'S JUST A LITTLE BIT OFF, FIVE
OR 10%, THE NEXT DAY IT'S A
FRONT-PAGE STORY IN EVERY
NEWSPAPER.
PRESS CONFERENCES WEREN'T EVEN
COVERED FOR OBAMA.
THEY WERE ON C-SPAN AND C-SPAN
TO AND THERE WAS NOTHING GOING
ON.
THESE PRESS CONFERENCES LIKE THE
THING ON DAYTIME TELEVISION.
THEY'RE BLOWING AWAY EVERYTHING
ON DAYTIME TELEVISION.
WHAT I WOULD LOVE TO DO IS STOP
THEM.
LAURA: SEE THE REST OF THAT
CONVERSATION ON JUSTICE WITH
JEANINE, JUDGE JEANINE,
9:00 P.M. EASTERN RIGHT HERE ON
THE FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
A 39-YEAR-OLD POLITICAL OUTSIDER
BECAME THE YOUNGEST PRESIDENT IN
FRENCH HISTORY.
WHAT HE VOWED TO DO IN FRONT OF
A DIVIDED NATION IN HIS
INAUGURATION SPEECH.
AND NEARLY 400 FALLEN OFFICERS
HONORED IN A SPECIAL VIGIL IN
WASHINGTON D.C.
THAT STORY, STRAIGHT AHEAD.
>> IT'S BETTER TO LIGHT ONE
CANDLE THAN TO CURSE THE
DARKNESS.
TONIGHT WE WILL ALL BE LIGHTING
A CANDLE AND LET'S CARRY THE
LIGHT OF THAT CANDLE TO OUR
FAMILIES AND COMMUNITIES AND
SYNAGOGUES AND CHURCHES AND
MOSQUES
MORE PEOPLE THAN EVER
ARE MAKING THE MOVE TO NISSAN.
BECAUSE OF ROGUE,
THE BEST SELLING SUV IN AMERICA.
TITAN, WITH AMERICA'S BEST
TRUCK WARRANTY.
AND THE MOST ADVANCED
SAFETY FEATURES ON ALITMA
AND OUR BEST SELLING MODELS.
THAT'S WHY WE'RE AMERICA'S
FASTEST-GROWING AUTO BRAND.
GET 0% FINANCING
FOR UP TO 72 MONTHS
ON 11 MODELS.
♪
Imagine if the things you
bought every day
earned you miles to
get to the places
you really want to go.
With the United MileagePlus
Explorer Card,
you'll get a free checked bag,
2 United Club passes...
Priority boarding...
and 50,000 bonus miles.
Everything you need
for an unforgettable vacation.
The United MileagePlus
Explorer Card.
Imagine where it will take you.
If you have moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis,
isn't it time
to let the real you
shine through?
Introducing Otezla, apremilast.
Otezla is not an injection
or a cream.
It's a pill that treats
plaque psoriasis differently.
Some people who took Otezla
saw 75% clearer skin
after 4 months.
And Otezla's
prescribing information
has no requirement for
routine lab monitoring.
Don't take Otezla
if you are allergic
to any of its ingredients.
Otezla may increase
the risk of depression.
Tell your doctor
if you have a history
of depression
or suicidal thoughts,
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should
monitor your weight
and may stop treatment.
Side effects
may include
diarrhea, nausea,
upper respiratory
tract infection,
and headache.
Tell your doctor
about all the
medicines you take,
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ask your dermatologist
about Otezla today.
Otezla.
Show more of you.
LAURA: NATIONAL POLICE WEEK IS
UNDERWAY AS THE COUNTRY HONORS
FALLEN POLICE OFFICERS.
FLAGS FLYING HALF STAFFED AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THEY ARE KICKING OFF THE WEEK OF
REMEMBRANCE WITH THE VIGIL,
SATURDAY, RECOGNIZING 400
OFFICERS KILLED IN THE LINE OF
DUTY.
EACH NAME READ ALOUD DURING THE
CEREMONY.
ATTORNEY GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS
HAD THIS TO SAY.
>> EACH OF THESE OFFICERS WAS
MORE THAN JUST A NAME.
THEY WERE PERSONS WHO MEANT THE
WHOLE WORLD TO SOMEONE, TO A
PARENT, SIBLING, SPOUSE OR A
CHILD.
WE ALSO REMEMBER THE ZEROS
BECAUSE THAT IS OUR WAY OF
REPAIRING A DEBT THAT CAN NEVER
BE FULLY REPAID.
>> 143 OF THE OFFICERS DIED LAST
YEAR WHILE THE OTHER 251 DIED
BEFORE 2016.
LAURA: EMMANUEL MACRON
OFFICIALLY BECOMING THE YOUNGEST
PRESIDENT IN FRENCH HISTORY.
VOTERS LOOKING ON AS THE
39-YEAR-OLD IS SWORN IN AND LEFT
THE MESSAGE OF ENCOURAGEMENT IN
HIS INAUGURATION SPEECH.
>> I AM VERY PROUD TODAY TO
PARTICIPATE IN THE INAUGURATION
OF EMMANUEL MACRON BECAUSE HE
REPRESENTS A HOPE FOR ME.
>> I HADN'T VOTED FOR HIM BUT I
AM CONFIDENT AND HOPE HE WILL BE
A GOOD PRESIDENT.
>> THE 39-YEAR-OLD LYRICAL
OUTSIDER BOWED TO REFORM THE
FRENCH ECONOMY AND TO RESTORE
FRANCE'S STANDING IN THE WORLD.
EMMANUEL MACRON IS A FOREIGN
INVESTMENT BANKER AND ALSO THE
FRENCH PRESIDENT ELECTED OUTSIDE
THE TWO MAINSTREAM PARTIES.
HE IS AN UNAPOLOGETIC SUPPORTER
OF THE EUROPEAN UNION AND WILL
MEET WITH CHANCELLOR ANDREA
MERKEL MONDAY.
THEY WORK TOGETHER TO STABILIZE
THE EU AFTER BRITAIN DECIDED TO
LEAVE THIS YOU LAST SUMMER.
HE IS NO POPULACE.
HE PAINTED A PICTURE TODAY OF
THE FRENCH ECONOMY THAT WILL
NEED TO EMBRACE AND GROW WITH
TECHNOLOGY.
IT WILL NEED TO BE OPEN TO THE
WORLD.
THE MESSAGE TODAY TO THE FRENCH
PRESIDENT IS TO EMBRACE THE
FUTURE AND EMBRACE IT WITH
FRENCH VALUES.
>> THE FRENCH PEOPLE HAVE ALWAYS
KNOWN HOW TO FIND THE ENERGY AND
THE SPIRIT OF HOW TO CONFRONT
PROFOUND CHANGE.
THAT IS WHERE WE STAYE STANFORDS
THIS MISSION I WILL HUMBLY SERVE
OUR PEOPLE.
>> DESPITE BEING ELECTED BY A
MASSIVE MAJORITY, DEFEATING
MAUREEN LE PEN, HE INHERITS I
FRACTURED COUNTRY WITH DEEP
DIVISION OVER FRANCE'S ROLE IN
EUROPE AND IMMIGRATION.
HE WILL HAVE TO FOUR VOTERS
AGAIN IN THE COMING WEEKS WITH
THE PARLIAMENT TERRY ELECTIONS
IN JUNE.
>> HIS NEW PARTY WILL NEED TO
SCORE A BIG WIN OR HE WILL BE
FORCED TO SHARE POWER WITH THE
PEOPLE HE HAS REPEATEDLY
CRITICIZED.
LAURA: THANK YOU.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
MOVING FORWARD ON PLANS TO BUILD
THE BORDER WALL AND PROGRESS IS
ABOUT TO TAKE A BIG STEP.
>> DO NOT WORRY, WE ARE GOING TO
BUILD THE WALL.
DON'T WORRY.
DON'T EVEN THINK ABOUT IT
per roll
More "Doing Chores For Dad"
More "Earning Something
You Love" per roll
Bounty is more absorbent,
so the roll can last 50% longer
than the leading ordinary brand.
So you get more "Life" per roll.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker Upper
LAURA: THE FLOW OF ILLEGAL
IMMIGRANTS INTO THE U.S. HAS
DROPPED DRAMATICALLY.
THAT IS NOT STOPPING PRESIDENT
TRUMP FROM PUSHING AHEAD WITH
HIS SIGNATURE CAMPAIGN PROMISES,
BUILDING A BORDER WALL.
CONSTRUCTION CONTRACTS WILL SOON
BE ANNOUNCED.
WILL CAR JOINS US WITH MORE FROM
L.A.
WHERE DO THINGS STAND RIGHT NOW?
>> IT APPEARS IT IS ONE STEP
CLOSER TO REALITY.
THERE IS STILL A BIG QUESTION,
WHO WILL FOOT THE BILL THAT
COULD RANGE FROM
20 - $70 BILLION.
LAST NIGHT JUDGE JEANINE ASKED
PRESIDENT TRUMP ABOUT HIS PLANS.
LISTEN TO HIS RESPONSE.
>> ARE YOU WANT TO BUILD THE
WALL.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IS THERE A QUESTION ABOUT THAT.
THERE IS NO QUESTION ABOUT IT.
>> MORE THAN 600 COMPANIES
SIGNED UP TO DESIGN THE WALL.
THE FINALISTS, WHICH WILL BE
ANNOUNCED SOON, WILL BUILD
PROTOTYPES NEAR THE BORDER IN
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA.
ONE COMPANY IS DARTH HOLS PULSE
TECHNOLOGY.
IT WILL HAVE CONNECTION FIBERS
BUILT IN AND UNDERNEATH.
>> WHERE WE CAN'T GET A WALL
BUILT DUE TO A TRAIN OR
ENVIRONMENTAL REASON, I THINK
HAVING SOME SORT OF CENTER IS
PART OF THAT PROCESS.
>> COOL TECHNOLOGY, BUT AGAIN IT
WILL COME WITH A PRICE.
YOU REMEMBER PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
MAINTAINED MEXICO WILL PAY FOR
THE WALL, BUT THE NEIGHBOR TO
THE SOUTH CONTINUES TO SAY THAT
IS NOT GOING TO HAPPEN BEFORE WE
MENTIONED AT THE TOP THAT BORDER
CROSSINGS ARE DOWN.
DO WE KNOW WHY?
>> BORDER AUTHORITIES ATTRIBUTE
THE DROP TO THE SUPPORT THEY ARE
RECEIVING FROM THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION AND NEWS COVERAGE
OF IMMIGRATION BUS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
WHEN YOU ADDED UP, THE NUMBERS
HAVE DROPPED DRAMATICALLY.
>> BACK IN OCTOBER, NOVEMBER,
DECEMBER WE HAD BETWEEN
750 - 900 PEOPLE A DAY.
NOW WE ARE AVERAGING 150, 145 ON
A DAILY BASIS.
THAT FREES UP BORDER DETENTION
CENTERS THAT ALLOWS THEM TO HOLD
THEM FOR COURT DOWN THE LINE
WHICH NORMALLY DOESN'T HAPPEN.
LAURA: THANK YOU.
ONE MAN PROVING YOU ARE NEVER
TOO OLD TO PURSUE YOUR DREAM AND
BREAK RECORDS WHILE YOU ARE AT
IT.
HIS INCREDIBLE FLIGHT HIGH ABOVE
THE GROUND.
♪ I'M LIKE A BIRD I DON'T KNOW
WHERE MY SOUL IS ♪
♪ I DON'T KNOW WHERE MY HOME IS
♪
Lilly.
She pretty much lives in her
favorite princess dress.
But once a week
I let her play sheriff
so I can wash it.
I use Tide to get out
those week old stains
and Downy
to get it fresh and soft.
You are free to go.
Tide and Downy
together.
DearThere's no other
way to say this.
It's over.
I've found a permanent
escape from monotony.
Together, we are
perfectly balanced,
our senses awake,
our hearts racing as one.
I know this is sudden,
but they say: If you
love something...
set it free.
See you around, Giulia
♪
I'm Dr. Kelsey McNeely and some
day you might be
calling me an energy farmer.
♪
Energy lives here.
Whoa,I just had to push one
button to join.
It's like I'm in the
office with you,
even though I'm here.
It's almost like the
virtual reality
of business communications.
No, it's reality.
Intuitive one touch video
conferencing is a reality.
And now it's included at
no additional cost
with Vonage Business.
See why 3,000 companies
a month are switching
to Vonage.
Business Grade.
People Friendly.
I wantI did my AncestryDNA
and where I came from.
and I couldn't wait
to get my pie chart.
The most shocking result was
that I'm 26% Native American.
I had no idea.
Just to know this
is what I'm made of,
this is where
my ancestors came from.
And I absolutely want to know
more about my
Native American heritage.
It's opened up
a whole new world for me.
Discover the story
only your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now at
AncestryDNA.com.
Anyone ever have occasional
constipation,diarrhea,
gas or bloating?
She does.
Help defend against
those digestive issues.
Take Phillips' Colon Health
Probiotic Caps daily
with three types of
good bacteria.
400 likes? Wow!
Try Phillips'
Colon Health.