THAT'S IT FOR THE SPECIAL REPORT
FROM WASHINGTON WHERE WE REMAIN
PROUD AND FEARLESS.
HAVE A GREAT FATHER'S DAY
WEEKEND.
>>> THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
NO WORD FROM THE COMMANDER IN
CHIEF AS THE UNITED STATES GETS
READY TO STEP INTO ANOTHER WAR.
INSTEAD, THE PRESIDENT'S
STAFFERS LAY OUT A VAGUE PLAN TO
ARM THE REBELS IN SYRIA.
>> THERE NEEDS TO BE A
CONSEQUENCE FOR A REGIME THAT
USES CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
>> NOW THE UNITED STATES IS
PLANNING TO SEND MILITARY
ASSISTANCE.
CRITICS SAY WE NEED TO DO MORE.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT GIVING
THEM MORE LIGHT WEAPONS?
IT IS INSANE.
>> AND WHY THIS IS NOT ABOUT
ONLY SYRIA BUT AN ENTIRE REGION
THREATENING TO BLOW UP WITH HELP
FROM THE TERRORIST GROUP
HEZBOLLAH AND THE IRANIANS.
AMERICAN INTERESTS AT STAKE AND
THE PRESIDENT'S NEXT MOVE.
>>> A SPORTS BAR DECK COLLAPSES.
DOZENS OF PEOPLE PLUNGE INTO THE
WATER.
>> WE JUST SAW THE BAR FALLING
INTO THE BAY.
TONIGHT A LOOK AT THE FIRST
FRANTIC MOMENTS AFTER THE DECK
CAME CRASHING DOWN AT CHECKERS.
BUT FIRST FROM FOX THIS FRIDAY
NIGHT, OUR NATION IS ABOUT TO
GET INVOLVED IN A CIVIL WAR IN
THE MIDDLE EAST.
THINK OF IT.
MAKE NO MISTAKE, IT IS A PROXY
WAR.
THE PLAYERS INCLUDE HEZBOLLAH,
LEBANON, RUSSIA AND THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT ON ONE SIDE WITH THE
SYRIAN REBELS AND NOW THE UNITED
STATES ON THE OTHER.
SO WHAT'S THE GOAL?
WHAT'S THE END GAME?
WHAT ARE THE LIMITS?
WHAT IF WE HELP THE REBELS AND
THE IRAN AND THE OTHER SIDE
WINS?
WHAT THEN?
IF THE WHITE HOUSE KNOWS OR HAS
A PLAN, IT IS NOT TELLING THE
AMERICAN PEEL.
LAST NIGHT THE WHITE HOUSE, NOT
THE PRESIDENT, ANNOUNCED THE
U.S. NOW HAS HIGH CONFIDENCE
THAT THE SYRIAN REGIME HAS USED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS TO KILL AT
LEAST 100 PEOPLE.
PRESIDENT OBAMA HAS SAID THAT
THE USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS
WOULD CROSS A RED LINE AND HIS
ADMINISTRATION IS MAKING MOVES
TO START ARMING SYRIAN
OPPOSITION FORCES.
WHAT KIND OF MOVES?
A GOOD QUESTION.
>> I'M NOT ABLE TO PROVIDE
DETAILS OF WHAT WE WILL PROVIDE
BUT IT IS A DIFFERENT SCALE AND
SCOPE OF WHAT WE'VE PROVIDED IN
THE PAST.
>> SHE DOES SAY THE OPTIONS DO
NOT INCLUDE PUTTING AMERICAN
TROOPS ON THE GROUND.
THE UNITED NATIONS ESTIMATES AT
LEAST 93,000 PEOPLE HAVE DIED IN
SYRIA'S TWO-YEAR CIVIL WAR.
SOME REPUBLICAN LAWMAKERS SAY WE
NEED TO DO MORE TO HELP THE
CIVILIANS DYING AT THE HANDS OF
A DICTATOR.
MARCO RUBIO RELEASE AD STATEMENT
WHICH READS IN PART, THERE IS NO
MORE TIME FOR HALF MEASURES.
OF COURSE, SYRIA IS SO
IMPORTANT, LARGELY BECAUSE OF
ITS LOCATION.
RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF AN
ALREADY VERY TENSE REGION.
TO THE EAST, JUST PAST IRAQ IS
IRAN.
AND AN ALLY THAT HAS BEEN
SENDING SUPPLIES TO THE SYRIAN
REGIME.
ON THE SYRIA'S WESTERN BORDER,
LEBANON WHERE THE TERRORIST
GROUP HEZBOLLAH RENEWED ITS
PLEDGE OF ASSISTANCE TO SYRIA'S
LEADER.
AND SOUTH OF THAT IS ISRAEL.
A NATION WHICH RECENTLY TARGETED
SUSPECTED WEAPONS SHIPMENTS NEAR
DAMASCUS AND TO SYRIA'S NORTH,
TURKEY WHERE THE GOVERNMENT IS
ENGAGED IN A CRACKDOWN OF ITS
OWN AGAINST PROTESTERS.
MORE CONTEXT ON ALL OF THAT IN A
MOMENT ALONG WITH SYRIA'S
REACTION.
FIRST LET'S GET TO ED HENRY AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
IF YOU CAN, PLEASE EXPLAIN TO US
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING IN THE
BUILDING BEHIND YOU.
>> Reporter: THEY'RE BEING AS
VAGUE AT THE WHITE HOUSE AS YOU
SAID A MOMENT AGO IN TERMS OF
DETAILS OF EXACTLY WHAT THE U.S.
MILITARY IS GOING TO DO.
WHAT WE'VE BEEN ABLE TO PIECE
TOGETHER ARE INDICATIONS THAT
WE'RE GOING TO BE SENDING SMALL
ARMS.
NOT THE HEAVY ARMS.
NOT THE ANTI-AIRCRAFT MISSILES
THAT SENATOR JOHN McCAIN AND
OTHERS HAVE BEEN SAYING YOU
REALLY NEED TO HELP THE REBELS
TURN THE TIDE AGAINST PRESIDENT
ASSAD.
ABOUT ALL THEY ARE SAYING
DIRECTLY IS THAT THEY IN NO WAY
PLAN TO SEND U.S. GROUND TROOPS
TO HAVE A DIRECT WAR INSIDE
SYRIA.
TAKE A LISTEN TO BEN RHODES.
>> WE DON'T THINK IT IS IN OUR
NAL NATIONAL INTERESTS TO SEND
TROOPS.
WE NEED TO BE HUMBLE ABOUT OUR
ABILITY TO SOLVE A PROBLEM LIKE
SYRIA.
CERTAINLY ON OUR OWN.
>> Reporter: AND THE OTHER THING
THEY'RE BASICALLY RULING OUT AT
LEAST IN THE SHORT TERM IS A
NO-FLY ZONE OVERSEER I CAN'T.
YOU'LL REMEMBER THE PRESIDENT
ADVOCATED THAT.
THAT WORKED IN 2011 HELPED GET
GADHAFI OUT OF POWER.
THEY'RE SAYING AT THE WHITE
HOUSE, IT WILL BE MUCH MORE
EXPENSIVE AND COMPLICATED TO
ACTUALLY IMPLEMENT THAT OVERSEER
I CAN'T SO THEY'RE NOT PLANNING
TO DO THAT.
>> WE ENDED UP IN IRAQ FOR
ANOTHER DECADE.
THAT DIDN'T WORK ANY WAY.
ONE MORE THING.
90,000 PLUS PEOPLE DID.
YET THE FOCUS STILL SEEMS TO BE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
>> Reporter: RIGHT.
THE WHITE HOUSE TRIED TO PUSH
BACK ON THAT DICHOTOMY OF SAYING
OF COURSE THEY CARE ABOUT THE
90,000 WHO HAVE BEEN KILLED.
IT IS NOT JUST ABOUT THE RED
LINE OVER THE CHEMICAL WEAPONS
THAT APPARENTLY KILL 150 PEOPLE
IN SYRIA.
THEY SAY THEY CARE ENOUGH ABOUT
THE TENS OF THOUSANDS THAT THAT
IS WHY THEY SAID ASSAD SHOULD GO
MONTHS AGO.
THAT'S WHY THEY IMPLEMENTED
SANCTIONS TO TRY TO PUSH HIM OUT
OF POWER.
BUT JOHN McCAIN SAID THAT IS NOT
GOOD ENOUGH.
HE SAID THE PROBLEM HERE IS
THERE'S BEEN TOO MUCH FOCUS ON
THAT RED LINE.
NOT ENOUGH ON THE FOCUS ON THE
SLAUGHTER OF THE SYRIAN PEOPLE.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> WE'VE DETERMINED THAT ASSAD
HAS KILLED ABOUT 100 TO 150
PEOPLE WITH CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
HOW DID HE KILL THE OTHER
93,000?
IT IS JUST, WHAT THE PRESIDENT
DID WAS HE GAVE THEM A RED LINE
BUT GAVE THEM A GREEN LIGHT TO
DO EVERYTHING ELSE.
>> YOU MENTIONED WE HAVE NOT
HEARD FROM THE PRESIDENT IN ALL
OF THIS IN THE LAST FEW DAYS.
WHEN WE WILL HEAR FROM HIM IS
NEXT WEEK.
THE G-8 SUMMIT IN NORTHERN
IRELAND.
HE'LL BE MEETING WITH ALLIES
LIKE THE BRITS AND THE FRENCH
WHO HAVE BEEN VERY ACTIVE ON
THIS ISSUE.
BUT ALSO INTERESTING, THE
PRESIDENT ON MONDAY WILL HAVE A
ONE-ON-ONE MEETING WITH THE
RUSSIAN PRESIDENT VLADIMIR
PUTIN.
RUSSIA HAS NOT BEEN AN ALLY ON
THIS.
RUSSIA IS HELPING ASSAD IN
SYRIA.
THAT WILL BE A PIVOTAL MEETING
ON MONDAY.
>> THE SYRIAN REGIME IS NOW
ACCUSING THE UNITED STATES OF
USING CHEAP TACTICS IN PUTTING
OUT A STATEMENT THAT WAS FULL OF
LIES.
IN RUSSIA A TOP FOREIGN AFFAIRS
ADVISER TO THE PRESIDENT SAID
THE CLAIMS DID NOT LOOK
CONVINCING.
LET'S GET TO THE FOX REPORT'S
CHIEF CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN
HUNT.
THERE IS A LITTLE MORE GOING ON
ON SYRIA.
>> IF YOU'RE LOOKING TO ANSWER
THE QUESTION WHY NOW FOR U.S.
ACTION, THE DEPUTY NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER BEN RHODES
ADMITTED THAT REBEL LOSSES
THE GROUND IN SYRIA HAD AT LEAST
AS MUCH TO DO WITH CHANGING
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S CALCULUS AS
DID THE USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
>> PARTICULARLY URGENT RIGHT NOW
IN TERMS OF THE SITUATION ON THE
GROUND IN SOME RESPECT, BECAUSE
WE HAVE SEEN HEZBOLLAH AND IRAN
INCREASE THEIR OWN INVOLVEMENT
IN THE CONFLICT.
>> AND HEZBOLLAH FIGHTERS HAVE
MADE A VERY REAL DIFFERENCE.
JOINING PRESIDENT ASSAD'S FORCES
IN THE RECENT BATTLE FOR THE
CRUCIALLY IMPORTANT TOWN OF
QUSAIR AND WINNING ALONGSIDE THE
EARL OF PRESIDENT ASSAD.
THAT BY THE WAY WAS A CITY THAT
THE REBELS HAD HELD FOR ONE
YEAR.
>> THE VIEWERS WILL REMEMBER
THAT HEZBOLLAH FOUGHT ISRAEL IN
THE SOUTH OF LEBANON AND
ACCORDING TO MANY OBSERVERS,
ISRAEL LOST.
NOW HEZBOLLAH'S LEADER IS
SPEAKING OUT ON THIS.
>> YEAH.
HE GAVE A SPEECH IN ONE OF HIS
STRONGHOLDS AT BEIRUT, LEBANON.
HE SAID THAT HEZBOLLAH HAS MADE
A CALCULATED DECISION TO SUPPORT
PRESIDENT ASSAD OF SYRIA AND
THEY WILL CONTINUE TO DO SO.
ACCORDING TO DAVID SHENKER OF
THE WASHINGTON INSTITUTE, THAT
SORT OF SUPPORT MAKES A REAL
DIFFERENCE.
LISTEN.
>> THEY ARE GETTING THE SUPPORT
FROM RUSSIA, HEZBOLLAH, THEY CAN
REVERSE THE MOMENTUM ENTIRELY
AND WIN.
THIS IS NOT IN OUR INTERESTS
EITHER.
>> NOW YOU HAVE HEZBOLLAH, IRAN
AND FOR THE MOMENT, AT LEAST,
RUSSIA ON ONE SIDE OF THIS
CONFLICT.
THE U.S. AND OTHER WESTERN
POWERS ON THE OTHER.
YOU HAVE THIS MAJOR SPLIT
BETWEEN SUNNI AND SHIA MUSLIMS.
THIS WHATEVER PATH WE CHOOSE
WILL NOT BE EASY.
>> AND VERY COMPLICATED.
WE DID GET WORD OF MASS
DEFECTIONS OF SYRIAN OFFICIALS.
TURKISH STATE MEDIA REPORT AS
MANY AS 73 SYRIAN MILITARY
OFFICERS AND THEIR FAMILIES HAVE
JUST CROSSED THE BORDER INTO
TURKEY WHERE THEY'RE SEEKING
REFUGE.
202 MEN, WOMEN AND CHILDREN IN
ALL, THEY TELL US.
ACCORDING TO THE REPORT THEY ARE
NOW IN A TURKISH REFUGEE CAMP
WITH OTHER DEIF HE CANNERS.
>>> A QUICK UPDATE ON THE NUMBER
OF HIGH CRIMINAL PROFILES WE'RE
FOLLOWING.
FIRST, THE JUDGE REJECTED THE
FT. HOOD SOLDIER'S DEFENSE THAT
HE SHOT TALIBAN LEADERS IN
AFGHANISTAN.
THE JUDGE SAID NONE OF THE
SOLDIERS POSED AN IMMEDIATE
THREAT TO ANYBODY OVERSEAS.
MAJOR YOU NEEDAL HASAN IS FACING
MANY COUNTS OF MURDER.
>>> AND GEORGE ZIMMERMAN HAS A
BOOK CALLED FLORIDA V.
ZIMMERMAN.
UNCOVERING THE MALICIOUS
PROSECUTION OF MY SON, GEORGE.
THE JUDGE ORDERED 23 POTENTIAL
JURORS TO RUSH TO COURT ON
TUESDAY FOR ANOTHER ROUND OF
QUESTIONING.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN HAS PLEAD NOT
GUILTY TO MURDER IN THE
SECOND-DEGREE AND SAID HE SHOT
AND KILLED THE UNARMED TEENAGER
TRAYVON MARTIN IN SELF-DEFENSE.
>>> IN THE TRIAL OF THE ACCUSED
MOB BOSS, TWO BOOKIES TESTIFIED
ABOUT THE THREATS THEY HEARD
FROM HIS ASSOCIATES.
PAY UP OR GET HURT.
EVEN KILLED.
WHITEY BULGER STANDS ACCUSED OF
TAKING PART IN 19 MURDERS IN THE
1970s.
A BIG REVELATION THAT COULD
BENEFIT MICHAEL JACKSON'S MOTHER
IN HER ENORMOUS CIVIL LAWSUIT
AGAINST AEG LIVE.
THAT IS THE COMPANY THAT
PROMOTED HER SON'S ILL-FATED
COMEBACK TOUR.
KATHERINE JACKSON SAID THE
COMPANY DID NOT PROPERLY
INVESTIGATE HER SON'S PERSONAL
PHYSICIAN CONRAD MURRAY.
TODAY THE CEO OF THAT COMPANY
AEG LIVE TESTIFIED THAT HE
RECEIVED CONFLICTING INFORMATION
ABOUT THE SINGER'S HEALTH JUST
DAYS BEFORE HIS DEATH.
FIRST, TOURING STAFF TOLD HIM IN
AN E-MAIL THAT JACKSON WAS
SHIVERING AND WOULD NOT EAT.
BUT HOURS LATER HE SAID THE
SINGER APPEARED FINE IN A
MEETING AND CONRAD MURRAY TOLD
HIM JACKSON WAS FINE.
A JUDGE SENTENCED MURRAY TO FOUR
YEARS IN PRISON IN 2011.
>>> ONE MINUTE THEY WERE
WATCHING A BASKETBALL GAME AT A
SPORTS BAR, AND THE NEXT THEY
WERE IN THE WATERS OF BISCAYNE
BAY.
SOME DRAMATIC IMAGES FROM
SHUCKERS BAR AND GRILL DECK
COLLAPSED JUST AHEAD.
AND THE FIRST 911 CALL FROM
FRANTIC WITNESSES.
>>> PLUS A DARING RESCUE IN THE
MIDDLE OF A FLOOD.
WAIT UNTIL YOU SEE HOW CREWS GOT
THAT LITTLE GIRL TO SAFETY.
IT'S ALL COMING UP.
...SO YOU SAY
MEN ARE SUPERIOR DRIVERS?
YEAH?
THEN HOW'D I GET THIS...
[ voice of Dennis ]
...SAFE DRIVING BONUS CHECK?
EVERY SIX MONTHS
WITHOUT AN ACCIDENT,
Allstate SENDS A CHECK.
SILENCE.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
PEOI GO TO ANGIE'S LISTTNCE.
FOR TO GAUGE WHETHER OR NOT
THE PROJECTS WILL BE DONE
IN A TIMELY FASHION
AND WITHIN BUDGET.
ANGIE'S LIST MEMBERS
CAN TELL YOU WHICH PROVIDER
IS THE BEST IN TOWN.
YOU'LL FIND REVIEWS
ON EVERYTHING
FROM HOME REPAIR TO HEALTHCARE.
NOW THAT WE'RE EXPECTING,
I LIKE THE FACT
THAT I CAN GO ONTO ANGIE'S LIST
AND LOOK FOR PEDIATRICIANS.
THE SERVICE PROVIDERS
THAT I'VE FOUND ON ANGIE'S LIST
ACTUALLY HAVE BLOWN ME AWAY.
JOIN TODAY AND FIND OUT
WHY OVER 1 MILLION MEMBERS
COUNT ON ANGIE'S LIST.
ANGIE'S LIST --
REVIEWS YOU CAN TRUST.
Yes. With New Nature
Made VitaMelts.
Can vitamins melt into
mouth-watering flavor?
Melt-in-your-mouth vitamin
supplements.
In flavors like
creamy vanilla...
...And juicy orange
Irresistibly melty
New Nature
Made VitaMelts.
Get a sample on our
facebook page
>>> THEY'RE SAYING IT WAS
PANDEMONIUM WHEN A DECK
COLLAPSED IN SOUTH FLORIDA.
WE HAVE THE FIRST 911 CALLS FROM
THE SCENE.
IT ALL HAPPENED IN MIAMI AT A
SPOT CALLED SHUCKERS BAR AND
GRILL.
YOU CAN SEE THE REMAINS OF THAT
DECK STILL SHOETING IN THE
SHALLOW WATER THEMSELVES SAY
THERE WERE ABOUT 100 PEOPLE ON
THE DECK WATCHING THE MIAMI HEAT
TAKE ON THE SAN ANTONIO SPURS IN
THE NBA FINALS.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, A LOUD BANG AND
THE DECK GAVE WAY.
>> ONCE THERE WAS 100 OR SO
PEOPLE DINING AND WATCHING THE
GAME.
NOW THERE WAS NOTHING.
DARKNESS.
YOU LOOK DOWN AND IN THE WATER,
THERE WERE THESE PEOPLE
SCREAMING AND SCRAMBLING TO TRY
TO GET OUT.
>> OUR LOCAL FOX STATION IS
RIGHT NEXT DOOR AND THEY GOT
THERE QUICKLY.
LOOK WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE IN THE
FEW MOMENTS AFTER THAT DECK
CRASHED INTO THE WATER.
THE WATER SHALLOW.
A FEW FEET DEEP.
FIVE TO TEN.
911 CALLERS DESCRIBE WHAT THEY
WERE SEEING.
>> WHAT IS YOUR EMERGENCY?
>> I'M AT SHUCKERS BAR AND GRILL
AND THE DECK JUST TOTALLY AND
COMPLETELY COLLAPSED.
THERE ARE AT LEAST 100 AT LEAST
PEOPLE IN THE WATER RIGHT NOW.
>> SO THE DECK COLLAPSED AND
EVERYONE IS IN THE WATER?
>> TOTALLY.
THE DECK COLLAPSED.
AT LEAST 100 PEOPLE IN THE
WATER.
OTHER PEOPLE ARE GOING TO SAVE
THEM BUT IT IS HORRIBLE.
>> MIAMI-DADE KOINL POLICE AND
FIRE.
>> THERE IS AN EMERGENCY IN
SHUCKERS IN MIAMI-DADE.
>> WHAT'S THE ADDRESS?
>> IT'S -- I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE
ADDRESS IS.
>> TRY TO CALM DOWN, OKAY?
>> THE WHOLE DECK AND THE WHOLE
BAR FELL AND EVERYONE IS IN THE
WATER.
I DON'T KNOW WHETHER THEY'RE
OKAY.
>> REMEMBER IT WAS DARK AND
FRIGHTENING.
A LOT OF PANIC AND A LOT OF
PEOPLE HURT.
PHIL KYOTOING
PHIL KEATING IS IN DOWNTOWN
MIAMI.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS HAVE
RULED OUT FOUL PLAY.
THE CAUSE OF THIS DECK COLLAPSE
STILL UNKNOWN.
NORMALLY THIS TIME OF NIGHT
EVERY TABLE WOULD BE FULL OF
LOCALS AND TOURISTS DRINKING AND
DINING.
INSTEAD ALL OF IT IS IN BISCAYNE
BAY.
INVESTIGATORS PHOTOGRAPHED THE
SCENE.
IT HAS SURVIVED NUMEROUS
HURRICANES AND THEY SAID IT WAS
BUILT TO HOLD OVER 100 PEOPLE
SAFELY.
TWO DOZEN PEOPLE WERE TAKEN TO
HOSPITALS.
ONE MAN WITH A BROKEN LEG BUT
MOSTLY CUTS, SPRAINS AND
STITCHES.
TWO PEOPLE REMAIN IN SERIOUS
CONDITION.
NUMEROUS CUSTOMERS AND EMPLOYEES
HEROICALLY PULLED PEOPLE OUT OF
THE WATER TO SAFETY.
ONE SURVIVOR TELLS US, EVERYONE
WAS ENJOYING THE EVENING AND
CHEERING FOR THE MIAMI HEAT WHEN
IN A FLASH, SHE REALLY BELIEVED
SHE WAS ABOUT TO DROWN.
>> OKAY.
THAT'S IT.
TODAY THIS IS THE END.
I TRIED TO GET OUT OF THE WATER
AND I GOT THIS TABLE ON TOP OF
ME IN A CHAIR AROUND MY LEG.
>> Reporter: SHE AND OTHER
SURVIVORS NOW HAVE NEW PROBLEMS.
THEIR PURSES, WALLETS, BILL
FOLDS, CREDIT CARDS, I.D.'S,
EVEN THEIR CAR KEYS REMAIN UNDER
WATER.
>> WOW, PHIL KEATING ON THE
CAUSE WAY OF MIAMI.
THE INTERIOR OF THE BAR AND
GRILL IS NOT AFFECTED BY THE
COLLAPSE.
FOR NOW SHUCKERS IS CLOSED.
THE OWNERS ARE NOT SAYING WHEN
IT WILL REOPEN.
>>> SOME MERGE WORKERS RISK
THEIR LIVES TO PULL THREE PEOPLE
FROM AN SUV IN A FLOODED DITCH.
LOOK AT THIS.
AN IOWA STATE PATROL LIEUTENANT
SAID THE DRIVER WENT OFF THE
ROAD DURING SOME HEAVY RAINS.
THE FIRST RESPONDERS ATTACHED A
HARNESS TO THE LITTLE GIRL IN
THAT SUV.
WATCH WHAT HAPPENS NEXT.
THEY PULLED HER ALONG THAT ROPE
BARELY OVER THE WATER ALL THE
WAY BACK TO THE BANK.
YOU CAN SEE THE GIRL LOOKS
SCARES BUT POLICE SAY SHE WAS
JUST FINE.
AND RESCUERS USED A RAFT TO PULL
TWO OTHER PEOPLE FROM THE
VEHICLE.
EVERYBODY IS OKAY.
IT HAPPENED IN NORTHERN IOWA IN
AN AREA NOW BRACING FOR MORE
POSSIBLE FLOODING THIS WEEKEND.
>>> THE ENORMOUS STORM THAT
SWEPT FROM THE MIDWEST ALL THE
WAY THROUGH THE MID-ATLANTIC IS
NOW BLAMED FOR KILLING AT LEAST
FIVE PEOPLE.
THREE OF THE LATEST CONFIRMED
DEATHS IN NORTH CAROLINA.
THE STORM CARRIED POWERFUL
WINDS.
MORE THAN 70 MILES AN HOUR IN
SOME SPOTS.
STRONG ENOUGH TO DAMAGE
BUILDINGS, TAKE OUT TREES AND
KNOCK OUT POWER TO HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
>> ONE DAY AFTER WE LEARN ONE OF
THE COLORADO WILDFIRES HAD
TURNED DEADLY, WE'RE GETTING A
BETTER SENSE OF HOW MASSIVE THE
MOST DESTRUCTIVE HISTORY IN
COLORADO HAS BECOME.
WE'RE LIVE IN COLORADO SPRINGS.
PLUS, ONE PSYCHIC'S APPARENT
MISTAKE HAS COST HER IN A HUGE
WAY.
WE'LL TELL YOU HOW MUCH SHE HAS
TO PAY FOR FALSELY CLAIMING
THERE WAS A MASS GRAVE OUTSIDE
SOMEBODY'S HOME.
[ Female Announcer ] CALTRATE'S
DONEVEN MORE TO MOVE US.
BECAUSE VITAMIN D3 HELPS BONES
ABSORB CALCIUM,
CALTRATE HAS THE HIGHEST LEVEL
OF VITAMIN D3.
MORE THAN
ANY OTHER BRAND,
TO HELP MAXIMIZE
CALCIUM ABSORPTION.
SO CALTRATE WOMEN
CAN MOVE THE WORLD.
>>> CREWS ARE BATTLING TO HOLD
THE LINE AGAINST THE MOST
DESTRUCTIVE WILDFIRE EVER IN
COLORADO AN AREA LARGER THAN
MANHATTAN.
SINCE IT BROKE OUT ON TUESDAY
NORTH AND EAST COLORADO SPRINGS.
WE LEARNED YESTERDAY THAT THE
FIRE TURNED DEADLY.
OFFICIAL SAY THEY'VE ORDERED A
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION AFTER
THEY FOUND TWO BODIES INSIDE A
GARAGE IN THE HEAVILY WOODED
AREA.
HOURS AGO, AUTHORITIES LIFTED
THE MANDATORY EVACUATIONS AROUND
THE CITY BUT THEY SAY THE FLAMES
HAVE DESTROYED 400 HOMES.
LOOK AT THE PATH OF THIS
DESTRUCTION IN ONE NEIGHBORHOOD.
THE BLACK AREAS MARK WHERE SOME
HOUSES ONCE STOOD WHILE OTHERS
WITHIN THAT CHARRED LANDSCAPE
MANAGED TO ESCAPE.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES ARE
STILL IN THE MIDDLE OF A
BRIEFING RIGHT NOW.
APPLAUSE BROKE OUT BECAUSE THEY
SAID THEY HAD A VERY GOOD DAY.
AND LATER IN THE AFTERNOON, LOOK
AT THIS.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENED.
RAIN.
A LOT OF IT WHICH IS MUCH, IT
WAS EXACTLY WHAT FIREFIGHTERS
NEEDED.
THEY SAID THEY HAD A TREMENDOUS
DAY TODAY BECAUSE OF THIS RAIN.
THIS IS WHAT THE SHERIFF
DESCRIBES.
LISTEN.
>> SOME THINGS FINALLY TURNED IN
OUR FAVOR.
I THINK IF YOU LOOK AT IT AS A
FIGHT, WE GOT OUR TAILS KICKED
FOR A COUPLE DAYS.
I THINK YESTERDAY WITH THE
AGREEMENT, WE SAW IT AS A DRAW.
I THINK TODAY WE DELIVERED SOME
BLOWS.
>> RICH HARVEY IS THE INCIDENT
COMMANDER WHO HAS ORGANIZED ALL
OF THE RESOURCES HERE IN
COLORADO.
RICH HARVEY ANNOUNCED THEY ARE
AT 30% CONTAINMENT.
HE THE SAY THEY ARE NOWHERE NEAR
WHERE THEY NEED TO BE AND
THEY'RE STILL BATTLING THIS
FEROCIOUS FIRE.
AND YOU MENTIONED THOSE
EVACUATION ORDERS THAT HAVE BEEN
LIFTED.
THERE ARE STILL TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE OUT OF THEIR
HOMES.
AND THE BURN AREA IS NOT
INCLUDED IN THAT SO THEY'RE
STILL UP TO 400 PEOPLE WHO STILL
DON'T KNOW WHETHER OR NOT THEY
HAVE SOMETHING TO RETURN TO.
>> THAT BLACK FOREST FIRE IS NOT
THE ONLY ONE BURNING.
THERE ARE TWO OTHERS RAGING IN
THE ROCKY MOUNTAINS.
ONE NORTH OF CORAL SPRINGS, THE
BIG MEADOW FIRE HAS AFFECTED A
FEW HUNDRED ACRES.
MEANWHILE THE ROYAL GORGE FIRE
HAS CHARRED MORE THAN 3,000
ACRES SOUTH AND WEST COLORADO
SPRINGS.
>>> A JUDGE HAS ORDERED A
SELF-PROCLAIMED PSYCHIC TO PAY
NEARLY $7 MILLION TO A COUPLE IN
TEXAS BECAUSE THAT PSYCHIC
FALSELY CLAIMED THERE WAS A MASS
GRAVE FULL OF DISMEMBERED BODIES
AT THE COUPLE'S HOME.
THE LAWSUIT FROM THE COUPLE
REPORTS THE WOMAN GOING BY THE
NAME OF ANGEL CALLED THE COPS
BACK IN 2011 SAYING THERE WERE
SMS 30 BODIES BURIED OUTSIDE
HOUSTON.
AN EXTENSIVE SEARCH OF THE
PROPERTY TURNED UP NOTHING.
THE SO-CALLED PSYCHIC TOLD THE
CHRONICLE SHE AND HER FRIENDS
WERE HAVING VISIONS ABOUT THREE
CHILDREN WHO MIGHT BE IN
TROUBLE.
IT IS STILL UNCLEAR WHETHER THE
WOMAN WILL BE ABLE TO PAY ANY OR
ALL OF THAT MONEY.
>>> THREE ENGINEERING STUDENTS
AT PURDUE SCHEMED TO HACK INTO
THEIR TEACHERS' ACCOUNTS FROM
F's TO A's.
EVEN A's TO A PLUSES.
THE PROSECUTORS SAY THE PAIR AND
AN ACCOMPLICE BROKE INTO THE
OFFICE, INSTALLED DEVICES ON KEY
BOARDS TO TRACK WHAT THEY WERE
TYPING.
THE THREE MEN FACE BURGLARY AND
COMPUTER TAMPERING CHARGES.
>>> EDWARD SNOWDEN CANNOT HIDE
FROM AMERICAN JUSTICE FOREVER.
THAT'S WHAT A TOP U.S. OFFICIAL
IS SAYING TONIGHT.
NOW THERE'S WORD THE FORMER NSA
CONTRACTOR COPIED THE CLASSIFIED
DOCUMENTS USING A DEVICE YOU MAY
ALREADY OWN.
>>> PLUS THE POLLS HAVE CLOSED
IN IRAN.
WE'RE WAITING TO FIND OUT WHO
THE PRESIDENT MAY BE.
NOW THE SUPREME LEADER IS
LASHING OUT AT THE UNITED
STATES.
AND POLICE SAY THE GUNMAN IN
THAT DEADLY SANTA MONICA
SHOOTING SPREE LEFT BEHIND A
NOTE.
DETAILS FROM THE FAREWELL
MESSAGE COMING UP AS WE APPROACH
THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR.
ursuit
we all share.
A better life for your family,
a better opportunity
for your business,
a better legacy
to leave the world.
We have always believed
in this pursuit,
striving to bring insight
to every investment,
and integrity to every plan.
We are Morgan Stanley.
And we're ready
to work for you.
LITTLE THINGS ANYONE CAN DO.
IT STEALS YOUR MEMORIES.
YOUR INDEPENDENCE.
ENSURES SUPPORT,
A BREAKTHROUGH.
AND SOONER THAN YOU'D LIKE.
SOONER THAN YOU'D THINK.
YOU DIE FROM
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
WE CURE ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
EVERY LITTLE CLICK, CALL
OR DONATION ADDS UP
TO SOMETHING BIG.
WE'RE SO CHOOSY
ABOUT THE CUTS OF BEEF
THAT MEET OUR HIGHER
KOSHER STANDARDS
THAT ONLY A SLOW-MOTION BITE
CAN CAPTURE
ALL THAT KOSHER DELIGHT.
AND WHEN YOUR HOT DOG'S KOSHER,
THAT'S A HOT DOG YOU CAN TRUST.
HEBREW NATIONAL.
>>> IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR.
TIME FOR THE TOP OF THE NEWS.
ED SNOWDEN WILL PAY THE PRICE
FOR EXPOSING NATIONAL
SURVEILLANCE AGENCY SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAMS.
THAT'S WHAT ATTORNEY GENERAL
ERIC HOLDER IS SAYING.
HE SAID THE LEAKS PUT AMERICA IN
DANGER AND I'M CONFIDENT THE
PERSON WHO IS RESPONSIBLE WILL
BE HELD ACCOUNTABLE.
AT LAST WORD, THAT PERSON WAS
REPORTEDLY HIDING OUT IN HONG
KONG THREATENING TO REVEAL MORE
SECRETS.
KATHERINE IS LIVE IN THE
NEWSROOM.
YOU'RE HEARING WE SHOULD TAKE
THIS THREAT SERIOUSLY.
>> Reporter: A PERSON FAMILIAR
WITH THE INVESTIGATION HAS
MONITORED SNOWDEN'S COMPUTER.
BASED ON HIS ELECTRONIC TRAIL
WILL YOU THE NSA COMPUTER
SYSTEMS, IT IS BELIEVED SNOWDEN
HAS MORE DOCUMENTS BEYOND A
HANDFUL OF LEAKS TO THE GUARDIAN
AND OTHER PAPERS.
AND HE SEEMS TO BOAST ABOUT WHAT
HE KNOWS.
>> I HAD ACCESS TO, YOU KNOW,
THE FULL ROSTERS OF EVERYONE
WORKING AT THE NSA.
THE ENTIRE JENGS COMMUNICATE AND
UNDERCOVER ASSETS ALL AROUND THE
WORLD.
>> Reporter: THE THREAT HE COULD
LEAK MORE CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
BASED ON THIS SEARCH IS SEEN AS
CREDIBLE.
>> NOW SOME SENATORS SAY THEY'RE
TRYING TO LIMIT THE
SURVEILLANCE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
BOTH EARLY CRITICS ARE NOW
INTRODUCING LEGISLATION THAT
WOULD LIMIT DATA COLLECTION ON
AMERICANS WHERE THERE IS NO,
WHAT THEY CALL, DEMONSTRABLE OR
VERIFIABLE LINK TO TERRORISM OR
ESPIONAGE.
THE STATEMENT READS IN PART, THE
DISCLOSURES OF THE LAST WEEK
HAVE MADE CLEAR TO THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE THE LAW IS BEING
INTERPRETED IN A WAY THAT
DAMAGES THEIR CIVIL LIBERTIES
AND THAT THE SYSTEM HAS BEEN SET
UP TO KEEP AMERICANS UNAWARE OF
THE INTRUSION.
NSA WHISTLE BLOWERS ARE RAISING
NEW QUESTIONS ABOUT A PROGRAM
PUBLICLY DESCRIBED BY THE FBI
DIRECTOR DURING CONGRESSIONAL
TESTIMONY TWO YEARS AGO.
IN THE WAKE OF THE FT. HOOD
TERRORIST ATTACK WHICH ALLOWS
FOR THE COLLECTION OF E-MAIL
FROM A U.S. CITIZEN ON U.S. SOIL
IN REAL-TIME.
WE PUT IN PLACE TECHNOLOGICAL
IMPROVEMENTS RELATING TO THE
CAPABILITIES OF A DATABASE TO
PULL TOGETHER PAST E-MAILS AND
FUTURE ONES AS THEY COME IN.
SO THAT IT DOES NOT REQUIRE AN
INDIVIDUALIZED SEARCH.
THE DATABASE IS SEPARATE FROM
THE P.R.I.S.M. PROGRAM, THE NSA
REFERRED FOX TO THE FBI AND
THERE WAS NO IMMEDIATE COMMENT
BY THE BUREAU WHERE THEY WERE
STUDYING THE TRANSCRIPT OF THE
TESTIMONY.
>> THANK YOU, MA'AM.
>>> THE BRITS ARE YOU NO
REPORTEDLY WARNING AIRLINES, DO
NOT LET ED SNOWDEN ON ANY
FLIGHTS TO THE UNITED KINGDOM.
BRITISH OFFICIALS SAY THEY WILL
NOT ALLOW HIM INTO THE COUNTRY.
AND THEY'RE THREATENING TO FINE
AIRLINES MORE THAN $3,000 IF HE
DOES GO INTO THE U.K.
THAT WILL DO IT.
I MEAN, $3,000.
THAT WILL BRING THE AIRLINE
DOWN.
NOW ONE COMMUNIST BACKED
NEWSPAPER IN CHINA IS SUGGESTING
THE GOVERNMENT HANG ON TO
SNOWDEN FOR A WHILE.
TRACE GALLAGHER, THIS GOVERNMENT
IS CALLING TO GET OUT OF HIM
WHAT THEY CAN.
>> EXACTLY.
MILK HIM OF ALL HIS INFORMATION
AND THEN SEND HIM BACK TO THE
UNITED STATES.
THEY BELIEVE THE SECRETS HE HAS
ARE VITAL TO CHINESE NATIONAL
SECURITY AND NATIONAL INTERESTS.
NOW, KEEP IN MINE THIS EDITORIAL
COMES ON THE HEEL OF SNOWDEN
SAYING THE U.S. HAS BEEN SPYING
ON HONG KONG AND CHINESE
COMPUTERS FOR YEARS.
IT READS IN PART, QUOTING HERE,
MAYBE HE HAS MORE EVIDENCE.
THE CHINESE GOVERNMENT SHOULD
LET HIM SPEAK OUT AND ACCORDING
TO WHETHER THE INFORMATION IS
PUBLIC, USE IT AS EVIDENCE TO
NEGOTIATE WITH THE UNITED STATES
OPENLY OR IN PRIVATE.
THE EDITORIAL WAS WRITTEN BY A
NEWSPAPER THAT HAS LONG
CRITICIZED THE UNITED STATES BUT
CHINA EXPERT GORDON CHENG
BELIEVES SNOWDEN TRULY IS A
BARGAINING CHIP.
LISTEN.
>> CLEARLY, BEIJING IS NOW IN A
CAT BIRD SEAT.
IT CAN DECIDE WHETHER TO KEEP
HIM OR SEND HIM BACK.
THE CHINESE WHO ARE RUTHLESSLY
PRACTICING MATTIC WILL DO
EVERYTHING THEY POSSIBLY CAN.
I THINK THAT GLOBAL TIMES
EDITORIAL THAT YOU REFERRED TO
IS ESSENTIALLY INCREASING THE
PRICE THAT WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
TO PAY TO GET SNOWDEN BACK.
WHEN WE GET HIM BACK, HE WILL
HAVE DISCLOSED EVERYTHING TO
BEIJING.
>> NOW "THE LOS ANGELES TIMES"
IS RT ROING THAT SNOWDEN SNUCK
THE TOP SECRET DOCUMENTS OUT OF
THE U.S. ON A THUMB DRIVE LIKE
THIS.
YOU KNOW THE KIND YOU BUY AT
STAPLES OR BEST BUY FOR $10.
NATIONAL SECURITY OFFICIALS TELL
FOX NEWS CHANNEL THAT THUMB
DRIVES AND OTHER OUTSIDE STORAGE
DEVICES ARE FROWNED UPON.
BUT BECAUSE HE WAS A SYSTEMS
ADMINISTRATOR HE WOULD HAVE MORE
LATITUDE TO HAVE THAT TYPE OF
STORAGE DEVICE ON HIM.
>> CBS IS CONFIRMING THAT
SOMEBODY HACKED ONE OF ITS
COMPUTERS MORE THAN ONCE LAST
YEAR.
CORRESPONDENT CHERYL ATKINSON
REPORTED THE SUSPICIOUS ACTIVITY
LAST MONTH AND NOW THE NETWORK
REPORTS AN INTRUDER ACCESSED HER
COMPUTER REMOTELY AND TRIED VERY
HARD TO REMOVE HER INFORMATION.
NOW WORD ON WHETHER THEY GOT ANY
INFORMATION AND NO COMMENT FROM
THE FBI.
>>> THE POLLS HAVE CLOSED IN
IRAN'S ELECTION BUT WE'RE STILL
WAITING FOR THE RESULTS.
THE CURRENT PRESIDENT IS ON THE
WAY OUT.
HE CAN'T RUN FOR A THIRD TERM
UNDER THE IRANIAN RULES.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY STENLED
VOTING BY FIVE HOURS BECAUSE THE
LINES ARE SO LONG.
AND THE HIGH TURNOUT COULD MEAN
MORE MODERATE VOTERS COULD SHOW
UP BUT REMEMBER THE AYATOLLAH
KHOMEINI REALLY RUNS THE
COUNTRY.
AND THIS COMMENT FROM THE
SUPREME LEADER, QUOTE, RECENTLY
I HAVE HEARD THAT A U.S.
SECURITY OFFICIAL HAS SAID THEY
DO NOT ACCEPT THIS ELECTION.
OKAY.
THE HELL WITH YOU.
>>> STOCKS TOOK A TUMBLE
FINISHING OFF A VOLATILE WEEK.
THE DOW FALLING MORE THAN 100
POINTS.
THE NASDAQ AND S&P ALSO IN THE
RED.
THE DOW SWUNG MORE THAN 200
POINTS EARLIER IN THE WEEK.
THE SEVENTH TIME IN THE PAST 15
TRADING DAYS.
IT JUST KEEPS GOING BACK AND
FORTH.
THE FOX BUSINESS NETWORK HAS THE
NEWS.
WHAT IS UP WITH THE MARKETS?
>> THE MARKETS HAVE BEEN RIDING
A REAL SEE-SAW THIS WEEK.
UP AND DOWN.
THE DOW, THE S&P AND THE NASDAQ
ALL DOWN MORE THAN 1% TODAY.
IT WAS THE THIRD TIME IN FOUR
WEEKS THAT ALL MAJOR AVERAGES
POSTED A WEEKLY LOSS.
NOW THE SLUGGISHNESS COMES AFTER
A NEW REPORT BY THOMPSON RITERS
SHOW CONSUMER CONFIDENCE FALLING
IN JUNE.
ANOTHER REPORT SHOWED FACTORIES
HAVE NOT BEEN AS BUSY AS
PROJECTED.
HERE'S THE ELEPHANT IN THE ROOM.
INVESTMENTS HAVE BEEN ON GUARD
AND JITTERY BECAUSE THEY'RE
WORRIED THE FED MAY ROLL BACK
THE STIMULUS SOON AND TAKE A
LOOK AT THIS CHART.
YOU CAN SEE THE DOW HAS BEEN
GROWING IN STEPS WITH HOW THE
FED INJECTS CASH INTO THE
ECONOMY.
BASICALLY IN SYNC THERE.
AND RECENTLY, FED CHAIR BEN
BERNANKE HAS TALKED ABOUT
SCALING BACK THE STIMULUS AND
JUST THE MERE MENTION OF THAT
HAS ROILED THE MARKET IN RECENT
WEEKS.
ALTHOUGH PULLING BACK ON THE
STIMULUS WOULD INDICATE A
POTENTIALLY HEALTHY ECONOMY,
ANALYSTS SAY YANKING IT NOW
COULD REVEAL THE GROWTH IS SOFT
AND SEND THE MARKETS TUMBLING
AGAIN.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> THE MAN WHO WENT ON THAT
DEADLY SHOOTING RAMPAGE ACROSS
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA LEFT BEHIND
A HANDWRITTEN NOTE.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM POLICE WHO
SAY THE NOTE WAS THREE OR FOUR
PAGES LONG.
IN IT HE TOLD HIS FRIENDS AND
FAMILY GOODBYE.
>> WE KNOW THAT HE LEFT BEHIND
WHAT CAN BE CALLED A FAREWELL
NOTE IN WHICH HE EXPRESSED HOPE
HIS MOTHER WOULD BE LOOKED AFTER
FINANCIALLY EVEN AS HE SAID
GOODBYE TO HIS FRIENDS AND
EXPRESSED REMORSE FOR HIS
ACTIONS IN THE KILLING OF HIS
BROTHER AND HIS FATHER.
>> POLICE SAY HE ALSO SET THEIR
HOUSE ON FIRE BEFORE HE WENT ON
A SHOOTING RAMPAGE.
THEY CAUGHT UP WITH HIM AT SANTA
MONICA COLLEGE WHERE THEY SHOT
HIM AND HE DIED.
SIX PEOPLE IN ALL.
HE WAS HEAVILY ARMED.
SOME 1,300 ROUNDS OF AMMUNITION
AND GET THIS.
TWO OFFICIALS NOW TELL THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS, HE ASSEMBLED
HIS ASSAULT STYLE RIFLE AS THEY
PUT IT IN HIS OWN BEDROOM.
>>> FLAMES AND TEAR GAS FILLED
THE STREETS.
THE PROTESTS TURNED VIOLENT AND
THAT TOPS OUR LOOK AT NEWS
AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 SECONDS.
BRAZIL.
THOUSANDS OF DEMONSTRATORS
RALLIED AGAINST NEW PUBLIC
TRANSPORTATION ARE FARE HIKES IN
THE NATION'S LARGEST CITY OF SAO
PAULO.
SOME HURLED MOLOTOV COCKTAILS.
POLICE SHOT RUBBER BULLETS INTO
THE CROWDS.
OFFICIALS SAY SEVERAL PEOPLE GOT
HURT.
STATE MEDIA REPORTS COPS MADE
MORE THAN 200 ARRESTS.
INDIA.
THE COAST GUARD RESCUED 22
PEOPLE FROM A SHIP SINKING IN
THE INDIAN OCEAN OFF THE
SOUTHERN COAST.
IT HAD BEEN ADRIFT FOR DAYS.
CREW MEMBERS SAY IT TOOK ON
WATER AS IT BATTLED ROUGH SEAS.
EVERYBODY ON BOARD GOT OUT
SAFELY.
RUSSIA.
MORE THAN 50 COMPETITORS FROM
SEVERAL COUNTRIES TAKING TO THE
SKIES FOR THE INTERNATIONAL
BALLOON MEET WEST OF MOSCOW.
TEAMS GET A COURSE TO NAVIGATE
AND 20 MINUTES TO PREPARE FOR
THE FLIGHT.
THE NINE-DAY EVENT WRAPS UP ON
SUNDAY.
>>> FRANCE.
IT IS CALLED THE DINNER IN
WHITE.
AN INVITATION ONLY PICNIC HELD
ANNUALLY AT DIFFERENT PARISIAN
LANDMARKS.
THIS YEAR SEVERAL THOUSAND FOLKS
DRESSED IN WHITE FROM HEAD TO
TOE FOR AN EVENING IN FRONT.
.
THEY KEPT IT A SECRET SINCE SUCH
GATHERINGS ARE NOT OFFICIALLY
ALLOWED IN PARIS.
THAT'S A WRAP
.
>>> WORD OF A POTENTIAL
BREAKTHROUGH FOR DEPRESSION.
IT AFFECTS MILLIONS OF PEOPLE IN
THIS COUNTRY.
THE DEPRESSION, NOT THE GRAPHIC.
CHILDREN ARE AFFECTED AS WELL.
NOW RESEARCHERS SAY THEY
DISCOVERED A SIMPLE SOLUTION TO
HELP DETERMINE HOW TO TREAT THE
DISEASE.
>>> PLUS, MEET SCHMEET.
CALL IT WHAT YOU WANT.
ONE SCIENTIST SAID HE HAS
CREATED THE FIRST HAS BEENER TO
GROWN HAMBURGER AND IT IS GOING
ON THE GRILL.
GUESS WHAT THAT THING COSTS
...SO YOU SAY
MEN ARE SUPERIOR DRIVERS?
YEAH?
THEN HOW'D I GET THIS...
[ voice of Dennis ]
...SAFE DRIVING BONUS CHECK?
EVERY SIX MONTHS
WITHOUT AN ACCIDENT,
Allstate SENDS A CHECK.
SILENCE.
ARE YOU IN GOOD HANDS?
( Bull Roar )
...if you don't attend
The Running of the Bulls.
Ole!
ICAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEVING HEARTBURN,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES
24-HOUR HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL
PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
I DID?
WHEN VISA SIGNATURE
ASKED EVERYBODY
CES
REALLY MATTERED...
YOU SUGGESTED
LUXURY CAR SERVICE
INSTD OF "STRENGTH TRAINING
WITH PATRICK WILLIS."
COME ON TODD!
FLAP THEM CHICKEN WINGS.
[ grunts ]
WELL,
I TRAVEL A LOT AND UMM...
[ Male Announcer ]
AT VISA SIGNATURE,
EVERY UPGRADEDXPERIENCE
COMES FROM LISTENING
TO OUR CARDHOLDERS.
VISA SIGNATURE.
YOUR IDEA
OF WHAT A CARD SHOULD BE.
.
>>> A POPULAR HAIR LOSS DRUG MAY
CURE YOUR DRINKING PROBLEM.
RESEARCHERS TRACKED 83 HEALTHY
YOUNG MEN UNDER THE AGE OF 46
WHO HAD STOPPED TAKING PROPECIA.
THEY FOUND THOSE GUYS APPEARED
TO DRINK MUCH LESS THAN THEY DID
BEFORE THEY STARTED TAKING
PROPECIA.
NEARLY TWO-THIRDS SAID THEY CUT
BACK FROM FIVE DRINK AS WEEK TO
TWO.
IT IS LIKELY IT INTERFERES WITH
THE ABILITY OF THE HORMONES.
>>> IT IS A DEADLY DISEASE
AFFECTING NEARLY 15 MILLION
AMERICAN ADULTS AND MILLIONS OF
CHILDREN.
IT IS CLINICAL DEPRESSION.
THE THING IS, DOCTORS SAY
TREATING IT IS DIFFICULT PROCESS
OF TRIAL AND ERROR.
AND THAT A ONE SIZE FITS ALL
APPROACH DOESN'T WORK.
NOW A GROUP OF RESEARCHERS AT
EMORY UNIVERSITY IN ATLANTA SAYS
THAT A QUICK BRAIN SCAN COULD
HELP SOLVE ALL OF THAT.
AND SAVE LIVES.
JONATHAN HAS THE NEWS TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: RESEARCHERS DO
BELIEVE NOW THAT BRAIN SCANS
WILL HELP DOCTORS PREDICT THE
BEST POSSIBLE TREATMENT FOR
THEIR PATIENTS WITH CLINICAL
DEPRESSION.
THE NEW STUDY SUGGESTS ACTIVITY
LEVELS IN A SMALL REGION OF THE
BRAIN CALLED THE ANTERIOR WILL
RESPOND TO THERAPY.
THEY MEASURE THE ACTIVITY AND
THEN RANDOMLY ASSIGN PATIENTS TO
12 WEEKS OF TREATMENT.
EITHER WITH THE COMMON
ANTI-DEPRESSANT OR PSYCHO
THERAPY.
AND HERE'S WHAT THEY FOUND.
>> THE PATIENTS WHO DO THE BEST
ON THE DRUG HAVE HIGH ACTIVITY
AND THE PATIENTS WHO DO THE BEST
ON THERAPY HAVE LOW.
>> THE GOAL IS TO GET PEOPLE
WELL AND TO DO IT AS FAST AS
POSSIBLE.
TO GET THEM WHAT THEY NEED AND
AT THE SAME TIME ENSURE WE DON'T
GIVE THEM A TREATMENT THAT WON'T
WORK FOR THEM.
>> THE HOPE IS THAT THIS WILL
LEAD TO ADDITIONAL RESEARCH THAT
ELIMINATES THE HIT AND MISS
FACTOR INVOLVED WITH TREATING
PEOPLE WITH DEPRESSION.
AN ADVOCATE WITH THE NATIONAL
ALLIANCE ON MENTAL ILLNESS SPENT
MUCH OF HER OWN LIFE WAITING FOR
A SUCCESSFUL TREATMENT TO
CONTROL HER OWN DEPRESSION.
SHE SAID ELIMINATING THAT WAIT
TIME COULD HELP.
>> IT IS A FATAL DISEASE.
MANY PEOPLE COMMIT SUICIDE AND
THEY DO IT IN THE TIME THAT
THEY'RE WAITING, QUITE OFTEN.
>> AND THE EMORY STUDY IS
PUBLISHED ONLINE.
>> THE FEDS SAY CLINICAL
DEPRESSION CAN DEVELOP AT ANY
AGE.
THE AVERAGE IS 32.
THEY SAY IT IS MORE COMMON IN
WOMEN THAN MEN.
>> SCHMEAT.
IT IS WHAT'S FOR DINNER AS LONG
AS YOU DON'T MIND YOUR DINNER
COMING FROM A PETRIE DISH.
A SIGN SAYS HE HAS GROWN A
BURGER PATTY IN A LAB.
IT TOOK TWO YEARS AND COST
$240,000.
SLIGHTLY MORE THAN YOUR AVERAGE
STEAK DINNER IN NEW YORK.
THE SCIENTIST SAID HE USED CELLS
FROM THE NECKS OF COWS AND HE
WILL GRILL IT LATER THIS MONTH
TO HELP RAISE MORE FUNDING FOR
MORE SCHMEAT.
ANIMAL RIGHTS PEOPLE SAY THEY'RE
THRILLED WITH IT.
STEAK LOVERS PROGRAMS LESS SO.
SCH-TERRIBLE.
THE GOVERNMENT IS BIG CHANGE
EVERY ON HOW IT DEAL WITH GULF
WAR ILL KNOW.
IT HAS AFFECTED THOUSANDS OF
VETERANS BUT SOME OF THE
VETERANS CLAIM THE GOVERNMENT IS
TRYING TO CHEAT THEM OUT OF
THEIR BENEFITS.
>>> PLUS A POLICE OFFICER WHO
SURVIVED THE RUN-IN WITH THE
BOSTON BOMBING SUSPECT IS OUT OF
THE HOSPITAL.
HIS INCREDIBLE STORY AND WHAT HE
SAID HE WAS REALLY LOOKING
FORWARD TO WHEN HE GOT HOME.
tos
on one easy to manage plan.
That means your smartphone,
her Blackberry,
his laptop,
Mark's smartphone...
But I'm still
on vacation...
...stilln the plan.
Nice!
So is his tablet, that guy's
hotspot, thentern's tablet.
The intern gets a tablet?
Everyone's devices.
His, hers,
oh sorry...
all easier to manage on
The Share Everything Plan
for Small Business.
Connecting more
so you can do more.
That's Powerful.
Verizon.
Get the Blackberry Q10
for $199.99.
IS THIS WHERE WE DO
THAT BUNDLING THING?
LET'S SEE WHAT YOU GOT.
RV, COVERED.
-WHY WOULD YOU PAY FOR A HOTEL?
-I NEVER DO.
MOTORCYCLES, CHECK.
ATV.
I RIDE THOSE.
-DO YOU?
-NO.
BOAT.
-HOUSE?
-HELLO, DEAR.
-HELLO.
OH! CHECK THIS --
[ HIP HOP MUSIC PLAYING ]
I'M GOING ON BREAK!
THE MORE YOU BUNDLE,
THE MORE YOU SAVE.
NOW THAT'S PROGRESSIVE.
SO YOU CAN MAKE EASY, NO-FEE
RELOADS WITH CASH AND CHECKS...
♪  ♪
AND KNOW YOU'RE NOT ON YOUR OWN.
SO YOU CAN GET THE RELOADABLE
CARD THAT KEEPS UP WITH YOU.
CHASE LIQUID.
SO YOU CAN.
>>> VETERANS ARE CLAIMING OUR
GOVERNMENT IS GUTTING THE GULF
WAR ILLNESS.
THEY CLAIM IT IS PAYBACK.
THE V.A. DENIES ATTEMPTING TO
NOT PAY BENEFITS.
THEY SAY IT INCLUDES TOXIC
CHEMICALS FROM OIL FIRES AND
ANTI-NERVE GAS PILLS THE TROOPS
TOOK DURING THE 1991 WAR.
SYMPTOMS ARE CHRONIC FATIGUE,
JOIN PAIN, RASHES, MEMORY LOSS.
JENNIFER GRIFFIN FROM THE
PENTAGON TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: LAST MONTH, V.A.
SECRETARY.
THE BOARD WAS RECOMMENDATIONS
ABOUT GULF WAR ILLNESS AND LIMIT
THE BOARD'S INDEPENDENCE FROM
THE V.A. AND MOVE VETERANS
ADVOCATES SAY IT IS DESIGNED TO
SWEEP GULF WAR ILLNESS UNDER THE
RUG.
HE WAS ANGERED BY THE VOTE OF NO
CONFIDENCE BY THE RESEARCH
ADVISORY COMMITTEE ON GULF WAR
ILLNESS.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, THE SECRETARY
WHEN CONFRONTED WITH THE
RECOMMENDATIONS ON OUR PART THAT
NEEDS TO BE INVESTIGATED, THEY
HAVE OPTED TO SHOOT THE
MESSENGER.
>> I'M VERY TROUBLED BY THE
CHANGES THAT ARE PURPORTED TO
HAVE BEEN MADE.
>> THE DEPARTMENT OF VETERANS
AFFAIRS HAS STRONGLY DENIED ANY
WRONGDOING, ARGUING HE HAS
RECOGNIZED NINE NEW DISEASES
ASSOCIATED WITH GULF WAR ILLNESS
SINCE 2010.
QUOTE, FUNDING FOR GULF WAR
RESEARCH HAS INCREASED FROM $5.6
MILLION IN 2011 TO $6.7 MILLION
IN 2012 TO AN ESTIMATED $7.3
MILLION IN 2013.
BUT A FORM HE V.A. RESEARCH
DOCTOR TURNED WHISTLE BLOWER
TOLD CONGRESS IN MARCH THE V.A.
WAS MANIPULATING EVIDENCE TO
AVOID CLAIM.
>> AND THE V.A. IS UNDER FIRE
ACCUSED OF MISMANAGING VETERANS
DISABILITY BENEFITS.
A SENIOR OFFICIAL THAT THEY ARE
STRUGGLING TO GET THEIR HANDLE
ON A BACKLOG OF CLAIMS AND IT
HAS REACHED A TIPPING POINT.
IT CONSISTS OF 600,000 CLAIM
WITH A PATIENT WAIT TIME OF MORE
THAN 270 DAYS ON AVERAGE.
>>> A MOMENT OF SILENCE IN
NEWTOWN, CONNECTICUT, AS
VICTIMS' FAMILIES HONOR THE
PEOPLE LOST THAT DAY.
THE SISTERS OF ONE OF THE
TEACHERS KILLED IN THAT SHOOTING
HAD REQUESTED THAT MOMENT OF
SILENCE.
IT LASTED FOR 26 SECONDS TO
HONOR THE 20 STUDENTS AND SIX
FACULTY MEMBERS KILLED WHEN THE
LONE GUNMAN OPENED FIRE BEFORE
KILLING HIMSELF.
OFFICIAL AND FAMILY MEMBERS
ISSUED A CALL TO ACTION ON GUN
CONTROL AT TODAY'S CEREMONY.
>>> A TRANSIT POLICE OFFICER WHO
SURVIVED A SHOOT-OUT WITH THE
ACCUSED BOSTON MARATHON BOMBERS
IS FINALLY HEADING HOME FROM THE
HOSPITAL.
HE NEARLY BLED TO DEATH AFTER
THAT SHOWDOWN IN APRIL.
HE SAID HE DOESN'T EVEN REALLY
REMEMBER THE GUN FIGHT.
BUT HE SAID HE'S MAKING PROGRESS
IN THE RECOVERY.
>> I'M HERE ON A CRUTCHES.
I CAN TAKE A FEW STEMS ON MY
OWN.
I CAN WALK WITH A CANE.
I'M BETTER IN SOME REGARDS.
>> THE OFFICER SAID HE IS
LOOKING FORWARD TO SPENDING MORE
TIME WITH HIS SON AND PLAYING
WITH THE FAMILY DOG.
HE SAID HE WANTS TO EVENTUALLY
RETURN TO WORK.
>>> THE FOCUS AT GUINNESS CALL
AT THIS TIME MOST FAMOUS SONG IN
THE ENGLISH LANGUAGE.
AND CHANCES ARE YOU'VE SUNG IT
PLENTY OF TIME A YEAR.
NOW A CLASSIC TUBE IS HEADED TO
COURT.
COMING UP, THE LAWSUIT OVER
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
[ Female Announcer ] DOCTORS
TRUST CALCIUM PLUS VITAMIN D
TO SUPPORT STRONG BONES.
AND THE BRAND
MOST RECOMMENDED BY...
MY DOCTOR.
MY GYNECOLOGIST.
MY PHARMACIST.
Citracal.
[ Female Announcer ]
YOU TRUST YOUR DOCTOR.
DOCTORS TRUST Citracal.
[ Male Announcer ]
EVERYONE HAS THE ABILITY
TO DO SOMETHING AMAZING.
♪
SOME JUST DO IT,
ON A MORE REGULAR BASIS.
♪
IN DEALERSHIPS EVERYWHERE.
IN THEATERS, JUNE 14TH.
I WORK FOR 47
DIFFERENT COMPANIES.
WELL, TECHNICALLY
I WORK FOR ONE.
THAT COMPANY, THE UNITED STATES
POSTAL SERVICE®
WORKS FOR THOUSANDS
OF HOME BUSINESSES.
BECAUSE AT USPS.COM®
YOU CAN PAY, PRINT
AND HAVE YOUR PACKAGES PICKED UP
FOR FREE.
I CAN EVEN DROP OFF FREE BOXES.
I WEAR A LOT OF HATS.
WELL, TECHNICALLY I WEAR ONE.
THE U.S. POSTAL SERVICE®,
NO BUSINESS TOO SMALL.
AND DIDN'T KNOW WHERE TO START.
USED A CONTRACTOR BEFORE
WELL, TECHNICALLY I WEAR ONE.
AT ANGIE'S LIST,
YOU'LL FIND REVIEWS
ON EVERYTHING
FROM HOME REPAIR TO HEALTHCARE
WRITTEN BY PEOPLE
JUST LIKE YOU.
NO COMPANY CAN PAY
TO BE ON ANGIE'S LIST,
SO YOU CAN TRUST
WHAT YOU'RE READING.
ANGIE'S LIST IS LIKE HAVING
THOUSANDS OF CLOSE NEIGHBORS
WHERE I CAN GO ASK
FOR PERSONAL RECOMMENDATIONS.
THAT'S THE IDEA.
BEFORE YOU HAVE ANY WORK DONE,
CHECK ANGIE'S LIST.
FROM ROOFERS TO PLUMBERS
TO DENTISTS AND MORE,
ANGIE'S LIST --
REVIEWS YOU CAN TRUST.
I LOVE YOU, ANGIE.
SORRY, HONEY.
VO: I've always thought the best
part about this country
is that we get to
create our future.
You get to take ownership
of the choices you make.
The person you become.
I've been around long enough to
recognize the people who are out
there owning it.
The ones getting involved
and staying engaged.
They're not sitting by
as their life unfolds.
And they're not afraid to
question the path they're on.
Because the one question
they never want to ask is
"How did I end up here?"
I started Schwab
for those people.
People who want to take
ownership of their investments,
like they do in every other
aspect of their lives.
>>> A PRODUCTION MAKING A CLAIM
HAS FILED OVER THE COPY RIGHT.
THE ARGUMENT, THE SONG HAPPY
BIRTHDAY SHOULD BE DEDICATED TO
PUBLIC USE AND IN THE PUBLIC
DOMAIN BECAUSE THE COPY RIGHT
EXPIRED DECADES AGO.
THE COMPANY THAT CLAIMS TO OWN
THE SONG HAS REPORTEDLY
RECOVERED MILLIONS IN LICENSING
FEES.
THE FILM COMPANY FILED ITS SUIT
AFTER HAVING TO PAY $1,500 FEES
TO USE THE SONG IN THE MOVIE.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE SAID
PRESIDENT OBAMA WILL STEP UP
U.S. MILITARY SUPPORT FOR THE
REBELS IN SYRIA'S CIVIL WAR
AFTER CONFIRMING THAT COUNTRY'S
REGIME HAS USED CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
STILL NO WORD FROM THE COMMANDER
IN CHIEF.
AND THE ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC
HOLDER PROMISED THE LEAKER ED
SNOWDEN WILL FACE CHARGES.
HE IS STILL HIDING IN HONG KONG.
AND POLICE IN MIAMI, FLORIDA SAY
TWO DOZEN PEOPLE ENDED UP IN HOT
AFTER THE OUTDOOR DECK OF THE
SPORTS BAR SHUCKERS COLLAPSED
DURING THE NBA FINALS GAME LAST
NIGHT.
>>> AND ON THIS DAY IN 1777, OUR
NATION GOT ITS FIRST FLAG WHEN
THE CONTINENTAL CONGRESS ADOPTED
THE STARS AND STRIPES.
13 RED AND WHITE STRIPES
REPRESENTING THE COLONY THAT'S
DECLARED INDEPENDENCE FROM GREAT
BRITAIN.
THE FOUNDING FATHERS BASED IT ON
THE GRAND UNION FLAG.
CONGRESS ADDED A CIRCLE OF STARS
ON A BLUE FIELD SYMBOLIZING WHAT
IT CALLED A NEW CONSTELLATION.
AS MORE STATES ENTERED THE
UNION, THE NUMBER OF STARS GREW.
THE NATION CELEBRATED THE FIRST
FLAG DAY MARKING 100 YEARS SINCE
THE CREATION OF THE STARS AND
STRIPES.
DECADES LATER, CONGRESS MADE
FLAG DAY A NATIONAL DAY OF
OBSERVANCE AND OLD GLORY WAS
BORN 236 YEARS AGO TODAY.
HAPPY FLAG DAY.
NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS FOR THIS
FRIDAY, JUNE 14th, 2013.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
I'M BE BACK ON MONDAY.
HAPPY FATHER'S DAY, ESPECIALLY
MINE.
I'LL HIT YOU UP ON SUNDAY.
OF COURSE, SUNDAY IS A VERY BIG
DAY.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S HAPPENING ON
SUNDAY.
TRUE BLOOD IS BACK.
I'M TELLING YOU.
>>> THE O'REILLY FACTOR IS ON.
>> HE ACTS AS IF HE STUMBLED
UPON THE SCENE OF AN ACCIDENT
AND HE IS CATCHING UP.
>>> THE BENGHAZI DEBACLE TO THE
STATE DEPARTMENT'S SEX AND DRUGS
SHOCKER.
CAN THE OBAMA PRESIDENCY
SURVIVE?
>> CAN YOU TELL ME HOW MANY
AGENTS AND INVESTIGATORS YOU'VE
ASSIGN TO THE CASE?
>> WE MAY BE ABLE TO DO THAT --
>> CAN YOU TELL ME WHO THE LEAD
INVESTIGATOR IS?
>> ON THE TOP OF MY HEAD, NO.
>> WHY CANNOT THE HEAD OF THE
FBI ANXIOUS SIMPLE QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE IRS INVESTIGATION?
SHOULD WE BE WORRIED?
>> YOU KNOW WHAT IT IS LIKE OUT
ON THE OPEN ROAD.
>> NEITHER DO YOU.