THROUGH THAT PRESS BRIEFING.
ANOTHER EXCITING ONE.
WE WILL BE BACK HERE TOMORROW.
JOIN US THEN AS WELL.
I'M MELISSA FRANCIS.
COMING UP NEXT HERE'S
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST.
3:00 IN D.C. WHERE WE'RE
WATCHING NEW FALLOUT OVER THE
FIRING OF THE FBI DIRECTOR,
JAMES COMEY.
NOW SOME REPUBLICANS ARE
REFUSING TO DEFEND PRESIDENT
TRUMP OR CALL HIM OUT.
LAWMAKERS TALKING ABOUT WHO THEY
WANT RUNNING THE BUREAU NEXT.
A PROFESSIONAL, NOT A
POLITICIAN.
ALSO, NEW ACCUSATIONS THAT THE
SYRIAN DICTATOR BASHAR AL-ASSAD
IS CARRYING OUTS EXECUTIONS
AND HAS BUILT A CREMATORIUM TO
HIDE EVIDENCE.
AND NORTH KOREA MARKS A
DANGEROUS AND NEW MILESTONE WITH
ITS LARGEST BALLISTIC MISSILE
FLIGHT SO FAR.
THE NORTH KOREANS CLAIM THIS
THING CAN CARRY A NUKE.
LET'S GET TO IT.
FIRST FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK ON
THIS BUSY MONDAY, THE WHITE
HOUSE STILL WILL NEITHER CONFIRM
NOR DENY THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS TAPES OF HIS CONVERSATIONS
WITH THE FORMER FBI DIRECTOR
JAMES COMEY.
ANALYSTS SAY THAT IS MAKING THE
WHITE HOUSE'S EFFORT TO RESPOND
TO CRITICISM OF HIS FIRING EVEN
MORE DIFFICULT.
THE SEARCH IS ON FOR A NEW FBI
DIRECTOR.
HERE'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT SAID
ABOUT IT WHEN SPEAKING WITH THE
CROWN PRINCE OF ABU-DHABI.
>> THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: THAT'S TODAY.
FRIDAY PRESIDENT TRUMP WARNED
JAMES COCMEY NOT THE SPEAK OUT
ABOUT HIS FIRING.
IT'S WORTH NOTING THE PRESIDENT
PUT TAPES IN QUOTES THERE,
SIMILAR TO WHEN HE PUT "WIRES
TAPPED" IN MARCH WHEN HE MADE
HIS UNFOUNDED CLAIM THAT
PRESIDENT OBAMA ORDERED
SURVEILLANCE AT TRUMP TOWER.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THE USE OF
QUOTES OPENED THE PHRASE TO A
BROAD DEFINITION OF
SURVEILLANCE.
THE PRESIDENT USED "TAP" NOT IN
QUOTES.
SO FAR THE WHITE HOUSE HAS NOT
SAID WHAT THE PRESIDENT MEANT
WHEN HE TWEETED ABOUT TAPES.
SEAN SPICER SAID THE PRESIDENT
HAD NOTHING FURTHER ON THAT
ISSUE.
THE REPUBLICAN SAID AT THE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE MEMBERS,
LINDSEY GRAHAM CALLED THE
PRESIDENT'S TWEET INAPPROPRIATE
AND THE REPUBLICANS NEED TO HAVE
COMEY TESTIFY BEFORE THE PANEL.
>> I WOULD ADVISE THE PRESIDENT
NOT THE TWEET ABOUT THE
INVESTIGATION AS WE GO FORWARD.
THE RUSSIANS INTERFERED IN OUR
ELECTION.
I DON'T THINK THEY CHANGED THE
OUTCOME BUT THE PRESIDENT NEEDS
TO BACK OFF HERE AND LET THE
INVESTIGATION GO FORWARD.
WE NEED TO CALL COMEY AND GOT TO
THE BET TOM OF THIS.
>> Shepard: SENATOR GRAHAM SAYS
HE DOES NOT BELIEVE THAT THE
PRESIDENT IS THE TARGET OF AN
INVESTIGATION INVOLVING POSSIBLE
COLLUSION BETWEEN THE TRUMP
CAMPAIGN AND RUSSIAN OFFICIALS.
ON THE PRESIDENT'S SUGGESTION
THAT TAPES MAY EXIST OF HIS
CONVERSATIONS WITH JAMES COMEY,
ANOTHER REPUBLICAN ON THE SENATE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE SAYS HISTORY
SHOWS US RESPECTS RECORDING
THEIR CONVERSATIONS IS NOT
NECESSARILY THE BEST IDEA.
HERE'S WHAT SENATOR MIKE LEE OF
UTAH TOLD CHRIS WALLACE ON "FOX
NEWS SUNDAY."
>> IF THAT'S TRUE, YOU THINK THE
PRESIDENT SHOULD TURN OVER ANY
RELEVANT TAPES TO THIS
INVESTIGATION TO THE CONGRESS?
>> I THINK IT'S PROBABLY
INEVITABLE, IF THERE ARE SUCH
RECORDINGS.
THEY WILL BE SUBPOENAED AND
PROBABLY HAVE TO TURN THEM OVER.
>> Shepard: WHEN IT COMES TO THE
FIRING OF JAMES COMEY, NIKKI
HALEY TOLD ABC'S "THIS WEEK"
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS A PRESIDENT
OF ACTION.
>> THE PRESIDENT IS A CEO OF THE
COUNTRY.
HE CAN FIRE AND FIRE WHOEVER HE
WANTS.
WHETHER YOU AGREE WITH IT OR
NOT, IT'S THE TRUE.
HE'S TRYING TO FIND HIS OWN
TEAM.
WERE THERE BETTER WAYS TO DO
THAT?
THAT'S FOR EVERYBODY ELSE TO
DECIDE.
>> NIKKI HALEY.
AS FOR THE POTENTIAL TAPES, SHE
SAID SHE'S ASSUMES SHE'S BEING
TAPED EVERYWHERE.
JAMES COMEY HAS DECLINED AN
INVITATION TO TESTIFY BEHIND
CLOSED DOORS TOMORROW BEFORE THE
SENATE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE.
BUT "THE NEW YORK TIMES" AND
OTHERS ARE REPORTING HE'S
WILLING TO TESTIFY AS LONG AS
IT'S OUT IN PUBLIC FOR EVERYBODY
TO SEE.
ONE KEY ISSUE IS A WHITE HOUSE
DINNER BETWEEN JAMES COMEY AND
PRESIDENT TRUMP JUST DAYS AFTER
THE INAUGURATION.
THE.
HAS ONE STORY.
HE SAYS HE THOUGHT JAMES COMEY
ARRANGED THE DINNER AND THAT
COMEY TOLD HIM THE FBI WAS NOT
INVESTIGATING HIM.
THE "NEW YORK TIMES" AND OTHERS
REPORT THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
INVITED JAMES COMEY AND THE
PRESIDENT ASKED REPEATEDLY
WHETHER THE FBI DIRECTOR WOULD
PLEDGE A LOYALTY TO HIM.
ACCORDING TO THE TIMES, DIRECTOR
COMEY DECLINED.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENCE JOHN ROBERTS IS
LIVE AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
WHAT IS THE WHITE HOU SAYING
ABOUT THESE POTENTIAL TAPES IF
ANYTHING AT ALL?
>> AS YOU POINTED OUT, SHEP,
THEY'RE NOT SAYING A LOT.
ABOUT ALL OF THE REPORTING GOING
ON ABOUT TAPES, PEOPLE ARE
SAYING WAS THERE AN OVAL OFFICE
RECORDING MECHANISM MUCH LIKE IN
THE NIXON ADMINISTRATION WHEN HE
RECORDED PRIVATE CONVERSATIONS
OF EVERYBODY THAT CAME IN.
EVEN IF THERE WAS AN OVAL OFFICE
SYSTEM, PROBABLY WOULDN'T
PERTAIN TO THE COMEY MEETING
BECAUSE HE WOULD HAVE HAD
MEETING DINNER IN THE ROOM OFF
THE OVAL OFFICE AND MORE LIKELY
EITHER IN THE RESIDENCE OR IN
ONE OF THE OFFICIAL ROOMS IN THE
MAIN MANSION HERE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
SO THAT WOULD IMPLY THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAD SOME SORT OF
RECORDING SYSTEM THAT WAS
AVAILABLE THROUGHOUT MANSION.
IT'S NOT KNOWN AT THIS POINT
WHEN THE PRESIDENT SAYS "TAPES"
ARE TALKING ABOUT A RECORDING
DEVICE OR OTHER CONVERSATION OR
MERELY TRYING TO PLAY WITH THE
MEDIA THERE AND JAMES COMEY
SAYING MAYBE THERE ARE TAPES.
HERE'S WHAT SEAN SPICER SAID
ABOUT IT AT THE BRIEFING A SHORT
TIME AGO.
>> IS THE WHITE HOUSE INTENDING
TO FURNISH THAT INFORMATION AS
REQUESTED IN WRITING?
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS NOTHING
FURTHER ON THAT.
>> DOES THAT MEAN THE PRESIDENT
WILL DENY --
>> I WAS VERY CLEAR THAT THE
PRESIDENT WOULD HAVE NOTHING
FURTHER ON THAT LAST WEEK.
>> IS THE SITUATION WITH THE
LEGISLATIVE BRANCH --
>> LISTEN, I MADE IT CLEAR WHAT
THE PRESIDENT'S POSITION IS ON
THAT ISSUE.
HUNTER?
>> SO THE PRESIDENT AND THE
PRESS SECRETARY SAYING NOTHING,
SHEP, WHETHER OR NOT THERE ARE
TAPES AND WHETHER OR NOT THE
TAPES WOULD BE PROVIDED TO
CONGRESS BECAUSE THERE ARE
INDICATIONS THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE
UP THERE ON CAPITOL HILL WOULD
LIKE TO HEAR THEM IF THERE ARE
TAPES.
I WOULD PAUSE IT, SHEP, IT'S
UNLIKELY THERE WOULD BE TAPES OF
A DINNER UNLESS SOMEBODY HAD A
RECORDING DEVICE NEARBY.
THE TWO PHONE CALLS ARE A
DIFFERENT STORY.
ALL OF THE PRESIDENT'S PHONE
CALLS ARE LOGGED AND SOME OF
THEM ARE TRANSCRIBED, SHEP.
>> WHAT ABOUT THIS MATTER OF
DISCUSSION OF A POSSIBLE SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR?
KEN STARR, THE ONE THAT COMES TO
MIND FOR MOST PEOPLE.
THEY END UP EXPANDING
INVESTIGATIONS.
THERE'S REPUBLICANS ON BOARD?
>> THE SPECIAL PROSECUTOR
STATUTE AS APPLIED TO KEN STARR
IS NO LONGER IN EXISTENCE.
A SPECIAL PROSECUTOR WOULD HAVE
TO BE PROVIDED AND NAMED BY THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE.
THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF COMPLAINTS
FROM DEMOCRATS ABOUT THE NEED
FOR A SPECIAL PROSECUTOR OVER
THE WEEKEND.
SOME DEMOCRATS SAID THEY WOULD
REFUSE TO CONSIDER THE NAME OF
THE NOMINEE IN CONFIRMATION
HEARINGS UNTIL A SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR IS APPOINTED.
I ASKED SEAN SPICER.
HERE'S HOW HE RESPONDED.
>> THERE'S FRANKLY NO NEED FOR A
SPECIAL PROSECUTOR.
YOU HAVE TWO SENATE COMMITTEES
LOOKING INTO THIS, THE FBI IS
CONDUCTING THEIR OWN REVIEW.
AND I THINK IF YOU EVEN LOOK AT
WHAT ACTING DIRECTOR McCABE
SAID, THEY HAVE THE RESOURCES
THEY NEED.
>> ONE THING THAT DIDN'T COME UP
AT THE BRIEFING, RECORDS OF A
MASSIVE STAFF SHAKEUP.
I'M TOLL A MASSIVE STAFF SHAKEUP
IS "NONSENSE."
THERE'S SOME TALK THERE MAY BE
CHANGES TO THE COMMUNICATIONS
SHOP AFTER WHAT HAPPENED WITH
THE COMEY FIRING LAST TUESDAY.
ALSO TOLD THAT THE WHITE HOUSE
CHIEF OF STAFF REINCE PRIEBUS
WHO HAS BEEN IN A LOT OF
REPORTING "ON THE BUBBLE" SINCE
JANUARY ALSO MAY NOT HOLD THE
COMPLETE FAVOR OF THE PRESIDENT
AT THIS MOMENT IN TIME.
SHEP, WE'VE HEARD THIS BEFORE
AND NOTHING HAPPENED.
COULD BE ANOTHER CASE OF THAT.
>> Shepard: JOHN ROBERTS AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THANK YOU.
LET'S GO TO JOSH GERSSTEIN.
ANY NEW NEWS?
>> I THOUGHT IT WAS INTERESTING,
SHEP, DURING THE BRIEFING THAT
SEAN SPICER TRIED TO PUT
TOGETHER ANOTHER RATIONALE FOR
THE FIRING OF JAMES COMEY SAYING
THE PRESIDENT THOUGHT THAT
FIRING COMEY WOULD BE DIFFICULT
FOR THE PRESIDENT AND WOULD HURT
HIM IN SOME WAY.
BUT SUGGESTING AGAIN THAT MAYBE
DIDN'T HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH
THE RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION.
SO SPICER TRYING TO STIR UP SOME
DUST OVER THAT ISSUE AGAIN.
>> Shepard: IS THERE ANY
AGREEMENT NOW ON HOW THIS THING
SHOULD GO FORWARD?
IS IT SEPARATED COMPLETELY ALONG
PARTISAN LINES?
>> WELL, THERE SEEMS TO BE SOME
INDICATION THAT SOME REPUBLICANS
MIGHT BE OPEN TO A SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR AT A CERTAIN POINT.
MARCO RUBIO SAID MAYBE WE'LL GET
TO A POINT THAT THAT WOULD BE
APPROPRIATE.
THE ISSUE IS MUDDLED TOGETHER
WITH THIS QUESTION OF
REPLACEMENT OF THE FBI DIRECTOR
WITH DEMOCRATS AS WE DISCUSSED
EARLIER SAYING THEY WOULDN'T
VOTE TO CONFIRM ANYONE UNTIL A
SPECIAL PROSECUTOR IS IN PLACE.
THAT LEAVES OPEN THE QUESTION OF
HOW THE WHITE HOUSE WILL GET
SOMEBODY CONFIRMED FOR THE FBI'S
DIRECTOR JOB.
THOSE VOTES FOR DIRECTOR CON
FORMATION VOTES OVER THE LAST
45, 50 YEARS HAVE BEEN
UNANIMOUS.
98-0.
93-1 UNANIMOUS CONSENT.
SO TO HAVE A PARTY LINE VOTE ON
CONFIRMING AN FBI DIRECTOR WOULD
BE AN EXTRAORDINARY DEPARTURE
FROM WHAT'S GO ON IN THE RECENT
DECADES.
>> Shepard: ON THE LIST OF
POTENTIAL CANDIDATES, A NUMBER
OF PEOPLE, POLITICIANS AND
JUDGES.
THIS IDEA OF A POLITICIAN AS THE
FBI DIRECTOR, IT'S A NEW ONE AND
DOESN'T SEEM TO BE FARING WELL.
>> IT DOESN'T.
THE WHITE HOUSE WILL HAVE TO
STEP APART FROM SOME OF THOSE
POSSIBILITIES LIKE WE HEARD
SENATOR JOHN CORNYN WAS ONE OF
THOSE INTERVIEWED AS I WAS
REPRESENTATIVE MIKE ROGERS.
I THINK THEY'RE BOTH HELD IN
HIGHEST STEAM IN THE CONGRESS.
YOU'VE HAD SENATOR LINDSEY
GRAHAM AND SOME OTHERS SUGGEST
THAT THIS IS NOT THE TIME TO SET
A NEW PRECEDENT OF HAVING A
POLITICIAN AS FBI DIRECTOR.
IT WOULD BE WISER TO PICK
SOMEBODY FROM THE FBI'S RANKS OR
A LONG-TERM PROSECUTOR AS WE'VE
SEEN, DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL,
MAYBE HAS THE CRIMINAL DIVISION
AT THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
THOSE ARE A GREATER POSSIBILITY
THAN A POLITICIAN.
>> Shepard: REGARDING THE ISSUES
THAT WE HEAR FROM PEOPLE DALE
LIVE.
WE DID FRIDAY, WE HAVE TODAY.
THEN WE HEAR THE TALK OF PEOPLE
HAVING GREAT CONCERN BEHIND THE
SCENES.
COULD YOU GIVE US WHAT YOU
THOUGH ABOUT THIS SORT OF
SENTIMENT?
>> WELL, THERE'S NERVOUSNESS AS
WE HEARD IN THE BRIEFING ABOUT
THE TAPE RECORDING SYSTEM AND
WHETHER THERE IS ONE OR ISN'T
ONE.
IT WAS JUST LIKE A FLAT OUT
NONRESPONSE FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY.
THIS IS AN ADMINISTRATION THAT I
THINK HAS STRUGGLED TO FIND
PEOPLE TO JOIN ITS RANKS.
SOME BECAUSE SOME PEOPLE WERE
NOT WILLING TO DO SO.
IN OTHER CASES BECAUSE THEY MAY
HAVE MADE STATEMENTS THAT WERE
SEEN AS DISLOYAL TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
THEY WERE SCRATCHED FROM THE
LIST.
YOU LOOK AT THAT POOL AGAIN WHEN
YOU CAN'T GET ASSURANCES THAT
YOU'RE NOT BEING RECORDED IN
YOUR PRIVATE CONVERSATIONS IN
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> JOSH GERSTEIN FROM POLITCO.
THANKS.
>> THANKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS DON'T AGREE ON MUCH OF
ANYTHING BUT WHEN IT COMES TO
THE SEARCH OF THE NEXT HEAD OF
THE FBI, THEY HAVE SEEMED TO
FIND COMMON GROUND.
AHEAD WHAT SENATORS OF BOTH
SIDES ARE REQUESTING.
WE'LL LOOK AT SOME OF THE TOP
POTENTIAL CANDIDATES, INCLUDING
MERRICK GARLAND, THE JUDGE
REPUBLICANS REFUSED TO CONFIRM
TO THE SUPREME COURT.
THAT AND THE REST OF THE NEWS
COMING UP FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK
ON THIS MONDAY AFTERNOON.
TECH: When your windshield
needs to be fixed...
trust Safelite AutoGlass.
For these parents, driving
around was the only way to get
their baby to sleep.
So when their windshield
got cracked...
CUSTOMER: We can't
drive this car.
TECH: ...they wanted it
fixed right.
So they scheduled with Safelite.
Our exclusive TrueSeal
technology means a strong,
reliable bond,
every time.
At Safelite,
we stand behind our work.
Bye, bye.
Because the ones you love,
sit behind it.
(PARENTS WHISPER JINGLE)
Safelite repair, Safelite
replace.
>> Shepard: LAWMAKERS ON BOTH
SIDES OF THE AISLE ARE URGING
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO AVOID PICKING
A POLITICIAN TO REPLACE JAMES
COMEY IN THE FBI.
REPUBLICANS SENATOR LINDSEY
GRAHAM SAID THE PRESIDENT SHOULD
PICK SOMEBODY WITHIN THE FBI
RANKS.
THE MINORITY LEADER, CHUCK
SCHUMER, SAID THE NEW FBI
DIRECTOR SHOULD BE SOMEONE OF
NOT A PARTISAN BACKGROUND.
FORMER PRESIDENT OBAMA'S SUPREME
COURT NOMINEE, MERRICK GARLAND
IS IN THE MIX.
THE FORMER AID TO MITCH
McCONNELL SAID THE SENATE
MAJORITY LEADER SUPPORTS THE
IDEA OF MERRICK GARLAND AS THE
NEXT FBI DIRECTOR.
EVEN THOUGH HE AND OTHER
REPUBLICANS REFUSE TO HOLD
HEARINGS FOR HIM AS A SUPREME
COURT JUSTICE.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE HAS MORE.
CATHERINE?
>> MERRICK GARLAND, IS THAT A
NAME THE PRESIDENT WOULD
POSSIBLY CONSIDER IN THE MOVE TO
NAME THE NEW FBI DIRECTOR?
>> THE SEARCH FOR A NEW FBI
DIRECTOR IS BEING HANDLED BY THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE.
MY EXPECTATION WOULD BE AS THEY
CONDUCT THAT SEARCH, THEY'LL
PRESENT NAMES TO THE PRESIDENT.
THEY'RE THE ONES LEADING THE
EFFORT.
>> A SENATE REPUBLICAN THAT SITS
ON THE COMMITTEE THAT WILL
HANDLE THE HEARINGS FOR THE NEXT
FBI DIRECTOR SAID SUNDAY THAT
GARLAND IS AN INSPIRED CHOICE.
>> IT'S A GREAT SUGGESTION.
ABSOLUTELY SERIOUS ABOUT IT.
THIS IS A VERY DIFFERENT POST
THAN THE SUPREME COURT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
IF PRESIDENT TRUMP WERE TO
NOMINATE MERRICK GARLAND, HIS
NOMINATION WOULD BE WELCOMED BY
PEOPLE ON BOTH SIDES OF THE
AISLE IN THE SENATE.
>> THE ADMINISTRATION SOURCE
TOLD FOX NEWS THE INTERVIEWS
OVER THE WEEKEND WERE STRONG AND
IMPRESSIVE.
THEY INCLUDED FRAN TOWNSEND AND
ALICE FISHER THAT SERVED UNDER
THE BUSH ADMINISTRATION AS A
SENIOR JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
OFFICIAL OVERSEEING THE CRIMINAL
DIVISION.
THE SIGNIFICANCE OF NOMINATING
THE FIRST WOMAN AS THE FBI
DIRECTOR IS NOT LOST ON THE
DECISION TEAM.
>> Shepard: SOME OF THE OTHER
CANDIDATES ARE FORMER FBIERS,
THEMSELVES, VETERANS.
>> OTHER CANDIDATES ARE ADAM
LEE.
THE SPECIAL AGENT IN CHARGE OF
THE RICHMOND VIRGINIA OFFICE,
ANDREW McCABE, THE ACTING
DIRECTOR AND MICHAEL J. GARCIA,
FORMER PROSECUTOR AND ASSOCIATE
JUDGE ON NEW YORK'S HIGHEST
COURT.
JOHN CORNYN, A FORMER TEXAS
ATTORNEY GENERAL WAS INTERVIEWED
AGAINST LONG WITH MIKE ROGERS
AND ALSO ON THE SHORT LIST, A
BUSH APPOINTEE, HENRY E. HUDSON.
OVER THE WEEKEND, REPUBLICANS
AND DEMOCRATS URGED THE
PRESIDENT TO AVOID A PARTISAN
CHOICE.
>> WHOEVER THE FUTURE DIRECTOR
SHOULD BE IS A FUTURE LAW
ENFORCEMENT PROFESSIONAL.
I HOPE THE PRESIDENT WON'T
CHOOSE A POLITICAL NOMINEE.
>> IT'S TIME TO PICK SOMEBODY
WITHIN THE RANKS OR SUCH A
REPUTATION THAT HAS NO POLITICAL
BACKGROUND AT ALL THAT CAN GO
INTO THE JOB ON DAY ONE.
>> TODAY BRAD SHERMAN OF
CALIFORNIA TOLD FOX NEWS THAT HE
BACKS A SPECIAL COUNSEL AND
COULD NOT WHAT SAY WHAT SENATE
TACTIC MIGHT GET THEM THERE.
THE REPUBLICANS HAVE THE
MAJORITY, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, CATHERINE.
A NEW LEGAL SHOWDOWN OVER THE
PRESIDENT'S TRAVEL BAN.
THE ORDER THAT WOULD SUSPEND THE
REFUGEE PROGRAM AND TEMPORARILY
PREVENT NEW VISAS FOR ANYBODY
FROM IRAN, LIBYA, SOMALIA,
SUDAN, SYRIA AND YEMEN.
ALL PRO DOMINANTLY MUSLIM
COUNTRIES.
A THREE-JUDGE PANEL OF THE NINTH
U.S. CIRCUIT COURT HEARD
ARGUMENT.
THE UNUSUAL THING ABOUT THIS, IT
WAS STREAMING LIVE AND A LOT OF
NEWS CHANNELS TOOK IT.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION TRYING
TO PERSUADE THE COURT TO
REINSTATE THE BAN.
THE REAL ISSUE IS WHETHER
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S COMMENTS
BEFORE HE TOOK OFFICE ABOUT
BANNING MUSLIMS FROM THE COUNTRY
AND ABOUT MUSLIM BANS IN
PAPERWORK THAT THEY HAD PUT
TOGETHER INCLUDING WEBSITE
PROVIDE IN TOTALITY A LEGAL
GROUND TO RULE HIS ORDER
UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
SUPPORTERS SAY IT WOULD INCREASE
NATIONAL SECURITY AND OTHERS SAY
IT DISCRIMINATES AGAINST
RELIGION.
SEAN SPICER SAID THE ORDER IS
LAW FUL AND WILL BE UPHELD.
THE WHITE HOUSE ANNOUNCING A
GLOBAL CYBER ATTACK AFFECTED
MORE PEOPLE THAN WE KNEW.
COMING UP, THE INCREDIBLE SCOPE
OF THIS ATTACK AND HOW YOU CAN
PROTECT YOURSELF.
All finished.
Umm...
You wouldn't want your
painter to quit part way,
I think you missed a spot.
so when it comes to
pain relievers,
why put up with
just part of a day?
Aleve, live whole not part.
You want this color
over the whole house?
What's the best way to get
V8 or a fancy juice store?s?
Ready, go!
Hi, Juice Universe?
One large rutabaga,
with eggplant...
Done!
That's not fair.
Glad I had a V8.
The original way to
fuel your day.
You totaNobody's hurt, new car.
but there will still be pain.
It comes when your insurance
company says they'll only pay
three-quarters of what
it takes to replace it.
What are you supposed to do?
Drive three-quarters of a car?
Now if you had Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
you'd get your whole car back.
I guess they don't want you
driving around on three wheels.
Smart.
With Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
we'll replace the full
value of your car.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
The shLike a bald penguin.
How do I look?
[ laughing ]
Show me the
Billboard Music Awards.
Show me Top Artist.
Show me the
Top Hot 100 Artist.
They give awards for being
hot and 100 years old?
We'll take 2!
[ laughing ]
XFINITY X1 gives you
exclusive access to the best
of the Billboard Music Awards
just by using your voice.
The Billboard Music Awards.
Sunday, May 21st eight
seven central only on ABC.
>> A POWERFUL CYBER ATTACK THAT
YOU HEARD ABOUT OVER THE WEEKEND
THAT SO FAR HIT MORE THAN
300,000 COMPUTERS AROUND THE
WORLD.
STILL HAPPENING.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS REPORTING ON
IT NOW.
HOMELAND SECURITY ADVISER TOM
BOSSERT.
THE ATTACK CALLED PROBLEMS FOR
MORE THAN 150 COUNTRIES
INCLUDING THE U.S.
IT FREEZES YOUR COMPUTER AND
RATHER THAN STEALING YOUR FILES,
IT HOLDS THEM HOSTAGE AND
REQUIRES YOU TO PAY A RANSOM TO
GET YOUR OWN ACCESS TO YOUR OWN
FEELS.
INVESTIGATORS ARE STILL TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT WHO IS BEHIND
THIS.
COLD TO MALWARE TECH, A GROUP
THAT MONITORS THIS SORT OF
THING, THE DOTS ON THIS MAP SHOW
WHERE THE SO-CALLED WANNA CRY
VIRUS -- THAT'S WHAT THEY CALL
IT -- WHERE IT'S HIT IN THE LAST
24 HOURS.
IT STARTED THIS TIME FRIDAY AND
HAS BEEN GOING THROUGH THE
WEEKEND.
A LOT OF PEOPLE GOT HIT TODAY
AFTER THE WEEKEND.
THERE IT IS.
BOSSERT DOES CONFIRM IT'S HIT
AMERICAN ISSUES.
FED EX REPORTED ISSUES FRIDAY.
AFFECTED BRITAIN'S NATIONAL
HEALTH SERVICES AND RUSSIAN'S
FOREIGN MINISTRY.
NOW THE SUN NEWSPAPER, WHICH IS
A CORPORATE COUSIN OF OURS,
REPORTS THAT THE RUSSIAN
PRESIDENT VLADIMIR PUTIN IS
BLAMING THE UNITED STATES
GOVERNMENT.
THE HACKERS USED VULNERABILITY
FROM LEAKED NSA DOCUMENTS.
HERE'S A LOOK AT WHAT PEOPLE SAW
IF IT HIT.
A SCREAM DEMANDING PAYMENT IN
BITCOIN.
IT'S A DIGITAL CURRENCY NOT
REGULATED BY ANY ONE COMPANY.
PAY HUNDREDS OF DOLLARS AND YOU
GET YOUR FILE BACK.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH MORE.
TRACE?
>> THE WAY THIS WORKS, THE
RANSOMWARE THAT IS MALICIOUS
SOFTWARE IS PRETTY EFFECTIVE
EXPLOITING MICROSOFT SYSTEMS.
ONCE CLICKED ON, LOCKS YOU OUT
AND DEMANDING MONEY.
SURE ENOUGH WHEN WORKERS LOGGED
ON THIS MORNING, THE VIRUS
STARTED SPREADING, ESPECIALLY IN
CHINA WHERE 40,000 ORGANIZATIONS
GOT HIT AND 11 INTERNET SECURITY
COMPANIES HAD TO STOP TRADING
BECAUSE THE STOCK JUMPED 10%,
WHICH IS THE ONE-DAY MAXIMUM IN
CHINA.
EUROPE WAS ON HIGH ALERT FOR A
SECOND WAVE BASED ON COPYCAT
MALWARE.
THE WHITE HOUSE HOMELAND
SECURITY ADVISER SAID PAYING THE
RANSOM IS A WASTE OF MONEY.
LISTEN TO HIM.
>> WE'RE NOT AWARE OF PAYMENTS
THAT HAVE LED TO ANY DATA
RECOVERY.
>> YEAH, YOUR DATA IS STILL
LOCKED UP.
THE GOAL WAS TO NOT ATTACK ANY
CERTAIN COMPANY BUT TO MAKE AS
MUCH MONEY AS POSSIBLE.
>> Shepard: WHAT IF PEOPLE WANT
TO PROTECT THEMSELVES FROM
SOMETHING LIKE THIS?
>> THE EUROPEAN CYBER CRIMES
CENTER SAYS THESE TYPES ATTACKS
HAVE A FEW THINGS IN COMMON.
THEY ATTEND TO GO AFTER OLDER
SOFTWARE THAT HACKERS HAVE
LEARNED TO EXPLOIT.
SO UPDATE YOUR SOFTWARE AND ONLY
INSTALL ANTI-VIRUS SOFTWARE.
IF YOU BROWSE SOFTWARE, MAKE
SURE IT'S FROM A TRUSTED SOURCE.
YOU SHOULD NOT CLICK ON BANNERS
AND LINKS AND DON'T INSTALL
MOBILE ANS FROM UNKNOWN USERS.
THIS IS ALL COMMON SENSE STUFF,
SHEP.
WE ALL TEND TO CLICK ON THAT
COMPELLING BANNER FROM TIME TO
TIME AND IT ENDS US GETTING IN
TROUBLE.
>> THANKS, TRACE.
>> Shepard: THE RUSSIAN
PRESIDENT VLADIMIR PUTIN SHOWING
OFF HIS MUSICAL SKILLS.
WE'RE SOMEWHAT ACCUSTOMED TO
PICTURES LIKE THIS ONE, RIGHT?
HE'S SHIRTLESS WITH A HUNTING
RIFLE.
CHECK HIM OUT IN A RECENT VISIT
TO CHINA.
♪
EXTRAORDINARY.
PUTIN SHOWING OFF HIS PIANO
SKILLS WHILE WAITING FOR THE
CHINESE PRESIDENT.
REPORTERS ASKED HIM WHAT SONGS
HE WOULD PLAY WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
MEET FIRST AND THEN TALK AND
CHOOSE THE TUNE TO MATCH.
NO DATE FOR THAT MEETING YET.
WHILE PUTIN YUKKED IT UP WITH
CHINA, RUSSIA IS SAYS SYRIA IS
SINKING TO A NEW LOW.
THEY'RE HIDING WAR CRIMES BY
BURNING BODIES.
IN NORTH KOREA, THEY LAUNCHED
ANOTHER MISSILE TEST.
I KNOW YOU HEARD.
ANOTHER NORTH KOREA MISSILE
TEST.
WHATEVER.
IN ONE EAR, OUT THE OTHER.
THIS ONE IS DIFFERENT.
THIS ONE IS VERY DISTURBING.
THIS ONE TOPS THE NEWS AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR NEXT.
We asked a group of young people
when they thought they should
start saving for retirement.
Then we asked some older people
when they actually
did start saving.
This gap between when
we should start saving
and when we actually
do is one of the reasons
why too many of us aren't
prepared for retirement.
Just start as early as you can.
It's going to pay
off in the future.
If we all start saving
a little more today,
we'll all be better
prepared tomorrow.
Prudential.
Bring Your Challenges.
WILL YOU BE READY WHEN
THE MOMENT TURNS ROMANTIC?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
A CHARTER BUSINESS FILLED WITH
CHILDREN FLIPPED OVER ON A
GUARDRAIL AND INJURED MORE THAN
25 PEOPLE.
HAPPENED THIS MORNING ON A
STRETCH OF 95 NORTH OF
BALTIMORE.
OUR FOX STATION REPORTS POLICE
ON A DIFFERENT BUS SAW THE CRASH
AND STOPPED TO HELP.
A WOMAN HAS DIED AFTER A FIRE AT
A HIGH RISE BUILDING IN
PITTSBURGH.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE FIRE
STARTED ON THE SIXTH FLORIDA AND
FORCED 100 PEOPLE TO EVACUATE.
CREWS TREATED FOUR PEOPLE AND
ARSON TEAM IS INVESTIGATING.
CHECK THIS OUT.
TWO SOLDIERS REENLISTED IN THE
ARMY AND TOOK A PLUNGE ON A
ROLLEDER COASTER.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I was always
"the girl with psoriasis."
People don't stare anymore.
I never joined in.
That wasn't fair to any of us.
I was covered.
I tried lots of things
over the years.
But I didn't give up.
I kept on fighting.
I found something that worked.
That still works.
Now?
SEE ME.
I found clear skin that lasts.
See if COSENTYX could make a
difference for you-
COSENTYX is proven to help
people with moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis...
...find clear skin that
can last.
Don't use if you're allergic
to COSENTYX.
Before starting COSENTYX,
you should be checked
for tuberculosis.
An increased risk of infections
and lowered ability
to fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection or symptoms.
Or if you have received a
vaccine or plan to.
If you have inflammatory
bowel disease,
tell your doctor if symptoms
develop or worsen.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
SEE ME
to know...
...clear skin can last.
Don't hold back...
...ask your dermatologist if
COSENTYX can help you
find clear skin that lasts.
REMEMBER HERE AT ALLY,
NOTHING STOPS US FROM DOING
RIGHT BY OUR CUSTOMERS.
WHO'S WITH ME?
WE'RE LIKE A SPORTS
TEAM HERE AT ALLY.
IF A SPORTS TEAM HAD OVER 7...
I'M IN.
7,000 PLAYERS.
OUR PLAYS ARE A
LITTLE UNORTHODOX.
BUT TO BEAT THE BIG BOYS,
YOU NEED SMARTER WAYS
TO SAVE PEOPLE MONEY.
WE KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
FROM A FINANCIAL COMPANY
AND WE'LL STOP AT...
NOTHING TO MAKE SURE YOU GET IT.
ONE, TWO...
AND WE MEAN NOTHING.
♪  ♪
>> Shepard: NORTH KOREA TOOK A
STEP FORWARD WITH A SUCCESSFUL
MISSILE TEST OVER THE WEEKEND.
FIRST SUCCESSFUL ONE IN A LONG
TIME.
ONE THAT HAS RAISED A LOT OF YOU
BROWS.
KIM JONG-UN SAID THE NEW-TYPE OF
MEDIUM RANGE BALLISTIC MISSILE
ROCKET CAN CARRY A NUCLEAR
WARHEAD AND HE CLAIMS THEY COULD
HIT THE U.S. MAINLAND.
ANALYSTS ARE NOT SURE BUT THIS
MISSILE COULD HIT ALASKA OR
HAWAII.
THIS IS THE FIRST SUCCESSFUL
TEST OF ITS KIND AFTER THREE
FAILED ATTEMPTS LAST MONTH.
THEY TELL FOX NEWS THAT THE
MISSILE FLEW FOUR MINUTES LONGER
THAN ANY OTHER AND HIGHER AND
FURTHER.
IT TOOK OFF HERE IN THE WESTERN
PART OF THE COUNTRY.
LANDED IN THE SEA BETWEEN NORTH
KOREA AND JAPAN.
NOT FAR OFF THE COAST OF RUSSIA.
YOU CAN SEE RUSSIA TO THE NORTH
THERE, 60 MILES.
THE WHITE HOUSE RELEASED A
STATEMENT SAYING WITH THE
MISSILE SO CLOSE TO RUSSIA'S
SOIL, THE PRESIDENT CANNOT
IMAGINE THAT RUSSIA IS PLEASED.
GREG PALKOT LIVE WITH MORE.
GREG?
>> SHEP, ONE OF OUR MOST TRUSTED
EXPERTS ON NORTH KOREA TOLD US A
SHORT TIME AGO THAT THIS IS THE
MOST SIGNIFICANT MISSILE LAUNCH
TO COME OUT OF NORTH KOREA YET.
LET'S FURTHER BREAK DOWN WHAT HE
MEANS.
IT STAYED ALOFT OVER THIS
WEEKEND SOME 30 MINUTES.
THE LONGEST EVER ANY KIND OF
PROJECTILE LIKE THAT HAS STAYED
UP THERE.
IN ADD THE EX-TO GOING 500 MILES
DOWN RANGE, WENT UP 1,300 MILES
HIGH.
IF IT WENT ON A STRATEGIC
TRAJECTORY OF 2,500 MILES.
THAT COULD HIT THE BASE ON THE
ISLAND OF GUAM AND THEN SOME.
THE NORTH KOREAN LEADER SAID WAS
TO BE ECSTATIC.
KIM JONG-UN MONITORING THE
PROCEEDINGS AND THAT THE MISSILE
COULD CARRY A HEAVY NUCLEAR
PROGRAM.
NO CONFIRMATION OF THAT.
BUT SHEP, EXPERTS TELL ME
THEY'RE CLOSE TO THAT.
THE BIGGEST NEWS TO COME OUT OF
THIS LAUNCH IS THIS KIND OF
MISSILE IS A PRECURSOR TO AN
INTERCONTINENTAL BALLISTIC
MISSILE.
THE KINDS OF MISSILES THAT WE
SAW AT A MILITARY PARADE LAST
MONTH VERY SIMILAR TO THAT.
WE SAW ATHEM.
THE WHITE HOUSE VERY STRONG
AGAIN OVER THE WEEKEND ABOUT
THIS.
THEY CALL IT A FLAGRANT MENACE
AND WE HEARD FROM SEAN SPICER
FOR THE WHITE HOUSE A SHORT
WHILE AGO CALLING ON ALL
COUNTRIES TO GANG UP ON NORTH
KOREA.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> I THINK THERE'S NO QUESTION
THAT NORTH KOREA CONTINUES TO
THREATEN THE UNITED STATES AND
OUR ALLIES AND ITS NEIGHBORS AND
CHINA AND RUSSIA.
WE ARE CALLING ON ALL OF THOSE
FOLKS IN THE REGION,
PARTICULARLY SHINE AND RUSSIA TO
DO EVERYTHING THEY CAN IN TERMS
OF SANCTIONS TO HELP RESOLVE THE
SITUATION AND BRING STABILITY TO
THE PENINSULA.
>> A BIG THREAT.
MEETING TOMORROW AT THE U.N.
SECURITY COUNCIL.
>> Shepard: THANKS, GREG.
AND PRESIDENT OF THE PLOW SHARES
FUND WORKING TO REDUCE AND
ELIMINATE THE DANGERS POSED BY
NUCLEAR WEAPONS AND THE AUTHOR
OF "NUCLEAR NIGHTMARES."
JOE, NICE TO SEE YOU.
>> PLEASURE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHERE ARE WE IN THE
LONG ARM OF TROUBLES WITH NORTH
KOREA?
>> IN IS A MAJOR STEP FORWARD TO
NORTH KOREA.
THE MOST DANGEROUS TEST THEY
HAVE DONE YET.
>> Shepard: WHY?
>> DEMONSTRATING NEW
CAPABILITIES.
IT DIDN'T TRAVEL VERY FAR BUT
THAT'S BECAUSE IT TOOK A LOFTED
TRAJECTORY.
WENT STRAIGHT UP AND CAME
STRAIGHT DOWN.
IT TRAVELED ABOUT 500 MILES, THE
DISTANCE FROM MAINE TO
WASHINGTON D.C., IF YOU FLATTEN
THAT OUT.
YOU GET TO IT 2,500 MILES AND
THE WIDTH OF THE UNITED STATES
AND COULD TRAVEL THAT IN ABOUT
30 MINUTES.
WHAT IS SIGNIFICANT ABOUT THIS,
WHY IT TOOK THE TRAJECTORY.
THEY RETESTED A RE-ENTRY
VEHICLE.
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT THIS BEFORE.
ONE OF THE OBSTACLES IS NOT ONLY
GETTING SOMETHING IN SPACE BUT
BRING IT BACK DOWN AND SURVIVE
THE HEAT.
THIS TEST MIMICKED WHAT IT WOULD
BE LIKE IN ICBM RANGE, THE HEAT
AND STRESS OF REENTRY AND THEY
APPARENTLY HAD A SUCCESSFUL TEST
OF THEIR REENTRY VEHICLE
TECHNOLOGY.
FINALLY, A STEPPING STONE ON THE
WAY TO THAT LONGER MISSILE.
VERY SIMILAR TO THE WAY THE
CHINESE DEVELOPED THEIR LONG
RANGE MISSILE.
THEY HAD A MISSILE LIKE THIS
CALLED THE DX 3.
WENT ABOUT THIS LONG.
A FEW YEARS LATER, THEY FOLLOWED
BY THE 4 AND USED THAT AS THE
FIRST STAGE OF THEIR
INTERCONTINENTAL BALLISTIC
MISSILE.
THAT IS WHAT WE THINK NORTH
KOREA IS UP TO.
>> Shepard: WE NEED DEES CALATIN
HERE.
ARE THE CHINESE A PARTNER IN
THAT?
>> THEY'RE DEFINITELY A PARTNER.
THEY WON'T TAKE CARE OF THE
PROBLEM FOR US.
THEY WILL PUT ON MORE SANCTIONS
AND MORE PRESSURE.
THEY AND RUSSIA, AS PUTIN
AFFIRMED TODAY, DON'T WANT TO
SEE A NUCLEAR ARMED NORTH KOREA
CONTINUING TO TEST LIKE THIS,
BUT THEY'RE NOT GOING TO PUT
SANCTIONS ON TO CAUSE THE NORTH
KOREAN REGIME TO COLLAPSE.
THAT IS SENDING MILLIONS OF
REFUGEES INTO CHINA
DESTABILIZING IT, CREATING
CHAOS.
THEY WANT THE UNITED STATES TO
MEET WITH NORTH KOREA TO
NEGOTIATE SOME AGREEMENT.
THAT IS THE COMPROMISE.
PRESSURE PLUS ENGAGEMENT COULD
STOP THE PROGRAM.
>> THANKS, JOE.
>> Shepard: THANKS.
AND SEAN SPICER SAID THAT
ASSAD'S REGIME IS MURDERING
THOUSANDS AND BURNING BODIES TO
COVER IT UP APPARENTLY WITH
SUPPORT FROM RUSSIA AND IRAN.
THEY RELEASED THE PICTURES OF
THE PRISON WITH THE CREMATORIUM.
OFFICIALS SAY SYRIANS ARE
HANGING AS MANY AS 50 PEOPLE A
DAY THERE.
THIS IS ABOUT A 45 MINUTE DRIVE
FROM DAMASCUS.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT IS APPALLED
BY THE ATROCITIES LIKE THIS.
AFTER LAST MONTH'S GAS ATTACKS
THAT KILLED DOZENS, THE AIR
FORCE BOMBED A SYRIAN AIR BASE.
RICH EDSON IS AT THE STATE
DON'T.
RICH?
>> THE ADMINISTRATION POINTS TO
THREE PHOTOS TAKEN OVER A
FOUR-YEAR PERIOD.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT SHOWED THAT
THEY DEMONSTRATE WHAT THEY SAY
IS A CREMATORIUM OF BUILDINGS ON
THE WESTERN EDGE OF THE COMPLEX.
THE U.S. CLAIMS THE PHOTOS SHOW
A PROBABLE AIR INTAKE, FIRE WALL
AND DISCHARGE STACK.
ONE FINAL PHOTO SHOWS MELTING
SNOW ON THE ROOF OF THIS
BUILDING LIKELY, ACCORDING TO
THE ADMINISTRATION, FROM THE
HEAT OF A CREMATORIUM BURNING
VICTIMS.
U.S. OFFICIALS SAY THEY CANNOT
RULE OUT THE HEAT IS FROM
ANOTHER SOURCE AND CANNOT SAY
FOR CERTAIN THAT IT'S A
CREMATORIUM.
ALL THOSE THEY'RE USING THE
PICTURES AND INTELLIGENCE.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT CITING
REPORTS THAT THE ASSAD REGIME
HAS ABDUCTED MORE THAN 100,000
AND PUTS 70 IN A PRISONERS
DESIGNED FOR FIVE.
AMNESTY INTERNATIONAL SAYS
BETWEEN 5,000 AND 13,000 PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN KILLED IN THIS
FACILITY FROM 2011-15, SHEP.
>> Shepard: NOT BRAND NEW
INFORMATION, RICH.
I WONDER IF THERE'S ANYTHING TO
MAKE OF THE TIMING OF THIS.
>> IT'S ALL TOO PRESSURE RUSSIA.
LAST WEEK, SERGEY LAVROV WAS AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE WHITE HOUSE WANTS THE
RUSSIANS TO REIGN IN THE ASSAD
REGIME.
THIS IS A WAY OF PUBLICLY
PRESSURING RUSSIA.
PART OF THE ADMINISTRATION IS
SAYING RUSSIA CANNOT ALLOW THE
ATROCITIES TO CONTINUE AND THEY
WANT RUSSIA TO LEAD ON THE ASSAD
REGIME TO STOP IT.
>> Shepard: THANKS, RICH.
FROM THE SAME AIRLINE THAT
BROUGHT US SCORPIONS ON PLAINS
AND MEN DRAGGED OFF PLANES, NOT
COCKPIT SECURITY CODES POSTS
ONLINE.
HOW UNITED AIRLINES IS
RESPONDING THIS TIME NEXT.
At Angie's List, we believe
there are certain things
you can count on,
like what goes down
doesn't always come back up.
[ Toilet flushes ]
So when you need a plumber,
you can count on us
to help you find
the right person for the job.
Discover all the ways
we can help at Angie's List.
It's about moving forward,
not back.T.
It's looking up, not down.
It's being in motion.
In body, In spirit,
In the now.
BOOST® High Protein
It's intelligent nutrition with
15 grams of protein
and 26 vitamins and minerals.
For when you need
a little extra.
BOOST®
The number one high protein
complete nutritional drink.
Be Up for It
>> Shepard: 14 MINUTES BEFORE
THE HOUR RIGHT NOW.
UNITED AIRLINES RECORDED THEIR
COCKPITS ARE SECURE.
THOUGH A FLIGHT ATTENDANT DID
POST SECURITY CODES FOR THE
COCKPITS ONLINE.
WHOOPS.
UNITED UTILIZES A NUMBER OF
MEASURES TO KEEP SAFE.
IN THE INTERIM, THIS PROTOCOL
ASSURES OUR COCKPITS REMAIN
SECURITY.
IT'S BEEN A TOUGH COUPLE MONTHS
FOR UNITED.
THERE'S BEEN SCORPIONS ON PLANES
AND SECURITY OFFICERS DRAGGED A
PASSENGER OFF OF ANOTHER FLIGHT.
THE FOX BUSINESS NETWORK'S GERRI
WILLIS IS HERE.
WHAT ARE WE GETTED FROM  UNITED?
>> THEY SAY THE INFORMATION WAS
SHARED INADVERTENTLY BUT NOT A
BREACH.
I DON'T KNOW WHY WE'RE SUPPOSED
TO BE ASSURED BY THIS.
EITHER WAY, IT'S NOT GOOD.
YOU DON'T WANT THIS INFORMATION
IN THE PUBLIC DOMAIN.
WE THINK IT'S A BREACH, THAT
SOMEBODY PROBABLY STOLE THE
INFORMATION.
BUT THAT DIDN'T HAPPEN.
IT WAS A UNITED EMPLOYEE.
A CALL FOR MORE PROTECTION FROM
THE PILOT'S UNION SAYING THEY'VE
BEEN ADVOCATING FOR THE
INSTALLATION OF SECONDARY
BARRIERS FOR 16 YEARS.
>> Shepard: SECONDARY BARRIERS.
>> ANOTHER STEP THAT WOULD KEEP
PEOPLE FROM GETTING THROUGH THAT
DOOR.
THERE'S SOME STUFF THAT ARE LIKE
THAT.
THERE'S CHIMES THAT PILOTS CAN
USE TO FIND OUT WHO IS COMING
IN.
THEY CAN STOP SOMEBODY THAT HAS
THE RIGHT CODE FROM COMING IN.
THERE ARE BARRIERS.
BUT PILOTS THINK IT'S NOT
ENOUGH.
>> IS UNITED BEEN FULLY
FORTHCOMING ON THIS MATTER?
>> NO.
I HAVE A LOT OF QUESTIONS.
YOU PROBABLY DO, TOO.
WHERE WAS THIS STUFF PUBLISHED?
IT WAS ON A WEBSITE SOMEWHERE,
INADVERTENT.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT WEBSITE.
HAS A UNITED EMPLOYEE BEEN
GROUNDED OR SUSPENDED?
PUNISHED?
WE DON'T KNOW.
HOW INADVERTENTLY -- HOW DO YOU
DO THAT?
INADVERTENTLY POST SOMETHING.
UNITED NATIONS ABOUT YOU BUT I
CAN BARELY SIGN ON TO MY
COMPUTER.
>> BUT IT'S FINE.
DON'T WORRY ABOUT IT.
IF YOU DIDN'T NEED IT, WHY WAS
IT THERE IN THE FIRST PLACE?
>> A GREAT QUESTION, NOT
ANSWERED.
>> GET THE SCORPIONS --
>> DON'T FORGET ABOUT THE BUNNY.
>> Shepard: FRIGHTENING ALMOST.
VERY LARGE.
FRIGHTENING IN ITS SCOPE.
>> SPECIAL AND BIG.
>> Shepard: IT WON'T BE THE
SAME.
>> I KNOW.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU, GERRI
WILLIS.
HERE IN NEW YORK CITY, A LOT OF
PEOPLE DON'T OWN CARS.
MOST PEOPLE I KNOW DON'T.
THEY GET AROUND WITH THE SUBWAY
OR YELLOW CABS OR SOMETHING.
IMAGINE THAT AROUND THE COUNTRY,
WITHOUT WORRYING ABOUT GAS OR
INSURANCE OR PARKING WHICH
COSTLY ROUGHLY 17 GAZILLION
DOLLARS.
A NEW REPORT PREDICTS MORE
AMERICANS WILL GIVE UP THEIR
CARS.
I MEAN LIKE MOST OF THEM.
SOON!
KENNEDY EXPLAINS ME NEXT.
It's just a burst pipe,
I could fix it.
(laugh)
No.
With Claim RateGuard
your rates won't go up
just because of a claim.
I totally could've -
No!
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> LOT OF CHANGE IN TEN YEARS.
A DECADE AGO, WE DIDN'T HAVE THE
iPHONE.
BY THE END OF THE NEXT DECADE,
WE MAY NOT OWN CARS.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO A GROUP
AFFILIATED WITH STANFORD
UNIVERSITY.
RETHINK X PREDICTS THIS.
BY THE YEAR 2030, THE VAST
MAJORITY OF US WILL ORDER
SELF-DRIVING CARS LIKE THESE ON
DEMAND.
BEST PART, THOSE RIDES COULD BE
FREE.
KENNEDY IS HERE HOST OF
"KENNEDY" ON THE FOX BUSINESS
NETWORK.
I LIKE A FREE RIDE.
>> THE FUTURE IS NOW.
THERE'S NO LONGER FUTURESTS.
THEY'RE PRESENTISTS BECAUSE FOR
DECADES AND GENERATION, THAT'S
WHEN WE WOULD SEE THE SHIFT IN
THE MASSIVE PARADIGMS IN
TRANSPORTATION.
WHAT WOULD HAVE THOUGHT THAT
WHEN THE AUTOMOBILE CAME TO BE
HOW MANY PEOPLE WHO OWN HORSE
WOULD BE LIKE NO ONE WILL EVER
GIVE UP THEIR HORSE.
IT TURNS OUT, THEY WERE WRONG.
YOU DON'T SEE TOO MANY FERRIERS
NOWADAYS.
>> NOT LIKE FIVE OR TEN YEARS
AGO.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> Shepard: THE IDEA HERE IS
THIS HAPPENS REALLY FAST.
BECAUSE THESE BIG COMPANIES COME
IN AND CHANGE THE WAY WE MOVE
AROUND.
SAVE US MONEY THAT WE CAN SPEND
ON OTHER THINGS.
CHANGES THE OIL INDUSTRY, THE
AUTO INDUSTRY.
>> YES.
THEY AUTONOMOUS VEHICLES WILL BE
POWERED BY THE SUN AND POWER
PLANTS WHICH WILL BE MOSTLY
SOLAR IN 10, 15, 20 YEARS.
THAT MEANS THE AUTOMOBILE
INDUSTRY AS WE KNOW IT AS WELL
AS THE ENERGY INDUSTRY AS WE
KNOW IT WILL HAVE TO CHANGE
DRASTICALLY.
THESE COMPANIES ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO GET A MOVE ON.
THEY HAVE TO UNDERSTAND AND SEE
THESE CHANGES IN ADVANCE IN
ORDER TO SURVIVE.
BLOCKBUSTER DIDN'T SURVIVE.
NETFLIX BECAME A VERTICALLY
INTEGRATED STUDIO AND THEY'RE
STILL ALIVE TODAY.
WHO WILL BE ALIVE WHEN THE NEXT
MAJOR SHIFT HAPPENS IN
AUTOMOTIVE PRODUCTION?
>> Shepard: SOUNDS LIKE
EVERYBODY BUT ME.
>> I STILL LOVE A CAR.
I THINK IN 20 YEARS I'LL BE IN
THE MINORITY.
A GREAT DRIVER, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHY WOULD THE RIDE
BE FREE?
>> THAT'S WISHFUL THINKING ON
THE FUTURE IST RIDERS PARTS.
I THINK THE GOVERNMENT WILL
SUBSIDIZE THE AEV.
BUT WHEN GOVERNMENT GETS
INVOLVED, IT STIFLES INNOVATION.
WE WANT FLYING CARS.
>> Shepard: WE CAN'T HAVE FLYING
CARS.
>> I THINK WE CAN.
I'M AN OPTIMIST.
I EMBRACE OR ROBOT OVER-LORDS
AND ANY FORM THEY TAKE,
ESPECIALLY ONE WINGED.
>> Shepard: IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE
THAT THIS SYSTEM WILL CHANGE
THAT QUICKLY.
THAT THEY'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO
CHANGE EVERYTHING ABOUT THE WAY
WE WANDERED HITHER AND FRO FOR
ALL OF THESE YEARS.
>> IF YOU THINK HOW FAST YOUR
PHONE IS COMPARED TO THE FIRST
AND LAPTOP YOU GOT, IT'S MIND
BLOWING.
THINK ABOUT THE ACCESS YOU HAVE
TO CONTEND, MUSIC AND MOVIES AND
EVERYTHING ELSE AND HOW THAT HAS
MOVED SO QUICKLY.
TECHNOLOGICAL ADVANCE WILL BE
EXPONENTIAL.
>> Shepard: FASCINATING.
WE'LL HEAR MORE ABOUT IT FROM
"KENNEDY."
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> SO MUCH IT HURTS.
That means, I'll get it
from here.
Yeah okay so.
I can just quit school and get a
job.
It's ok. Daddy's here.
Daddy.
Hey.
Hi.
Hey buddy
Hey dad
I think we can do this.
Really?
Adam Baily.
My friI say not if you this
protect yourself.ary.
What is scary?
Pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's a serious disease.
My doctor said the risk is
greater now that I'm over 50!
Yeah...ya-ha...
Just one dose of the PREVNAR 13®
vaccine can help protect you
from pneumococcal pneumonia-
an illness that can cause
coughing, chest pain,
difficulty breathing,
and may even put you
in the hospital.
PREVNAR 13® is approved for
adults 18 and older to help
prevent infections from
13 strains of the bacteria that
cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
You should not receive
PREVNAR 13® if you have had
a severe allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
If you have a weakened
immune system,
you may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects
were pain, redness,
and swelling at
the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Get this one done!
Ask about PREVNAR 13®
at your next visit to your
doctor's office or pharmacy.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
A PLANE CRASH OUTSIDE NEW YORK
CITY AT TETERBORO.
IT'S WHERE ALL THE SMALL
CORPORATE JETS COME IN AND OUT
OF.
THIS IS A VIDEO THAT WE HAVE OF
THE PLANE.
WE BELIEVE IT WAS COMING IN FOR
A LANDING.
IT SOUNDS AS IF FROM THE EARLY
RECORDS ON SCENE, SOUNDS LIKE
THIS WAS A LEER JET, MAKE A LEER
35.
AN OLDER JET.
TWO PEOPLE ON BOARD.
THIS IS LIVE PICTURES THAT ARE
COMING IN TO US FROM TETERBORO.
JUST ACROSS THE RIVER FROM NEW
YORK CITY IN NEW JERSEY.
THERE'S NO EXPRESS HIGHWAY TO
GET THERE.
YOU HAVE TO KIND OF GO ON THE
MAIN ROADWAYS.
IT'S NOT EASY TO GET THERE.
A FULL GROUND STOP AT TETERBORO
RIGHT NOW WHICH MEANS GROUND
TRAFFIC IN NEW YORK CITY IS A
MESS.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
"YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL CAVUTO
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> Neil: ALL RIGHT.
WE'RE ON TOP OF THE PLANE CRASH.
MEANTIME, WHERE WERE YOU 20
YEARS AGO TODAY?
IT'S A CURIOUS BIRTHDAY.
BILL CLINTON WAS PRESIDENT AND
NEWT GINGRICH WAS SPEAKER OF THE
HOUSE.
AND AMAZON WAS JUST GETTING
STARTED.
IT WAS START OF THE DOT-COM
BOOM.
>> A LOT GOING ON TODAY.
WELCOME.
I'M NEIL CAVUTO.
>> INTERNET BOOK SELLER
amazon.com WAS A BIG SELLER ON
THE FIRST DAY OF PUBLIC TRADING.
THEY