ARTICLES ABOUT MOMS.
LET'S GIVE OURSELVES THE
ULTIMATE IN LUXE ARE YOU GIFTS
THE BREAK.
GIVE EVERY MOTHER YOU KNOW A
BREAK AS WELL, TOO.
WE TRY TOO HARD, DRIVE OURSELVES
SO HARD AND EXPECT SO MUCH.
ENJOY THE LOVE AROUND YOU.
HERE'S SHEPARD SMITH.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST.
3:00 AT THE WHITE HOUSE WHERE
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES IS WARNING HIS FIRED FBI
DIRECTOR AGAINST LEAKING TO THE
MEDIA AND SUGGESTING THERE MAY
BE TAPES OF THEIR CONVERSATIONS.
MINUTES AGO, WE HEARD FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE SPOKESMAN ON THAT
LIVE ON TELEVISION, WHICH IS
INTERESTING CONSIDERING THE
PRESIDENT FLOATING THE IDEA OF
CANCELLING PRESS BRIEFINGS
BECAUSE IT'S NOT POSSIBLE FOR
HIS PEOPLE TO BE TOTALLY
ACCURATE.
AND THE LAWYERS HAVE SAID
THEY'VE GONE THROUGH THE TAX
RETURNS AND HE HASN'T MADE MONEY
FROM RUSSIAN SOURCES WITH A FEW
EXCEPTIONS.
AND VLADIMIR PUTIN SAYS HE CAN
HELP REDUCE KIM JONG-UN'S
NUCLEAR THREAT.
LET'S GET TO IT.
>> FIRST FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK
THIS FRIDAY AFTERNOON, THE WHITE
HOUSE IS REFUSING TO SAY WHETHER
PRESIDENT TRUMP RECORDED
CONVERSATIONS WITH THE FORMER
FBI DIRECTOR, JAMES COMEY.
THAT'S AFTER HE SENT THIS TWEET.
THAT LED TO THIS EXCHANGE IN
TODAY'S WHITE HOUSE BRIEFING.
>> DID PRESIDENT TRUMP RECORD
HIS CONVERSATIONS WITH JAMES
COMEY?
>> I ASSUME YOU'RE REFERRING TO
THE TWEET.
THE PRESIDENT SAID HE HAS
NOTHING FURTHER ON THAT.
>> WHY DID HE TWEET THAT?
WHAT SHOULD WE INTERPRET FROM
THAT?
>> THE PRESIDENT HAS NOTHING
FURTHER TO ADD.
>> ARE THERE RECORDING DEVICES
IN THE OVAL OFFICE OR THE
RESIDENCE?
>> THERE'S NOTHING FURTHER TO
ADD ON THAT.
>> DID HE THREATEN MR. COMEYTO ?
>> IT'S NOT A THREAT.
THE TWEET SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
I'M MOVING ON.
>> Shepard: HISTORIANS ARE
COMPARING THE TWEET WITH
PRESIDENT NIXON THAT RECORDED
PEOPLE IN THE WHITE HOUSE.
NOW THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE IS
RESPONDING TO THE PRESIDENT'S
TWEET.
THE COMMITTEE IS CONDUCTING ITS
OWN INVESTIGATION TO RUSSIAN
MEDDLING AND POTENTIAL COLLUSION
WITH THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN.
ADAM SCHIFF SAID IF THE
PRESIDENT HAS TAPES OF HIS
CONVERSATIONS OF DIRECTOR COMEY,
IT'S BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF MADE THEM.
FOR A PRESIDENT THAT BASE LESSLY
ACCUSES OF WIRE TAPING, THAT
MR. TRUMP WOULD HAVE ENGAGED IN
SUCH CONDUCT IS STAGGERING.
THE PRESIDENT SHOULD PROVIDE ANY
SUCH RECORDINGS TO CONGRESS OR
ADMIT, ONCE AGAIN, TO HAVE MADE
A THREATENING STATEMENT.
THE CONGRESSMAN IS REFERRING TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S UNFOUNDED
CLAIM THAT PRESIDENT OBAMA HAD
TRUMP TOWER WIRETAPPED.
BACK IN MARCH, DIRECTOR COMEY
SAID THERE WAS NO EVIDENCE TO
BACK UP THAT CLAIM.
ASIDE FROM A LETTER, WE HAVEN'T
HEARD FROM JAMES COMEY SINCE THE
PRESIDENT AXED HIM.
ABC NEWS NOW CITES SOURCES THAT
SAY THAT COMEY WAS FURIOUS AT
THE LACK OF RESPECT THE WHITE
HOUSE SHOWED HIM.
REMEMBER, HE WAS IN LOS ANGELES
GIVING A SPEECH TO BUREAU
EMPLOYEES WHEN NEWS OF HIS
FIRING FLASHING ON TV SCREENS.
THAT'S HOW HE LEARNED OF IT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS CLAIM THE FBI RANK AND
FILE LOST CONFIDENCE IN DIRECTOR
COMEY AS PART OF THE REASONING
FOR THE FIRING.
BUT IN A CONTRADICTION, THE
PRESIDENT SAID THAT WAS NOT
TRUE.
THEN THERE'S THIS FROM THE
FORMER JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
OFFICIAL MATTHEW MILLER.
HE TWEETED, ONE THING I LEARNED
AT DOJ, HE LEAVES A PROTECTIVE
PAPER TRAIL WHEN HE DEEMS
SOMETHING INAPPROPRIATE
HAPPENED.
STAY TUNED.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JOHN ROBERTS ON
THE NORTH LAWN.
WHAT ELSE IS THE PRESIDENT
SAYING?
>> NOT A WHOLE LOT, SHEP.
THIS MORNING AFTER THE PRESIDENT
SAID AT THAT TWEET AT THE UPPER
PRESS OFFICE WHEN I TALKED TO
SEAN SPICER AND SARAH HUCKABEE
SANDERS AND I ASKED THEM ABOUT
THIS, WHEN THE PRESIDENT TALKS
TO SOMEBODY AS HE DID ON THE
TELEPHONE WITH THE FBI DIRECTOR,
ARE THE CALLS LOGGED OR ARE
THERE TRANSCRIPTS MADE OF THEM?
THEY SAID THEY WOULDN'T GO INTO
MORE LEVEL OF DETAIL THAN THAT.
OF COURSE, THEY REITERATED THAT.
IT'S IMPORTANT TO POINT OUT THAT
THE DIRECT OF COLUMBIA IS A
ONE-PARTY CONSENT RECORDING
DISTRICT.
IT'S NOT A STATE.
ONLY ONE PARTY CONSENTING BEFORE
YOU CAN RECORD SOMEBODY.
THE ONLY OTHER CASE WHERE
SOMEBODY WAS RECORDED HERE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE, THERE WAS A
HEATED CONVERSATION BETWEEN A
WHITE HOUSE STAFFER AND A
REPORTER.
SOMEBODY FROM THE WHITE HOUSE
PRESS OFFICE RECORDED THAT.
I ACTUALLY LISTENED TO THAT
CONVERSATION.
BUT SHEP, NOTHING TO INDICATE AT
THIS POINT THAT THE PRESIDENT
HAS ANY KIND OF NIXONIAN TAPING
SYSTEM IN THE OVAL OFFICE OR ANY
TRANSCRIPTS OR RECORDINGS MADE
OF THE TELEPHONE CONVERSATIONS
THAT HE HAD WITH THE FORMER FBI
DIRECTOR.
>> Shepard: JOHN, THERE'S
REPORTS THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
MONTHS AGO ASKED DIRECTOR COMEY
TO PLEDGE HIS LOYALTY.
THERE WERE REPORTS IN "THE NEW
YORK TIMES" HE MAY HAVE DONE
SEEN AT A DINNER.
WHAT IS THE WHITE HOUSE SAYING
ON THIS?
>> THAT'S WHAT THE TWEET WAS
ABOUT IN TERMS OF LEAKING.
THERE'S A STORY IN "THE NEW YORK
TIMES" THAT QUOTES A SOURCE
CLOSE TO COMEY SAYING HE ASKED
FOR A LOYALTY PLEDGE.
HERE'S HOW SEAN SPICER HANDLED
THAT QUESTION.
>> DID THE PRESIDENT IMPLORE HIM
TO PLEDGE HIS LOYALTY?
IS THAT TRUE?
>> NO.
>> FOR IMPORTANT IS IT THAT THE
FBI DIRECTOR BE LOYAL TO THE
PRESIDENT?
IS THAT A QUALITY THE PRESIDENT
WANTS TO SEE IN ANY ONE,
PARTICULARLY THE FBI DIRECTOR?
>> THE PRESIDENT WANTS LOYALTY
TO THE COUNTRY AND RULE OF LAW.
>> SO I DID KNOW SOMEBODY, SHEP,
THAT WAS THE HEAD OF AN AGENCY
THAT WAS A HOLDOVER FROM THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION WHO WHEN
THE PRESIDENT TOOK OVER WAS
ASKED QUESTIONS ABOUT LOYALTY.
HIS ANSWER WAS I'M LOYALTY TO
THE UNITED STATES OF AMERICA,
NOT TO ANY ONE POLITICIAN IN
PARTICULAR.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: JOHN, ANOTHER
STUNNING MOVE THIS MORNING.
THE PRESIDENT ALSO SUGGESTED HE
MIGHT DO AWAY WITH THE DAILY
PRESS BRIEFING AFTER HE
CONTRADICTED HIS OWN
ADMINISTRATION OVER WHY AND WHEN
HE DECIDED TO FIRE JAMES COMEY.
THE PRESIDENT TWEETED AS A VERY
ACTIVE PRESIDENT WITH LOTS OF
THINGS HAPPENING, IT'S NOT
POSSIBLE FOR MY SURROGATES TO
STAND AT THE PODIUM WITH PERFECT
ACCURACY.
MAYBE THE BEST THING TO DO IS
CANCEL ALL PRESS BRIEFINGS HAND
OUT WRITTEN RESPONSES FOR THE
SAKE OF ACCURACY.
AGAIN, THE PRESIDENT SAYS IT'S
IMPOSSIBLE FOR HIS OWN
COMMUNICATIONS TEAM TO BE ON THE
SAME PAGE THAT HE'S ON ALL THE
TIME.
THE WHITE HOUSE INITIALLY SAID
THAT THE PRESIDENT ACTED ON
RECOMMENDATIONS FROM HIS
ATTORNEY GENERAL BEFORE HE FIRED
COMEY.
YESTERDAY THE PRESIDENT TOLD NBC
NEWS HE WAS GOING TO FIRE COMEY
ANYWAY.
BACK TO JOHN ROBERTS AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
DID THE PRESIDENT JUST DOUBLE
DOWN ON THIS WITH AN INTERVIEW
WITH ONE OF OUR FOLK?
>> SPECIFICALLY TO THAT POINT,
HE SAID HE'S MOVING SO FAST HIS
PRESS OFFICE CANNOT KEEP UP WITH
HIM.
WATCH THIS EXCHANGE BETWEEN
JUDGE JANINE AND THE PRESIDENT.
>> ARE YOU MOVING SO QUICKLY
THAT YOUR COMMUNICATIONS KEPT
CANNOT KEEP UP WITH YOU?
>> YES, THAT'S TRUE.
>> SO WHAT DO WE DO ABOUT THAT?
>> WE DON'T HAVE PRESS
CONFERENCES AND WE DO --
>> YOU DON'T MEAN THAT.
>> DON'T HAVE THEM UNLESS I HAVE
THEM EVERY TWO WEEKS AND I DO
THEM MYSELF.
WE DON'T HAVE THEM.
I THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
FIRST OF ALL, YOU HAVE A LEVEL
OF HOSTILITY THAT IS INCREDIBLE.
SARAH HUCKABEE IS A LOVELY YOUNG
WOMAN.
YOU KNOW SEAN SPICER.
HE'S A NICE MAN.
>> IS HE'S YOUR PRESS SECRETARY
TODAY AND TOMORROW?
>> HE'S DOING A GOOD JOB BUT HE
GETS BEAT UP.
>> WILL HE BE THERE TOMORROW?
>> HE'S BEEN THERE FROM THE
BEGINNING.
>> THE PRESIDENT KNEW WHAT THE
REASONS WERE FOR COMEY'S FIRING.
THEY WERE NOT ARTICULATED OR
THEY'RE COMING UP WITH AN
ALTERNATE CASE FOR WHY HE WAS
FIRED.
THE REAL REASON WASN'T
ARTICULATED TO THE VICE
PRESIDENT.
WEDNESDAY MORNING HE WENT OUT
THERE AND GAVE AN INCOMPLETE
ANSWER AS WELL.
SO SEE WHERE IN GOES.
>> Shepard: JOHN, THANK YOU.
THE PRESIDENT'S LAWYERS SAY A
REVIEW OF HIS LAST DECADE OF TAX
RETURNS DOES NOT REFLECT ANY
INCOME OF ANY TYPE FROM RUSSIAN
SOURCES FOR ANY DEBT OWED TO
RUSSIAN LENDERS.
BUT THE LAWYERS CLAIM THERE'S
SOME EXCEPTIONS.
FOR INSTANCE, A PROPERTY SOLD TO
A RUSSIAN BILLIONAIRE FOR $95
MILLION IN 2008.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS NOT RELEASED
THE TAX RETURNS SO FOX NEWS
CANNOT CONFIRM ANY OF THIS.
MEANTIME, THE LAW FIRM WHICH
WROTE THE LETTER FOR THE
PRESIDENT HAS EXTENSIVE TIES TO
RUSSIA AND ACCORDING TO A PRESS
RELEASE ON HIS OWN WEB SITE, THE
LAWSUIT WON A RUSSIAN LAW FIRM
OF THE YEAR AWARD IN 2016.
THE FOX BUSINESS NETWORK'S GERRI
WILLIS IS HERE.
THAT'S ALMOST FUNNY.
>> IT'S ALMOST FUNNY.
>> IT IS FUNNY.
>> THE FIRM IS MORGAN LEWIS.
I HAVE A COPY OF THE LETTER
HERE.
YOU CAN SEE THE LETTER THEY
WROTE ON BEHALF OF THEIR CLIENT.
LET'S BE CLEAR.
TRUMP IS THE CLIENT OF THIS
ORGANIZATION.
THEY REPORT TO HIM.
HE'S PAYING THE 48 -- FREIGHT
HERE.
I HAVE TO TELL YOU, IF YOU READ
BETWEEN THE LINES HERE,
UNDERSTAND THAT MAJOR COMPANIES
IN RUSSIA USE SUBSIDIARIES IN
OTHER PLACES LIKE CYPRESS, LIKE
THE BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS.
AT THE END OF THE DAY, MAYBE
THERE'S SOMETHING ELSE THAT
WE'RE NOT SEEING.
>> Shepard: WHY DID THIS LETTER
COME ABOUT?
DID SOMEONE ASK FOR THIS?
>> SENATOR LINDSEY GRAHAM ASKED
FOR THIS LETTER AS PART OF HIS
INVESTIGATION.
I TRIED TO REACH OUT TO HIS
OFFICE TO FIND OUT WHAT THEY
MAKE OF THIS LETTER, IF IT
SATISFIES THEM.
I WAS UNABLE TO DO SO.
IN AN INVESTIGATION THIS MIGHT
BE STEP NUMBER 1.
YOU WANT TO SEE THE RESULTS, THE
FILINGS TO ASCERTAIN WHAT'S
GOING ON.
>> Shepard: THE TAX RETURNS
ANSWER THE QUESTION.
>> IT WOULD HELP.
WHAT DOES THE IRS DO FOR A LIST
SOMETHING THEY MATCH W 2s WITH
REPORTED INCOME.
INTERNATIONAL FINANCE, IT'S
ANOTHER THING.
>> Shepard: THEY DO A GREAT JOB.
NEVER SPEAK POORLY.
>> WE LOVE THE IRS.
>> Shepard: OBVIOUSLY.
>> THEY'RE OUR FAVORITE PEOPLE.
>> Shepard: THEY ARE.
GO METS!
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
MORE FROM CHRIS WALLACE COMING
UP FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK ON
THIS MERCIFULLY FRIDAY AGAINST.
STAY WITH US.
♪
To err is human.
To anticipate is Lexus.
Experience the Lexus RX
with Advanced Safety standard.
Experience amazing.
the uncertainties of Hep C.
Wondering, What if?
I let go of all those feelings.
Because I am cured with Harvoni.
Harvoni is a revolutionary
treatment for the most common
type of chronic hepatitis C.
It's been prescribed to more
than a quarter million people.
And is proven to cure up to
99% of patients who have had no
prior treatment with 12 weeks.
Certain patients can be cured
with just 8 weeks of Harvoni.
Before starting Harvoni,
your doctor will test to see if
you've ever had hepatitis B,
which may flare up and cause
serious liver problems during
and after Harvoni treatment.
Tell your doctor if you've
ever had hepatitis B,
a liver transplant,
other liver or kidney problems,
HIV or any other medical
conditions and about all
the medicines you take
including herbal supplements.
Taking amiodarone with Harvoni
can cause a serious slowing
of your heart rate.
Common side effects of Harvoni
include tiredness,
headache and weakness.
Ready to let go of Hep C?
Ask your Hep C Specialist
about Harvoni.
>> Shepard: CONTINUING COVERAGE
OF THE PRESIDENT'S SUGGESTION
THAT CONVERSATIONSES  IN THE
OVAL OFFICE MAY BE RECORDED.
CHRIS WALLACE JOINS US WITH
MORE.
THIS WAS COMMON PRACTICE IN THE
NIXON ADMINISTRATION?
RECORDING CONVERSATIONS.
>> WHEN I HEARD THAT EXCHANGE
TODAY BETWEEN JEFF MASON, WHITE
HOUSE REPORTER, AND SEAN SPICER
SPEAKING FROM THE PODIUM IN THE
BRIEFING ROOM FOR THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES, IT TOOK MY
BREATH AWAY.
THAT'S WHAT IN WATERGATE THEY
CALL A NONDENIAL DENIAL.
HE WAS ASKED SPECIFICALLY, IS
THERE A RECORDING DEVICE IN THE
OVAL OFFICE OF THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
HE SAID I HAVE NOTHING FOR YOU
ON THAT.
HE COULD HAVE SAID NO.
HE COULD HAVE SAID YES.
HE SAID I HAVE NOTHING FOR YOU
ON THAT.
THAT IS A NONDENIAL DENIAL.
IT MAY JUST BE THAT THE
PRESIDENT IS TROLLING THE PRESS
CORPS AND SAYING WORK YOURSELF
INTO A FRENZY ABOUT THIS AND
TURNS OUT IT NOTHING.
WHY WOULD HE DO THAT?
WHY WOULD HE WANT TO DECREASE
THE CREDIBILITY WHICH IS ALREADY
IN QUESTION OF THIS WHITE HOUSE
AND COMMENTS MADE FROM THAT
PODIUM?
SEEMS TO ME THAT YOU'RE PLAYING
A VERY DANGEROUS GAME WITH THE
CURRENCY OF THE CREDIBILITY OF
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
>> Shepard: THIS FIRST CAME UP
IN THE CONTEXT OF DISCUSSION
REGARDING JAMES COMEY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS THE TWEET THAT CAME FROM
THE PRESIDENT THIS MORNING WHEN
HE SAID, YOU KNOW, HE BETTER
HOPE THERE'S NO TAPES IF HE WILL
KEEP LEAKING, THIS GOES BACK TO
YESTERDAY WHEN THE PRESIDENT
TOLD LESTER HOLT ON THREE
SEPARATE OCCASIONS, INCLUDING
ONCE AT THE WHITE HOUSE, A WEEK
AFTER THE INAUGURATION, THAT
COMEY TOLD THE PRESIDENT THAT HE
WAS NOT A TARGET OF THE
INVESTIGATION.
THAT ALWAYS SEEMED DUBIOUS GIVEN
THE FACT THAT YOU CAN ARGUE THAT
COMEY HAD AN OVERLY INFLATED
SENSE OF HIS OWN INTEGRITY.
BUT THE IDEA THAT HE WOULD SAY
TO THE POTENTIAL TARGET OF AN
INVESTIGATION, YOU'RE OFF THE
HOOK, THAT ALWAYS SEEMED
UNLIKELY.
SURE ENOUGH THIS MORNING, COMEY
THROUGH SOURCES, ASSOCIATES,
LEAKED THE STORY TO "THE NEW
YORK TIMES," TOLD A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT STORY THAT SAID THAT
THE PRESIDENT CALLED FOR THE
DINNER AND AT THE DINNER ASKED
HIM THREE SEPARATE TIMES, WILL
YOU PLEDGE YOUR LOYALTY TO ME.
COMB MY REFUSED TO DO SO.
THAT LED TO THE TWEET.
LOOK, HERE'S THE REAL THING THAT
I WONDER ABOUT HERE, SHEP.
IF THE WHOLE POINT A WEEK AGO
WAS THAT THE PRESIDENT WAS FED
UP WITH THE HIGH PROFILE OF THE
RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION AND THE
HIGH PROFILE OF JAMES COMEY,
LOOK AT EVERY STEP THAT'S BEEN
TAKEN IN THE LAST SEVEN DAYS.
YOU SAID IF HE HAD GONE ABOUT IT
AS PURPOSELY TO RAISE COMEY'S
PROFILE AND RAISE QUESTIONS
ABOUT THE RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION,
HE COULDN'T HAVE DONE IT BETTER
THAN HE HAS.
I FIND IT ONE OF THE MOST
ASTONISHING WEEKS THAT I'VE EVER
COVERED IN THIS TOWN.
>> Shepard: WHAT DOES THIS TELL
US ABOUT THE INNER WORKINGS OF
THE WHITE HOUSE?
THE ABILITY TO HAVE THE TRUST OF
THE PEOPLE ON BIG MATTERS, IF
AND WHEN SOMETHING HAPPENS?
BECAUSE SOMETHING WILL.
>> WELL, YOU WONDER ABOUT THE
TRUST OF THE PEOPLE INSIDE THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THE PRESIDENT WAS FURIOUS ON
TUESDAY AFTER HE SUDDENLY
ANNOUNCED COMEY'S FIRING THAT
THERE WASN'T A MORE CONCERTED
EFFORT ON HIS COMMUNICATIONS
TEAM TO DEFEND HIM.
THE REASON WAS, THEY DIDN'T SET
UP TIME TO THINK ABOUT IT AND
ORGANIZE.
THERE'S A CREDIBLE TEAM.
THEY COULD HAVE PUT TOGETHER AN
ARGUMENT.
THEN OF COURSE, THE OTHER THING,
TURNED OUT THE ORIGINAL REASON
THAT THEY WERE GIVEN AND THE
PRESIDENT HIMSELF PUT IN HIS
LETTER FIRING COMEY TURNS OUT
NOT TO HAVE BEEN TRUE.
HE SAID IN A LETTER I DID THIS
UNDER RECOMMENDATION OF THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL AND THE DEPUTY
ATTORNEY GENERAL BECAUSE OF THE
WAY COMEY HANDLED THE CLINTON
INVESTIGATION.
YESTERDAY HE SAID IT WASN'T
TRUE.
HE PLANNED TO FIRE HIM BEFORE HE
MET WITH THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT.
SO EVERY STEP HE'S TAKEN THIS
WEEK HAS CUT INTO THE
CREDIBILITY OF THIS WHITE HOUSE,
THE TRUST OF THE PEOPLE INSIDE
THE WHITE HOUSE AND CLEARLY I
THINK THE TRUST THAT THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE PAY TO THIS
PRESIDENT AND THE WHITE HOUSE
STAFF.
>> Shepard: CHRIS, YOU COVERED A
LOT OF WHITE HOUSES.
I WONDER IF THE OBJECTIVE
JOURNALIST YOU ARE, HOW YOU
WOULD DESCRIBE THE STATE OF THIS
WHITE HOUSE IN THIS PRESIDENCY
AT THIS MOMENT.
>> I'VE BEEN THINKING ABOUT THAT
A LOT TODAY.
I'VE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE IT
AND I FIND IT TROUBLING AND
TROUBLED.
I JUST DON'T UNDERSTAND THE GAME
THAT THEY'RE PLAYING.
IT ISN'T A GAME.
YOU'RE DEALING WITH VERY SERIOUS
ISSUES.
IF THE PRESIDENT IS UPSET --
JUST THINK OF THIS.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT HE WANTS
TOLD LESTER HOLT, I WANT TO GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
IT WANT IT DOWN QUICKLY BUT FIND
OUT.
TODAY HE SENDS OUT A TWEET AND
HE SENT ONE OUT EARLIER IN THE
WEEKS SAYING IT'S A HOAX AND A
TAX-PAYER FUNDED CHARADE.
DOES HE WANT TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION OR JUST WANT TO
GET TO THE END OF THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION?
THAT'S A LEGITIMATE QUESTION.
>> Shepard: IS THERE A DANGER IN
THIS LEVEL OF DISARRAY?
>> SURE.
THIS IS THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
THIS IS THE MAN WHO IS RUNNING
THE COUNTRY.
THIS IS THE MAN THAT WE HAVE TO
TRUST AS YOU POINT OUT IN A
CRISIS, AND THERE WILL BE A
CRISIS.
EVERYTHING THAT HAS HAPPENED
THIS WEEK HAS CHIPPED AWAY AT
THAT CREDIBILITY.
IT'S A VERY DISTRESSING
SITUATION.
>> Shepard: WE TEND TO LOOK AT
THESE THINGS OF THE VIEW OF
THOSE THAT SUPPORT AND THE VIEWS
OF THOSE THAT ARE CRITICS.
IN THIS CASE IT COMES FROM ALL
SIDES.
THERE'S A GENERAL OBSERVATION
THAT WE'RE IN A LEGAL OF UNUSUAL
THAT MOST PEOPLE WOULDN'T HAVE
HAD ANY CONTACT CAN'T FIND
REFERENCE TO HISTORICALLY.
MANY QUESTIONS ABOUT HOW YOU
MIGHT GET OUT OF THIS CYCLE,
THIS CYCLE THAT THIS WHITE HOUSE
SEEMS TO BE INTO SO WE CAN GET
ABOUT THE BUSINESS OF THE
NATION.
CHRIS, IT'S CLEARLY ALL STOPPED.
>> YEAH.
THAT'S ANOTHER POINT THAT I FIND
ASTONISHING.
THE PRESIDENT DID HAVE SOME
MOMENTUM FINALLY FOR HIS
LEGISLATIVE INITIATIVES, HIS
LEGISLATIVE AGENDA THIS LAST
WEEK WITH THE PASSING AND REPEAL
AND REPLAC CAN LIKE THE BILL, ND
IT.
IT HAD PASSED THE HOUSE.
A MAJOR BARRIER.
THE REPUBLICANS AND THE SENATE
SET UP A WORKING GROUP TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT TO DO NEXT.
WE WERE GETTING DOWN TO SERIOUS
BUSINESS TO SOLVE PROBLEMS IN
THE NATION.
TALK ABOUT TAX REFORM.
TALK ABOUT TRADE.
SUDDENLY WE HAVE SPEND A WEEK
AND IT'S GOING TO GO ON LONGER
THAN THIS.
THIS WON'T BE OVER SUNDAY.
THIS WILL GO INTO NEXT WEEK AND
MAYBE BEYOND.
THERE'S TALK ABOUT ROD
ROSENSTEIN, THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL, HAVING TO TESTIFY
BEFORE THE ENTIRE SENATE AND
BRIEF THEM ON THIS SITUATION.
THERE'S GOING TO BE THE
ANNOUNCEMENT OF A REPLACEMENT
FOR COMEY.
CONFIRMATION HEARINGS THAT WILL
BE CONTROVERSIAL.
THIS WILL STOP ALL OF THE
BUSINESS THAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE
DONE TO DEAL WITH THE PROBLEMS
OF THE AMERICAN PEOPLE FOR A
LONG PERIOD OF TIME.
WE'RE GOING TO BE IN ONE OF THE
WORST BACK FIGHTING, CONFUSING,
QUAGMIRES OF THE PRESIDENT'S OWN
MAKING.
>> CHRIS WALLACE, SEE YOU THIS
SUNDAY.
THANK YOU.
I was always
"the girl with psoriasis."
People don't stare anymore.
I never joined in.
That wasn't fair to any of us.
I was covered.
I tried lots of things
over the years.
But I didn't give up.
I kept on fighting.
I found something that worked.
That still works.
Now?
SEE ME.
I found clear skin that lasts.
See if COSENTYX could make a
difference for you-
COSENTYX is proven to help
people with moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis...
...find clear skin that
can last.
Don't use if you're allergic
to COSENTYX.
Before starting COSENTYX,
you should be checked
for tuberculosis.
An increased risk of infections
and lowered ability
to fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection or symptoms.
Or if you have received a
vaccine or plan to.
If you have inflammatory
bowel disease,
tell your doctor if symptoms
develop or worsen.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
SEE ME
to know...
...clear skin can last.
Don't hold back...
...ask your dermatologist if
COSENTYX can help you
find clear skin that lasts.
Thereit comes to technology,
about my small business so when
I need someone that understands
my unique needs.
My Dell Small Business Advisor
has gotten to know our business
so well that is feels like he's
a part of our team.
With one phone call, he sets me
up with tailored products
and services.
And when my advisor is focused
on my tech,
I can focus on my small
business.
♪
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night,
so he got home safe.
Yeah, my dad says our
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
The shLike a bald penguin.
How do I look?
[ laughing ]
Show me the
Billboard Music Awards.
Show me Top Artist.
Show me the
Top Hot 100 Artist.
They give awards for being
hot and 100 years old?
We'll take 2!
[ laughing ]
XFINITY X1 gives you
exclusive access to the best
of the Billboard Music Awards
just by using your voice.
The Billboard Music Awards.
Sunday, May 21st eight
seven central only on ABC.
>> Shepard: THIS WEEKEND ON "FOX
NEWS SUNDAY," CHRIS WALLACE WILL
HAVE THE LATEST ON THE FIRING OF
JAMES COMEY AND THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
HI GUEST, MIKE LEE FROM THE
JUDICIARY COMMITTEE AND MARK
WARNER ON "FOX NEWS SUNDAY" ON
YOUR LOCAL FOX STATIONS.
CHECK YOUR LISTINGS.
ATTORNEY GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS
IS TELLING PROSECUTORS TO GO
AFTER THE MOST SERIOUS CHARGES
FOR MOST ACCUSED CRIMINALS.
THIS MOVE REVERSES SOME OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION POLICIES THAT
WERE MEANT TO FIGHT OVERCROWDING
IN U.S. PRISONS.
ANALYSTS SAY IT WILL PUT MORE
PEOPLE BEHIND BARS AND FOR
LONGER PERIODS OF TIME.
ATTORNEY GENERAL SESSIONS HAS
PROMISED TO CRACK DOWN ON DRUGS
A TOP PRIORITY AT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT.
HE SAID THE NEW POLICY WILL
IMPROVE MORE CONSISTENCY IN
SENTENCING.
BUT CRITICS SAY LOW LEVEL
CRIMINALS WILL FACE MANDATORY
SENTENCES.
PETER DOOCY HAS MORE.
>> SHEP, THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION TRIED TO EMPTY
PRISONS OF PEOPLE THAT WERE
THERE FOR NONVIOLENT DRUG
OFFENSES.
THAT POLICY ENDED TODAY.
THE NEW ATTORNEY JERN RALEIGH
JEFF SESSIONS SAYS THAT HE'S
READY TO ENFORCE LAWS JUST AS
CONGRESS WROTE THEM.
>> I HAVE EMPOWERED OUR
PROSECUTORS TO CHARGE AND PURSUE
THE MOST SERIOUS OFFENSE AS I
BELIEVE THE LAW REQUIRES, MOST
SERIOUS READILY PROVABLE
OFFENSE.
IT MEANS THAT WE'RE GOING TO
MEET OUR RESPONSIBILITY TO
ENFORCE THE LAW WITH JUDGMENT
AND FAIRNESS.
IT'S SIMPLY THE RIGHT AND MORAL
THING TO DO.
>> ONE OF ATTORNEY GENERAL
SESSIONS PREDECESSOR, ERIC
HOLDER PUSHES THE SMART ON CRIME
PLAN.
HE SAID HE THINKS THIS PLAN IS
DUMB ON CRIME.
UNDER THE SMART ON CRIME PLAN,
THERE WOULD BE WIGGLE ROOM FOR
PROSECUTORS LIKE NOT DISCLOSING
IN COURT WHAT QUANTITY A DRUG A
DEFENDANT WAS ARRESTED WITH AS
LONG AS NOBODY GOT HURT DURING
THE CRIME OR THE ARREST.
THAT POLICY IS OVER.
RESCINDED BY THIS ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
NOW SOME PRISON ADVOCATES,
REFORM ADVOCATES, ARE ALARMED.
>> ONE THING WE KNOW ABOUT LONG
PRISON SENTENCES, THEY PRODUCE
DIMINISHING RETURNS FOR PUBLIC
SAFETY.
PEOPLE ARE IN THEIR 30s, 40s AND
50s ARE MUCH LESS LIKELY TO BE
INVOLVED IN CRIME THAN PEOPLE IN
THEIR TEENS AND 20s.
SO BY LENGTHENING PRISON TERMS,
WE'RE GETTING LESS PUBLIC SAFETY
IMPACT FROM EACH SUCCEEDING YEAR
AND COMES AT A GREATER COST TO
THE TAXPAYERS.
>> I WAS WITH ATTORNEY
GENERALING SESSIONS IN WEST
VIRGINIA YESTERDAY WHERE HE
ANNOUNCED A NEW INITIATIVE TO
USE TOUGHER TACTICS TO ROUND UP
DRUG DEALERS.
THERE'S OBVIOUSLY GOING TO BE A
MORE AGGRESSIVE EFFORT TO ARREST
DRUG DEALERS.
NOW HE'S SAYING WHAT HE WANTS TO
DO ONCE THEY'RE IN CUSTODY, THEY
FACE A MANDATORY MINIMUM
SENTENCE.
>> Shepard: PETER DOOCY, THANK
YOU.
NORTH KOREA IS GETTING PERSONAL
WITH ITS LATEST THREATS.
KIM JONG-UN'S BRUTAL REGIME IS
NOW VOWING TO PUNISH AMERICAN
DETAINEES IN THE COUNTRY.
THAT COMES DAYS AFTER ANOTHER
U.S. CITIZEN IS BEHIND BARS.
ALL OF THIS AFTER THEY PROMISE
TO PURSUE A KNEW NUCLEAR TEST.
GORDON CHANG JOINS US NEXT FROM
THE FOX NEWS DECK.
[hissing]
Uh-
I-
[sound of wrench]
[intricate guitar riff]
[engine starts]
[guitar continues]
how to brush his teeth.
(woman VO)
In March, my husband
didn't recognize our grandson.
(woman 2 VO)
That's when moderate Alzheimer's
made me a caregiver.
(AVO)
If their Alzheimer's
is getting worse,
ask about once-a-day NAMZARIC.
NAMZARIC is approved for
moderate to severe
Alzheimer's disease
in patients who are
taking donepezil.
It may improve cognition
and overall function,
and may slow the worsening
of symptoms for a while.
NAMZARIC does not change
the underlying
disease progression.
Don't take if allergic
to memantine,
donepezil, piperidine,
or any of the ingredients
in NAMZARIC.
Tell the doctor
about any conditions;
including heart, lung, bladder,
kidney or liver problems,
seizures, stomach ulcers,
or procedures with anesthesia.
Serious side effects may occur,
including muscle
problems if given anesthesia;
slow heartbeat, fainting,
more stomach acid
which may lead to
ulcers and bleeding;
nausea, vomiting,
difficulty urinating,
seizures, and worsening
of lung problems.
Most common side effects
are headache, diarrhea,
dizziness, loss of appetite,
and bruising.
(woman 2 VO)
I don't know
what tomorrow will bring
but I'm doing what I can.
(AVO)
Ask about NAMZARIC today.
>> Shepard: AN ISLAMIC STATE
TERRORIST MISS ADD TARGET AND
MURDERED TWO DOZEN PEOPLE IN
SOUTHWEST PAKISTAN.
THEY TARGETED THE LEADER OF THE
SENATE BUT MISSED.
ISIS HAS CLAIMED RESPONSIBILITY
FOR THE ATTACK.
STORMS KNOCKED DOWN TREES AND
DAMAGED THE ROOF OF A BAPTIST
CHURCH IN TEXAS, WHITE OAKS.
ONE TREE SPLIT IN HALF AND
TOSSED OTHERS.
NO REPORTS OF INJURY.
HAPPENED YESTERDAY EAST OF
LOS ANGELES.
CREWS RESCUED THE RIDER AND THE
HELICOPTER LIFTED THE 1,200
POUND ANIMAL.
HAD A HECK OF A RIDE OUT OF THE
DEAL.
THE NEWS CONTINUES AFTER THIS.
All finished.
Umm...
You wouldn't want your
painter to quit part way,
I think you missed a spot.
so when it comes to
pain relievers,
why put up with
just part of a day?
Aleve, live whole not part.
You want this color
over the whole house?
>> Shepard: A RUSSIAN FIGHTER
JET ARMED WITH AIR-TO-AIR
MISSILES CAME WITHIN 20 FEET OF
A SURVEILLANCE PLANES OVER THE
BLACK SEA.
THAT'S WHAT U.S. OFFICIALS ARE
TELLING FOX NEWS.
WE'RE TOLD IT HAPPENED TUESDAY
IN INTERNATIONAL AIRSPACE NEAR
CRIMEA.
THAT'S PART OF THE UKRAINE THAT
RUSSIAN CLAIMED AS THEIR OWN.
U.S. OFFICIALS SAID IT'S VERY
RARE AND HIGHLY PROVOCATIVE FOR
A VISIBLY ARMED RUSSIAN JET TO
INTERCEPT AN AMERICAN PLANE.
WE'RE ALSO LEARNING THAT SOUTH
KOREA'S AIR FORCE INTERCEPTED A
RUSH JET FLYING NEAR SOUTH KOREA
AND THE U.S.S. CARL VINSON
STRIKE GROUP IN THE SEA OF
JAPAN.
LAST WEEK, A PAIR OF RUSSIAN
BOMBERS FLEW OFF THE COAST OF
ALASKA FORCING THE AIR FORCE TO
SCRAMBLE JETS TO INTERCEPT THE
BOMBERS.
VLADIMIR PUTIN SAYS HE'S READY
TO PLAY A CONSTRUCTIVE ROLE IN
DEALING WITH NORTH KOREA'S
NUCLEAR THREAT.
VLADIMIR PUTIN MADE THE COMMENT
DURING A PHONE CALL WITH SOUTH
KOREA'S NEW LEADER.
SOUTH KOREA HAS BEEN ONE OF
AMERICA'S LOWEST ALLIES AND HAD
A MAJOR LEADERSHIP CHANGE.
THE FORMER PRESIDENT -- THE
CURRENT PRESIDENT TOOK THE OATH
OF OFFICE THIS WEEK AFTER A
CORRUPTION SCANDAL LED TO THE
IMPEACHMENT OF THEIR FORMER
PRESIDENT.
THE NEW PRESIDENT HAS CALLED FOR
TALKS WITH NORTH KOREA.
RICH EDSON HAS MORE.
>> SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON AND THE UNITED STATES
WERE ASKING RUSSIA TO
PARTICIPATE IN THIS PRESSURE
CAMPAIGN THAT THEY'RE WORKING ON
TO TRY TO CONVINCE NORTH KOREA
TO SURRENDER NUCLEAR WEAPONS AND
THE BALLISTIC MISSILE PROGRAM.
IT'S UNCLEAR WHAT PRESIDENT
VLADIMIR PUTIN MEANS BY A
CONSTRUCTIVE ROLE FOR RUSSIA.
THE U.S. IS WORKING ON THAT
PRESSURE CAMPAIGN.
THEY WANT TO ISOLATE NORTH KOREA
DIPLOMATICALLY AND ECONOMICALLY,
PARTICULARLY WANTS TO GET CHINA
ON BOARD THERE.
HOWEVER, THE NEWLY-ELECTED SOUTH
KOREAN PRESIDENT WAS PUSHING FOR
MORE DIALOGUE WITH NORTH KOREA.
THE UNITED STATES SAYS THEY
WOULD ENGAGE IN A DISCUSSION
WITH NORTH KOREA ONLY AFTER IT
CHANGES ITS BEHAVIOR.
THEY HAVE NOT BEEN SPECIFIC TO
THE U.S. ON WHAT THE CONDITIONS
COULD BE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT IS THE LATEST
ON THE FOUR AMERICANS THE NORTH
KOREANS HAVE DETAINED?
>> WE'RE HEARING FROM NORTH
KOREAN STATE MEDIA.
NORTH KOREA RESERVES THE RIGHT
TO RUTHLESSLY PUNISH AMERICAN
CITIZENS THEY HAVE ARRESTED AND
THE IDEA THAT THESE CAPTIVES
HAVE BEEN TAKEN BY NORTH KOREA
TO BE USED AS BARGAINING CHIPS
IS PURE IGNORANCE.
THEY SAID THEY WILL REVEAL THE
EXTENT OF THE CHARGES AGAINST
THESE FOUR AMERICANS.
THE PROBLEM HERE, SHEP, THE
UNITED STATES ALSO HAS NO
DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS WITH NORTH
KOREA.
THEY HAVE TO GO THROUGH THE
SWEDISH EMBASSY OR THE RULES
THEY HAVE ESTABLISHED, THE
SWEDISH OFFICIALS SHOULD CHECK
ON THESE AMERICANS IN A COUPLE
DAYS.
BUT THE U.S. STATE DEPARTMENT
SAYS THOSE MEETINGS AND
CHECK-ONS ARE CONSTANTLY PUSHED
BACK, DELAYED, SOMETIMES NEVER
HAPPEN.
EARLIER THIS WEEK THE STATE
DEPARTMENT REISSUED TRAVEL
WARNING TO NORTH KOREA TELLING
AMERICANS NOT TO GO THERE
BECAUSE THOSE ARRESTED ARE
TREATED BY THE WARTIME LAW OF
NORTH KOREA.
FOUR AMERICANS THERE NOW, SHEP.
>> Shepard: RICH EDSON FROM THE
STATE DEPARTMENT.
LIKE WE NEEDED A WARNING NOT TO
GO THERE.
I DON'T KNOW.
AND NOW AUTHOR OF "NUCLEAR SHOW
DOWN TAKES ON THE WORLD", ARTHUR
CHANG.
WHERE ARE WE NORTH KOREA?
LOOKS LIKE A MESS.
>> YEAH, IT CONTINUES TO BE A
MESS.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
CONSUMED BY THE COMEY FIRING.
THEY'RE NOT PAYING ATTENTION TO
NORTH KOREA.
NOW YOU HAVE PUTIN MAKING
COMMENTS ABOUT BEING A
CONSTRUCTIVE FORCE.
>> Shepard: YEAH WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OF THIS?
>> I DON'T THINK PUTIN WILL GET
INVOLVED.
THEY WEREN'T INVOLVED IN 2003.
THEY WERE A MEMBER BUT NEVER
PARTICIPATED.
IF PUTIN -- LAST THING HE WANTS
TO GET IN A COMPETITION ABOUT
SUPPORTING NORTH KOREA.
HE DOESN'T HAVE THE MONEY TO DO
THAT OR THE INTEREST IN HIS FAR
EAST.
SO HE'S GOING TO SAY THINGS LIKE
THIS BECAUSE THE SOUTH KOREAN
PRESIDENT CALLS HIM.
IT STROKES HIS EGO.
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO BE TOO
INVOLVED.
>> Shepard: THE NORTH KOREAN SAY
THEY'RE GOING TO DO A SIXTH
NUCLEAR TEST.
WHERE IS OUR LEVERAGE WITH CHINA
AND HOW DO WE APPLY IT?
>> OUR LEVERAGE IS, WE CAN
UNPLUG CHINESE BANKS FOR MONEY
LAUNDERING FROM THE CHINESE.
WE HAVE NEVER DONE IT.
PRESIDENT OBAMA THREATENED TO DO
THAT IN SEPTEMBER.
BUT HE NEVER CARRIED THROUGH.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS IN
THIS COOPERATIVE FACE WITH
CHINA.
THEY'RE NOT THREATENING
ANYTHING.
WE DO HAVE IT.
WE DON'T HAVE THE POLITICAL
WILL.
WE HAVE SO MUCH MORE LEVERAGE
THAN CHINA THAN CHINA HAS OVER
US BUT WE DON'T USE IT.
IT'S A HOLD RIGHT NOW.
>> Shepard: PRACTICALLY
SPEAKING, I'M CURIOUS TO FIND
OUT WHAT WILL HAPPEN IF THEY
MAKE A SIXTH TEST.
EVEN THE CHINESE HAVE WARNED
THEM.
>> THE CHINESE HAVE AND WILL
POSE MORE PRESSURE ON THEM.
THE BALL IS IN PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
COURT.
NORTH KOREA WON'T GET THE
ABILITY TO LAND A NUKE ON
U.S.
HE HAS THREE OR FOUR YEARS TO
STOP THEM.
>> Shepard: WHERE DO WE GET THAT
NUMBER?
>> THAT'S THE NUMBER OF YEARS IT
WOULD TAKE FOR NORTH KOREA TO
DEVELOP THE TECHNOLOGY, THE HEAT
SHIELDING TO PUT A NUCLEAR
WARHEAD ON A BALLISTIC MISSILE.
THEY HAVE NUKES FOR INTERMEDIATE
RANGE MISSILES THAT CAN HIT
JAPAN.
BUT THEY CAN'T REALLY GET TOO
FAR INTO THE AMERICAN HOMELAND.
THAT'S THAT FOUR-YEAR TIME
FRAME.
PEOPLE SAY THREE, SOME SAY FIVE.
IT'S REALLY CLOSE.
PROBABLY WITHIN PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S TERM.
>> Shepard: IS PERCEIVED
DISARRAY IN WASHINGTON, DOES
THAT HAVE AN EFFECT ON NORTH
KOREA RIGHT NOW?
>> YES, WITH HISTORY AS A GUIDE.
THEY THEY WE'RE NOT LOOKING OR
WE'RE NOT IN A CAPACITY TO
RESPOND.
RIGHT NOW WITH THE FOE
CONTRIBUTION ON DOMESTIC
AFFAIRS, IT'S A PERFECT TIME FOR
KIM JONG-UN TO SET OFF THAT
SIXTH NUCLEAR TEST.
HE WANTED TO NOT DO IT BEFORE
MAY 9th.
THAT'S THE SOUTH KOREAN
ELECTION.
HE DIDN'T WANT TO DERAIL THE
CHANCES OF THE NEW PRESIDENT WHO
IS PRO NORTH KOREA.
NOW MOON HAS BEEN ELECTED.
NORTH KOREA CAN SET THAT TEST
OFF ANY TIME THEY THINK IS
POLITICALLY ADVANTAGEOUS.
I THINK THEY WILL WAIT A FEW
WEEKS.
WE'LL WAIT.
>> Shepard: GORDON CHANG.
THANKS.
>> THANKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: AND MITCH McCONNELL
SAID WOMEN CAN TALK PART IN ALL
TALKS ON THE HEALTHCARE BILL.
McCONNELL SAID THE MEETINGS ARE
NOW OPEN TO ANY REPUBLICAN
SENATOR THAT WANTS TO ATTEND.
SENATE REPUBLICANS HAVE BEEN
WORKING ON THE HEALTHCARE BILL
SINCE THE HOUSE PASSED ITS
VERSION LAST WEEK.
MIKE EMANUEL IS ON CAPITOL HILL
WITH AN UPDATE.
MIKE?
>> SHEP, GOOD AFTERNOON.
I'M TOLD THE PRICE TAG AND
IMPACT OF THE HOUSE HELD CARE
BILL IS EXPECTED IN THE NEXT TEN
DAYS OR SO, THE WEEK OF MAY 22
FROM THE CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
OFFICE.
MITCH McCONNELL HAS BEEN DOING
OUTREACH TO WOMEN SENATORS
ACCORDING TO SENATE SOURCES.
McCONNELL AIDES SAY HE'S INVITED
ALL SENATORS TO ATTEND
HEALTHCARE WORKING GROUP
MEETINGS AFTER TAKING HEAT THAT
THE GROUP WAS MADE UP OF 13 MEN.
>> LET ME TRY AGAIN.
THERE IS NO PARTICULAR WORKING
GROUP BECAUSE WE'RE MEETING --
ALL 52 OF US HAVE LUNCH EVERY
DAY.
TUESDAY, WEDNESDAY AND THURSDAY.
EVERYBODY IS AT THE TABLE.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT THE BASIS
WAS FOR MAKING UP THIS GROUP.
REALLY IS UP TO THE LEADERS TO
DECIDE WHOM THEY WANT.
SO I'M NOT REALLY TROUBLED BY IT
BECAUSE I'M GOING TO CONTINUE TO
WORK WITH OTHER SENATORS AND
PUSH FORWARD THE BILL THAT WE
INTRODUCED.
>> THERE'S CURRENTSLY FIVE
REPUBLICAN WOMEN SENATORS AND
THEY SOUND INTERESTED IN
ATTENDING THE MEETINGS GOING
FORWARD, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHAT ARE THE FOCUS
POINTS OF THE HEALTHCARE TALKS,
MIKE?
>> I'M TOLD THE MAJOR AREAS OF
DISCUSSIONS ARE DIVIDED INTO
FOUR KEY GROUPS, MAJOR BUCKETS
THEY'RE LOOKING AT.
FOR EXAMPLE, MEDICAID EXPANDED
UNDER OBAMACARE.
WHAT DO THEY DO GOING FORWARD?
THERE'S CONCERN ABOUT AN ABRUPT
CUT OFF.
TAX CREDITS TO HELP POOR PEOPLE
AFFORD INSURANCE.
INSURANCE REGULATIONS INCLUDING
PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS.
MANY REGULATIONS ARE INCLUDED IN
OBAMACARE, MANY REPUBLICANS WANT
TO GET RID OF THEM.
SOME ARE OBVIOUSLY CONCERNED
ABOUT PEOPLE WITH PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS.
AND THEN INSURANCE MARKET
STABILITY.
MANY HEADLINES ABOUT INSURERS
PULLING OUT OF OFFERING PLANS IN
CERTAIN STATES.
HOW DO YOU GET MORE COMPETITION
FOR YOUR CONSTITUENTS?
AS WE HEARD BEFORE, IT'S
COMPLICATED.
>> Shepard: THANKS, MIKE.
IN OHIO TODAY, SIX CHILDREN ARE
LIVING WITH A TERRIBLE NEW
REALITY.
THEIR FATHER, THE POLICE CHIEF,
WILL NEVER WALK THROUGH THE DOOR
AGAIN.
HE RESPONDED TO A REPORT OF A
GUNMAN AT A NURSING HOME.
THE GUNMAN SHOT HIM DEAD.
THAT BRAVE POLICE CHIEF WAS ONE
OF THE VICTIMS THIS MORNING.
AHEAD, THE EFFORT TO FIND OUT
WHAT HAPPENED AND WHY.
Hey, The Future,
what's her problem?
Apparently, I kept her up
all night.
She said The Future
freaks her out.
How come no one
likes me, Jim?
Intel does!
Just think of everything
Intel's doing right now
with Artificial Intelligence.
And pretty soon AI
is going to help executives
like her see trends to stay
ahead of her competition.
No more sleepless nights.
- We're going to be friends!
- I'm sorry about this.
Don't be embarrassed
of me, Jim.
I'm getting excited
about this!
We know the future.
We're going to be friends!
Because we're building it.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS NOW.
A GUNMAN SHOT AND KILLED A
POLICE CHIEF BEFORE BURSTING
INTO A NURSING HOME AND KILLING
TWO STAFFERS.
HAPPENED IN THE VILLAGE OF
KIRKERSVILLE 25 MILES EAST OF
COLUMBUS, THIS IS A LIVE LOOK
NOW AS AUTHORITIES HAVE JUST
BEGUN A NEWS CONFERENCE AT THE
SHERIFF'S OFFICE THERE.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE POLICE
CHIEF WAS RESPONDING TO A REPORT
OF A MAN WITH A GUN.
THE CHIEF RADIOED IN AS THE
STORY GOES, THAT HE HAD THE
SUSPECT IN HIS SIGHT.
THAT HE WAS THE LAST IN HIS
DEPARTMENT TO HEAR FROM HIM.
THE SUSPECT IS DEAD.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW HE DIED.
THE CHIEF WAS JUST THREE WEEKS
INTO THE JOB.
HE HAD SIX CHILDREN.
ANOTHER ONE ON THE WAY MATT FINN
IS MONITORING THIS NEWS
CONFERENCE.
>> SHEP, RIGHT NOW POLICE ARE
PROCESSING SEVERAL CRIME SCENES
ATTACHED TO THE SHOOTING THAT
ROCKED THE SMALL OHIO TOWN
TODAY.
ONE OF THE BIG QUESTIONS IS IF
THERE WAS A CONNECTION BETWEEN
THE SHOOTER AND THE EMPLOYEES
THAT HAVE BEEN FOUND DEAD.
THEY'RE ALSO INVESTIGATING A
MOTIVE.
POLICE SAY OTHER PEOPLE
BARRICADED THEMSELVES IN ROOMS
AND NO PATIENTS WERE HARMED.
THE ENTIRE COMMUNITY IS
GRIEVING.
THE SENSELESS LOST OF THESE
VICTIMS, A POLICE CHIEF, A
FATHER OF SIX WHO HAD BEEN ON
THE JOB A FEW WEEKS.
THE COUNTY SHERIFF DESCRIBES THE
BRAVERY OF THAT SHERIFF THAT RAN
TOWARDS THE GUN FIRE.
>> I'M SORRY TO RECORD TODAY
THAT LINCOLN COUNTY HAS LOST A
POLICE OFFICER, THE CHIEF OF
KIRKERSVILLE, STEPHEN PROSARIO.
HE ENGAGED THE SUBJECT.
THE DEPUTIES WERE IN ROUTE TO
BACK HIM UP.
WHEN DEPUTIES ARRIVED, THEY
DISCOVERED HIM IN THE STREET.
>> AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL JUST
BLOCKS AWAY FROM THE SHOOTING
WAS ON LOCK DOWN.
THE STUDENTS WERE BUSSED TO THE
MIDDLE SCHOOL WHERE PARENTS
PICKED THEM UP EARLY.
NO I.D. ON THE SHOOTER.
REPORT PORTMAN AND THE OHIO
GOVERNOR HAVE TWEETED OUT
CONDOLENC
CONDOLENCES.
>> Shepard: MATT FINN, THANK
YOU.
>> AND THE MASSIVE CYBER ATTACK
ACROSS THE WORLD TODAY HAS
AFFECTED 74 COUNTRIES.
OFFICIALS IN GREAT BRITAIN SAID
IT HIT THEIR PUBLIC HEALTH
SYSTEM, WHICH IT DID.
THEN THE PRIME MINISTER, THERESA
MAY, SAID THE ATTACK HAD A
BIGGER IMPACT THAN THAT.
IT REPORTEDLY INVOLVED A LEAKED
HACKING TOOL FROM THE NATIONAL
SECURITY AGENCY.
THIS IS STILL DEVELOPING.
74 COUNTRIES AFFECTED.
LOOKS LIKE 2,400 DIFFERENT
VICTIMS IN THIS THING.
WORD IS STILL COMING IN.
WE'LL HAVE MORE FOR YOU AS WE
GET IT.
THE U.S. MARINES LAUNCHING A NEW
TELEVISION ADD.
THEY SAID THEY'RE TRYING TO ADD
MORE WOMEN TO THE RANKS OF THE
FEW AND THE PROUD.
THAT'S NEXT.
What's the best way to get
two servings of veggies?
V8 or a powdered drink?
Ready, go.
Ahhhhhhhh!
Shake! Shake!
Shake! Shake! Shake!
Done!
You gotta shake it!
I shake it!
Glad I had a V8.
The original way
to fuel your day.
>> Shepard: THE U.S. MARINES HAS
THE LOWEST PERCENTAGE OF ALL
WOMEN IN THE MILITARY BRANCHES.
LESS THAN 10% OF RECRUITS ARE
WOMEN.
NOW THE CORPS IS LAUNCHING A NEW
NATIONAL TELEVISION AD TO TRY TO
CHANGE THAT.
TRACE GALLAGHER HAS THE NEWS.
THIS IS BASED ON A REAL PERSON,
THIS AD?
>> IT IS.
IT'S CALLED BATTLE UP AND REFERS
A REAL-LIFE MARINE.
THE AD BEGINS WITH A YOUNG GIRL
BREAKING UP A FIGHT IN THE
SCHOOL HALLWAYS AND FLASHES TO
HER PLAYING RUGBY AND ENDS WITH
HER PLAYING ON THE BATTLEFIELD.
HERE'S THE AD.
WATCH.
>> NO ONE KNOWS WHERE IT COMES
FROM.
BUT SOME HAVE IT AND SOME DON'T.
IT'S THE FIGHTING SPIRIT.
IT CONSUMES FEAR AND WEAKNESS.
>> AND DEMCO SAYS FILMING WAS
TOUGH BECAUSE SHE WAS SUBMERGED
HOLDING A RIFLE IN THE WATER AND
COATED WITH A LAYER OF ICE.
SHE'S NOW IN OKINAWA, JAPAN.
THERE'S 83,000 MARINES AND 8%
ARE WOMAN.
BUT THEY HOPE BY 2019, 10% WILL
BE WOMANS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: SEEMS LIKE THE
MARINES NOT LONG AGO THEY WERE
COMPLAINING ABOUT WOMEN IN THE
RANKS.
>> YEAH, IN 2015 THEY
COMPLAINED.
AND SECRETARY DEFENSE ASH CARTER
THAT DISMISSED THEIR CLAIMS AND
SINCE THEN, 74% OF WOMEN HAVE
MOVED TO MARINE COMBAT
POSITIONS.
THE MARINES HAD A SCANDAL WHEN A
FACEBOOK PAGE CALLED MARINES
UNITED WENT PUBLIC.
THEY USED THE PAGE TO CHAT,
SHARE AND EGG EACH OTHER ON
ABOUT POSTING NUDE PHOTOS AND
SOMETIMES CALLING THE WOMEN OUT
BY NAME OR WHERE THEY WERE
BASED.
AFTER THE NAVY INVESTIGATED,
THERE WERE NUMEROUS LEVELS OF
DISCIPLINE HANDED OUT INCLUDING
SEVERAL DEMOTIONS.
THE MARINES REWROTE THEIR SOCIAL
MEDIA POLICY.
SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, TRACE.
NASA ASTRONAUTS PERFORMING A
MILESTONE 200th SPACEWALK AT THE
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION
TODAY.
A WATER LEAK CUT IT SHORT.
NASA OFFICIALS SAY THE LEAK CAME
FROM A HOST ATTACHED TO JACK
FISHER'S SPACESUIT.
IT HAPPENED IN HIS FIRST
SPACEWALK.
NASA OFFICIALS SAY FISHER AND
PEGGY WHITSON WILL STILL ABLE TO
REPLACE A FAULTY ELECTRONICS
BOX.
WHITSON HOLDS THE REPORT FOR
MORE SPACE WALKS THAN ANY OTHER
WOMEN.
THIS WAS HER NINTH.
THE POPE WAS IN PORTUGAL WHERE
HE'S SET TO NAME TWO NEW SAINTS
TOMORROW.
IT WILL HAPPENED IN A SHRINE IN
FATIMA.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY EXPECT A
MILLION PEOPLE TO VISIT JUST
THIS WEEKEND.
ACCORDING TO THE CATHOLIC
CHURCH, THE POPE WILL CANNONIZE
TWO CHILDREN THAT SAID THE
VIRGIN MARY APPEARED TO THEM 100
YEARS AGO.
POPE FRANCIS ARRIVING IN AN AIR
BASE.
CROWDS OF PEOPLE GREETED HIM
THERE.
HERE'S THE POPE TOUCHING A
CHILD'S FOREHEAD AT THE BASE.
THE PRESIDENT OF PORTUGAL
GREETING THE PONTIFF.
THEY MET TOGETHER PRIVATELY AT
THE AIR BASE.
HERE'S A PHOTO OF THE POPE
PRAYING AT FATIMA.
THIS NUN WAVING A SOUTH AFRICAN
FLAG AS SHE WAITS FOR THE POPE.
AN AMERICAN PILOT BECAME THE
FIRST WOMAN TO FLY AROUND THE
WORLD'S BIGGEST OCEAN AND
HAPPENED IN THIS DAY IN HISTORY.
A naturally aspirated
5.0-liter V8 engine.
A 10-speed Direct-Shift
transmission.
A meticulously
crafted interior.
All of these are feats
of engineering.
Combining them with
near-perfect weight
distribution...
...is a feat of amazing.
Experience the first-ever
471-horsepower
Lexus LC 500
or the Multistage
Hybrid LC 500h.
Experience Amazing.
(announcer VO)
there's a moment of truth.etes,
And now with Victoza®
a better moment of proof.
Victoza® lowers my A1C
and blood sugar
better than
the leading branded pill,
which didn't get me to my goal.
Lowers my A1C better
than the leading
branded injectable.
The one I used to take.
And better than that
diabetes pill I used to take.
(Jeff)
Victoza® works with your body
to lower blood sugar
in three ways--
in the stomach, the liver,
and the pancreas.
And while it
isn't for weight loss,
Victoza® may help you
lose some weight.
Non-insulin Victoza® comes in
a pen and is taken once a day.
(announcer VO)
Victoza® is not recommended
as the first medication
to treat diabetes,
and is not for people
with type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not take Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine Neoplasia
syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you get a lump or swelling
in your neck
or if you develop any allergic
symptoms including itching,
rash, or difficulty breathing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
The most common side effects
are headache, nausea,
diarrhea, and vomiting.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may cause kidney problems.
Now's the time for
a better moment of proof.
Ask your doctor about Victoza®.
>> Shepard: YESTERDAY THE NEWSY
WARNING TO THOSE THAT TRAVELLED
TO AUSTRALIA THAT TOADS ARE
TRYING TO HITCHHIKE TO GET INTO
THE COUNTRY, NOW IT APPEARS
SCORPIONS HAVE TAKEN NIGHT.
FROM A FLIGHT FROM HOUSTON TO
ECUADOR DELAYED DEPARTURE AFTER
SOMEONE SPOTTED A SCORPION.
SAID THE SCORPION EMERGED TO
SHOCK AND HORROR FROM A
PASSENGER'S CLOTHING.
LAST MONTH, A SCORPION STUNG
THIS GUY OUT OF A FLIGHT FROM
HOUSTON.
THE PARAMEDICS SAID HE WAS OKAY.
THE FLIGHT GOT GOING HOURS LATER
ON NEW JET BECAUSE THE OLD ONE
NOW NEEDS TO BE DECONTAMINATED
WITH FLAME FLOWERS.
I DON'T KNOW.
ON THIS DAY IN 1963, AN AMERICAN
BECAME THE FIRST WOMAN TO FLY
SOLO ACROSS THE PACIFIC OCEAN.
BETTY MILLER MET PRESIDENT
KENNEDY AFTER MAKING THE TRIP.
SHE BROUGHT HER LUCKY TROLL DOLL
THAT FLEW WITH HER.
AT THE TIME SHE RAN A FLIGHT
SCHOOL IN SANTA MONICA.
SHE FLEW FROM CALIFORNIA TO
AUSTRALIA TO DELIVER A PLANE TO
A CUSTOMER.
SHE FINISHED THE TRIP IN TWO
WEEKS AS SHE AS HER TRUST Y CO
PILOT SOARED INTO THE HISTORY
BOOKS.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN BECAUSE BREAKING NEWS
CHANGES EVERYTHING ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
"YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL CAVUTO IS
NEXT.
SEE YOU LATER.
>> CONSIDERING CANCELLING THE
DAILY PRESS BRIEFINGS?
>> HE'S DISMAYED AS A LOT OF
PEOPLE THAT WE COME OUT HERE DO,
EVERYTHING WE CAN TO PROVIDE YOU
AND THE AMERICAN PEOPLE ON WHAT
HE'S DOING TO KEEP THE NATION
SAFE AND GROW JOBS AND JET WE
SEE TIME AND TIME AGAIN AN
ATTEMPT TO PARSE EVERY LITTLE
WORSE AND MAKE IT MORE OF A GAME
OF "GOT YA."
>> MAYBE THAT'S GOING BY WAY OF
THE DINOSAUR.
I'M NEIL CAVUTO.
YOU'RE WATCHING "YOUR WORLD."
WHAT IN THE WORLD IS THE FUTURE
OF A PRESS GRIEVING WE HAVE
TAKEN FOR GRANTED FOR MUCH OF
THE MODERN TV ERA?
IT COULD BE GOING OR CHANGING OR
AT LEAST GETTING MINIMIZED.