GETTING WORK DONE.
ERIC: IT'S A THREE-YEAR PROJECT
TO REFURBISH THE TOWER.
IT WILL COST ABOUT $42 MILLION
WILL TAKE HALF A YEAR JUST TO
PUT UP THE SCAFFOLDING.
THE CLOCK WILL BE STOPPED FOR
THREE MONTHS TO DO THE
MAINTENANCE.
ARTHEL: JULIA'S UP NEXT.
JULIE: PRESIDENT TRUMP
REPORTEDLY TRYING TO SMOOTH
THINGS OVER A MONTH THE
HIGH-LEVEL PEOPLE IN HIS OFFICE
IN THE TURMOIL.
AS THE PRESIDENT AND HIS
ADVISERS -- I'M JULIE BANDERAS
AND THIS IS "THE FOX REPORT".
AMERICAN TOMAHAWK MISSILES
NEARLY LEVELING A SYRIAN AIRBASE
HANGER.
>> DEMOLISHED AND RUNWAYS DAMAGE
THE SYRIAN FORCES ARE LASHING
OUT AT REBEL TARGETS.
WHAT IS THE NEXT STEP FOR THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS THE
GLOBAL REACTION POURS IN?
THE MAN WHO KILLED OSAMA BIN
LADEN SAYS DIPLOMACY MUST BE A
FACTOR.
>> THEIR PEOPLE AT THE PENTAGON
PLANNING THIS SINCE 2003.
THE PLAN WILL BE THERE BUT AGAIN
IT'S NOT GOING TO BE WAR COME IS
GOING TO BE DIPLOMACY.
JULIE: WE HAVE TO "FOX NEWS"
TEAM COVERAGE.
WE BEGIN WITH KRISTIN FISHER WHO
IS TRAVELING WITH THE PRESIDENT
THIS WEEKEND AT MAR-A-LAGO IN
FLORIDA AND KRISTIN IT'S BEEN
OVER 48 HOURS SINCE HE TOOK HIS
VERY FIRST BIG MILITARY ACTION
AS PRESIDENT.
ANY INDICATION OF HOW HE'S DOING
TONIGHT?
>> BY ALL ACCOUNTS PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S VERY PLEASED THAT HIS
DECISION TO STRIKE AND WITH HOW
IT'S PLAYING OUT.
HIS DECISION TO STRIKE HAS
RECEIVED WIDESPREAD PRAISE FROM
OUR ALLIES IN THE REGION.
THE SAUDI TEAM CALLED A
COURAGEOUS ACT AND SPRAYS BY
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS ON
CAPITOL HILL.
THE ONE AREA WHERE PRESIDENT
TRUMP HAS RECEIVED CRITICISM
THAT WAS HIS DECISION TO ACT
WITHOUT FIRST SEEKING
CONGRESSIONAL APPROVAL BUT EVEN
ON THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP DEFENDED
THAT DECISION TODAY IN A LETTER
TO CONGRESS.
HE WROTE THAT I ACTED IN THE
VITAL NATIONAL SECURITY AND
FOREIGN-POLICY INTERESTS OF THE
UNITED STATES PURSUANT TO MY
CONSTITUTIONAL AUTHORITY TO
CONDUCT FOREIGN RELATIONS AND AS
THE COMMANDER IN CHIEF AND CHIEF
EXECUTIVE.
THE U.S. WILL TAKE ADDITIONAL
ACTION AS NECESSARY AND
APPROPRIATE TO FURTHER ITS
IMPORTANT NATIONAL INTERESTS.
THE TWO BIG TAKEAWAYS THERE ARE
THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP REITERATING
WHAT THE AMBASSADOR TO THE U.N.
NIKKI HALEY SAID YESTERDAY, THAT
THE U.S. MAY BE WILLING TO TAKE
FURTHER ACTION IF NECESSARY IF
ASSAD DOES NOT STOP THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACKS AGAINST HIS OWN
PEOPLE AND THEN IT ALSO, THEY
SHOW PRESIDENT TRUMP BELIEVES HE
CAN TAKE THAT ACTION WITHOUT
RECEIVING CONGRESSIONAL APPROVAL
TO DO SO.
I AM SURE A LOT OF FOLKS ON
CAPITOL HILL WOULD DISAGREE WITH
THAT.
JULIE: WHAT ARE YOU HEARING
KRISTIN ABOUT ALL THESE REPORTS
OF A SHAKEUP WITH SENIOR WHITE
HOUSE STAFF?
ANY TRUTH TO THEM?
>> THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS NO TRUTH
THAT THIS HAS KIND HAVE BEEN
BREWING FOR SOME TIME.
THE MAIN SOURCE OF CONFLICT IS
BETWEEN SENIOR ADVISER JARED
KUSHNER AND STEVE BANNON.
AND THEN OF COURSE IS A
NONINTERVENTIONIST.
HE BELIEVES THE U.S. SHOULD NOT
INTERVENE IN PLACES LIKE SYRIA
AND THERE ARE REPORTS THAT HE
ARGUED AGAINST THE STRIKE.
LAST NIGHT AT THE PRESIDENTS
REQUEST THE TWO SAT DOWN AT
MAR-A-LAGO BUT THESE IDEOLOGICAL
DIVISIONS REMAIN.
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
FORMER CAMPAIGN MANAGER COREY
LEWANDOWSKI PUTS IT IN
PERSPECTIVE.
>> ANYONE WHO WANTS TO PRETEND
TO SPEAK ON BEHALF OF THE
PRESIDENT MAY FIND THEMSELVES
BACKTRACKING VERY QUICKLY WHAT
WE KNOW IS THE PRESIDENT IS THE
ONE WHO MAKES THE DECISIONS IN
THE WHITE HOUSE ABOUT WHO IS
GOING TO LEAD.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE DOWNPLAYING
ANY REPORTS OF A STAFF SHAKEUP
IS AN ATTEMPT TO DISTRACT FROM
THE GOOD WEEK THE PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S HAD.
JULIE: TO SERIOUS MISSILE LAUNCH
SIGNAL A SHIFT IN THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION?
>> I THINK THIS RIFT BETWEEN
BANNON AND KUSHNER IS INDICATIVE
OF THE CROSSROADS THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP IS AT.
IS PRESIDENT TRUMP GOING TO
CONTINUE ON WITH HIS AMERICA
FIRST THEME INSTEAD OF COUNTRIES
LIKE SYRIA OR IS HE BECOMING A
BIT MORE OF A HUMANITARIAN
INTERVENTION IS SOMETHING THAT
HE WARNED AGAINST ON THE
CAMPAIGN TRAIL.
ANOTHER QUESTION IS IS HE NOW
TURNING ON RUSSIA A COUNTRY THAT
STRONGLY SUPPORTED BASHAR
AL-ASSAD ESPECIALLY SINCE THERE
HAVE BEEN ALL THESE REPORTS BY
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND HIS HIS
ASSOCIATES THAT THEY'VE BEEN TOO
COZY WITH RUSSIA AND THERE ARE
SEVERAL INVESTIGATIONS INTO
WHETHER OR NOT SOME OF HIS
ASSOCIATES BROKE THE LAW.
ONE THING IS CLEAR THOUGH AND
THAT IS THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
WILLING TO BE VERY FLEXIBLE.
HE'S WILLING TO CHANGE HIS MIND
TO DEFAULT.
THE BIG QUESTION THOUGH IS
EVOLVE INTO WHAT?
EXACTLY WHAT KIND OF POLICIES HE
GOING TO HAVE GOING FORWARD AND
WILL IT ALIGN WITH THE JARED
KUSHNER BRANCH OF THE WEST WING
OR WHAT SIDE MORE WITH STEVE
BANNON?
JULIE: KRISTIN FISHER FOR
TONIGHT, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THE U.S. ATTACK APPARENTLY HAS
NOT SLOWED SYRIA DOWN MUCH.
THAT IS THE WORD.
JUST HOURS LATER SYRIAN
WARPLANES FROM OTHER BASES
APPARENTLY STRUCK OPPOSITION
TARGETS INCLUDING ONE NEAR THE
SITE OF A DEADLY CHEMICAL ATTACK
WHICH PROVOKED THE U.S. RESPONSE
OF THE VERY FIRST PLACE.
THIS CHAIRMAN OF THE SENATE
ARMED SERVICES COMMITTEE JOHN
McCAIN SEEN THE AMERICAN
STRIKE WAS A GOOD START BUT MORE
NEEDS TO BE DONE.
LISTEN.
>> I WOULD ARGUE FOR A NO-FLY
ZONE AND ARMING AND TRAINING THE
FREE SYRIAN ARMY.
AT THE SAME TIME WE MUST
CONTINUE TO TAKE MOSUL AND RAQQA
AND STOP THIS FLOW THAT IS
COMING OUT OF RAQQA AND BEING
SENT TO EUROPE AND TO THE UNITED
STATES TO PREVENT TERROR.
SO I THINK THE PRESIDENT MADE
THE RIGHT FIRST STEP AND I THINK
HE HAS THE SUPPORT OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
JULIE: PENTAGON PRODUCER LUKE IS
THOMAS AND IS LIVE WITH THE VERY
LATEST.
WHAT ELSE WOULD I GUESS WE LIKE
TO SEE AS FAR AS AIRSTRIKES INTO
SYRIA, WHAT MORE THEY TALKING
ABOUT?
>> JULIE TODAY AN OLD ARCH ENEMY
OF THE ASSAD REGIME TURKISH
FOREIGN MINISTER SAID THIS EARLY
TODAY IN TURKEY.
>> WE SEE THE U.S. INTERVENTION
AS APPROPRIATE.
THIS IS NOT ENOUGH EITHER.
DEFENSE INTERVENTION OF AN
AIRBASE THAT DOES NOT CONTINUE
IF WE DON'T REMOVE THE REGIME
FROM POWER AND THIS REMAINS A
COSMETIC INTERVENTION.
ANIMOSITY BETWEEN TURKEY AND
ASSAD REGIME GOES BACK DECADES.
1939 TURKEY ANNEXED LAND AT
NORTHWEST AREA WHICH TODAY IS
TURKEY'S SOUTHERNMOST PROVINCE.
SENIOR MILITARY OFFICIALS HELPED
A RUSSIAN DRONES SEEN OVER A
HOSPITAL WHERE VICTIMS OF
TUESDAY'S CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACK WERE TAKEN AND FIVE HOURS
LATER RUSSIAN AND SYRIAN JETS
BOMBED IT IN AN EFFORT TO KILL
MORE PEOPLE AND DESTROY THE
EVIDENCE OF THE CHEMICAL ATTACK
RADIOS OFFICIALS SAY RUSSIA HAS
CHEMICAL WEAPONS EXPERTS INSIDE
SYRIA INVESTIGATING THE ORIGINAL
ROLE -- A LITERAL PRE-TWO DAYS
AFTER THE TOMAHAWK CRUISE
MISSILE STRIKE IN SYRIA "FOX
NEWS" HAS LEARNED THE U.S.
MILITARY IS RAMPING UP EFFORTS
TO PROTECT THE NEARLY 1000
AMERICAN TROOPS ON THE GROUND IN
SYRIA OR U.S. OFFICIALS SAY THE
COALITION IS CUT BACK ON SOME OF
ITS AIRSTRIKES AGAINST ISIS
THERE BECAUSE U.S. AIR FORCE
F-22 STEALTH FIGHTER JETS FROM
THE AIRBASE IN TURKEY NOT FAR
FROM THE SYRIAN BORDER ARE
CONDUCTING IN CREASED AIR
PATROLS A CASE OF SYRIAN OR
RUSSIAN MILITARY TRIES TO ATTACK
AMERICAN FORCES ON THE GROUND.
FOR THIS MOMENT JULIE U.S.
OFFICIALS SAY THE ASSAD REGIME
HAS NOT BEEN MAKING ANY
THREATENING MOVES THE KEEP IN
MIND IN ADDITION TO THE HUNDREDS
OF SPECIAL OPERATIONS FORCES ON
THE GROUND YOU HAVE A U.S.
MARINE CORPS ARTILLERY BATTERY
OUTSIDE OF RAQQA SUPPORTING
U.S.-BACKED FORCES AS THEY TRY
TO RECAPTURE.
JULIE: AND THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
EXPECT MORE AMERICAN AIRSTRIKES
AGAINST ASSAD REGIME BECAUSE IT
SEEMS AS THOUGH THE WHITE HOUSE
HAS HINTED THAT THERE ARE MORE
TO COME AND OF COURSE THEIR
POLICY AT THIS POINT AT LEAST
WHY PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS MADE
CLEAR IS THAT HE DOESN'T PLAN ON
MAKING AN ANNOUNCEMENT.
OBVIOUSLY YOU'RE NOT GOING TO
HEAR WHAT THEIR PLAN IS UNTIL IT
HAPPENS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT IN OFFICIALS
I'VE SPOKEN TODAY SAID NOT TO
EXPECT ANY MORE AIRSTRIKES ON
THE ASSAD REGIME ANYTIME SOON.
AS WAS ALLUDED TO THIS WEEK
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS HANDED MORE
PLANTS TO STRIKE THE ASSAD
REGIME.
MADE THE DECISION IN FOUR HOURS
LATER THE TOMAHAWK CRUISE
MISSILES LEFT THE RAIL.
YESTERDAY THE U.S. AMBASSADOR
THE UNITED NATIONS NIKKI HALEY
SAID THE UNITED STATES COULD
STRIKE AGAIN IN THE FUTURE.
>> UNITED STATES TOOK A VERY
MEASURED STEP LAST NIGHT.
WE ARE PREPARED TO DO MORE BUT
WE HOPE THAT WILL NOT BE
NECESSARY.
>> JULIE ONE OF THOSE U.S.
WARSHIPS THAT FIRED THE TOMAHAWK
CRUISE MISSILES INTO SERIOUS
HEADING TO AN UNDISCLOSED
LOCATION IN THE MEDITERRANEAN TO
REARM.
I JUST RECEIVED NEWS A FEW
MINUTES AGO THE USS CARL VINSON
AIRCRAFT CARRIER WHICH HAD BEEN
PREVIOUSLY SCHEDULED IN A PORTED
AUSTRALIA HAS TURNED AROUND AND
WILL BE PROCEEDING OUT THE
KOREAN PENINSULA IN THE WAKE OF
RECENT NORTH KOREAN
PROVOCATIONS.
JULIE: VERY INTERESTING.
LUCAS TOMLINSON THANK YOU VERY
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S MOVE TO STRIKE
THE SYRIAN AIRBASE WINNING
PRAISE FROM OUR ALLIES AROUND
THE WORLD WHILE RUSSIA AND IRAN
ARE PREVENTING THE ATTACK --
CONDEMNING THE ATTACK.
PROTESTERS LINING THE STREETS OF
DAMASCUS CALLING THE ATTACK AND
AGGRESSION AGAINST THE ENTIRE
NATION BUT RUSSIA REMAINS THE
MOST CRITICAL.
KATIE LOGAN HAS MORE FROM OUR
LONDON BUREAU.
>> UK, THE STRONGEST OBJECTIONS
ARE COMING FROM RUSSIA.
THEY VOICED SUPPORT FOR THE U.S.
ACTION IN SYRIA IS THE SAUDIS
CALLING IT A COURAGEOUS DECISION
BUT REFLECTING A REGION OVER
SYRIA IRANIAN PRESIDENT A STRONG
ALLY OF ASSAD HAS BEEN CRITICAL
OF U.S. DECISION.
IT WAS THESE IMAGES OF THE
HORRIFIC CHEMICAL STRIKE IN
NORTHERN SYRIA WHICH SPARKED
GLOBAL OUTRAGE THAT LED TO THE
U.S. MILITARY RESPONSE.
U.S. OFFICIALS ARE LOOKING INTO
WHETHER RUSSIA MAY HAVE
SUPPORTED US.
GOVERNMENT IN CARRYING OUT THE
ATTACK BUT ALL EYES ARE NOW ON
THE RUSSIAN REACTION TO THE KEY
ROLE IN SYRIA WHILE STANDING BY
ASSAD AGGRESSION.
RUSSIA HAS BEEN THE MOST
CRITICAL OF THE U.S. MISSILE
STRIKE SAYING THEY WERE IN
VIOLATION OF INTERNATIONAL LAW.
IT ALSO SAYS IT'S A SETBACK FOR
RELATIONSHIPS WITH U.S. AND MAY
HAVE SERIOUS CONSEQUENCES FOR
THE REGION.
RUSSIA KEEPS UP A STRONG
MILITARY PRESENCE ACTIVELY
ASSISTING THE ASSAD REGIME IN
THE COMPANY.
YESTERDAY THIS RUSSIAN WARSHIP
PASSED THROUGH TURKISH WATERS
HEADING TOWARDS THE SYRIAN
COAST.
SECRETARY OF STATE REX TILLERSON
WILL NO DOUBT BE DISCUSSING
SYRIA WHEN HE DOES -- VISITS
RUSSIA NEXT WEEK.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT KEEPS
PRESSURE ON THE SYRIAN REGIME.
JULIE: SENATOR RAND PAUL AND A
CRITIC OF PRESIDENT TRUMP
EXPRESSING DOUBT OF U.S. STRIKE
ON SYRIA SAYING THE PRESIDENT
SHOULD OBEY THE CONSTITUTION AND
ASK OR CONGRESSIONAL APPROVAL
BEFORE USING MILITARY ACTION.
>> WAR HAS CAUSED THESE REFUGEES
TO FLEE SO WILL MORE WAR
ACCELERATE OR ACCENTUATE THE
CURRENT INVOLVEMENT?
WILL THERE BE LESS REFUGEES
UNLESS DEATH?
I WOULD SAY THERE WOULD BE MORE
DEATHS AND MORE REFUGEES.
I DON'T KNOW THAT OUR BOMBING
WILL LEAD TO PEACE.
JULIE: BUT SENATOR IF WE DON'T
GET INVOLVED WHAT DID THEY DO
JUST CHEMICALLY GASSED EVERY
BABY IN THE PLACE AND EVERY
WOMAN AND CHILD?
>> IS DOING IT ON HIS OWN.
>> THAT'S ABSOLUTELY DEPLORABLE.
ATROCITY IS NOT AN EXCUSE TO
DISOBEY THE CONSTITUTION.
JULIE: HEAR MORE FROM THE SENDER
TONIGHT AT 9:00 P.M. EASTERN
WITH JUSTICE WITH JUDGE JUDY
AIRING ON THE "FOX NEWS"
CHANNEL.
RIGHT NOW VICTIMS FROM A DEADLY
ATTACK IN SWEDEN ARE B
HONORED AFTER YESTERDAY'S DEADLY
TRUCK ATTACK IN SOUTH HOLMES OR
THE SUSPECT REMAINS IN CUSTODY.
INVESTIGATORS ARE SAYING ABOUT
HIS PATH IN THIS TERROR ATTACK.
A MANHUNT FOR A MAN POLICE ARE
CALLING A NATIONAL THREAT.
WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT THE SUSPECT
IS ACCUSED OF STEALING GUNS AND
SENDING A MANIFESTO TO THE
PRESIDENT AND SECRETLY RECORDING
IT, NEXT.
C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING
WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE MY BODY TO
DO WHAT IT'S SUPPOSED TO DO
RELEASE ITS OWN INSULIN.
TRULICITY RESPONDS WHEN
MY BLOOD SUGAR RISES.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS ITCHING, RASH,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING;
A LUMP OR SWELLING IN YOUR NECK;
OR SEVERE PAIN IN
YOUR STOMACH AREA.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCLUDE PANCREATITIS,
WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS WORSE.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING YOUR
A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR NUMBERS
WITH A NON-INSULIN OPTION,
CLICK TO ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
WITH A NON-INSULIN OPTION,
CLICK TO ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
I think we could finally get
youra bigger place.
Yeah, let me check
my score too.
Try Credit Karma. It's free.
Credit Karma.
Give yourself some credit.
Bounty is more absorbent,Mom"
per roll
so the roll can last 50% longer
than the leading ordinary brand.
So you get more "Life" per roll.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker Upper
that just tastes better.
Fresher.
More flavorful.
Delicious.
Only one egg
with better nutrition-
like more vitamins
D, E, and Omega 3s.
And 25% less saturated fat.
Only one egg good enough
for my family.
Because why have ordinary
when you can have the best.
Eggland's Best.
The only egg that
gives you so much more:
Better taste.
Better nutrition.
Better eggs.
♪
Everything your family
touches sticks with them.
Make sure the germs they
bring home don't stick around.
Use Clorox
disinfecting products.
Because no one kills germs
better than Clorox.
TO HACK ONE SUSPECT IN CUSTODY
AFTER A BOMB LIKE DEVICE WAS
DISCOVERED IN OSLO NORWAY.
THE DEVICE IS NOT HARMFUL
HOWEVER A LARGE AREA IS BEING
ROPED OFF WHILE THEY INVESTIGATE
NORWAY IS ON HIGH ALERT AFTER
NEIGHBORING SWEDEN SUFFERED A
TERROR ATTACK ON FRIDAY.
TONIGHT'S VICTIMS FROM THAT
DEADLY TERROR ATTACK IN
STOCKHOLM ARE BEING HONORED WITH
CANDLES AND FLOWERS LAID OUT
WHERE THIS SCENE TOOK PLACE, A
TRUCK CRASHING INTO DEPARTMENTS
ARE KILLING AT LEAST FOUR PEOPLE
AND INJURED MORE THAN A DOZEN
OTHERS.
POLICE NOW TO HAVE CUSTODY OF
THE SUSPECT WHO HAS BEEN ON THE
RADAR APPARENTLY IN THE PAST.
RIGHT NOW WE ARE LEARNING MORE
ABOUT HIS BACKGROUND.
BRYAN LLENAS IS HERE WITH MORE.
WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT THE SUSPECT
AND A POSSIBLE MOTIVE?
>> WE DON'T REALLY KNOW THE
MOTIVE IN TERMS OF HE HAS NOT
SPOKEN YET BUT POLICE SAY THEY
ARE CONFIDENT THE 39-YEAR-OLD
UZBEKISTAN MAN WITH THE DRIVER
BEHIND THE STOLEN BEER TRUCK
THAT PLOWED THROUGH CROWD IN
CENTRAL STOCKHOLM KILLING FOUR
AND WOUNDING 15 OTHERS ON
FRIDAY.
THIS IS CELL PHONE VIDEO OF THE
SUSPECT BEING ARRESTED 25 MILES
NORTH OF STOCKHOLM.
HE HAD BEEN ON INTELLIGENCE
RADAR SOMETIME AGO BUT WAS
DEEMED QUOTE A MARGINAL
CHARACTER.
HE IS NOW FACING TERROR MURDER
CHARGES.
WE DON'T KNOW THE SUSPECTS NAMES
OR WHETHER HE'S A LEGAL RESIDENT
OF SWEDEN.
POLICE CONDUCTED OVERNIGHT RAIDS
AROUND STOCKHOLM QUESTIONING
PEOPLE IN CONNECTION WITH THE
CASE AND THEY HAVE NOT RULED OUT
THERE WILL BE OTHER ARRESTS.
>> WE DO NOT KNOW WHETHER THERE
ARE FURTHER PERSONS INVOLVED.
WE ARE NOT EXCLUDING THAT.
WE ARE WORKING ON A
COMPREHENSIVE APPROACH TO SEE
WHETHER THERE IS ANY POSSIBILITY
THAT FURTHER INDIVIDUALS ARE
INVOLVED.
THE MAN IS ACCUSED OF STEALING A
BEER TRUCK EARLY ON THE DAY ON
FRIDAY RAMMING INTO CROWD BEFORE
CRASHING INTO A POPULAR
DEPARTMENT STORE.
POLICE FOUND A DEVICE THAT COULD
BE AN INCENDIARY DEVICE OR BOMB
IN SWEDISH PUBLIC BROADCAST SAYS
IT WAS A BAG OF EXPLOSIVES AND
THE ATTACKERS SUFFERED BURNS
FROM THESE EXPLOSIVES AFTER HE
FAILED TO DETONATE IT PROPERLY.
NO ONE HAS CLAIMED
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THIS ATTACK
THOUGH NEWS OF YESTERDAY'S
ATTACK SPREADS QUICKLY ON ICE
AND SLEET SOCIAL MEDIA COUNTS.
JULIE: WHAT HAS THE REACTION
BEEN TO THIS?
>> SHOP THEN STUNNED.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE TODAY
GATHERING OF MEMORIAL AT THE
CRASH SITE OUTSIDE A DEPARTMENT
STORE.
MOURNERS INCLUDING THE PRIME
MINISTER HIMSELF LAYING FLOWERS
AND OFFERING PRAYERS.
FLAGS ARE FLYING AT HALF-STAFF
TO COMMEMORATE THE VICTIMS.
MONDAY WAS DECLARED A NATIONAL
DAY OF MOURNING AND THE CROWN
PRINCES VISITED THIS SITE THE
PRIME MINISTER SAYING CITIZENS
WILL GET THROUGH THIS AND HE HAS
BEEN WALKING THE STREETS
SPEAKING TO PEOPLE IN STOCKHOLM.
HE SAYS ALL INDICATIONS ARE THAT
THIS IS INDEED OR WAS A
TERRORIST ATTACK JULIE.
JULIE: BRYAN LLENAS THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
THE FBI IS NOW REVIEWING THE
HANDLING OF THOUSANDS OF
TERRORISM RELATED -- FOLLOWING A
STRING OF RECENT TERRORIST
ATTACKS.
THE AGENCY IS TRYING TO ENSURE
TIPS OVER THE PAST THREE YEARS
WERE PROPERLY INVESTIGATED AND
NO OBVIOUS RED FLAGS OR MISS
WITH THE REVIEW FOLLOWS ATTACKS
BY PEOPLE WHO ARE ONCE ON THE
FED'S RADAR INCLUDING THEIR LAND
OF NIGHTCLUB SHOOTER OMAR MATEEN
AND THE MAN WHO OPENED FIRE FORT
LAUDERDALE AIRPORT IN JANUARY
ESTEBAN SANTIAGO.
SEEMS THE FBI IS FACING
CHALLENGES IN PREDICTING WHICH
OF THE THOUSANDS OF TIPS THEY
RECEIVE ANNUALLY MIGHT ONE DAY
MATERIALIZE INTO A VIABLE VIABLE
THREAT.
U.S. TO THE U.S. MATURE
CONFIRMING AN AMERICAN SOLDIER
HAS BEEN KILLED IN ACTION IN
AFGHANISTAN.
THE ATTACK APPARENTLY HAPPENING
IN THE EASTERN PART OF THE
COUNTRY DURING AN OPERATION
AGAINST AN ISIS AFFILIATED GROUP
SPECIAL OPS HAVE BEEN FIGHTING
THEIR FOR THE PAST TWO YEARS.
HEALTH OFFICIALS SAY THE TERROR
GROUP IS CONTAINED INSIDE TO
DISTRICT DEVICES REMAINS A BIG
THREAT.
THEY'RE CURRENTLY MORE AMERICAN
TROOPS IN AFGHANISTAN IN IRAQ
AND SYRIA COMBINED.
TWO ACTIVE-DUTY MARINES
RECEIVING THE FIRST PUNISHMENT
IN CONNECTION WITH NUDE
PHOTOGRAPHS THAT WERE SHARED ON
LINE.
THE DISCIPLINE THEY NOW WILL
FACE PLUS THIS MAN CONSIDERED
ARMED AND VERY DANGEROUS.
WHY POLICE ARE INTENSIFYING
THEIR SEARCH FOR A MAN THEY SAY
HAS BECOME HIGHLY AGITATED BY
NATIONAL POLITICS.
>> MY DAD ACTUALLY KNOWS HIM SO
IT'S EVEN MORE AWKWARD THAT
SOMEONE SO INNOCENT COULD DO
SOMETHING SO TERRIFYING
Hey, how's it going?
Um... who are you?
I'm Val. The Orange Money
retirement squirrel from Voya.
I represent the money you save
for the future. See?
We're putting away acorns to
show the importance of being
organized.
That's smart. Who's he?
He's the green money you can
spend now. What's up?
Oh you know, gonna pay some
bills, maybe buy a new tennis
racket.
Tennis racket for a squirrel?
He's got a killer backhand.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement, it's time to get
Voya.
Various: (Shouting) Heigh!
Ho!
( ♪ )
It's off to work we go!
Woman:
On the Gulf Coast,
new ExxonMobil projects
are expected to create
over 45,000 jobs.
And each job created
by the energy industry
supports two others
in the community.
Altogether,
the industry supports over
9 million jobs nationwide.
These are jobs that natural
gas is helping make happen,
all while reducing
America's emissions.
Energy lives here.
can make any occasion feel
more special.ie
all while reducing
America's emissions.
So she makes her pie crust
from scratch.
And sprinkles on brown sugar
streusel.
So that you can spend more time
making special moments with
your family.
Marie Callender's
It's time to savor
There'Try Phillips' Fiberway to
gGood Gummies..
They're delicious...
And a good source of fiber
to help support regularity.
Mmm. These are
good.
Nice work, Phillips'!
Try Phillips' Fiber
Good Gummies!
could save money
on car insurance.e
In fact, safe drivers
who switch from GEICO
to Esurance could save hundreds.
So if you switch to Esurance,
saving is a pretty safe bet.
Auto and home insurance
for the modern world.
Esurance. An Allstate
company. Click or call.
JULIE: THE U.S. NAVY DECIDED TO
GROUND ALL P45 TRAINING JETS
INDEFINITELY AFTER AN EXCLUSIVE
FOX REPORT THAT NAVY PILOTS
REFUSE TO FLY THE JETS BECAUSE
THEY SAID THE OXYGEN SYSTEM WAS
TAINTED AND THE AIR OF THE
PILOTS WERE BREATHING WAS --
THERE NEARLY 200 AND SERGEANT
WICKER OF THE HOUSE ARMY
COMMITTEE ADDRESSED THE ISSUE
TODAY.
LISTEN.
>> I'M ENCOURAGED THAT A SERIOUS
PROBLEM HAS BEEN ACKNOWLEDGED
AND THAT'S A DIFFERENT APPROACH
BE TAKEN TO ARRIVING AT A
SOLUTION.
THAT WOULD BE COMPLETELY TAKEN
APART.
THE KIND OF ANALYSIS THAT CAN BE
DONE THAT HAS NOT BEEN DONE
BEFORE.
I THINK WE ARE IN A POSITION
WHERE THERE IS EVERY HOPE THAT
WE WILL BE ABLE TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THE PROBLEM.
JULIE: THE NAVY PREVIOUSLY
ANNOUNCED A THREE-DAY PAUSE TO
THE TRAINING SCHEDULES WHICH WAS
BY THE WAY DUE TO EXPIRE MONDAY.
A MASSIVE MANHUNT UNDERWAY RIGHT
NOW FOR SUCH A CONSIDERED A
NATIONAL THREAT BY LAW
ENFORCEMENT POLICE ARE CURRENTLY
LOOKING FOR THIS MAN 32-YEAR-OLD
JOSEPH JAKUBOWSKI AFTER THEY SAY
HE STOLE FIREARMS FROM A GUN
SHOP AND THEN THREATEN TO USE
THEM AGAINST SEVERAL -- HE'S
ALSO THE USE OF SENDING AN ANGRY
MANIFESTO TO PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
OF COURSE VIDEOTAPING ALL THE
EVIDENCE.
WILL CARR JOINS ME LIVE FROM OUR
WESTERN BUREAU WITH MORE ON
THIS.
HOW DID THIS ALL START?
>> JULIA TOOK AUTHORITIES A
COUPLE OF DAYS TO PIECE A
TIMELINE TOGETHER.
EVERYTHING STARTED TUESDAY WHEN
JOSEPH JAKUBOWSKI WAS IN THE
POST OFFICE IN JANESVILLE
WISCONSIN AND CELL PHONE VIDEO
SHOWS HIM ADDRESSING A MANIFESTO
TO PRESIDENT TRUMP TO TAKE A
LISTEN TO THE MOMENTS JUST
BEFORE HE PUTS THE MANIFESTO
INTO THE MAIL.
>> REVOLUTION.
TIME FOR CHANGE.
APRIL 4, 2017 AT 5:43.
YOU SEE MY NAME.
STAMPED, GAME TIME.
>> JAKUBOWSKI'S ALLEGEDLY STOLE
GUNS FROM A LOCAL GUN SHOP
INCLUDING A RIFLE.
HE HAD A BULLETPROOF VEST AND A
MILITARY STYLE HAMMOCK.
POLICE BELIEVE THAT JAKUBOWSKI
TORCHED HIS CAR AND DISAPPEARED
IN THURSDAY'S SO-CALLED
ASSOCIATE TOLD LOCAL AUTHORITIES
THAT JAKUBOWSKI MADE A VAGUE
THREAT ABOUT A SCHOOL BECAUSE A
NUMBER OF WISCONSIN SCHOOLS TO
CLOSE ON FRIDAY AND AT LEAST ONE
CHURCH DECIDED NOT TO HOLD
SERVICES THIS WEEKEND.
THE SAME ASSOCIATE TOLD
AUTHORITIES ABOUT THE 161 PAGE
MANIFESTO.
THE ROCK COUNTY SHERIFF TELLS ME
PART OF THE CALLED MEMBERS OF
LAW ENFORCEMENT QUOTE AGENTS OF
THE 1% WHO ENSLAVE AND KEEP THE
POPULATION DOWN.
WITH ALL OF THAT IN MY JULIE THE
FBI IS OFFERING A 10,000-DOLLAR
REWARD.
JULIE: WHAT DO WE KNOW ABOUT
THIS GUY?
IT'S AMAZING TO ME THEY HAVE NOT
FOUND HIM.
WE KNOW HIS NAME AND WE HAVE
SEEN HIS FACE AND NOBODY HAS
COME FORWARD.
>> WE KNOW THAT HE IS WELL-KNOWN
TO LAW ENFORCEMENT.
HE HAS MORE THAN 30 TRAFFIC
CITATIONS.
HE ALSO HAS RESISTING OR ARREST
IN TRYING TO DISARM A POLICE
OFFICER.
NOW HE'S CONSIDERED ARMED AND
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS AND THE
LOCAL SHERIFF TOLD ME IF ANYBODY
IN THE AREA HAPPENS TO SEE HIM
THEY ARE ASKED TO SIMPLY CALL
911 TO KEEP THEIR DISTANCE.
JULIE: DID HE AT ANY POINT A
MENTION OF WANTING TO OFF
POLITICIANS FOR THE GOOD OF THE
PEOPLE OR THE GOOD OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE?
VSO VENGEANCE APPARENTLY OUT FOR
POLITICIANS.
>> THE SHERIFF TELLS ME THAT HE
MADE THREATS AGAINST LAW
ENFORCEMENT AND THE MANIFESTO.
THEY'RE NOT RELEASING THE
SPECIFIC TYPES OF THREATS OR THE
SPECIFIC DETAILS BUT 161 PAGES
IN THAT MANIFESTO IN MANY OF THE
SENTIMENTS ARE ANTI-GOVERNMENT
ANTI-LAW ENFORCEMENT IN HIS
WRITINGS.
JULIE: WILL CARR FROM LOS
ANGELES THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
THAT'S DISTURBING.
CONGRESS IS OFF FOR A LITTLE
BREAK BUT AN AGENDA IS WAITING
IN WASHINGTON INCLUDING HEALTH
CARE REFORM AND THE POTENTIAL
THREAT FOR A GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN
HOW LIKELY IS THAT ANYWAY?
WE'LL TALK ABOUT IT PLUS
DEMONSTRATORS LINED THE SIDEWALK
OUTSIDE OF THE SENATE MAJORITY
LEADER'S HOME STATE OFFICE
ROWLING FOR HEALTH CARE, NOT
REPEAL BUT EXPANSION.
>> OF ALL THE FORMS OF
INEQUALITY AND INJUSTICE INgot..
HEALTH CARE IS THE MOTION
DOCKING AND INHUMAN.
Indeed.
It's good to be IN, Good Hands.
six of you for when
thyou stretch out.t
I want you to stay this
bright blue forever,
that's why you'll
stay in this drawer forever.
I can't live without you,
and that's why I'll
never ever wash you.
Protect your clothes
from stretching,
fading and fuzz with
Downy Fabric Conditioner.
It smooths and
strengthens fibers
to protect clothes
from the damage of the wash.
So your favorite clothes
stay your favorite clothes.
Downy Fabric Conditioner.
or how high the pollen count,
Flonase Allergy Relief
keeps your eyes and nose clear.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause nasal congestion
and itchy, watery eyes.
For relief beyond the nose.
Flonase.
At Red Lobster's Lobsterfestime.
any of these 9 lobster dishes
could be yours.
So don't resist delicious new
Lobster Mix and Match
or Lobsterfest Surf and Turf
because you won't have this
chance for long.
Or keeping a hotel's guests
cuttinconnected.i to 35,000
fans...
Businesses count on
communication,
and communication counts on
CenturyLink.
♪
TAKE ON THE MAINSTREAM.
INTRODUCING NISSAN'S
NEW MIDNIGHT EDITION.
♪
It's my decision
Ito make beauty last.
RoC® Retinol,
started visibly reducing
my fine lines and wrinkles
in one week.
And the longer I use it,
the better it works.
Retinol Correxion® from RoC.
METHODS, NOT MIRACLES.™
TUNE I'M JULIE BANDERAS.
IT'S TIME FOR THE TOP OF THE
NEWS.
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION'S
DECISION TO LAUNCH AIRSTRIKES IN
SYRIA GETTING PRAISE AND
CRITICISM ARE MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS SOME THINKING THE
MATTER NEEDS TO BE DEBATED ONCE
THEY RETURN FROM EASTER RECESS
IN TWO WEEKS THROUGH PUBLIC
ENCOURAGEMENT TOM McCLINTOCK
WEIGHING IN AT A TOWN HALL IN
CALIFORNIA TODAY SAYING WHILE
SUCH AN ATTACK MAY BE NECESSARY
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS NEED TO MAKE
THE DECISION, NOT THE PRESIDENT
ALONE.
>> WHAT A CHAR AL-ASSAD DID IS A
WAR CRIME.
IT IS AN ATROCITY.
IT IS A CRIME AGAINST HUMANITY
BUT THE FOUNDERS WERE VERY CLEAR
THAT IF THIS COUNTRY NEEDS TO
COMMIT TO WORK NEEDS TO BE UNDER
THE SAY-SO OF THE CONGRESS
REPRESENTING ALL THE PEOPLE AND
NOT THE DECISION OF ONE
INDIVIDUAL.
JULIE: AND IN KENTUCKY HEALTH
CARE WAS ON THE MINDS OF MANY
PROTESTERS OUTSIDE THE SENATE
MAJORITY LEADER'S OFFICE.
SENATOR MITCH McCONNELL
GATHERED IN LOUISVILLE FOR A
SIDEWALK TOWN MEETING IN FAVOR
OF A SINGLE-PAYER HEALTH CARE
PLAN.
IT'S BEEN A BUSY WEEK YOU CAN
SAY THAT FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
HIS ADMINISTRATION HOSTING THE
MINISTER OF CHINA A SUCCESSFUL
VOTE ON HIS SUPREME COURT
NOMINEE AND OF COURSE THE
MISSILE STRIKE AGAINST SYRIA BUT
IN THE SHADOW OF ALL OF THAT THE
ONGOING INVESTIGATION OF
RUSSIA'S INFLUENCE IN THE U.S.
ELECTION AND THE PRESIDENT'S
UNPROVEN CLAIMS THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION TAPPED HIS PHONE.
NOW HE APPEARS TO HAVE LOST A
BIG ALLY ON THE HILL.
>> JULIE U.S. RELATIONS WITH
RUSSIA CONTINUED TO WORSEN THE
SECRETARY OF STATE REX TILLERSON
IS PREPARING TO TRAVEL TO MOSCOW
NEXT WEEK AND CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATORS ARE EXAMINING
RUSSIA'S ROLE IN THE
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
NOW THOSE CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATIONS HAVE BECOME
CONTROVERSIAL DEVIN NUNES IS
RECUSING HIMSELF AGAINST THE
COMMITTEE'S INVESTIGATION INTO
RUSSIAN INTERFERENCE IN THE
PRESIDENT'S ELECTION BECAUSE AN
INVESTIGATION INTO WHETHER HE
MADE UNAUTHORIZED DISCLOSURES OF
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
NUNES CALLED THAT INVESTIGATION
POLITICALLY MOTIVATED.
>> IR TO GIVE A STATEMENT ON
THAT.
I EXPECT THIS TO GET DONE VERY
QUICKLY.
>> AND YOUR STATEMENT THAT YOU
DID NOTHING WRONG.
>> ABSOLUTELY RIGHT.
CONGRESSMAN MIKE CONAWAY SENIOR
MEMBER OF THE COMMITTEE WILL NOW
LEAD THE INVESTIGATION.
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATORS ALSO
EXAMINING PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
UNSUBSTANTIATED CLAIM THAT
PRESIDENT OBAMA WIRETAPPED HIM
AN OUT CALLS ON SUSAN RICE TO
TESTIFY.
THAT ISSUE HER A REQUEST TO NAME
TRUMP ASSOCIATES CAUGHT AND
SURVEILLANCE.
THAT SURVEILLANCE IS ROUTINE AND
WHEN AMERICANS ARE CAUGHT
SPEAKING WITH FOREIGN NATIONALS
THE NAMES ARE MASTER PROTECTED
IN A SPREAD RICE CLAIMS SHE
ASKED FOR THE NAMES TO BETTER
UNDERSTAND THE MAIN INTELLIGENCE
AND MAINTAIN SHE NEVER REBUILT
THOSE NAMES PUBLICLY.
JULIE: RICH EDSON WILL THANK
YOU.
CONGRESS HAS ADJOURNED FOR TWO
WEEKS FOR THE EASTER HOLIDAY
THAT LAWMAKERS WILL HAVE PLENTY
OF WORK WAITING FOR THEM WHEN
THEY RETURN INCLUDING THE BATTLE
OVER OBAMACARE.
HOUSE SPEAKER PAUL RYAN
INSISTING THEY ARE CLOSE TO
REACHING AN AGREEMENT, VERY
CLOSE HE SAID BETWEEN
CONSERVATIVE AND MODERATE WINGS
OF THE PARTY IN REPEALING THE
AFFORDABLE CARE ACT HOWEVER HE
SPOKE AT THE REPUBLICAN CORPSMEN
WHO SAID NOT NECESSARILY THAT
CLOSE TO IT WHICH IS GOOD AND
WHAT IS THE LATEST?
PETER DOOCY JOINS US FROM D.C..
HOW ARE LAWMAKERS EXPLAINING THE
DELAY IN REPEALING OBAMACARE?
>> JULIE WE WATCHED HOW ONE
REPUBLICAN DID IT IN A TOWN HALL
IN CALIFORNIA WHERE CONGRESSMAN
TOM McCLINTOCK TRIED TO TELL
US SOMETIMES ROWDY CROWD THAT IT
IS TAKING A WHILE FOR HIS PARTY
TO UNITE AROUND A REPLACEMENT.
>> WE HAVE GOT TO GET THIS RIGHT
AND IT'S NOT GOING TO BE FOR --
PERFECT PLAN.
OUR SYSTEM WAS NEVER DESIGNED TO
BE PERFECT.
IF OUR SYSTEM WAS DESIGNED TO
MAKE THE BEST LAW ACCESSIBLE TO
MOST PEOPLE.
>> THERE IS ONE MODERATE
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN CASTING
DOUBT ON SPEAKER RYAN'S
REASSURANCES THAT THE REPEAL AND
REPLACE EFFORT IS STILL ON TRACK
NOW THAT SOME OF THE FREEDOM
CAUCUS BACKS AN AMENDMENT THAT
LEADERSHIP SAYS THEY CAN LIVE
WITH.
>> I DON'T BELIEVE THAT WE ARE
AS CLOSE AS MANY WOULD SAY ON
THE HEALTH CARE BILL RIGHT NOW.
THERE WAS AN AMENDMENT OFFERED
WHICH ON BALANCE WAS GOOD
$15 BILLION OVER EIGHT YEARS FOR
HIGH-RISK POOLS BUT IN MY VIEW
THERE OTHER STRUCTURAL CLAUSES
OF THE LEGISLATION.
TODAY'S HE WARNED HIS LEADERS
AGAINST RUSHING TO REPEAL.
JULIE: HOW LIKELY IS A
GOVERNMENT SHUTDOWN AT THE END
OF THE MONTH?
>> JULIE DEMOCRATS ARE SAYING AT
THE WHITE HOUSE STOPS ASKING
THEM TO FUND THE BORDER WALL AND
CUT OUT MONEY TO DOMESTIC
PROGRAMS THEY'RE WILLING TO PLAY
BALL.
A SPOKESMAN FOR THE SENATE
MINORITY LEADER CHUCK SCHUMER
SAID SAID THIS QUOTE THE ONLY
THING THAT COULD DERAIL THAT
PROCESS IS THE WHITE HOUSE
INSISTING ON THEIR EXTRANEOUS
DEMANDS WHICH WOULD MEAN
BIPARTISAN OPPOSITION.
IT DOES NOT SOUND LIKE LAWMAKERS
FEEL THE NEED TO CUT RECESSION
OR WERE TO WORK ON THE BUDGET OR
TO AUTHORIZE THE USE OF FORCE IN
SYRIA EVEN THOUGH THEY SAY THEY
WANT TO BE INVOLVED.
>> WE CAN'T ACT ON AUTHORIZATION
UNLESS THE PRESIDENT ASKED FOR
AUTHORIZATION SO THERE'S NOTHING
FOR US TO STAY HERE TO ACT ON.
THERE'S NO INDICATION THAT
PRESIDENTS COMING FORWARD WITH A
REQUEST TO CONGRESS.
IN A LETTER TO LAWMAKERS
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID HE WILL
KEEP THEM UPDATED ABOUT ANY
FUTURE ACTIVITY GETS ASSAD THAT
DID NOT ASK FOR AUTHORIZATION.
JULIE: PETER DOOCY THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
THE HIGHEST COURT IN ONE STATE
IS WEIGHING A VERY SENSITIVE
QUESTION.
SHOULD THE STATE BE ABLE TO STEP
IN AND DETAIN IMMIGRANTS FOR
I.C.E.?
PLUS A MASSIVE MUDSLIDE LEAVES
HOMEOWNERS SCRAMBLING.
A CLOSER LOOK AT THE DAMAGE,
NEXT.
>> I HAVE SEEN ENOUGH OF THIS
RAIN.
WE ALL WANTED RAIN AT THE
BEGINNING OF THE WINTER BUT.
You do all this research
on a perfect car,
then smash it into a tree.
Your insurance company
raises your rates...
Maybe you should've done
more research on them.
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't raise
your rates
due to your first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
♪
Whoa that's amazing...
Hey, I'm the Internet!
I know a bunch of people
who would love that.
The Internet loves
what you're doing...
...so build a better website
in under an hour with...
...GoCentral from GoDaddy.
Type in your idea.  Select from
designs tailored just for you
And publish your site with just
a few clicks-even from your...
...mobile  phone.
The Internet is waiting
Start for free today at GoDaddy.
DearThere's no other
way to say this.
It's over.
I've found a permanent
escape from monotony.
Together, we are
perfectly balanced,
our senses awake,
our hearts racing as one.
I know this is sudden,
but they say: If you
love something...
set it free.
See you around, Giulia
♪
THIS IS PETE'S YARD.
AND IT'S BEEN
WITHERED BY WINTER.
BUT ALL PETE NEEDS IS
SCOTTS TURF BUILDER LAWN FOOD.
IT'S THE FAST AND EASY WAY TO
A THICK, GREEN, RESILIENT LAWN,
WITH TWO SIMPLE FEEDINGS.
ONE NOW, AND ONE
LATER THIS SPRING.
IT TAKES GRASS FROM HUNGRY -
TO HEALTHY.
PETE MAY NOT BE AN EXPERT,
BUT LOOK AT THAT GRASS.
THIS IS A SCOTTS YARD.
FOR A QUICK AND EASY
LAWN CARE PLAN,
DOWNLOAD THE MY LAWN APP.
JULIE: THE MASSACHUSETTS SUPREME
COURT CONSIDERING WHETHER STATE
OR LOCAL AUTHORITIES CAN HELP
DETAIN IMMIGRANTS WANTED BY
I.C.E. OFFICIALS BASED SOLELY ON
THEIR REQUEST PRECLUDE THIS
DECISION HAVE FAR-REACHING
EFFECTS LIKE "FOX NEWS"
CORRESPONDENT MOLLY LINE HAS
MORE FROM WASHINGTON.
>> THE SUPREME JUDICIAL COURT OF
MASSACHUSETTS IS TRYING TO
DETERMINE WHETHER LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICERS AND COURT
IN THE STATE CAN LEGALLY HOLD
SOMEONE BASED SOLELY ON AN
IMMIGRATION BECAME A REQUEST
FROM U.S. IMMIGRATION AND
CUSTOMS ENFORCEMENT.
CRITICS CHARGE THE CONTAINER
REQUESTS OR ORDERS TO KEEP
SOMEONE IN JAIL UNTIL THE FEDS
CAN GET THEM ARE
UNCONSTITUTIONAL.
>> MASSACHUSETTS LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICERS SIMPLY CANNOT MAKE AN
ARREST WITHOUT A WARRANT JUST
BECAUSE SOMEONE ASKED THEM TO
EVEN IF THE PERSON THAT ASKS
THEM IS THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
>> LAWYERS FOR THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT DISAGREED ARGUING IN
THE AMERICAN SYSTEM OF DUAL
SOVEREIGNTY THE UNITED STATES
ABILITY TO ENFORCE IMMIGRATION
LAWS DEPEND ON THE CORPORATION
OF STATES.
CHECK OFFICIALS CHOOSE TO
COOPERATE BASED ON THEIR REQUEST
THEY HAVE THAT AUTHORITY
SPECIFICALLY TAKING THAT
AUTHORITY AWAY FROM THEM FROM
OUR PERSPECTIVE.
>> A MAN NAMED -- CAME TO
AMERICA AS A REFUGEE BY
FOLLOWING A STRING OF CRIMINAL
CONVICTIONS WAS SLATED FOR
DEPORTATION IN 2008.
CAMBODIA DECLINED TO TAKE HIM
AND HE WAS RELEASED.
IN OCTOBER OF 2016 HE WAS
ARRESTED AGAIN FACING UNARMED
ROBBERY CHARGES BY THE
COMMONWEALTH FAILED TO PROSECUTE
IN THE COURT DISMISSED CHARGES.
LAWYERS ASKED HIM TO BE RELEASED
BUT AFTER SEVERAL HOURS IN A
COURTHOUSE HOLDING CELL I.C.E.
AGENTS ARRIVED AND TOOK HIM INTO
CUSTODY.
>> HE WAS FACED WITH PROLONGED
UNLAWFUL CONSTITUTIONAL ARRESTS
AND HE WANTED TO CHALLENGE THAT.
SMITH THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
CALLING SO-CALLED SANCTUARY
CITIES THAT ALLOW IMMIGRATION
AUTHORITIES COULD MEAN A LOSS OF
GRANT FUNDING BUT IT'S NOT
ALWAYS ABOUT COMPLIANCE.
SOME CITIES ARGUE YOU DON'T HAVE
THE RESOURCES TO HOLD ALL OF THE
PEOPLE THAT I.C.E. WANTS.
IN BOSTON MOLLY LINE "FOX NEWS."
JULIE: THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY LOOKING TO
RAMP UP SECURITY IN THE SOUTHERN
BORDER.
NOW THE AGENCY IS TURNING TO
SOME OF THE BRIGHTEST TECH MINDS
IN THE COUNTRY FOR HELP.
SILICON VALLEY.
CLAUDIA COWAN HAS MORE.
SOME OF THE GOVERNOR HAS BEEN
USING DRONES FOR YEARS.
THAT THE AIR FORCE SAID THERE'S
MORE DEMAND FOR DRONE OPERATORS
THAN ANY OTHER PILOT.
NEW INITIATIVES HELPS TO  --
HOPES TO SPEED UP THE
PROCUREMENT PROCESS SAVING TIME
MONEY AND LIVES.
AND THAT WE ARE LOOKING FOR THE
LATEST AND GREATEST TECHNOLOGIES
THAT WE CAN GET FOR OPERATORS
HAVE A HUGE MISSION OF SECURING
U.S. BORDERS AND THEY CAN DO IT
MORE EFFECTIVELY AND KEEP THEM
SAFE.
>> THAT MEANS EYES IN THE SKIES
AS U.S. CUSTOMS AND BORDER
PROTECTION IS PAYING STARTUPS TO
FIT HIS PURPOSE.
IMAGINE WORKING ALONE OR IN
SMALL GROUPS IN A REMOTE AREA.
THEY WANT TO KNOW IF THEY WILL
ENCOUNTER GROUP AND HOW MANY
PEOPLE ARE THERE AND IF THEY
HAVE WEAPONS OF THE KNOW-HOW TO
RESPOND TO GET THERE.
>> SEATTLE RATER MANUFACTURE
ECO-DYING TOWARD ONE OF THE
FIRST CONTRACTS FOR SENSORS THAT
CAN BE MOUNTED ON A SMALL DRONE
THAT MEASURE THE DISTANCE
BETWEEN OBJECTS EVEN IF THEY ARE
MOVING EVEN IN BAD WEATHER.
THE ABILITY TO HAVE A SMALL
HIGH-PERFORMANCE RADAR IS WHAT
IS UNIQUE ABOUT WHAT WE ARE
DOING.
LOCAL LAW ENFORCEMENT MEMBERS
WHO USE DRONES TO FIGHT CRIME
SEE A COST BENEFIT.
>> WE GET REAL-TIME INFORMATION
WHICH IS THE CRITICAL PART AT A
LOW COST POINT IN RELATION TO
ASSESS THAT CAN COST US UPWARDS
OF $1800 AN HOUR.
THE SMALLER DRONES WE FIRE
COSTING US NEARLY NOTHING OTHER
THAN MAN-HOURS.
>> IT AT A RECENT DRONE EXPO IN
SAN JOSE INDUSTRY LEADERS
PRAISED THE PARTNERSHIP.
>> WE KNOW THE CAPABILITY IS
THERE.
WE KNOW THE COST SAVINGS IS
THERE AN ULTIMATELY AND MOST
IMPORTANTLY WINNOW THE ABILITY
TO PROTECT PROPERTY AND SAVE
LIVES IS THERE.
THE DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND
SECURITY HAS OPENED AN OFFICE IN
SILICON VALLEY A SIGNAL THAT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT WILL CONTINUE
TO PARTNER WITH STARTUPS TO GET
THESE TECHNOLOGIES INTO THE
FIELD FAST BEFORE THEY ARE
OBSOLETE.
SAN FRANCISCO CLAUDIA COWAN "FOX
NEWS".
JULIE: ANOTHER DAY OF CHAOS FOR
DELTA AIRLINES.
THE COMPANY CANCELING NEARLY 300
MORE FLIGHTS THREE DAYS AFTER
SEVERE THUNDERSTORMS BLEW
THROUGH THE EASTERN U.S. AND
CREATIVE DISRUPTIONS IN ATLANTA.
THE NUMBER TWO U.S. AIRLINE HAS
ALREADY CANCELED AROUND 3000
FLIGHTS SINCE WEDNESDAY AND SAYS
IT'S POSSIBLY BEEN MORE FLIGHTS
WILL BE CALLED OFF.
WHILE IN NORTHERN CALIFORNIA
SEVERAL FAMILIES NOW HOMELESS
AFTER MUDSLIDES TRIGGERED I
HEAVY RAINS.
POWERFUL STORMS YESTERDAY ALSO
LEADING TO POWER OUTAGES TO MORE
THAN 100,000 HOMES.
>> WE HEARD A STRANGE NOISE.
IT WAS LIKE A PILE OF BRICKS
TUMBLING DOWN THE HILL.
>> HE CAME IN THE BACK BEDROOM
AND DOWN THROUGH THE HALLWAY
THROUGH THE PATIO.
>> HE CAME DOWN INTO ARGUABLY
FAST.
JULIE: MEANTIME CALIFORNIA
GOVERNOR JERRY BROWN ISSUING AN
EXECUTIVE ORDER TO LIFT A
DROUGHT EMERGENCY FOR THE STATE
BUT SINCE THE MEASURE DOESN'T
REMOVE MOST OF THE RESTRICTIONS
EXPERTS SAYING ONE RAINY WINTER
WON'T CHANGE THE LONG-TERM
OUTLOOK.
THE MARINE CORPS DEMOTING TO
MARINES IN CONNECTION WITH A
NUDE PHOTO SCANDAL.
THEY ARE ACCUSED OF POSTING
NEGATIVE COMMENTS ABOUT A PHOTO
OF A WOMAN ON A SOCIAL MEDIA
SITE TO CURRENT AND FORMER
FEMALE MARINES ARE NOW COMING
FORWARD TO SAY PHOTOGRAPHS OF
THEM ARE POSTED ON LINE WITHOUT
THEIR CONSENT.
TWO DOZEN OTHER MILITARY MEMBERS
ARE ALSO UNDER INVESTIGATION.
THE DEADLINE TO FILE YOUR TAXES
IS LESS THAN TWO WEEKS AWAY.
OFFICIALS HAVE A WARNING.
THEY WARNED THE LATER YOU FILE,
THE HIGHER THE RISK OF BECOMING
A VICTIM OF IDENTITY THEFT, TAX
FRAUD.
HOW THE GOVERNMENT IS TRYING TO
PREVENT THIS PLUS OHIO STATE
UNIVERSITY WILL BE HONORING ONE
OF THEIR STUDENTS WHO PASSED
JUST MONTHS BEFORE GRADUATION IN
A SPECIAL WAY.
different.
It works with the
water in your body
to hydrate
and soften.
Unblocking your
system naturally.
MiraLAX.
that just tastes better.
Fresher.
More flavorful.
Delicious.
With more great nutrition.
And 25% less saturated fat.
Only Eggland's Best.
Better taste.
Better nutrition.
Better eggs.
[Student] I can just quit school
and get a job.
[Ex student] Daddy's
here.
[Wife] Hi
[Dad] Hey buddy
[Son] hey dad
[Wife] I think we can do this.
[Chancellor] Adam Baily.
JULIE: OKAY SO IF YOU HAVEN'T
YET FILED YOUR TAXES YOU ARE NOT
ALONE BUT THE LONGER YOU WAIT
AND HUGE DIDN'T KNOW THIS BUT
YOU SHOULD KNOW THE MORE PRONE
YOU ACTUALLY ARE BECOMING A
VICTIM OF TAX FRAUD.
NOW THE GOVERNMENT HAS NEW RULES
THAT COULD PROVIDE MORE
PROTECTION TO CONSUMERS BUT "FOX
BUSINESS" NETWORKS LAUREN
SIMONETTI HAS THE STORY.
>> WEST ARE MORE $4 BILLION WERE
LOST TO TAX FRAUD IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THE IRS CONFIRMS MORE THAN
THREE-QUARTERS OF A MILLION
FRAUDULENT RETURNS AND MORE THAN
230,000 PEOPLE FILED FORMAL
AFFIDAVIT SAYING THEY WERE
VICTIMS.
IN ORDER TO LOWER THESE NUMBERS
STATES ARE TAKING ACTIONS.
STATE ISSUED I.D.s ARE
REQUIRED ON NEW YORK ALABAMA AND
OHIO TO ADD SECURITY.
>> IT'S VERY POSSIBLE THAT
SOMEONE MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN A HOLD
OF YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY NUMBER
AND EVEN YOUR NAME, YOUR ADDRESS
AND OTHER PERSONAL INFORMATION
DATA THAT THEY MIGHT NOT HAVE
YOUR DRIVER'S LICENSE.
>> MOST E. FILING OFF FOR
OPTIONS STATING HE DID NOT NEED
AN I.D. BUT SOME TAXPAYERS THAT
YOU DON'T WANT TO PROVIDE THAT
INFORMATION.
>> IT'S A BIG CONCERN FOR
TAXPAYERS BECAUSE IF YOU WERE TO
WALK INTO MY OFFICE AND YOU HAVE
NEVER SEEN ME BEFORE AS A NEW
CLIENT AND THE FIRST THING I ASK
YOU FOR IS YOUR SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBER, YOUR DATE OF EARTH AND
NOW LET ME TAKE A PICTURE OF
YOUR DRIVER'S LICENSE OR GATHER
THE DATA FROM IT, THAT'S HUGE.
>> AT THE FEDERAL LEVEL THE IRS
IS ROLLING OUT PROGRAM AS WELL.
>> THERE IS A 16 CHARACTER CODE
ASSOCIATED WITH THAT.
IT CHANGES EVERY YEAR AND WHEN
YOU BE FILE YOUR TAXES YOU HAVE
TO PUT IN THAT CODE SO CRIMINALS
DON'T HAVE THAT CODE THEY ARE
NOT GOING TO GET ANYWHERE.
>> HE SAYS THERE'S NO WAY TO
COMPLETELY STOP CRIMINALS BUT IF
YOU FILE EARLY DON'T USE PUBLIC
WI-FI TO ACCESS INFORMATION AND
DON'T GIVE YOUR INFORMATION OUT
OVER THE PHONE OR E-MAIL YOU ARE
TAKING THE RIGHT PRECAUTIONS.
>> SHRED YOUR DOCUMENTS THAT YOU
NO LONGER NEED SECURELY
THROUGHOUT THE DOCUMENT AND
EIGHT -- TEXAS WAS IN THE EARLY
YOU FILE THE LESS LIKELY YOU ARE
TO BECOME A TAX FRAUD VICTIM AND
SOMEONE RECEIVING YOUR REFUND TO
THE TAX DEADLINE THIS YEAR'S
APRIL 18.
LAUREN SIMONETTI "FOX NEWS".
JULIE: U.S. COAST GUARD
SEARCHING FOR GEORGIA MAN WHO
FELL OFF THE DECK OF A CRUISE
SHIP YESTERDAY.
32 RICO SCOTT WAS ON A CARNIVAL
CRUISE SHIP WITH HIS NEW WIFE ON
THEIR HONEYMOON JUST OUTSIDE THE
BAHAMAS.
THEY WERE APPARENTLY RENEWING
THEIR VOWS WHEN HE DISAPPEARED
INTO THE OCEAN ABOUT 10 MILES
WEST OF THE ISLANDS.
THE SHIP PARTICIPATING IN THE
SEARCH BUT HAS NOW RESUMED.
WE ARE TOLD IT'S POSSIBLE HE
JUMPED THE SHIP.
ALL OHIO STATE UNIVERSITY
HONORING A FORMER STUDENT WITH A
POSTHUMOUS DEGREE.
21-YEAR-OLD REAGAN TOKES WAS
KILLED JUST THREE MONTHS BEFORE
HER GRADUATION.
TOQUES WILL BE HONORED WITH A
BACHELOR'S DEGREE FROM THE
COLLEGE OF ARTS AND SCIENCES.
29 EUROS BRIAN GOLSBY IS CHARGED
CHARGED WITH AGGRAVATED MURDER
RAPE AND KIDNAPPING IN HER DEATH
AND COULD FACE THE DEATH PENALTY
IF CONVICTED.
SOMETIMES YOU JUST NEED YOUR
CHOCOLATE FIX LIKE THIS GUY AT A
STORE.
WATCH THEM FREAK OUT WHEN A
CREDIT CARD COMPANY WOULD LET
HIM GET HIS M&MS.
OH GOSH.
Ho!
( ♪ )
It's off to work we go!
Woman:
On the Gulf Coast,
new ExxonMobil projects
are expected to create
over 45,000 jobs.
And each job created
by the energy industry
supports two others
in the community.
Altogether,
the industry supports over
9 million jobs nationwide.
These are jobs that natural
gas is helping make happen,
all while reducing
America's emissions.
Energy lives here.
all while reducing
America's emissions.
WHY PAUSE A
SPONTANEOUS MOMENT?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
..
per roll
More "Doing Chores For Dad"
More "Earning Something
You Love" per roll
Bounty is more absorbent,
so the roll can last 50% longer
than the leading ordinary brand.
So you get more "Life" per roll.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker Upper
gives you a reason to slow down
and pull up a seat to the table.
That's why she takes the time to
season her turkey to perfection,
and make stuffing from scratch.
So that you can spend time
on what really matters.
Marie Callender's.
It's time to savor.
Our 18 year old wase Army
in an accident.'98.
When I call USAA
it was that voice asking me,
"Is your daughter ok?"
That's where I felt relief.
We're the Rivera family,
and we will be with USAA
for life.
JULIE: ARE THOSE THE PRODUCERS
SINGING IN MY EAR?
M & M'S MELT IN YOUR MOUTH.
BUT ONE MAN HAD A TOTAL MELTDOWN
WHEN HIGGS CREDIT CARD WAS
DECLINED WHEN HE TRIED TO BUY
M & Ms.
HE END WENT AFTER THE POOR
BANANAS.
THIS IS A 7-ELEVEN IN
LOS ANGELES.
HE CAUSED HUNDREDS OF DOLLARS IN
DAMAGE.
THE ATTACK HAPPENED IN FEBRUARY
AND POLICE ARE RELEASE THE
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO HOPING
SOMEONE WILL CATCH HIM.
TALK ABOUT BUYER'S REGRESSION.
LUCKILY THE STORE CLERK WAS FINE
AND DIDN'T GET HIT IN THE HEAD
WITH A FLYING BANANA.
TOM BRADY'S SUPER BOWL JERSEY IS
FINALLY IN IT RIGHTFUL PLACE.
IT WAS STOLEN AFTER THE TEAM'S
2015 SUPER BOWL WIN.
IT WAS RECOVERED IN MEXICO.
[♪]
"WATTERS WORLD" IS ON.
>> TONIGHT I ORDERED A TARGETED
MILITARY STRIKE ON THE AIRFIELD
IN SYRIA.
JESSE: PRESIDENT TRUMP FINALLY
ENFORCING PRESIDENT OBAMA'S RED
LINE.
BUT IS IT ENOUGH?
AND WHAT DOES THE MEAN FOR
RUSSIA?
MARK STEYN AND NEWT GINGRICH
HERE TO DISCUSS.
>> WE SEE NO EVIDENCE THAT SHE
HAS DONE ANYTHING IMPROPER.
JESSE: THE MEDIA CIRCLING THE
WAGONS AROUND SUSAN RICE.
ARE OUR OWN INTELLIGENCE
AGENCIES HELPING THEM?