[SOBBING]
>> Shepard: THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH THE DAY
AFTER THE STORM IN THE
MIDDLE OF NEIGHBORHOOD
KINGS MANOR AND TELEPHONE
ROAD PICKING UP THE PIECES
SEARCHING FOR SURVIVORS.
TEAM FOX COVERAGE BEGINS
NOW.
>> Shepard: LIVE NOW
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, A SUBURB
OF OKLAHOMA CITY AND
COMMUNITY IN AMERICA'S
HEARTLAND THAT IS RIGHT NOW
DEALING WITH A DISASTER ON
UNMANAGEABLE SCALE.
TONIGHT SEARCH CREWS AND
SEARCH LOOKING FOR SOMEONE
BURIED ALIVE ONE DAY AFTER
THE TORNADO SCRAPED THE
LANDSCAPE RAW.
THREE HOURS AGO THE
NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE
CONFIRMED WHAT MANY OF US
SUSPECTED THE TORNADO THAT
HIT THIS CITY AND THIS AREA
WAS AN EF-56789 THE TOP
LEVEL POSSIBLE.
THAT MEANS IT CARRIED WINDS
IN EXCESS OF 200 MILES PER
HOUR.
AND YOU CAN SEE WHAT THOSE
WINDS DID.
BLOCK AFTER BLOCK AFTER
BLOCK.
HOMES HERE GONE, SHREDDED,
CRUSHED WALLS AND
FURNITURE.
PHOTOGRAPHS.
ALL THE ORDINARY EFFECTS OF
EVERY DAY LIFE TURN TO
PIECES AND SCATTERED IN THE
WIND AFTER A COLUMN OF
DESTRUCTION DROPPED FROM
THE SKY AND CHEWED A
17-MILE PATH ACROSS THIS
CITY AND REGION.
THE FIRE CHIEF HERE SAYS HE
IS 98% SURE THAT TEAMS FROM
ALREADY FOUND ALL THE
SURVIVORS AND VICTIMS.
HE SAID THEY ARE GOING TO
HIT THE STREETS SEARCH THE
ENTIRE COMMUNITY AT LEAST
TWICE MORE, JUST TO BE
SURE.
AND OKLAHOMA'S GOVERNOR
SAYING TODAY SHE STILL
DOESN'T KNOW HOW MANY
PEOPLE ARE LISTED AS
MISSING.
>> WE KNOW THAT THERE ARE
PEOPLE AND BODIES THAT HAVE
BEEN TAKEN TO THE MEDICAL
EXAMINER'S OFFICE, BUT WE
HAVE ALSO HEARD THAT THERE
MAY BE BODIES THAT HAVE
BEEN TAKEN TO LOCAL FUNERAL
HOMES.
AND SO, WE ARE WORKING REAL
HARD RIGHT NOW TO TRY TO
GET A MORE ACCURATE COUNT
OF THE LOSS OF LIFE AND WE
HOPE TO HAVE BETTER NUMBERS
ON THAT.
>> Shepard: RIGHT NOW THE
MEDICAL EXAMINER SAYS AT
LEAST 24 PEOPLE ARE
CONFIRMED DEAD.
NINE OF THOSE CHILDREN.
HOSPITAL WORKERS ALSO SAY
THEY HAVE TREATED MORE THAN
200 PEOPLE SO FAR.
MORE THAN 70 THEM KIDS.
RIGHT NOW I AM STANDING
NEAR WHAT USED TO BE A
BOWLING ALLEY RIGHT BEHIND
ME.
ABOUT A HALF MILE EAST OF
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
BEFORE AND AFTER IMAGES
SHOW DESTRUCTION AT THAT
SCHOOL WHERE SEVEN CHILDREN
DIED.
AND WHERE RESCUERS FOUND
OTHERS STILL ALIVE.
WE HAVE AN IMAGE OF ONE
CHILD WHO PHOTOGRAPHER SAYS
WAS CALLING OUT FOR HIS
FATHER AS MEN PULLED HIM
FROM THE SHATTERED CONCRETE
OF THAT SCHOOL.
AND WE HAVE ALSO HEARD FROM
A GRANDFATHER WHOSE
DAUGHTER AND CHILDREN AS
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY.
SHE WENT TO GET THEM BEFORE
THE TORNADO HIT.
MAYBE SAVE THEIR LIVES.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT I
WOULD HAVE DONE IF I HAD
LOST MY GRAND KIDS.
SO I'M PROUD OF HER FOR
BEING SMART.
SHE DID THE RIGHT THING.
>> Shepard: OTHERS WHO
SURVIVED THIS TORNADO ARE
DESCRIBING WHAT IT WAS LIKE
WHEN IT HIT.
WHEN THE WIND STARTED
BLASTING IN THEIR
DIRECTION.
[SIREN]
>> A LOT OF RUMBLING.
THE THING THAT GOT ME IS
WHEN THINGS STARTED HITTING
THE HOUSE HARD ENOUGH TO
SHAKE THE HOUSE.
>> WE WENT UNDER A BRIDGE
AND TOOK COVER UNDER THE
BRIDGE.
WE HEARD THE STORM.
IT WENT RIGHT OVER US AND
FELT THE DEBRIS.
HE GOT HIT WITH SOME ROCKS
AND STUFF.
BUT, IT WAS SCARIEST THING
THAT I HAVE EVER WENT
THROUGH.
>> IT LOOKED LIKE A WAR
ZONE.
IT JUST LOOKED LIKE BOMBS
HAD BEEN IGNITED
EVERYWHERE.
IT WAS -- THERE IS A CAR
PART IN MY BEDROOM YOU
KNOW.
EVERYTHING IS GONE, YOU
JUST IN A MATTER OF 30
MINUTES YOUR WHOLE LIFE IS
TORN UPSIDE DOWN.
>> Shepard: A LOT OF PEOPLE
IN THAT SAME SITUATION.
SOME AS FOX REPORTS TONIGHT
WITH NOTHING LEFT.
SHEAR IS A PHOTO OF ONE
FAMILY'S HOME BEFORE THE
TORNADO AND THEN AFTER IT.
THAT'S MARY BARNHILL
SITTING NEXT TO HER
DAUGHTER-IN-LAW BRENDA.
THEY ARE IN FRONT OF
BRENDA'S HOUSE OR WHAT
REMAINS OF IT.
TODAY, AMERICANS ACROSS
THIS COUNTRY ARE TRYING TO
HELP PEOPLE LIKE BRENDA AND
HER NEIGHBORS.
TEXAS SENDING AN ELITE
SEARCH AND RESCUE TEAM
ABOUT 70 FIRST RESPONDERS
WHO SPECIALIZE IN GETTING
PEOPLE OUT FROM UNDER
WRECKAGE.
FROM THE UNIVERSITY OF NEW
MEXICO A 26 MEMBER TEAM
INCLUDING DOCTORS AND
NURSES AND FROM JOPLIN,
MISSOURI POLICE AND
FIREFIGHTERS HEADED TO THE
SCENE.
PAY BACK AS THEY PUT IT FOR
THE HELP THAT COMMUNITY
RECEIVED AFTER ITS OWN
DEVASTATING TORNADO IN
2011.
IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO HELP
THOSE WHO HAVE LOST SO MUCH
IN OKLAHOMA, THE RED CROSS
IS ACCEPTING DONATIONS.
CAN YOU VISIT RED CROSS.ORG
OR CALL 1-800-RED CROSS.
THIS MORNING PRESIDENT
OBAMA SPOKE FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
HE TOLD ALL THOSE AFFECTED
THAT THEIR COUNTRY WILL BE
THERE TO HELP TODAY AND
FOR AS LONG AS IT TAKES.
>> THERE ARE HOMES AND
SCHOOLS TO REBUILD
BUSINESSES AND HOSPITALS TO
REOPEN THERE ARE PARENTS TO
CONSOLE.
FIRST RESPONDERS TO COMFORT
AND OF COURSE FRIGHTENED
CHILDREN WHO WILL NEED OUR
CONTINUED LOVE AND
ATTENTION.
THERE ARE EMPTY SPACES
WHERE THERE USED TO IT BE
LIVING ROOMS AND BEDROOMS
AND CLASSROOMS.
>> Shepard: A LOT OF
EMPTINESS HERE IN MOORE
OKLAHOMA.
AND A LOT OF WORK YET TO BE
DONE, OF COURSE.
BUT THIS COMMUNITY HAS
FACED SITUATIONS LIKE THIS
IN THE PAST.
AFTER THE TORNADO THAT
DEVASTATED THIS AREA AN MAY
THE 3RD 1999.
SO TONIGHT, EVEN AS PEOPLE
OF MOORE TAKE STOCK OF ALL
THEY HAVE LOST, AS FAMILIES
MOURN THEIR DEAD AND
COMFORT THE LIVING, WE KNOW
THAT THEY WILL RECOVER.
AND THEY WILL REBUILD.
"THE FOX REPORT'S"
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
IS HERE WITH US IN MOORE
THIS EVENING.
SOME INSPIRATION OUT THERE
AMID ALL THE LOSS.
>> AMAZING STORIES OF LOSS,
SHEP.
AMAZING STORIES OF
SURVIVAL.
AND STORIES OF PARENTS
HAVING TO MAKE UNIMAGINABLE
CHOICES.
TODAY, WE CAME ACROSS TRACY
STEPHAN IN HER BACKYARD,
WHAT USED TO BE HER
BACKYARD SIFTING THROUGH
THE WRECKAGE OF HER HOME.
YESTERDAY, SHE WAS AT HOME
WHEN SHE HEARD THE TORNADO
WARNINGS.
SHE LEFT HER2 YOUNGEST
CHILDREN THERE WITH A
FRIEND AND RUSHED TO THE
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL TO TRY TO FIND HER
ELDEST DAUGHTER.
SHE WAS NOT ALLOWED INTO
THAT SCHOOL.
THE DOORS WERE ALREADY
LOCKED.
SHE THEN HAD TO CHOOSE
WHETHER TO STAY THERE
CLOSE TO HER ELDEST
DAUGHTER OR RUSH HOME TO
HER TWO YOUNGEST CHILDREN.
LISTEN.
HONESTLY I FELT LIKE I HAD
TO PICK AND CHOOSE STAYING
AT THE SCHOOL WITH ONE
CHILD OR COMING BACK HOME
TO MY TWO OTHER CHILDREN.
IT'S A TOUGH DECISION I
DON'T WANT TO GO THROUGH
AGAIN.
>> TRACY CHOSE TO COME HOME
TO HER TWO YOUNGEST
CHILDREN.
SHE HID WITH THEM IN THE
CELLAR.
THEN, WHEN THE TORNADO HAD
PASSED SHE RUSHED BACK TO
THE SCHOOL, DESPERATELY
TRYING TO FIND HER ELDEST
DAUGHTER.
LISTEN AGAIN.
>> WERE SAVED HER LIFE.
SHE HOVERED OVER HER DURING
THE WHOLE TIME, SUCH
SELFLESS ACT.
SHE ENDED UP NEEDING TO
SEEK MEDICAL ATTENTION
BECAUSE SHE HAD CUTS AND
SCRAPSZ AND WAS BLEEDING.
SAVED MY DAUGHTER'S LIFE.
>> YOU CAN EXPLAIN THAT
MOMENT WHEN YOU FIRST SAW
YOUR DAUGHTER; THE HAPPIEST
DAY OF MY LIFE.
IT WAS AMAZING.
BEING ABLE TO SEE HER AND
SHE IS OKAY.
AND SHE WAS EXCITED THAT
THERE WAS NO MORE SCHOOL.
>> TRACY'S DAUGHTER EXCITED
THAT THERE WAS NO MORE
SCHOOL AND TRACY'S
DAUGHTER SAVED BY THE
ACTION SHEP, OF THAT
HEROIC TEACHER'S AIDE WHO
JUST COVERED HER UP AND
SAVED HER FROM ALMOST
CERTAIN DEATH.
>> AMAZING STORIES COMING
FROM SO MANY PLACES.
JONATHAN THANKS VERY MUCH.
FOR A WHILE, MOST OF THE
IMAGES WE GOT WERE FROM
ABOVE.
THIS AFTERNOON THE WEATHER
WAS SO BAD HERE IN MOORE
OKLAHOMA.
THEY WERE NOT TORNADO
WARNINGS BUT SEVERE
WARNINGS.
WARNINGS OF LARGE SIZE
HAIL.
THANKFULLY THAT DIDN'T
HAPPEN.
THE RAINS CAME AND ALL THE
CHOPPERS CAME OUT OF AIR.
OUR FRIENDS AT WTOV AND
KOTV HAVE PUT THEIR CHOPPER
BACK UP IN THE AIR AND
WE'RE ABLE TO GET LIVE
PICTURES NOW.
WE ARE SHOWING YOU THE
DESTRUCTION AROUND THIS
AREA AS WE SPEAK.
OF COURSE, THERE ARE LOTS
OF WAYS TO HELP THE PEOPLE
HERE IN OKLAHOMA AND ACROSS
THE REGION.
WE HAVE A COUPLE PERFORM
OPTIONS.
CAN YOU DONATED TO THE RED
CROSS IF YOU LIKE OR THE
SALVATION ARMY, OF COURSE,
ONLINE OR BY PHONE.
WE HAVE MOORE INFORMATION
AT OUR WEB SITE.
IT'S VERY EASY.
JUST GO TO FOXNEWS.COM/SHEM
AND IT'S ALL THERE FOR YOU.
AFTER YESTERDAY'S TORNADO,
A PHOTOGRAPHER TOOK A
PICTURE NEAR THE PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
AND TODAY IT APPEARS ON THE
COVERS OF NEWSPAPERS FROM
CALIFORNIA TO FLORIDA AND
BEYOND.
A WOMAN CARRYING A CHILD
THROUGH A FIELD.
WE DON'T KNOW THEIR NAMES
OR WHAT'S BECOME OF THEM,
FRANKLY, BUT WE'LL HAVE
MORE ON THE SCENE AT PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY COMING UP
INSIDE FOX REPORT.
WE'LL ALSO HEAR FROM SOME
OF THOSE WHO HAVE BEEN
TAKING PART IN THE MASSIVE
SEARCH AND RESCUE
OPERATION.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE ARE JUST
VERY SAD.
I MEAN, AS CAN YOU IMAGINE
HAVING TO PULL ANYBODY
WHETHER IT BE CHILDREN OR
ADULTS IS JUST GOING TO BE
OVERWHELMING FOR A PERSON.
SO YOU KNOW, AT THIS
POINT, WHEN IT WENT FROM A
CERTAIN AND RESCUE TO
SEARCH AND RECOVERY.
THE MOOD OVER THERE HAS
DEFINITELY CHANGED.
>> THAT AND CONTINUING
COVERAGE OF THE DISASTER IN
THE HEARTLAND.
COMING UP FROM THE
JOURNALISTS OF FOX NEWS ON
THIS TUESDAY FOX REPORT,
LIVE FROM MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
OKLAHOMA STRONG.
WE LEARNED A LOT OF US  HAVE KNOWN
SOMEONE  WHO'S LIVED WELL INTO THEIR
90S.  AND THAT'S A GREAT THING.  BUT
EVEN THOUGH  WE'RE LIVING LONGER,
ONE THING  THAT HASN'T CHANGED MUCH
IS THE OFFICIAL RETIREMENT AGE.  ♪
♪  THE QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU MAKE
SURE YOU HAVE THE MONEY YOU NEED
TO ENJOY ALL OF THESE YEARS.  ♪ ♪
What makes the Sleep
Number store different?  You walk
into a  conventional mattress
store, it's really not  about you.
They say, "Well, if you  wanted a
firm bed you can
lie on one of those.
We provide the exact  individualization
that
your body needs.
Oh, yeah!
Wow.
Once you experience it  there's no
going back.
At the Sleep Number  Memorial Day
Sale,
save on the closeout of  our Classic
Special
Edition bed set.
Now just $1299-a savings  of $600.
Only at the Sleep Number  store.
Sleep Number.
Comfort Individualized.
I'M SO GLAD YOU CALLED.  THANK YOU.
WE'RE NOT IN LONDON,  ARE WE?  NO.
WHY?  APPARENTLY  MY DEBIT CARD IS.
WHAT?  I KNOW.  DON'T WORRY,  WE HAVE
CANCELLED YOUR OLD CARD.  GREAT. THANK
YOU.  IN ADDITION TO US  MONITORING
YOUR ACCOUNTS  FOR UNUSUAL ACTIVITY,
YOU COULD ALSO SET UP  FREE ACCOUNT
ALERTS.  OKAY.    [ Female Announcer
]    AT WELLS FARGO WE'RE WORKING
AROUND THE CLOCK    TO HELP PROTECT
YOUR MONEY    AND FINANCIAL    INFORMATION.
HERE'S YOUR  TEMPORARY CARD.  WELCOME
BACK.  HOW WAS LONDON?    [ Female
Announcer ]    WHEN PEOPLE TALK,
GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.
>> Shepard: THE PICTURES
YOU SEE ON THE OTHER SIDE
OF THE SCREEN FROM KOTV --
LET'S SEE FROM KWTV AND
KOTV OUR NEWS AFFILIATES
WHO HAVE THEIR DHOPPERS UP
LIVE TONIGHT.
WE WILL BE SHOWING YOU THE
DEVASTATION AND CLEANUP AS
THE NEWSCAST CONTINUES.
TONIGHT WE ARE HEARING FROM
RELATIVES OF CHILDREN WHO
SURVIVED THE TORNADO'S
DIRECT HIT ON THAT SCHOOL
PLAZA ELEMENTARY AS I
REPORTED AT THE TOP OF THIS
NEWSCAST OFFICIALS TELL US
AT LEAST SEVEN CHILDREN
DIED IN THAT SCHOOL.
BUT RESCUE WORKERS DID
MANAGE TO PULL SOME OF THE
KIDS OUT OF THE RUBBLE
FORMING A HUMAN CHAIN TO
PASS THEM TO SAFETY.
TODAY ON "STUDIO B" I SPOKE
WITH A MAN WHOSE 6-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER MADE IT OUT OF
THAT SCHOOL ALIVE.
>> SHE WAS A LITTLE FREAKED
OUT O.
SHE SAID THAT THE SCHOOL
FELL DOWN.
AND SHE GOT A COUPLE
SCRAPES AND SCRATCHES.
NOTHING TOO SERIOUS.
DOESN'T QUITE UNDERSTAND
WHY IT HAPPENED TO US.
BUT SHE IS HAPPY THAT WE
ARE ALL FINE AND HER DOG IS
FINE.
SO SHE IS ACTUALLY QUITE
HAPPY ABOUT IT THAT WE ARE
ALL OKAY.
>> Shepard: THEY ARE ALL
OKAY.
THIS IS WHAT IS LEFT OF
THEIR HOUSE.
JUSTIN TOLD ME HE WAS AT
WORK WHEN THE TORNADO HIT.
HIS WIFE AND TWO CHILDREN
RODE OUT OTHE STORM IN A
NEIGHBOR'S BASEMENT.
HE ALSO TOLD ME HE IS NOT
WEARING A JACKET TODAY
BECAUSE HE COULDN'T FIND
HIS CLOSET.
HE HAS SINCE GONE TO
SHELTERS AND GOTTEN A NEW
ONE BUT JOHN ROBERTS IS AT
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
TONIGHT OR WAS EARLIER
TODAY AND IS HE LIVE HERE
IN MOORE TONIGHT.
JOHN WHAT'S THE LATEST ON
THAT SCHOOL.
DO WE KNOW?
>> THERE IS A SMALL PIECE
OF GOOD NEWS, SHEP.
IF THERE IS ANY GOOD NEWS
IN THIS DISASTER.
IS THE FACT THAT FOR ABOUT
17 OR 18 HOURS IT WAS
BELIEVED AS MANY AS TWO
DOZEN CHILDREN HAVE BEEN
TRAPPED IN PARISH IN
ADDITION TO THE SEVEN YOU
MENTIONED ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
IT APPEARS NOW THAT WAS
SIMPLY THE FOG OF CONFUSION
FOLLOWING THE INITIAL
STRIKE OF THE TORNADO.
RESCUE WORKERS WENT THROUGH
A ELEMENTARY SCHOOL A
NUMBER OF TIMES TODAY AND
DID NOT FIND ANY MORE
VICTIMS.
THE DEATH TOLL HOLDING
STEADY NOW AT 24.
IT STILL COULD RISE BUT AT
LEAST WE BELIEVE NOW 24
ADDITIONAL CHILDREN DID NOT
DIE.
WE'RE ALSO LEARNING A
LITTLE MORE ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED INSIDE THAT SCHOOL
IN BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY
FROM AN A.P. STORY THAT
CAME OUT JUST A LITTLE
WHILE AGO.
AS THE STORM WARNINGS WENT
OUT, THOSE TORNADO WARNINGS
ALL THE CHILDREN WERE TAKEN
OUT OF THEIR CLASSROOMS AT
PLAZA TOWER SENT TO THE
CALF FEAR I CAN'T TO WAIT
FOR THEIR PARENTS TO PICK
THEM UP.
BUT WHEN THE TORNADO SIRENS
WENT OFF SCHOOL OFFICIALS
SCRAMBLED TO GET THEM ALL
INTO THE HALLWAY AN AREA
THEY THOUGHT WOULD BE A
SAFE PLACE.
BUT ONE TEACHER AT PLAZA
TOWERS SAID THIS HALLWAY IS
NOT SAFE.
SHE GRABBED A BUNCH OF KIDS
AND TOOK THEM INTO THE
BATHROOM.
WHEN THE T. HIT THE
CHILDREN SURVIVED.
SIMILAR TORE THE CHILDREN
TOOK THEM INTO THE HALLWAY
IT'S NOT SAFE.
TOOK THEM A FEW OF THEM AND
WENT INTO THE CLOSET.
THAT'S ONE OF THE REASONS
WHY NONE OF THE CHILDREN AT
BRIAR WOOD PERISHED.
WE SHOULD POINT OUT SHEP,
NEITHER BRIAR WOOD NOR
PLAZA TOWERS HAD ANY KIND
OF SAFE ROOM OR HARDENED
TORNADO SHELTER.
THE STUDENTS SIMPLY HAD THE
STRUCTURE TO PROTECT THEM.
WE SAW HOW WELL THAT DID
DURING THIS TORNADO.
>> Shepard: BECAUSE OF ALL
OF THAT JOHN, IT'S MY
UNDERSTANDING YOU MET A MAN
WHOSE DAUGHTER REALLY
DIDN'T TRUST THAT THE
SCHOOLS COULD BE SAFE IN
THE STORM.
>> FELLOW WHO LIVES JUST
ACROSS THE STREET, HIS NAME
IS JIM GARNER.
HE SAID THAT YESTERDAY
AFTERNOON HIS DAUGHTER, WHO
HAS FOUR KIDS AT PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY GOT A
HINKY FEELING ABOUT
EVERYTHING THAT WAS GOING
TO HAPPEN.
HE PICKS UP THE TIME LINE
FROM THERE.
SHE KNEW THIS WAS COMING.
SHE HAD A BAD FEELING.
SO SHE WENT TO THE SCHOOL
AND PICKED MY GRAND KIDS UP
FROM SCHOOL.
>> WHAT TIME WAS THAT AT.
>> AROUND 2:00.
>>
2:59?
>> YES SIR.
SHE MADE A GOOD DECISION.
SHE WENT AND GOT THEM OUT
OF SCHOOL AND BROUGHT THEM
HOME.
>>
>> BROUGHT THEM HOME AND
TOOK THEM IMMEDIATELY TO
THE UNDERGROUND TORNADO
SHELTER RIGHT BEHIND THEIR
HOUSE.
SHE ADDED SIX MORE
CHILDREN.
JIM GARNER, HIS DAUGHTER
AND 10 CHILDREN RODE OUT
THIS TORNADO IN UNDERGROUND
STORM SHELTER SHEP.
THEY ALL ESCAPED UNSCATHED.
THOUGH JIM TOLD ME HE HAD
TO HOLD ON TO THAT DOOR
BECAUSE IT FELT LIKE THE
TORNADO WAS TRYING TO SUCK
IT OPEN AND SUCK THEM OUT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: MAN, JOHN
ROBERTS LIVE HERE IN MOORE
WITH US TONIGHT IN
OKLAHOMA.
LAWMAKERS FROM THIS AREA
SAY HELP IS REALLY ALREADY
POURING IN FROM ACROSS THE
COUNTRY AND FOR THAT MATTER
AROUND THE WORLD.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS IS HE
TAKING STEPS TO SPEED
DISASTER RELIEF FROM
WASHINGTON.
HE WHITE HOUSE.
BUT, FIRST SHEAR LOOK AT
SOME OF WHAT I SAW EARLIER
TODAY JUST AFTER WE LANDED
IN MOORE OKLAHOMA.
>> 24 HOURS LATER AND YOU
COULD TAKE THIS CAMERA TO
ANY PLACE WITHIN MILES AWAY
AND FIND SOMETHING EXACTLY
LIKE THIS.
SEE THE SIDE OF THIS HOUSE
HERE?
COVERED IN MUD.
THE TORNADO THREW IT UP
AGAINST THE HOUSE.
BEAMS COMING DOWN, METAL IN
THE TREES.
ALL ALONG HERE, DEBRIS FROM
WE DON'T EVEN KNOW WHERE.
THESE ARE EITHER POWER
LINES AND SOMEBODY'S GAS
CAN.
AND OVER HERE YOU CAN SEE
THE REST THAT WAS DONE BY
THE STORM.
THAT'S A TREE THERE IN THE
THE CENTER THAT WAS A TREE.
AND NOW ROOF AFTER ROOF IS
GONE.
PEOPLE HAVE COME IN TO TRY
TO GET SOME OF THEIR THINGS
TODAY.
AND THIS IS RIGHT ON THE
CORNER NEAR THE BIG MEDICAL
CENTER THAT YOU HEARD ABOUT
YESTERDAY.
STAY RIGHT THERE SCOTT, SO
YOU YOU CAN SEE IT BACK
BEHIND YOU.
THIS IS THE MEDICAL CENTER
OVER HERE.
IT JUST WIPED OUT.
YOU CAN SEE THIS WAS THE
MAIN ENTRANCE.
THE WOMAN CENTER AND BACK
BEHIND JUST WHAT'S LEFT OF
THIS FACILITY.
AND AS SCOTT WALKS OVER TO
HIS LEFT, YOU WILL BE ABLE
TO SEE IN THE DISTANCE
THERE CAR AFTER CAR SCOTT
PAN TO THE RIGHT AND IT IS
AS IF THE TORNADO JUST
PICKED ALL OF THESE CARS UP
AND JUST PUSHED THEM INTO
THIS BUILDING.
YOU SEE THE X'S ON THE SIDE
OF THESE VEHICLES, RIGHT?
AN X MEANS THAT THEY HAVE
SEARCHED THE VEHICLE AND
THERE IS NOBODY INSIDE.
BY THE THOUSANDS PART-TIME
HAVE COME HERE.
TO TRY TO VOOL TIER.
AND OVER HERE, AN AMERICAN
FLAG IS UP.
IT'S OKLAHOMA.
IT'S THE HEARTLAND OF
AMERICA.
THEY HAVE BEEN THROUGH THIS
BEFORE.
A DEVASTATING STORM IN
1999.
THE DEVASTATING ALFRED T.
MURROW FEDERAL BUILDING
BOMBING.
ANOTHER HORRIBLE STORM IN
2003.
AND NOW THEY ARE AT IT
AGAIN.
AND EACH TIME THEY HAVE
BEEN AN INSPIRATION TO THE
NATION.
AS THEY COME IN WITH A
SHOPPING CART WITH WHAT
THEY HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
SALVAGE FROM THEIR HOME, A
REMINDER OF EACH SINGLE
INDIVIDUAL'S STRUGGLE AND
THE STRUGGLE THAT WILL GO
ON FOR MONTHS AND MONTHS TO
COME.
OKLAHOMA NEEDS YOUR PRAYERS
AND YOUR HELP.
YEARS AGO, MY DOCTOR TOLD ME  TO TAKE
A CENTRUM SILVER  MULTIVITAMIN EVERY
DAY.  I TOLD HIM, SURE.  CAN'T HURT,
RIGHT?  AND NOW TODAY,  I SEE THIS
IN THE NEWS.  ONCE AGAIN, CENTRUM
SILVER  WAS CHOSEN BY RESEARCHERS
FOR ANOTHER LANDMARK STUDY.  THIS
TIME LOOKING AT EYE HEALTH.  MY DOCTOR!
HE KNOWS HIS STUFF.    [ Male Announcer
] CENTRUM.    THE MOST STUDIED.
THE MOST RECOMMENDED.    AND THE MOST
PREFERRED    MULTIVITAMIN BRAND.
THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
♪ ♪  ♪ WONDER IF I GAVE AN OREO ♪
♪ TO SOMEBODY OUT THERE  WHO I DIDN'T
KNOW ♪  ♪ WOULD THEY LAUGH  AFTER
I'D GONE? ♪  ♪ OR WOULD THEY PASS
THAT WONDER ON? ♪  ♪ I WONDER HOW
IT'D CHANGE  YOUR POINT OF VIEW ♪
♪ IF I GAVE ONE TO YOU? ♪  ♪ ♪
I'M SORRY  FOR YOUR LOSS.  STL DOESN'T
FEEL REAL.
OUR TIME TOGETHER WAS...
SO SHORT.
WELL, SINCE YOU HAD
PROGRESSIVE'S  TOTAL LOSS COVERAGE,
WE WERE ABLE TO REPLACE  YOUR TOTALED
BIKE
WITH  A BRAND-NEW ONE.
THE TANK  THE EXHAUST...
WELL, SHE LOOKS  JUST LIKE ROXY!
YOU KNOW, I'LL BET SHE'S IN  A BETTER
PLACE NOW.
I'M SURE SHE IS.
[ ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MOTORCYCLE REVVING ]
GETTING YOU BACK    ON A BRAND-NEW
BIKE.
NOW,  THAT'S  PROGRESSIVE.
HEY, LOOK!  A SHOOTING STAR!  MAKE
A WISH!  I WISH WE COULD  LIE HERE
FOREVER.  I WISH THIS TEST DRIVE WAS
OVER  SO WE COULD HEAD BACK  TO THE
DEALERSHIP.    [ Male Announcer ]
IT'S PRACTICALLY YOURS.  TEST DRIVE!
BUT WE STILL NEED    YOUR SIGNATURE.
VOLKSWAGEN SIGN THEN DRIVE    IS BACK.
AND IT'S NEVER BEEN EASIER    TO GET
A JETTA.    THAT'S THE POWER    OF
GERMAN ENGINEERING.    GET $0 DOWN,
$0 DUE AT SIGNING,  DEPOSIT    AND
$0 FIRST MONTH'S PAYMENT    ON ANY
NEW VOLKSWAGEN.    VISIT VWDEALER.COM
TODAY.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT OBAMA
IS PRAISING THE HEROS HERE
IN THE HEARTLAND AND
PROMISING THAT THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT WILL DO
EVERYTHING IT CAN TO HELP.
HE SAYS HE HAS ALREADY
SIGNED A DISASTER
DECLARATION TO GET THINGS
MOVING RIGHT AWAY.
>> OUR PRAYERS ARE WITH THE
PEOPLE OF OKLAHOMA TODAY.
OUR GRATITUDE IS WITH THE
TEACHERS WHO GAVE THEIR ALL
TO SHIELD THEIR CHILDREN
WITH THE NEIGHBORS FIRST
RESPONDERS AND EMERGENCY
PERCH NELL TO HO RACED TO
HELP AS SOON AS THE TORNADO
PASSED.
AND WITH ALL OF THOSE WHO
AS DARKNESS FELL SEARCHED
FOR SURVIVORS THROUGH THE
NIGHT TENT THE FLAG ON
CAPITOL HILL IS STILL
FLYING AT HALF-STAFF IN
HONOR OF THE VICTIMS IN
OKLAHOMA.
ED HENRY LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE TONIGHT.
ED?
>> SHEP IT'S INTERESTING
BEFORE THE PRESIDENT MADE
COMMENTS AT THE WHITE HOUSE
HE HAD A HIGH LEVEL
BRIEFING WITH SOME OF THE
ADVISORS INCLUDING JANET
NAPOLITANO.
YOU CAN SEE THE OFFICIAL
WHITE HOUSE PHOTO OF THAT,
LISA MONICA.
ONE OF THE OTHER ADVISORS
THERE.
YOU REMEMBER SHE WAS
PIVOTAL IN THE BOSTON
BOMBING INVESTIGATION AS
WELL IN TERMS OF KEEPING
THE PRESIDENT IN THE LOOP
ABOUT THE LATEST
DEVELOPMENT.
AND THE PRESIDENT MADE
CLEAR THAT THE FULL FORCE
OF THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT
WILL BE ON HAND IN OKLAHOMA
TO DEAL WITH THIS TRAGEDY.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> NEIGHBORHOODS WERE
DESTROYED.
DOZENS OF PEOPLE LOST THEIR
LIVES.
MANY MORE WERE INJURED.
AND AMONG THE VICTIMS WERE
YOUNG CHILDREN TRYING TO
TAKE SHELTER IN THE SAFEST
PLACE THEY KNEW, THEIR
SCHOOL.
>> INTERESTING AS WELL
BECAUSE CRAIG FUGATE WAS
NOT IN THIS BRIEFING WITH
THE PRESIDENT ONLY BECAUSE
HE WAS ALREADY ON HIS WAY
TO OKLAHOMA.
SO HIS DEPUTY WAS HERE TO
HELP BRIEF THE PRESIDENT
THE HOMELAND SECURITY
SECRETARY JANET NAPOLITANO
IS NOW ON HER WAY AS WELL.
SHE WILL BE IN OKLAHOMA
WHERE YOU ARE TOMORROW,
SHEP.
MEANWHILE, IN TERMS OF THE
PRESIDENT WE DON'T KNOW
YET WHEN HE WILL GO.
BUT WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS
ARE SAYING PRIVATELY THAT
LIKELY GO AT SOME POINT BUT
RIGHT NOW PUBLICLY, THEY
ARE SAYING HE DOES NOT WANT
TO GET IN THE WAY OF ALL
THE FIRST RESPONDERS TRYING
TO YOU KNOW, BRING
EVERYONE TOGETHER, TRY IN
THAT RECOVERY MISSION TO
DEAL WITH EVERYONE ON THE
GROUND.
THE LAST THING YOU WANT TO
DO IS BRING THE PRESIDENT'S
SECURITY DETAIL IN AND
DISTRACT FROM ALL OF THAT,
SHEP.
WE WON'T SEE HIM FOR AT
LEAST A COUPLE DAYS.
>> Shepard: THEY COULDN'T
TAKE MUCH MORE TRAFFIC
CONGESTION HERE FOR SURE.
ED HENRY AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THERE HAVE BEEN MANY
STORIES OF FAMILIES WHO
RODE OUT THIS TORNADO IN
THEIR UNDERGROUND STORM
SHELTERS.
EARLIER TODAY OUR CASEY
STEGALL WENT OUT INTO ONE
OF THOSE SMALL SPACES AND
GOT A SENSE OF WHAT IT
MIGHT HAVE BEEN LIKE FOR
PEOPLE TO CLIMB BACK OUT
ONLY TO FIND HEIR HOMES
WERE I DON'T KNOW IF GONE.
>> IN OKLAHOMA, THESE ARE
COMMON IN THE HOMES.
THEY ARE JUST A LITTLE
SPACE AND YOU HAVE LUGGAGE
IN HERE.
SOME BOTTLED WATER.
MAYBE YOUR RADIO WEATHER
RADIO, A FLASH LIGHT.
LOOK AT THIS.
THIS IS THE GARAGE.
YOU CAN SEE THAT'S WHAT'S
LEFT OF THE HOME.
>> Shepard: PILES OF DEBRIS
ALL AROUND.
THE FEAR IS SOME HOMES MAY
HAVE COLLAPSED ON TOP OF
THOSE STORM SHELTERS AND
THE FEAR IS SOME PEOPLE
COULD STILL BE TRAPPED.
SO THEY ARE FEVERISHLY
SEARCHING.
COME COMING UP A LIVE
REPORT FROM THE DISASTER
SCENE AND WORD ON THE COST
OF THIS DEVASTATION.
FIRST, WE ARE TRACKING
THREATS OF MORE SEVERE
WEATHER RIGHT NOW.
OUR METEOROLOGIST JANICE
DEAN IN THE FOX EXTREME
WEATHER CENTER LIVE BACK IN
NEW YORK.
JANICE?
>> HI, SHEPARD YES.
WE STILL HAVE ARKANSAS,
LOUISIANA, MISSISSIPPI UP
TOWARDS TENNESSEE AND
KENTUCKY.
AND SEVERAL SEVERE
THUNDERSTORM WARNINGS JUST
EAST OF DALLAS.
NORTH AND EAST OF AUSTIN,
MOVING IN TOWARDS THE
CAROLINAS.
GEORGIA, TENNESSEE AND
KENTUCKY EACH THE
NORTHEAST WE ARE SEEING
MANY SEVERE THUNDERSTORM
WARNINGS.
SO SOMETHING WE ARE GOING
TO TRACK THROUGHOUT THE
EVENING.
THERE IS YOUR SEVERE RISK
IN THE YELLOW WITH THAT RED
SHADED AREA WHERE WE STILL
THINK WE COULD HAVE THE
POTENTIAL FOR HAIL
DAMAGING WINDS AND EVEN
TORNADOES.
THE GOOD NEWS IS STY SKIES
ARE CLEARING IN MOORE
OKLAHOMA.
MORE COVERAGE WITH SHEPARD
SMITH LIVE FROM MOORE
OKLAHOMA WHEN WE RETURN.
KILLING THAT BACTERIA  YESTERDAY,
JUST FLAUNTING IT?  AND DID YOU SEE
THE MAGIC ERASER  CLEAN UP THAT CRAZY
KITCHEN MESS?  IT WAS LIKE SUPER DIRTY,
SUPER CLEAN. HOW?  WISH I HADN'T.
[ sniffs ]  WHAT'S THAT AMAZING SMELL?
IT'S MR. CLEAN WITH  THE AMAZING SCENT
OF GAIN.  WOW!  YOU KNOW, IF I HAD
A TEAM,  YOU'D BE ON IT.  [ gasps
] OUR MASCOT COULD BE  A CLEANOSARUS
REX.  YOU'RE OFF THE TEAM.    [ Male
Announcer ] DIRT    AND GRIME HAVE
NOWHERE TO HIDE    WITH THE MR. CLEAN
CLEAN TEAM    ON YOUR SIDE.
The first time I saw a Sony 4k  TV,
it was like opening my eyes.  It's
four times the  detail of HD.
Colors become richer.
Details become clearer.
Which for a filmmaker,  changes everything.
Because now
there are no  more barriers between
the  world that I see
and the ones I can show you.
The Sony 4k Ultra HD TV.
WE REALLY WANTED TO TAKE  A RELAXING
TRIP TO FLORIDA.  YOU KNOW?  JUST
TO UNWIND.
BUT WE CAN ONLY AFFORD  ONE TRIP THIS
YEAR
AND HIS HIGH SCHOOL REUNION  IS COMING
UP IN SEATTLE.
EVERYONE'S GOING.
THEN WE HEARD  ABOUT HOTWIRE...
AND REALIZED WE COULD ACTUALLY  AFFORD
TO TAKE BOTH TRIPS.
[WOMAN] SEE, WHEN REALLY NICE  HOTELS
HAVE UNSOLD ROOMS
THEY USE HOTWIRE TO FILL THEM.
SO WE GOT OUR FOUR STAR HOTELS  FOR
HALF PRICE.
I SHOULD HAVE BEEN VOTED  "MOST LIKELY
TO TRAVEL."
♪ H-O-T-W-I-R-E ♪
♪ HOTWIRE.COM ♪
HOT RATE HOTELS NOW ON SALE.
SAVE UP TO 70% ON    ANY WEEKEND STAY.
>> Shepard: I'M SHEPARD
SMITH.
IT'S "THE FOX REPORT."
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR, TIME FOR THE TOP OF
THE NEWS FROM MOORE
OKLAHOMA.
THE COMMUNITY HERE WILL
REBUILD.
IT WILL NEVER BE THE SAME.
THERE IS NOTHING LEFT TO
REPAIR.
NOTHING FOR FAMILIES TO
SALVAGE.
INSTEAD, THEY ARE HAVING TO
CLEAR EVERYTHING OUT AND
FRANKLY START FROM SCRATCH.
JUST WATCH HERE AS ONE
FAMILY CONFRONTED THE
BRUTAL REALTY THEY RECORDED
THE MOMENT THAT THEY
EMERGED FROM THEIR
UNDERGROUND STORM SHELTER
EVERYTHING THEY OWN IN A
PILE OF RUBBLE.
RIGHT WHERE THEIR HOME HAD
BEEN.
NOT A SINGLE STRUCTURE
STANDING AS FAR AS THE
CAMERA COULD SEE.
WE CANNOT MEASURE OF HUMAN
COST OF THIS TRAGEDY YET.
BUT THE DAMAGE TO HOMES AND
BUSINESSES COULD BE IN THE
BILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
IN FACT, OKLAHOMA'S
INSURANCE COMMISSIONER
PREDICTS IT WILL TOP THE
$3 BILLION IN DAMAGE FROM
THE JOB PALESTINIAN
MISSOURI STORM A COUPLE OF
YEARS AGO.
TODAY WE SPOKE WITH A WOMAN
WHO WENT TO JOPLIN BACK
THEN TO HELP.
SHE SAYS SHE REMEMBERS
VIVIDLY THOSE HEART BROKEN
SURVIVORS NOW SHE IS ONE OF
THEM.
>> I'M FROM KANSAS
ORIGINALLY.
SO FRIENDS AND I WENT OVER
AND WE JUST HELPED PASS OUT
WATER AND WE HELPED PEOPLE
GO THROUGH HOMES AND GET
WHAT THEY COULD AND, YOU
KNOW YOU ALWAYS PRAY AND
HOPE THAT IT'S NEVER YOU.
AND I HOPED IT WASN'T US
BUT, UNFORTUNATELY
UNFORTUNATELY IT WAS.
>> Shepard: THAT WOMAN
SPENT THE DAY CLIMBING
THROUGH THE WRECKAGE OF HER
HOME SEARCHING FOR HER DOG.
HER PUT WAS IN A BACK ROOM
WHEN THE TWISTER HIT.
SHE SAYS THE ENTIRE ROOM
VANISHED DOG AND ALL.
CASEY STEGALL SPOKE TODAY
WITH THAT WOMAN AND MANY OF
THE OTHER VICTIMS.
CASEY, WHAT ARE YOU SEEING
THERE WHERE YOU ARE?
>> WELL, SHEPARD YOU KNOW,
WHEN WE STARTED OUR DAY
THIS MORNING IT WAS A
MEMBER OF YOUR OWN TEAM WHO
SAID HEY WHERE ARE YOU
LOCATED?
I LOOKED AROUND AND I WAS
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHERE
TO TELL THEM TO GO AND I
REALIZED I WAS LOOKING IN
THE WRONG SPOT TO TELL THEM
WE WERE AT HEATHER LANE AND
SOUTHWEST SIXTH STREET.
SHEPARD, ON THE OUTSIDE
TODAY WAS ABOUT SIFTING
THROUGH THE RUBBLE IT WAS
ABOUT PICKING THROUGH THE
PIECES AND CLEANING UP.
BUT ON THE INSIDE, IT WAS
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE ALL
TOGETHER IT WAS ABOUT HOPE.
HOPE THAT MORE SURVIVORS
WOULD BE FOUND AND HOPE
THAT THE DEATH TOLL
WOULDN'T RISE AND THAT IS
EXACTLY EMBODIED RIGHT BACK
THERE.
LOOK AT THAT A POWERFUL
IMAGE, A TATTERED AMERICAN
FLAG HANGING.
THE HOMEOWNER THERE SAYS
THAT HIS WIFE AND TWO
CHILDREN RODE THE STORM OUT
IN THEIR BATHTUB.
THEY ARE OKAY.
HE SAID HE WANTED TO HANG
THAT FLAG THERE AS A
REMINDER THAT NEIGHBORS ARE
HELPING THY NEIGHBOR AND
THIS COMMUNITY WILL
REBUILD.
WE ALSO WERE HERE THIS
MORNING WHEN THIS PERIMETER
WAS UNSEALED AND THEY LET
THE RESIDENTS IN FOR THE
VERY FIRST TIME AND WE WERE
WITH THIS WOMAN WHEN SHE
SAW EVERYTHING FIRSTHAND
EVERYTHING I KNOW, I RODE
MY STREET, MY BIKE THROUGH
THIS STREET.
THESE ARE MY FRIENDS
HOUSES.
I USED TO TAKE THE BUS
ROUTE AROUND HERE AND NOW
I DON'T KNOW, JUST REALLY
SAD AND SCARY AND IT'S
GOING TO TAKE SO LONG TO
REBUILD.
>> BUT THEY WILL REBUILD.
WE HAVE SEEN IT DONE
ELSEWHERE.
AND WE WILL SEE IT HERE.
IT WILL TAKE SOME TIME BUT
WE WILL GET THERE.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: YEAH, IT
CERTAINLY WILL TAKE SOME
TIME.
CASEY STEGALL IN THE MIDDLE
OF IT ALL.
CASEY, THANKS.
DISASTER RELIEF IS WELL
UNDERWAY HERE.
SALVATION ARMY OFFICIALS
SAY THAT THEY HAVE
DISPATCHED RESPONSE TEAMS
AND SET UP MOBILE FOOD
STATIONS TO GET REALLY
WHATEVER THEY CAN TO THE
VICTIMS.
THE RED CROSS SENDING
SIMILAR HELP TO THE AREA.
IT'S ALSO CREATED A WEB
SITE SO IF YOU WANT TO
CONNECT WITH PEOPLE
SEARCHING FOR LOVED ONES IN
THE WAKE OF THE STORM, YOU
CAN.
IF YOU WANT TO GO TO GO TO
SAFE AND WELL.ORG.
ENTER YOUR INFORMATION AND
LIST YOURSELF AS SAFE AND
YOU CAN CHECK WITH PEOPLE
WHO HAVE REGISTERED AS
WELL.
PEOPLE ARE HELPING OUT IN
SHELTERS.
OUR ALICIA ACUNA IS LIVE IN
ONE OF THE MOORE COMMUNITY
CENTER WHICH IS THE SHELTER
FOR EVERYBODY HERE TONIGHT.
HOW IS IT GOING ALICIA.
>> HOW IS IT GOING
SHEPARD.
SOME ARE COMING HERE TO
SLEEP SOME TO REST.
IF YOU TAKE A LOOK, THIS IS
WHERE A LOT OF FOLKS ARE
DROPPING OFF SUPPLIES.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT HAS
BEEN GOING ON DAY.
FOLKS TRYING TO HELP OUT
ANY WAY THEY CAN.
NOW, THE RED CROSS SAYS
THAT A LOT OF PEOPLE
ACTUALLY PREFER TO STAY
WITH FAMILY AND FRIENDS.
BUT, STILL THE UNIVERSITY
OF OKLAHOMA IS ON SUMMER
BREAK AND IT SAYS THAT IT
IS OPENING UP ITS DORMS TO
DISPLACED FAMILIES ALSO.
AND TODAY A HUGE CELEBRITY
HERE.
OU HEAD FOOTBALL COACH BOB
STUCKS BROUGHT STACKS OF
$50 GIFT CARDS AND DECIDED
TO COME HERE AND VISIT WITH
THE FAMILIES AT THIS
SHELTER.
A LITTLE RELIEF AND BROUGHT
A BUNCH OF HATS AND
T-SHIRTS AND SOME DRY WEAR
FOR PEOPLE WHO HAVE BEEN
OUT ALL DAY AND TRYING TO
PASS THEM OUT.
AND HELP THEM A LITTLE BIT.
>> AS PART OF THE HEALING
PROCESS HERE, SOME OF THE
KIDS WERE ALLOWED TO GET
BACK TO BEING KIDS.
ART SUPPLIES PROVIDED TO
THE YOUNGEST WHO WERE
KICKED FROM THEIR HOMES BY
THAT TORNADO.
SO SHEP, THEY GOT TO
COLOR, WHICH IS GOOD FOR
EVERYONE HERE TO SEE.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: COLORING IS
ALWAYS FUN.
WE HAVE GOT A COUPLE HERE
WITH US YOU WILL NEAT A
SECOND WHO LOVE IT AS WELL.
CHRIS CATHY'S FAMILY WAS IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE CHAOS AND
DESTRUCTION.
THE HOME THEY HAD BEEN RENT
SOMETHING NOW LEVELED.
ONE OF CHRIS' CHILDREN IS A
KINDERGARTNER AT PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY.
THE SCHOOL WHERE THE
TORNADO -- WELL, THE
TORNADO THE SCHOOL TORNADO
FLATTENED.
CHRIS AND CORY AND HIS SON
CASH ARE ALL WITH US
TONIGHT.
HOW ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
>> PRETTY GOOD.
>> I MEAN, NOW IT'S MY
UNDERSTANDING, CORY, YOU
WERE IN SCHOOL RIGHT?
WERE YOU?
I KNOW HELLO KITTY IS MUCH
MORE INTERESTING THAN ME.
I UNDERSTAND.
THIS I WAS JUST WONDERING
HOW IS SHE DOING THERE?
>> SHE SAID SHE WASN'T
SCARED BUT I KNOW IT WAS
PROBABLY A DIFFERENT STORY
IN THERE I WASN'T THERE.
I WAS ABOUT AN HOUR AWAY
AND RUSHING TO GET THERE.
I'M SURE SHE WAS PRETTY
SHAKEN UP.
SHE WAS SHAKEN UP WHEN I
SAW HER.
>> Shepard: IS SHE ALWAYS
QUIET OR DOESN'T LIKE
TELEVISION LIFE.
>> SHE IS VERY SHY.
>> WHAT ABOUT YOU CASH?
I DON'T THINK -- THESE ARE
THE ONLY CHILDREN IN THE
WORLD THAT DON'T TALK.
YOU ARE A VERY LUCKY MAN.
IN ALL SERIOUSNESS THOUGH,
DID YOU LOSE EVERYTHING?
>> PRETTY MUCH.
PRETTY MUCH EVERYTHING.
WE HAVE SALVAGED SOME
PICTURES AND SOME CLOTHES
AND EVERYTHING ELSE I JUST
COUNT IT AS A LOSS.
>> WHAT DO YOU PLAN TO DO?
>> JUST REBUILD EVERYTHING
IS REPLACEABLE BUT THESE
TWO.
>> WE ARE SHOWING PICTURES
WHAT'S LEFT OF YOUR HOUSE.
IT'S JUST UNBELIEVABLE.
IT'S SOMETHING TO SEE.
I DIDN'T EXPECT IT TO BE
THAT BAD.
>> NOW CORY'S TEACHER IS
IN THE HOSPITAL, RIGHT
WITH AN ARM INJURY.
>> RIGHT.
>> WHAT HAPPENED TO HER?
>> I'M NOT SURE.
I GUESS THE WALLS CAVED IN
WHERE THEY WERE AND THEY
TOLD ME SOMETHING HAD
LANDED ON HER ARM.
I DON'T KNOW HOW BAD IT IS
YET.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN ABLE TO
THINK ABOUT NOT JUST WHAT
TOMORROW BRINGS BUT ABOUT
WHAT THE NEXT WEEKS AND
MONTHS BRING?
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
THINK OF MUCH.
I'M JUST TRYING TO GET A
PLAN TOGETHER.
I HAVEN'T GIVE IT MUCH
FUTURE THOUGHT YET.
>> I GUESS TODAY IS HARD
ENOUGH.
>> RIGHT.
IT'S TOO SOON.
>> WHERE ARE YOU STAYING
AND CASH NEEDS A HUG.
>> WE ARE STAYING IN A
HOTEL ON NORTH MERIDIAN.
WE WILL BE THERE FOR A
WHILE UNTIL I FIGURE
EVERYTHING OUT.
>> HAVE YOU AND YOUR
NEIGHBORS BEEN ABLE TO GET
WHAT YOU NEED?
>> SO FAR.
SO FAR WE HAVE BEEN
BLESSED.
EVERYBODY HAS BEEN HELPING
OUT.
FAMILIES CAME DOWN.
BEEN LETY GOOD.
>> YOUR KIDS SEEM SO TIRED.
I UNDERSTAND HOW THEY WOULD
BE.
THAT RAIN TODAY AND COLD
AND REALLY DRAINING.
>> YEAH, IT'S TAKEN A LOT
ON THEM.
WORE THEM OUT A LITTLE BIT.
>> HAVE THEY SEEMED OKAY?
CASH ARE DO YOU GO GOOD?
YEAH, ALL RIGHT.
WE GOT A NOD OUT OF HIM
ANYWAY AND A VERY COOL
SNUGY.
WERE THESE THINGS DONATED?
>> YEAH.
THEY WERE DONATED.
HER COUSIN HAD CAME DOWN
AND BROTHER AND THEY
BROUGHT SOME SUPPLIES.
>> Shepard: Y'ALL HAVE
PEOPLE TO STAY WITH AND
SOME SUPPORT AROUND YOU?
>> YEAH.
WE HAVE SOME SUPPORT.
MY GRANDPARENTS LIVE UP
HERE.
>> Shepard: YOU ARE LUCKY
THAT WAY.
CASH I THINK YOU NEED IT A
NAP, DON'T YOU CASH AND
CORY AND CHRIS YOU NEED
SOME SHOES TOO BABE.
SHE LEFT THEM IN THE CAR.
NOT THAT THEY ARE SHOELESS.
GOOD LUCK TO YOU GUYS.
I HOPE EVERYTHING GOES
WELL.
>> WE APPRECIATE IT REALLY
DO.
>> Shepard: IF THEY DECIDE
TO TALK GIVE US A CALL WE
WOULD LOVE TO CHAT WITH
THEM.
>> ALL RIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: OH MY
GOODNESS.
MIGHTY TOUGH FOR ALL THESE
FAMILIES.
IT'S ONE THING YOU KEEP
YOUR KIDS IN A ROUTINE AND
EVERY DAY YOU WANT TO EAT
AT THIS TIME.
AND YOU GO TO THE BUS AT
THIS TIME.
WE ARE GOING TO GO TO BED
AT THAT TIME.
ALL ROUTINES ARE OUT THE
DOOR.
AND CHILDREN ARE A LOT OF
WORK FOR A LOT OF FOLKS
AROUND HERE NOW.
MUCH MORE AHEAD FROM
OKLAHOMA.
WE'LL BRING YOU THE
BREAKING DETAILS AS THEY
COME IN.
PLUS WE'RE FOLLOWING OTHER
BIG STORIES TODAY.
INCLUDING THE TRIAL OF JODI
ARIAS WHO SPOKE OUT TODAY
IN COURT.
YOU WILL HEAR WHY SHE SAYS
SHE WOULD PREFER NOT TO DIE
IN PRISON AND ALL THAT SHE
HAS TO PROVIDE SOCIETY FROM
INSIDE PRISON, THAT AND THE
HORROR IN THE HEARTLAND
JUST AHEAD AS FOX REPORTS
LIVE TONIGHT.
rsity WOULD  GIVE ME THE SKILLS  THAT
I NEEDED TO MAKE  ONE OF THOSE TECH
JOBS MINE.  WE TEACH CUTTING-EDGE
ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY  COMPUTER INFORMATION
SYSTEMS  NETWORKING  AND COMMUNICATIONS
MANAGEMENT --  THE THINGS THAT OUR
STUDENTS  NEED TO KNOW IN THE WORLD
TODAY.  OUR COUNTRY NEEDS  MORE COLLEGE
GRADS  TO HELP FILL  ALL THE OPEN
TECHNOLOGY JOBS.  TO HELP MEET THAT
NEED, HERE AT  DeVry University  WE'RE
OFFERING $4 MILLION   DOLLARS IN TECH
SCHOLARSHIPS  FOR QUALIFIED NEW STUDENTS.
LEARN MORE AT DeVry.edu.
What makes the Sleep
Number store different?  You walk
into a  conventional mattress
store, it's really not  about you.
They say, "Well, if you  wanted a
firm bed you can
lie on one of those.
We provide the exact  individualization
that
your body needs.
Oh, yeah!
Wow.
Once you experience it  there's no
going back.
At the Sleep Number  Memorial Day
Sale,
save on the closeout of  our Classic
Special
Edition bed set.
Now just $1299-a savings  of $600.
Only at the Sleep Number  store.
Sleep Number.
Comfort Individualized.
>> Shepard: BACK LIVE IN
MOVE OKLAHOMA WITH MORE ON
THE KILLER TORNADO IN THE
HEARTLAND.
FIRST, JURORS HAVE BEGAN
DELIBERATING WITH JODI
ARIAS GETS LIFE OR DEATH
AFTER SHE REVEALED TODAY
THAT SHE NO LONGER WANTS TO
DIE OR SO SHE SAYS IS.
SHE NOW SAYS SHE WANTS LIFE
IN PRISON.
>> UNTIL VERY RECENTLY, I
COULD NOT HAVE MANAGED
STANDING BEFORE YOU ALL AND
ASKING YOU TO GIVE ME LIFE.
TO ME, LIFE IN PRISON WAS
THE MOST UNAPPEALING
OUTCOME I COULD POSSIBLY
THINK OF.
I THOUGHT I WOULD RATHER
DIE.
BUT AS I STAND HERE NOW, I
CAN'T IN GOOD CONSCIENCE
ASK TO YOU SENTENCE ME TO
DEATH.
>> Shepard: OF COURSE
THAT'S NOT WHAT SHE TOLD
OUR STATION FOX 10 IN
PHOENIX JUST HOURS AFTER
THE JURY FOUND HER GUILTY
OF MURDER IN THE FIRST
DEGREE AFTER SHE STABBED
HER EX-BOYFRIEND 27 TIMES
SHOT HIM AND SLIT HIS
THROAT.
AT THAT TIME SHE CALLED
DEATH THE ULTIMATE FREEDOM
BUT TODAY SHE TOLD THE JURY
SHE HAS MORE PERSPECTIVE
NOW ABOUT THE POSITIVE
CHANGE SHE CAN MAKE IN
PRISON.
>> I DESIGNED A T-SHIRT.
THIS IS THE T-SHIRT.
WHICH 100% OF THE PROCEEDS
GO TO SUPPORT NONPROFIT
ORGANIZATIONS WHICH ALSO
IS OTHER VICTIMS OF
DOMESTIC VIOLENCE.
>> Shepard: REMEMBER AREAS
AND THE DEFENSE DID NOT
PRESENT MUCH EVIDENCE TO
SUPPORT THE CLAIM THAT SHE
HERSELF WAS A VICTIM OF
DOMESTIC VIOLENCE.
THERE WAS NO PHYSICAL
EVIDENCE AT ALL.
TODAY SHE SAID THAT PEOPLE
THAT DON'T BELIEVE HER ARE
ENTITLED TO THEIR OPINIONS.
SHE ALSO SHOWED OFF SOME OF
HER AFTER THE -- ARTWORK
DRAWINGS OF FRANK SINATRA
ELVIS PRESLEY AND ELIZABETH
TAYLOR.
JODI ARIAS SAYS AS IT
STANDS SHE WILL NEVER
CREATE ANOTHER OIL PAINTING
IN HER LIFE AND WE ARE NOW
ABOUT TO HEAR EVEN MORE
FROM THIS, WOMAN BECAUSE
SHE HAS AGREED TO
INTERVIEWS WITH MAJOR
TELEVISION NETWORKS,
INCLUDING FOX LATER
TONIGHT.
TRACE GALLAGHER LIVE IN THE
WEST COAST NEWS HUB.
MAYBE THIS WILL BE THE LAST
OF IT.
JURY HAS THE CASE AGAIN
SHEP.
THEY DELIVERED IT FOR AN
HOUR AND HOUR AND A HALF.
15 MINUTES AGO 10:00 LOCAL.
1:00 IN THE EAST.
EXPERTS DO NOT BELIEVE
THESE DELIBERATIONS DIDN'T
LAST VERY LONG.
REMEMBER DURING THE GUILT
PHASE DELIBERATED 15 HOURS.
DURING THE AGGRAVATING
PHASE THEY ONLY DELIBERATED
FOR AN HOUR AND A HALF.
HERE NOW IS A SAMPLE OF THE
CLOSING ARGUMENTS FROM BOTH
SIDES.
>> ALL OF THIS IS BEING
PRESENTED TO YOU DURING
THIS PHASE OF THE
PROCEEDINGS.
MOST OF IT HAS COME FROM
THE DEFENDANT'S MOUTH.
THIS INDIVIDUAL THAT WILL
NOT HESITATE WHEN THE TRUTH
FAILS TO COME UP WITH A
LIE.
>> BUT LYING IS NOT A
CAPITAL CRIME.
AND LYING DOES NOT GIVE YOU
THE DEATH PENALTY AND LYING
ISN'T EVEN AN AGO
AGGRAVATING FACTOR.
>> IF SHE GETS LIFE SHE
GOES BACK TO THE MARICOPA
COUNTY JAIL FOR A SHORT
TIME AND THEN TO PRISON.
IF SHE GETS DEATH.
SHE GOES DIRECTLY TO DEATH
ROW, SHEP.
>> Shepard: WELL SHE HAS
PERSPECTIVE NOW TRACE.
IF I IF I FILL US IN ON ALL
THIS PERSPECTIVE.
>> YEAH, SHE SAID THAT IF
SHE ASKED FOR THE DEATH
PENALTY IT WOULD BE LIKE
COMMITTING SUICIDE AND THAT
WOULD BE EXTREMELY PAINFUL
FOR HER FAMILY AND SHE SAYS
HER FAMILY HAS BEEN THROUGH
ENOUGH PAIN.
SHE SAYS IF SHE GETS LIFE
IN PRISON, SHE WOULD TEACH
INMATES SPANISH EVEN SIGN
LANGUAGE.
MAYBE EVEN START UP A BOOK
CLUB.
SHE SAYS THE TIME FOR
HEALING HAS BEGUN.
LISTEN.
>> THIS IS THE WORST
MISTAKE OF MY LIFE.
THE WORST THING I HAVE EVER
DONE.
IT'S THE WORST THING I EVER
COULD HAVE SEEN MYSELF
DOING.
IN FACT, I COULDN'T SEE
MYSELF DOING IT BEFORE THAT
DAY I WOULDN'T EVEN WANT TO
HARM A SPIDER.
>> YOU COULD SEE JODI ARIAS
WAS CLEARLY NERVOUS AS SHE
WAS READING THAT STATEMENT.
THE FAMILY OF TRAVIS
ALEXANDER SAT IN THE
BACKGROUND MOTIONLESS.
JODI ARIAS WILL SPEAK WITH
FOX TONIGHT 9:30 LOCAL TIME
AND WE WILL AIR PARTS OF
THAT INTERVIEW TOMORROW.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: WITH THE FOX
BROADCAST NETWORK OR FOX
NEWS CHANNEL OR WHAT?
>> SHE IS INTERVIEWING WITH
LOCAL FOX AS WELL AS FOX
NEWS CHANNEL TONIGHT AT
9:30.
SO WE WILL HAVE THAT ON
TAPE.
BRING IT BACK TO THE TRUCK
FEED IT AND IT CAN BE
BROADCAST ANY TIME AFTER
11:00 TONIGHT LOCAL.
>> Shepard: I'M SURE LIFE
WON'T BE COMPLETE WITHOUT
IT TRACE GALLAGHER LIVE IN
LOS ANGELES.
THANK YOU.
THERE IS A NEW DEVELOPMENT
NOT JUSTICE DEPARTMENT'S
SEIZURE OF JOURNALIST
RECORDS INCLUDING THE
PERSONAL INFORMATION OF FOX
NEWS CORRESPONDENT.
THAT STRAIGHT AHEAD.
AND BACK HERE IN MOORE A
COMMUNITY DEALING WITH
TREMENDOUS SHOCK AND GRIEF.
BUT AMID THE DEATH AND
DESTRUCTION A SYMBOL OF
STRENGTH.
RESCUE CREWS SEARCHING FOR
SURVIVORS YESTERDAY FOUND
AN AMERICAN FLAG AND RAISED
OLD GLORY ABOVE THE RUBBLE.
FOX NEWS COVERAGE
CONTINUES.
THAT'S NEXT.
♪
AS YOUR LIFE CHANGES    FIDELITY IS
THERE
R YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY,
HELPING YOU READJUST    ALONG THE
WAY,
REFOCUS AS CAREERS CHANGE
AND KIDS HEAD OFF TO COLLEGE
AND REVISIT YOUR INVESTMENTS
AS RETIREMENT GETS CLOSER.
WHEREVER YOU ARE TODAY
FIDELITY'S GUIDANCE    CAN HELP YOU
FINE-TUNE    YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY.
START TODAY WITH A FREE
ONE-ON-ONE REVIEW    OF YOUR RETIREMENT
PLAN.
Tony used Priceline to book this
4 star hotel. Tell 'em why.  Free
breakfast  With Express Deals, you
can save   big and find a hotel
with free breakfast   without bidding.
Don't you just love those   little
cereal boxes?  Priceline savings
without the bidding.
FOR 150 YEARS, CALIFORNIA EDUCATORS
HAVE STOOD UP FOR WHAT HAPPENS IN
THE CLASSROOM.
IN 1866, PIONEERING
THE FIRST FREE PUBLIC SCHOOLS
FOR ALL KIDS.
AND TODAY STILL STANDING STRONG,
WITH EFFORTS TO CLOSE ACHIEVEMENT
GAPS...
REDUCE CLASS SIZES...
AND GIVE EVERY STUDENT
A WELL-ROUNDED EDUCATION.
EVEN AS TIME AND TECHNOLOGY CHANGE
THE WAY WE TEACH,
OUR COMMITMENT TO CHILDREN NEVER WILL.
BECAUSE THE CALIFORNIA TEACHERS ASSOCIATION
KNOWS QUALITY PUBLIC SCHOOLS
MAKE A BETTER CALIFORNIA FOR ALL OF
US.
>> Shepard: WE'RE LEARNING
MORE ABOUT HOW THE FEDS
TARGETED A FOX NEWS
CORRESPONDENT AS PART OF A
LEAK INVESTIGATION.
AS IT TURNS OUT THE FEDS
DIDN'T JUST ACCESS JAMES
ROSEN'S PERSONAL EMAIL HIS
G MAIL ACCOUNT THEY ALSO
GOT AHOLD OF HIS PHONE
RECORDS.
SHANNON BREAM LIVE IN THE
D.C. NEWSROOM TONIGHT.
SHANNON?
>> WELL, SHEPARD PERSONAL
EMAILS AND PHONE RECORDS
AND WE ARE LEARNING TONIGHT
THEY GO FAR BEYOND JUST
JAMES ROSEN'S INFORMATION.
IN A COURT FILING MADE BY
THE U.S. ATTORNEY'S OFFICE
DATED OCTOBER 13TH, 2011
THE GOVERNMENT DETAILS
NUMEROUS PIECES OF EVIDENCE
THAT HAD T. HAS COLLECTED
INCLUDING SCORES OF PHONE
RECORDS THAT HAVE AREA
CODES AND EXCHANGES THAT
MATCH UP TO MANY FOX NEWS
OFFICE HARD LINES AND
EMPLOYEE'S CELL PHONES.
IN THE REDACTED VERSION OF
THAT GOVERNMENT WE CANNOT
SEE THE FINAL FOUR NUMBERS
IN EACH OF THE PHONE
NUMBERS BUT THE AREA CODE
AND EXCHANGE MATCH UP TO
FOX EMPLOYEE AND THE OFFICE
PHONES INCLUDING THE PHONE
LINES THAT RUN TO OUR WORK
SPACE AT THE WHITE HOUSE
PENTAGON, AND STATE
DEPARTMENT.
THE RECORDS ALSO APPEAR TO
SHOW THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
GATHERED PHONE RECORDS
LINKED TO FOX NEWS
EXECUTIVES.
WE HAVE REACHED OUT TO THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT AND
WHITE HOUSE FOR COMMENT.
WHITE HOUSE PRESS SECRETARY
JAY CARNEY TELLS OUR
COLLEAGUE ED HENRY HE QUOTE
CAN'T COMMENT ON ONGOING
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION.
THESE NEW REVELATIONS COME
ON THE HEELS OF NEWS THAT
AN FBI AGENT SIGNED AN
AFFIDAVIT ACCUSING ROSEN OF
COMMITTING A CRIME BY
ALLEGEDLY OBTAINING
INFORMATION FROM A STATE
DEPARTMENT EMPLOYEE AND
THAT LED TO A SEARCH
WARRANT THAT GAVE THE
GOVERNMENT ACCESS TO
ROSEN'S PERSONAL EMAIL
ACCOUNT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: SHANNON, THE
MAN THAT WAS RUNNING THE
IRS WHEN IT TARGETED
CONSERVATIVE GROUPS IS
REFUSING TO APOLOGIZE TO
THOSE GROUPS.
THE FORMER COMMISSIONER
DOUGLAS SHULLMAN TESTIFIED
ABOUT THE SCANDAL ON
CAPITOL HILL FOR THE FIRST
TIME TODAY.
HE HE SAYS IS HE DEEPLY
SADDENED BY WHAT HAPPENED
BUT INSISTS IS HE NOT TO
BLAME.
I'M CERTAINLY NOT
RESPONSIBLE FOR FORMING A
LIST THAT HAD INAPPROPRIATE
MATERIAL ON IT WHEN THAT
SAID IT HAPPENED ON MY
WATCH AND I'M IT HAPPENED
ON MY WATCH.
>> THE IRS OFFICIAL WHO
FIRST RESEALED THE AGENCY
TARGETING CONSERVATIVES IS
APPARENTLY FINISHED
TALKING.
HER LAWYER SAYS LOTS --
LERNER HAD -- SAYS THAT
LERNER WILL TAKE THE FIFTH
TOMORROW WHEN IT IS HER
TURN TO TESTIFY UP ON
CAPITOL HILL.
WILT HERE IN OKLAHOMA,
PICTURES HAVE SHOWN ONLY A
FRACTION OF THE
DEVASTATION.
TO GIVE YOU A BETTER IDEA
OF JUST HOW FAR IT
STRETCHES.
ONE SHOT -- I SHOT THE
VIDEO THIS AFTERNOON OF OUR
TEAM'S DRIVE FROM OKLAHOMA
AND CITY TO THE AIRPORT
FROM THE AIRPORT THERE TO
HERE.
GETTING AROUND IS DIFFICULT
WITH DEBRIS CLOGGING SOME
STREETS.
HOUSE AFTER HOUSE.
BUSINESS AFTER BUSINESS
WIPED OUT IN SOME CASES.
WE PASSED ONE FAMILY'S
HOME NOW JUST A CAMPING
TENT TO SHIELD THEM FROM
THE RAIN.
AND THEN THERE ARE SOME OF
THE SMALL VICTIMS IN THIS
DISASTER.
PEOPLE'S PETS.
AND DESPITE ALL THE LOSSES,
SOME FAMILIES HAVE BEEN
GETTING MUCH OF THAT REALLY
GOOD NEWS.
AND THAT'S NEXT.
lief, try Dulcolax  laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief  overnight
unlike Miralax  and Metamucil that
can take up  to 3 days.  For predictable
relief try  Dulcolax.
Our landing time got    moved back
another hour.  ( crowd chatters and
groans )
Hunger creeping up on you ?
Stash a Ritz  Crackerfuls.
Made with real cheese  and whole grain.
Don't get caught hungry.  Ritz Crackerfuls.
LOOK WHAT MOMMY  IS HAVING.  MOMMY'S
HAVING  A FRENCH FRY.  YES SHE IS,
YES SHE IS.  [ bop ]
[ Male Announcer ]    COULD'VE HAD
A V8.    100% VEGETABLE JUICE    WITH
THREE OF YOUR DAILY    VEGETABLE SERVINGS
IN EVERY LITTLE BOTTLE.
I'M SO GLAD YOU CALLED.  THANK YOU.
WE'RE NOT IN LONDON,  ARE WE?  NO.
WHY?  APPARENTLY  MY DEBIT CARD IS.
WHAT?  I KNOW.  DON'T WORRY,  WE HAVE
CANCELLED YOUR OLD CARD.  GREAT. THANK
YOU.  IN ADDITION TO US  MONITORING
YOUR ACCOUNTS  FOR UNUSUAL ACTIVITY,
YOU COULD ALSO SET UP  FREE ACCOUNT
ALERTS.  OKAY.    [ Female Announcer
]    AT WELLS FARGO WE'RE WORKING
AROUND THE CLOCK    TO HELP PROTECT
YOUR MONEY    AND FINANCIAL    INFORMATION.
HERE'S YOUR  TEMPORARY CARD.  WELCOME
BACK.  HOW WAS LONDON?    [ Female
Announcer ]    WHEN PEOPLE TALK,
GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.
>> Shepard: DEADLY TORNADO
HERE IN OKLAHOMA HAS
SEPARATED MANY PETS FROM
THEIR OWNERS.
DURING AN EMOTIONAL
INTERVIEW WITH A CBS
STATION HERE, ONE WOMAN
DESCRIBED HOW THE CHAOS OF
THE STORM TORE HER DOG FROM
HER BUT WATCH WHAT HAPPENED
NEXT.
>> HI PUPPY.
>> OH, OH, OH BLESS YOUR
LITTLE BITTY HEART.
>> Shepard: THAT HAPPENED
LIVE ON TV.
AND BEFORE THEY KNEW IT THE
DOG WAS UP AND WALKING
AROUND.
SHE HAD NO IDEA THE DOG WAS
THERE THERE ARE OTHER
STORIES LIKE THIS ONE.
IN THIS PICTURE ONE MEMBER
OF THE ONE DAY RANCH PET
RESCUE SAVES A KITTEN FROM
DEBRIS IN A MOBILE HOME.
HERE A MAN IS ABLE TO GET A
ROPE AROUND THIS HORSE'S
NECK TO HELP IT OFF THE
WRECKAGE OF WHAT WAS ONCE A
DAY CARE.
AND ON THIS DAY IN 1881,
HUMANITARIAN CLARA BARTON
AND SOME FRIENDS FOUNDED
THE AMERICAN RED CROSS IN
WASHINGTON D.C.
CLARA BARTON HAD GAINED
FAME YEARS EARLIER AS A
NURSE ON THE FRONT LINES OF
THE CIVIL WAR.
WHEN THE FIGHTING ENDED
THE ANGEL OF THE
BATTLEFIELD DISCOVERED THE
SWISS BASED RED CROSS
NETWORK WHILE VISITING
EUROPE.
BACK IN THE STATES SHE
STARTED A U.S. BRANCH AND
LED ITS FIRST DISASTER
RELIEF PROGRAMS NOW OF
COURSE THE RED CROSS
RESPONDS TO ROUGHLY 70,000
DIFFERENT DISASTERS EACH
YEAR WITH THE HELP OF
GENEROUS CONTRIBUTIONS OF
TIME BLOOD AND MONEY FROM
THE AMERICAN PUBLIC.
BUT ITS MISSION TO SUPPORT
THOSE IN NEED BEGAN 132
YEARS AGO TODAY TODAY THAT
MISSION CONTINUES AS THE
RED CROSS WORKS TO HELP
VICTIMS IN THE HEARTLAND.
IF YOU WOULD LIKE TO
DONATE.
CAN YOU CALL THE RED CROSS
AT 1-800-RED-CROSS.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS
FOR THIS TUESDAY MAY THE
21st 2013.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH LIVE IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
OKLAHOMA STRONG.
O'REILLY IS UP RIGHT NOW.
>> Bill: THE O'REILLY
FACTOR IS ON.
TONIGHT:
>> HOW DID THIS HAPPEN?
>> MR. CHAIRMAN, I CAN'T
SAY THAT I KNOW THAT
ANSWER.
>> ONCE AGAIN THEY DON'T
KNOW.
THE FORMER CHIEF OF THE IRS
SAYS HE HAS NO IDEA WHY
CONSERVATIVES WERE
TARGETED.
THIS ON THE HEELS OF THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL SAYING HE
HAS NO IDEA WHY THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT IS SNOOPING
AROUND REPORTERS.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED THERE ABOUT
INTERACTION BETWEEN THE
A.P. AND THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT.
I WAS RECUSED FROM THE
CASE.
>> AND PRESIDENT OBAMA
SAYING HE HAS NO IDEA HOW
BENGHAZI GOT SO SCREWED UP.
>> WE WERE NOT CLEAR WHO
EXACTLY HAD CARRIED IT OUT
AND HOW IT OCCURRED AND
WHAT THE MOTIVATIONS WERE.
>> Bill: TONIGHT CHARLES
KRAUTHAMMER AND I WILL
ANALYZE THE SEE NO EVIL
STRATEGIES.
>> WE HAD TO PULL A CAR OUT