TRUMP.
WE'LL HAVE THAT AND ALL SORTS OF
NEW THINGS ON "THE DAILY BRIEFS"
TOMORROW.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> Shepard: IT'S 3:00 ON THE
EAST COAST.
NOON IN LAS VEGAS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS MEETING WITH
SOME OF THE HEROS OF THE
ATTACKS.
MEN AND WOMEN THAT STEPPED
FORWARD TO SAVE OTHERS.
AMONG THEM, POLICE OFFICERS.
NEWLY RELEASED VIDEO SHOWS WHAT
THEY WERE UP AGAINST.
KILLER'S GIRLFRIEND RETURNS TO
THE UNITED STATES.
DID SHE KNOW WHAT HE WAS
PLANNING?
HER SISTERS SAY NO WAY.
INVESTIGATORS ASK HER QUESTIONS.
WE'LL TAKE YOU TO VEGAS FOR A
LOOK AT THE CITY IN MOURNING AND
AN INVESTIGATION UNRELENTING.
LET'S GET TO IT.
FIRST FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK
THIS WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON,
PRESIDENT TRUMP ABOUT TO MEET
WITH HEROS OF THE LAS VEGAS
ATTACK INCLUDING THE FIRST
RESPONDERS AND ORDINARY PEOPLE
THAT RISKED THEIR LIVES TO SAVE
OTHERS.
WE'LL HAVE THAT LIVE WHEN IT
HAPPENS.
WE'RE EXPECTING IT IN 20
MINUTES.
THIS COMES AS WE GET A FIRST
HAND LOOK AT THE POLICE OFFICERS
THAT RISKED THEIR LIVES THAT
NIGHT.
LAS VEGAS POLICE RELEASED BODY
CAM FROM OFFICERS SHOWING THE
OFFICERS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
THE LOCATION OF THE SHOOTER AND
GET PEOPLE TO SAFETY AS BULLETS
RAIN DOWN FROM THAT HOTEL ROOM.
>> GET DOWN, GET DOWN!
GO THAT WAY.
GET OUT OF HERE.
THERE'S GUN SHOTS COMING FROM
OVER THERE.
GO THAT WAY.
>> GO THAT WAY, GO THAT WAY.
THEY'RE SHOOTING RIGHT AT US,
GUYS.
STAY DOWN.
>> WHERE IS IT AT?
>> IT'S AT THE MANDALAY BAY.
COMING OUT OF A WINDOW.
>> GO BACK, GO BACK.
GET BACK.
>> THERE'S MULTIPLE SHOTS COMING
UP THERE.
>> Shepard: BODY CAM FROM THE
RESPONDERS.
FBI AGENTS ARE INTERVIEWING THE
GUNMAN'S VIDEO RIGHT THIS MINUTE
THEY TELL US.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY'RE
CONFIDENT THEY WILL FIGURE OUT
WHY STEPHEN PADDOCK OPENED FIRE
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
DANLEY, THE GIRLFRIEND, ARRIVED
IN LOS ANGELES OVERNIGHT.
SHE WAS IN THE PHILIPPINES AT
THE TIME OF THE SHOOTING
ACCORDING TO AUTHORITIES.
THE SHERIFF SAYS SHE'S A PERSON
OF INTEREST, NOT A SUSPECT.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY WANT TO
FIND OUT WHETHER SHE KNEW WHAT
THE GUNMAN WAS PLANNING.
THE SHERIFF SAYS THE GUNMAN, THE
MURDERER, PLANNED THE MASSACRE
EXTENSIVELY.
STOCKPILING HE SAYS NEARLY TWO
DOZEN GUNS IN HIS HOTEL ROOM AT
MANDALAY BAY.
INVESTIGATORS SAY HE SET UP
CAMERAS ON A ROOM SERVICE CART
OUTSIDE THE DOOR SO HE COULD SEE
BOTH WAYS DOWN THE HALL AND
ANOTHER IN THE PEEP HOLE.
APPARENTLY TO WATCH FOR POLICE
OR SECURITY GUARDS.
THE SHERIFF SAYS THE GUNMAN
KILLED HIMSELF AS SWAT TEAMS
APPROACHED.
JOHN ROBERTS IS LIVE IN
LAS VEGAS ON THE TRIP WITH THE
PRESIDENT OUTSIDE MANDALAY BAY
THIS AFTERNOON.
JOHN?
>> SHEP, GOOD MORNING TO YOU.
THE PRESIDENT JUST WRAPPED UP A
MEETING WITH SOME VICTIMS.
SOME WITH GRIEVOUS INJURIES AND
FAMILY MEMBERS, MEMBERS OF THE
TRAUMA TEAM, THE SURGEONS, O.R.
NURSES AND ALL THOSE THAT HELPED
TO SAVE LIVES.
HE SAID HE WAS OVERWHELMED BY
WHAT HE SAW THERE.
THE PRESIDENT REALLY WANTED TO
COME HERE.
MONDAY WHEN ANNOUNCED THAT HE
WAS GOING TO COME, SITTING DOWN
AND TALKING WITH THE THAI PRIME
MINISTER, NOBODY FROM HIS STAFF
NEW THE PRESIDENT PLANNED TO
COME WEDNESDAY.
HE SAID I'M GOING TO BE HERE
WEDNESDAY AND HERE HE IS.
HE MAY BE COMING AGAIN AS WELL
DEPENDING HOW THINGS PROGRESS
WITH THE INVESTIGATION.
IF THERE'S A MEMORIAL SERVICE
THIS WEEKEND TO ATTEND, THE
WHITE HOUSE IS LOOKING TO ALL OF
THAT.
BACK TO THE UNIVERSITY MEDICAL
CENTER AND THE TOUR THE
PRESIDENT TOOK.
LET'S LISTEN TO WHAT HE SAID
WHEN HE MET WITH THE DOCTORSES
AND MEETING THE PERSONNEL IN THE
HOSPITAL.
>> SOME OF THE MOST AMAZING
PEOPLE.
WE MET PATIENTS THAT WERE
ABSOLUTELY TERRIBLY WOUNDED AND
THE DOCTORS, THE NURSES, ALL OF
THE PEOPLE OF THE HOSPITAL HAVE
DONE A JOB THAT IS
UNDESCRIBABLE.
THEY WERE FULL THE NIGHT THAT IT
HAPPENED BEFORE IT HAPPENED.
AND THEY FOUND ROOM FOR MANY
PEOPLE.
HOW MANY PEOPLE CAME IN, DOCTOR?
>> WE HAD 100 COME IN AND WE
ADMITTED 50.
>> WHAT I SAW TODAY IS AN
INCREDIBLE TRIBUTE TO
PROFESSIONALISM.
WHAT THEY HAVE DONE IS
INCREDIBLE.
YOU NEVER WANT TO SEE IT AGAIN.
>> JUST REMARKABLE STORIES,
SHEP, OF HOW EVERYBODY IN THIS
AREA WHO WAS INVOLVED WITH THE
MEDICAL COMMUNITY PITCHED IN.
THEIR STORIES OF PEDIATRIC
SURGEONS OPERATING ON ADULTING,
OB-GYNS THAT TYPICALLY ARE NOT
IN THE TRAUMA CENTER MANNING THE
TABLES.
SO MANY PEOPLE COMING IN, SHEP,
THAT IT WAS JUST KIND OF FULL TO
OVERFLOWING.
EVERYBODY DID AN AMAZING JOB.
THE PRESIDENT WANTED TO PAY
TRIBUTE TO THAT.
FROM HERE, THE PRESIDENT WANTS
TO MEET THE HEROS OF THE EVENT
THAT WERE AT THE IT IS ON SUNDAY
NIGHT.
LAW ENFORCEMENT THAT RAN INTO
THE BULLETS TO PIN DOWN THE
SHOOTNER THE 32nd FLOOR OF THE
MANDALAY BAY BEHIND ME AND MANY
CIVILIANS, SOME OF WHO GAVE
THEIR LIVES TO PROTECT OTHER
PEOPLE AND STORIES OF PEOPLE
GRABBING PICKUPS OFF OF THE
STREETS, FILLING THE BEDS WITH
THE WOUNDED AND TAKING THEM TO
THE HOSPITAL.
A LOT OF PEOPLE THE PRESIDENT
WANTS TO THANK.
>> Shepard: AND JOHN, HE GOT A
QUESTION ABOUT GUN CONTROL AFTER
DOING THAT.
>> HE DID.
THE PRESIDENT HAS RECEIVED A
NUMBER OF QUESTIONS ABOUT GUN
CONTROL.
HE GOT A COUPLE FROM YESTERDAY.
THE PRESIDENT DEFERRING THE TALK
OF THE DISCUSSION OF GUN CONTROL
FOR THE MOMENT.
HE SAID THERE WILL BE TIME FOR
THAT.
NOT NOW.
I ASKED HIM ABOUT THE SILENCER
BILL THAT APPEARED TO BE
SHELVED.
HE SAID WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT
LATER.
A LOT OF TALK FOR THE NEED FOR
MORE GUN CONTROL.
DEMOCRATS ARE PUSHING THAT.
SOME MEMBERS OF CONGRESS ON THE
REPUBLICAN SIDE THAT ARE SAYING,
WE DON'T NEED MORE GUN CONTROL
MEASURES.
THEY'RE LOOKING AT THE SO-CALLED
BUMP OR SLIDE STOCKS THAT THE
SHOOTER HAD INSTALLED ON A FEW
RIFLES, MIGHT AS BE AS MANY AS
12, WHICH ALLOWS YOU TO FIRE A
SEMIAUTOMATIC RIFLE AT ALMOST
AUTOMATIC SPEED.
THESE WERE THINGS APPROVED IN
2010 BY THE ATF DURING THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION.
NOW YOU HAVE SENATOR JOHN CORNYN
SAYING MAYBE WE NEED TO LOOK AT
BANNING THESE.
NEWT GINGRICH WAS ON THE AIR,
MAYBE YOU LUMP THEM IN WITH THE
1934 LAW THAT BANS AUTOMATIC
WEAPONS BY CIVILIANS.
TOM COLE ON ANOTHER NETWORK
SAID, THIS.
>> NO QUESTION WE OUGHT TO LOOK
INTO THAT.
AUTOMATIC WEAPONSES -- WHEN I
SAW THE CLIPS AND HEARD THE
FIRE, I ASSUMED HE HAD AN
AUTOMATIC WEAPON.
I DIDN'T KNOW THAT THERE WAS
TECHNOLOGY CAPABLE THAT CHEAPLY
OF TRANSFORMING A SEMIAUTOMATIC
INTO AN AUTOMATIC WEAPON.
YEAH, I DON'T THINK THERE'S ANY
QUESTION WE OUGHT TO LOOK AT
THAT.
>> EVEN REPUBLICANS ARE
DESCRIBING THIS AS A LOOP HOLE,
ONE THAT THEY CAN CLOSE QUICKLY.
DEMOCRATS, PEOPLE LIKE JOHN
LEWIS OUT THERE ON THE STEPS OF
THE CAPITOL SAYING HOW MANY MORE
PEOPLE ARE GOING TO BE KILLED
BEFORE WE GET MORE GUN CONTROL
MEASURES?
THERE'S DEFINITELY GOING TO BE A
CLASH IN CONGRESS OVER HOW FAR
TO GO IN THE WAKE OF THIS
INCIDENTS.
AGAIN, SHEP, THE PRESIDENT
SAYING LET'S MOURN THE DEAD,
TEND TO THE BOUNDED AND THEN
LET'S HAVE THE POLITICAL
DISCUSSION, SHEP.
>> Shepard: JOHN ROBERTS LIVE IN
MANDALAY BAY.
THANK YOU.
THE SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON IS NOT DENYING THAT HE
CALLED PRESIDENT TRUMP A
BLANKING MORON.
THE SECRETARY IS INSISTING THAT
HE NEVER THREATENED TO QUIT.
HE'S RESPONDING TO AN NBC NEWS
REPORT THAT MIKE PENCE HAD TO
CONVINCE SECRETARY TILLERSON NOT
TO STEP DOWN.
>> THE VICE PRESIDENT HAS NEVER
HAD TO PERSUADE ME TO REMAIN THE
SECRETARY OF STATE BECAUSE I
HAVE NEVER CONSIDERED LEAVING
THIS POST.
I'M NEW TO WASHINGTON.
I HAVE LEARNED THAT THERE'S SOME
THAT TRY TO SOW DISSENSION TO
ADVANCE THEIR OWN AGENDA BY
TEARING OTHERS APART AND AN
UNDERSTOOD TO UNDERMINE THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN AGENDA.
I DO NOT AND I WILL NOT OPERATE
THAT WAY.
>> WHEN A REPORTER ASKED
SPECIFICALLY WHETHER SECRETARY
TILLERSON CALLED THE PRESIDENT A
MORON, HE RESPONDED THAT HE
WASN'T GOING TO DEAL WITH PETTY
STUFF LIKE THAT.
RICH EDSON IS AT THE STATE
DEPARTMENT.
HEATH
HEATHER NAUERT HAS COME FORWARD
TO DENY THAT CLAIM.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE DAILY PRESS BRIEFING JUST
WRAPPED UP.
HEATHER DENIED THAT THE
SECRETARY OF STATE CALLED THE
PRESIDENT A MORON.
>> THE SECRETARY DOES NOT USE
THAT TYPE OF LANGUAGE.
THE SECRETARY DID NOT USE THAT
TYPE OF LANGUAGE TO SPEAK ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
HE DOES NOT USE THAT LANGUAGE TO
SPEAK ABOUT ANYONE.
I HOPE THAT THAT CLARIFIES IT.
>> HE NEVER SAID THAT?
>> HE DID NOT SAY THAT.
>> Shepard: SO THERE YOU HAVE
IT.
THE PRESIDENT NOW LIVE WITH
FIRST RESPONDERS.
WE DIDN'T EXPECT THIS.
LET'S LISTEN LIVE.
>> I'VE ALWAYS KNOWN YOU GUYS
ARE GOOD BUT YOU PROVED IT.
HE'S A SICK, DEMENTED MAN.
HAVE THEY FOUND OUT ANYTHING
ELSE?
>> STILL A LITTLE BIT SOON.
WE HAVE A COUPLE OF GOOD LEADS.
WE'RE WORKING OUR WAY THROUGH
THAT.
WE'RE GOING TO GET THE ANSWERS.
>> MIGHT BE SOMEBODY THERE.
THE WIRES ARE SCREWED UP.
MIGHT BE SOMETHING THERE.
I'M GOING TO SAY A FEW WORDS TO
YOUR GROUP.
I WANTED TO SAY HELLO AND
CONGRATULATE YOU.
I WAS A FAN BEFORE THIS.
YOU KNOW THAT.
EVERYONE IN THIS ROOM KNOWS
THAT.
A BIG FAN BEFORE THIS.
YOU CAN BE MORE OF A FAN, I'M
MORE OF A FAN NOW.
YOU SHOWED THE WORLD AROUND THE
WORLD WAS WATCHING AND YOU
SHOWED WHAT PROFESSIONALISM IS
ALL ABOUT.
SOMETHING LIKE THAT CAN TAKE
PLACE FOR HOURS AND HOURS AND
HOURS.
YOU CAN'T FIGURE IT OUT.
YOU SHOULD BE VERY PROUD.
>> A MATTER OF IDENTIFICATION,
OFFICER HANCOCK AT THE END TO
YOUR RIGHT THERE, HE WAS THE
FIRST SWAT OFFICER TO ENGAGE THE
INDIVIDUAL.
OFFICER DRISCOLL THERE, THE K-9
OFFICER ASSISTED.
OFFICER MORRIS WAS ONE OF THE
TWO I DESCRIBED PARTNERED WITH
THE SECURITY GUARDS.
>> THEY DID A GOOD JOB.
YOU DID A GOOD JOB.
HIS OPTION WOULD HAVE BEEN TO DO
IT HIMSELF.
IF IT DOESN'T WORK, YOU WOULDN'T
HAVE HAD THE INFORMATION MAYBE,
RIGHT?
HE DID THE RIGHT THING?
>> HE DID.
WE RELIED ON THE INFORMATION.
>> THAT'S GREAT.
>> EVERYONE ELSE SEATED IN AND
BEHIND THE PRESS THERE WERE
INTEGRAL IN SAVING NUMEROUS
LIVES.
THE GENTLEMAN TO YOUR LEFT, THAT
FIREFIGHTER RIGHT THERE WAS OFF
DUTY WATCHING THE CONCERT AND
SAVED SEVERAL LIVES.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR YOU TO KNOW
THAT EVERY PERSON IN HERE WAS
INSTRUMENTAL IN LIFE SAVING
MEASURES.
THESE TWO YOUNG LADIES HERE ARE
DISPATCHERS.
PROBABLY THE MOST IMPORTANT
PEOPLE IN THE ROOM.
IF YOU EVER HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY
TO LISTEN TO THE RADIO TRAFFIC,
THESE TWO YOUNG LADIES ARE
AMAZING.
THERE WAS A THIRD YOUNG LADY.
SHE DECIDED TO GO TO COLLEGE.
>> Shepard: PARDON THE
INTERVENTION WHILE OUR FOX
TELEVISION STATIONS JOIN US.
GOOD AFTERNOON FROM FOX NEWS IN
NEW YORK, A LIVE LOOK WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS MEETING SOME
OF THE FIRST RESPONDERS, THE
HEROS OF THE ATTACK OUTSIDE THE
MANDALAY BAY AT THE COUNTRY
MUSIC FESTIVAL SUNDAY NIGHT.
LET'S LISTEN LIVE.
AND AS LUCK WOULD HAVE IT, THE
WHITE HOUSE POOL HAS WALKED OUT.
THE PRESIDENT SHARING
PLEASANTRIES AND THANKS WITH
FIRST RESPONDERS.
OUR AUDIENCE ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL
JUST A MOMENT AGO MET THE FIRST
POLICE OFFICERS CREDITED WITH
ENGAGING THE SUSPECT INSIDE THE
ROOM.
WE'VE HEARD THE 911 CALLS, THE
DIFFERENT POLICE RESPONDERS, THE
DISPATCH FROM POLICE
HEADQUARTE
HEADQUARTERS.
IT'S BEEN A VERY GOOD DAY FOR
THANK YOUS TO THE FIRST
RESPONDERS AND EVERYDAY FOLKS
THAT HELPED OUTSIDE THE LUXOR
AND MANDALAY BAY ON THE
LAS VEGAS STRIP.
WE'RE WAITING FOR THE PRESIDENT
TO APPEAR AGAIN IN JUST A
MOMENT.
THAT WAS SORT OF AN UNSCHEDULED
PHOTO OP, MEET AND GREET WITH
SOME OF THE FIRST RESPONDER
THERE'S.
YOU CAN SEE A LIVE LOOK NOW IN
LAS VEGAS AT POLICE HEADQUARTERS
WHERE THE PRESIDENT WILL BE
MEETING WITH -- AND THE FIRST
LADY TO MEET WITH FIRST
RESPONDERS AND HEROS OF THE
ATTACK IN JUST A MOMENT.
JOHN ROBERTS FOLLOWING ALONG
WITH THE PRESIDENT OUT IN
LAS VEGAS TODAY.
THEY HAVE MADE A REAL EFFORT,
JOHN, TO PUT THESE HEROS OF THIS
TRAGEDY FRONT AND CENTER AND
THESE MEET AND GREETS.
FOR THOSE JOINING US ON FOX
TELEVISION STATIONS, HE GAVE AN
INVITATION TO THOSE IN THE
HOSPITAL ROOMS, THE O.R.s.
IF YOU'RE EVER IN WASHINGTON
D.C., COME SEE ME AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU.
A CONCERTED EFFORT ON THE PART
OF THIS WHITE HOUSE.
GREAT TO SEE.
>> ALL THROUGH THE CAMPAIGN AND
AS PRESIDENT, SHEP, PRESIDENT
TRUMP REALLY WAS A CHAMPION OF
LAW ENFORCEMENT.
SO MANY CAMPAIGNED EVENTS ACROSS
THE COUNTRY, HE WOULD ALWAYS
HOLD THEM UP FOR PRAISE.
HE'S DONE THAT AGAIN AS
PRESIDENT.
ANY TIME HE GETS IN THE SAME
ROOM WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT OR
MILITARY FOR THAT MATTER, HE
ALWAYS HAS THE HIGHEST PRAISE.
I KNOW THAT HE WAS VERY TAKEN,
NOT ONLY WITH THE SCOPE AND THE
DEPTH OF THIS TRAGEDY AND THE
HORRIBLE FACT THAT SO MANY
PEOPLE WERE KILLED.
WHEN THERE WERE BULLETS RAINING
DOWN FROM THE WINDOWS BEHIND ME,
50, 75 AT A TIME BECAUSE HE HAD
BIG MAGAZINES, THE OFFICERS TOOK
COVER BUT MOVED TOWARD THE
DANGER.
THEY WERE BLOWING THE DOOR OPEN
WITHIN MINUTES TO GET INSIDE AND
CLEARLY HAD CORNERED THIS GUY,
THE SHOOTER.
HE TOOK HIS OWN LIFE WHEN HE
KNEW THEY WERE COMING IN THROUGH
THE DOOR.
THE FACT THAT AS YOU POINTED
OUT, SO MANY CIVILIANS DOVE ON
THEIR LOVED ONES OR SACRIFICED
THEIR OWN LIVES OR STOLE PICKUP
TRUCKS TO PUT PEOPLE IN THE BEDS
BECAUSE THE AMBULANCES WERE SO
OVERWHELMED.
WHEN THEY GOT TO THE HOSPITALS,
THE DOCTORS AND NURSES ON STAFF
AND ALL OF THE MEDICAL STAFF
FROM ACROSS THE VALLEY HERE THAT
CAME IN TO THE TRAUMA CENTERS
AND THE HOSPITALS EVEN THOUGH
THEY WERE OFF DUTY.
JUST DIDN'T EVEN NEED TO PICK UP
THE PHONE.
RAN IN TO HELP WHEN THE SCOPE
BECAME CLEAR.
THE PRESIDENT WANTED TO TAKE
TIME TO RECOGNIZE ALL OF THOSE
PEOPLE.
HE SAYS THAT THEY HAVE DONE AN
INCREDIBLE SERVICE FOR THEIR
COMMUNITY.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT HE WANTS TO
HOLD UP AS AN EXAMPLE NOT ONLY
TO THE REST OF THE COUNTRY BUT
THE WORLD AS WELL TO SAY THIS IS
HOW WE RESPOND TO TRAGEDY IN
AMERICA AND HOPEFULLY TAKE STEPS
TO MAKE SURE SOMETHING LIKE THIS
NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN.
THAT'S WHERE YOU'RE GOING TO GET
INTO A REAL TUSSLE OF A DEBATE
IN CAPITOL HILL.
THERE'S GOING TO BE PEOPLE ON
ONE SAID THAT SAY WE NEED MORE
GUN CONTROL MEASURES, PEOPLE ON
THE OTHER SIDE THAT SAYS THERE'S
SOME THINGS THAT WE CAN DO ABOUT
THESE SO-CALLED PUMP STOCKS OR
SLIDE STOCKS THAT ALLOW
SEMIAUTOMATIC WEAPONS TO BE
FIRED AT A HIGH RATE OR OTHER
MEASURES TO BE TAKEN TO STOP
PEOPLE FROM CONVERTING THESE WE
POPS INTO A HIGH RATE OF FIRE.
WE DON'T NEED TO GO FURTHER THAN
THAT.
WE NEED TO ENFORCE EXISTING
LAWS.
EVERYTHING THAT THIS FELLOW
SEEMED TO DO SHORT OF WHAT HE
DID SUNDAY NIGHT WAS WITHIN THE
LETTER OF THE LAW.
IT'S A DILEMMA HOW THAT DEBATE
WILL GO FORWARD AS TO WHAT LAW
COULD BE CRAFTED TO STOP WHAT
HAPPENED SUNDAY NIGHT.
ALL OF THIS STUFF IS
RETROSPECTIVE AS OPPOSED TO
PROSPECTIVE.
YOU'RE ALWAYS REACTING TO THE
LAST INCIDENT.
IT'S DIFFICULT AND A HEATED
DEBATE GOING FORWARD, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JOHN.
LET'S GO TO A.B. STODDARD.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU, SHEP.
>> Shepard: THIS DEBATE WILL
COME, THOSE ON THE GUN CONTROL
SIDE, ARE PUSHING FOR IT TODAY.
THEIR ARGUMENT IS THERE'S NO
TIME LIKE ON THE HEELS OF A
TRAGEDY TO KEEP ANOTHER TRAGEDY
FROM HAPPENING.
THAT'S THEIR POSITION.
>> THEY'RE MAKING AN ARGUMENT
THAT IS REASONABLE THAT THE TIME
TO TALK ABOUT THESE THINGS IS
WHEN THEY HAPPEN AND VICTIMS
FAMILIES ARE GRIEVING AND WANT
SOMETHING DONE ABOUT IT.
IF THIS IS A TERRORIST ATTACK,
WE TALK ABOUT WAYS TO KEEP THE
HOMELAND SAFE FROM TERRORISTS.
SO GUN CONTROL ADVOCATES TALK
ABOUT THE NEED TO CLOSE THE GUN
SHOW LOOP HOLE AND LOOK AT THE
ACCESSORIES LIKE THE BUMP STOP
MECHANISM TO MAKE A
SEMIAUTOMATIC TO AN AUTOMATIC
WEAPON.
I THINK IT'S INTERESTING IN THIS
INCREDIBLY POLARIZED TIME, SHEP,
WITH THIS DEBATE THAT NEVER GOES
ANYWHERE, THAT THERE'S SOME
REPUBLICANS WILLING TO LOOK
AT -- YOU PLAYED CLIPS FROM TOM
COLE, THE REPUBLICAN, REPORTS
THAT SENATOR JOHN CORNYN, THE
NUMBER 2 IN LEADERSHIP ON THE
SENATE SIDE IS INTERESTED.
I READ THAT CONGRESSMAN BILL
FLORES FROM TEXAS IS INTERESTED
IN IT.
SO THERE MIGHT BE SOME
INCREMENTAL PATH FORWARD TO SOME
KIND OF DISCUSSION ABOUT HAVING
TO DO THIS KIND OF WEAPONRY
WHERE 800 ROUNDS CAN GO OFF IN A
MINUTE AND KILL SO MANY
PEOPLING.
GENERALLY SPEAKING, I'LL BE
SURPRISED IF IT DOES BECAUSE
THEY BREAK DOWN SO QUICKLY IN
ALL OF THIS POLARIZING AND ALL
OF THE DIFFERENCES AND IF DEBATE
GOES NOWHERE BECAUSE OF THE
VOTES AND THE WAY THEY'RE SET UP
IN CONGRESS NOW.
>> Shepard: ALL RIGHT, A.B.
STODDARD LIVE FROM WASHINGTON.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
WE'RE WATCHING ANOTHER LIVE
EVENT AS WELL.
THE PRESIDENT ABOUT TO COME INTO
THIS ROOM WE'RE TOLD TO MEET
WITH ANOTHER SET OF FIRST
RESPONDERS.
THIS IS THE THIRD SET WE'VE SEEN
ON CAMERA.
FOLKS SITTING AROUND, WAITING TO
MEET THE PRESIDENT,
COMMANDER-IN-CHIEF AS HE MAKES
THE ROUNDS THERE IN LAS VEGAS.
WE'LL HAVE COVERAGE OF THAT ON
FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
THOSE OF YOU WATCHING ON FOX
TELEVISION STATIONS ACROSS THE
NATION, MUCH MORE ON THIS A
LITTLE LATER ON YOUR LOCAL NEWS.
IT CONTINUES NOW ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL ON SATELLITE AND CABLE.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
FOX NEWS, NEW YORK.
AS WE CONTINUE HERE ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL, WE'RE WAITING FOR THESE
FIRST RESPONDERS TO MEET WITH
THE PRESIDENT AND WE'LL HAVE
THAT LIVE FOR YOU IN JUST A
MOMENT.
TO MEET THE HEROS OF LAS VEGAS
THIS HELPED SAVE LIVES DURING
THE SHOOTING.
FIRST, THE LATEST FROM THE
INVESTIGATORS ON SCENE AND THE
PICTURES NOW THAT SHOW THE
INSIDE OF THE MURDER'S SWEET.
THAT'S COMING UP ON THE FOX NEWS
DECK THIS AFTERNOON.
I was always
"the girl with psoriasis."
People don't stare anymore.
I never joined in.
That wasn't fair to any of us.
I was covered.
I tried lots of things
over the years.
But I didn't give up.
I kept on fighting.
I found something that worked.
That still works.
Now?
SEE ME.
I found clear skin that lasts.
See if COSENTYX could make a
difference for you-
COSENTYX is proven to help
people with moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis...
...find clear skin that
can last.
Don't use if you're allergic
to COSENTYX.
Before starting COSENTYX,
you should be checked
for tuberculosis.
An increased risk of infections
and lowered ability
to fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor if you have an
infection or symptoms.
Or if you have received a
vaccine or plan to.
If you have inflammatory
bowel disease,
tell your doctor if symptoms
develop or worsen.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
SEE ME
to know...
...clear skin can last.
Don't hold back...
...ask your dermatologist if
COSENTYX can help you
find clear skin that lasts.
[He has a new business teaching
lessons.
Rodney wanted to know how his
business was doing...
...so he got QuickBooks.
It organizes all his accounts,
so he can see his bottom line.
Ahhh...that's a profit.
Know where you stand instantly.
Visit QuickBooks-dot-com.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
THE FIRST LADY MELANIA TRUMP IN
LAS VEGAS MEETING WITH THE HEROS
OF THE MASSACRE AND FIRST
RESPONDERS AND ORDINARY PEOPLE
THAT HELPED AFTER THE SHOOTING
STARTED.
EARLIER, THE PRESIDENT AND THE
FIRST LADY MET VICTIMS AND MED
CAT WORKERS AT A HOSPITAL IN
LAS VEGAS.
LET'S LISTEN.
WE'LL HAVE -- WELL, I THOUGHT WE
WOULD LISTEN TO SOUND FROM THAT
TIME.
APPARENTLY NOT.
WHEN THIS BEGINS, WE'LL TAKE YOU
THERE.
THE LAS VEGAS GUNMAN ENCOURAGED
HIS GIRLFRIEND, MARILOU DANLEY,
TO LEAVE THE COUNTRY FOR THE
MASSACRE.
THAT'S WHAT DANLEY'S SISTER TOLD
A TV SISTER IN AUSTRALIA.
HE SENT HER AWAY AT ONE POINT.
THEY SAY THE MURDERER BROUGHT
DANLEY A PLANE TICKET TO THE
PHILIPPINES SO SHE WOULDN'T GET
IN THE WAY OF HIS PLANS.
WE'RE NOT SURE HOW THEY KNOW
THAT.
THAT'S WHAT THEY TELL US.
IN THE INTERVIEW, THEIR FACES
ARE BLURRED TO PROTECT THEIR
IDENTITIES.
HERE, LOOK.
>> I KNOW THAT SHE DOESN'T KNOW
ANYTHING AS WELL LIKE US.
SHE WAS SENT AWAY.
SHE WAS SENT AWAY SO THAT SHE
WOULD NOT BE THERE.
>> Shepard: WE DON'T KNOW IF
THEY KNOW THAT OR IF SHE'S
SPECULATING ON THAT MATTER.
INVESTIGATORS QUESTIONING DANLEY
RIGHT NOW WE'RE TOLD THE FBI
HEADQUARTERS IN LOS ANGELES SAY
THEY HOPE SHE CAN GIVE THEM ANY
CLUES ABOUT WHAT DROVE PADDOCK
TO COMMIT MASS MURDER.
TRACE GALLAGHER ON THE CASE IN
LAS VEGAS.
LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
SHOOTER'S ARSENAL TODAY, TRACE.
>> THEY RECOVERED SOME 47
WEAPONS FROM THREE LOCATIONS.
ONE FROM THE MANDALAY BAY BEHIND
ME AND HIS TWO HOMES, ONE IN
MESQUITE, NEVADA AND THE OTHER
ONE IN RENO, NEVADA.
THOSE GUNS WORTH BETWEEN
$100,000 AND $110,000.
THE SEMIAUTOMATICS ARE WORTH
BETWEEN $1,500 AND $3,000.
THESE PICTURES ARE FROM THE
DAILY MAIL.
THEY WERE PUT ON THE FLOOR OF
THE HOTEL SWEEP IN MANDALAY BAY.
WE SHOULD KNOW THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK HAS BEEN COLLECTING GUNS
FOR YEARS.
BUT IN THE PAST YEAR ALONE, HE
HAS AMASSED SOME 30-PLUS
WEAPONS, A GUN SHOP OWNER IN
MESQUITE WHERE HE HAD A HOME
SAID THAT ON SEPTEMBER 28th,
PADDOCK BOUGHT A WEAPON AND THAT
IS THE SAME DAY THAT HE CHECKED
IN TO THE MANDALAY BAY HOTEL.
LISTEN TO THE GUN SHOP OWNER.
>> I WAS ILL.
MADE ME ILL TO THINK THAT WE HAD
INTERACTED WITH HIM AND HE
COMMITTED A TRAGEDY.
>> HE WENT ON THE SAY THAT HE
DID NOT SELL STEPHEN PADDOCK ANY
AMMUNITION OR ANY OF THOSE BUMP
STOCKS WE'VE TALKED ABOUT ALL
DAY LONG.
THAT'S WHAT KIND OF MAKES THE
TRIGGER TURN INTO AUTOMATICALLY
ENGAGED WEAPON, SHEP.
HE ALSO POINTS OUT AND WE SHOULD
POINT THIS OUT, THE REASON THE
BUMP STOPS ARE LEGAL IN NEVADA
IS BECAUSE THEY DON'T PHYSICALLY
ALTER THE WEAPON.
IT'S TAKEN ON AND TAKEN OFF.
SO IT'S LEGAL NOW.
>> Shepard: WHAT ELSE ARE WE
LEARNING FROM INVESTIGATORS
ABOUT THE GIRLFRIEND?
>> WE KNOW THAT MARILOU DANLEY
IS IN HER THIRD HOUR OF
QUESTIONING IN LOS ANGELES.
SHE FLEW IN TO LOS ANGELES FROM
THE PHILIPPINES LAST NIGHT.
THEY CLEARLY WANT INFORMATION
ABOUT STEPHEN PADDOCK'S MENTAL
STATE, HIS RELIGIOUS BELIEFS,
HIS POLITICAL AFFILIATIONS AND
ANYTHING THAT COULD LEAD THEM TO
A POSSIBLE MOTIVE.
THE BIG TICKET ITEM FOR A LOT OF
INVESTIGATORS WHAT SHE KNEW
ABOUT THIS ARSENAL OF WEAPONS
AND HIS INTENT.
REMEMBER, THEY FOUND DOZENS AND
DOZENS OF WEAPONS INSIDE THE
HOMES THAT SHE LIVED IN WITH HIM
ALONG WITH EXPLOSIVES AND
SUITCASES OF AMMUNITION.
THEY WOULD LIKE TO FIND OUT WHAT
SHE KNEW ABOUT THAT.
HER FAMILY SAYS THAT THE REASON
HE SENT HER TO THE PHILIPPINES
IS BECAUSE HE WAS AFRAID THAT
SHE WOULD STOP HIM FROM COMMITS
THIS CRIME.
LISTEN TO THE FAMILY AGAIN.
>> NOBODY CAN PUT IT TOGETHER
EXCEPT MARILOU.
ONLY MARILOU CAN MAYBE HELP.
>> INVESTIGATORS ARE INTERESTED
IN THE $100,000 THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK SENT TO PHILIPPINES IN
RECENT WEEKS.
THE SPIC YOULATION IS THAT HE
SENT IT TO HER BECAUSE HE KNEW
AS SOON AS HE COMMITTED THE
CRIME THAT ALL OF HIS ASSETS
WOULD BE LOCKED DOWN POSSIBLY
FOREVER AND SHE WOULDN'T GET ANY
KIND OF MONEY OUT OF THAT AT
ALL.
WE SHOULD KNOW THIS FBI
INTERVIEW IN LOS ANGELES COULD
GO FOR SEVERAL MORE HOURS.
THERE'S A NEWS CONFERENCE COMING
UP.
WE HOPE TO GET MORE INFORMATION
ABOUT WHAT THEY'RE GLEANING FROM
THE INTERVIEW IN THE NEXT HOUR
OR SO.
>> Shepard: WE'LL CHECK IN FOR
YOU ON THAT.
TRACE, THANKS VERY MUCH.
COMING UP HERE, ANDREW
NAPOLITANO, THE JUDGE, ON WHERE
THE INVESTIGATION GOES FROM HERE
AND WHAT HAPPENS IN THE
SHOOTER'S GIRLFRIEND STOPS
COOPERATING WITH INVESTIGATORS?
THAT AND WE'RE WAITING FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO COME IN AND
MEET WITH FIRST RESPONDERS,
POLICE OFFICERS AND FIREFIGHTERS
THAT WILL MEET WITH HIM SHORTLY.
WE'LL BE THERE LIVE FOR THAT AS
THE NEWS ROLLS ON ON THIS
WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON.
RLY... OR T.
OR MAKE ME FEEL LIKE
I'M NOT REALLY "THERE."
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-234-2424.
It's OK
that everybody
ignores me
when I drive.
It's fine, 'cause I get
a Safe Driving Bonus Check
every six months
I'm accident-free.
And I don't share it
with Mom. Right, Mom?
Right.
Safe Driving Bonus Checks,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH A FOX
REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
IN SPAIN, LAWMAKERS IN THE
NORTHEASTERN REGION OF CATALONIA
ARE THREATENING TO BREAKAWAY
FROM THE COUNTRY NEXT WEEK.
THOUSANDS FILL THE STREETS IN
BARCELONA TO PRO TEST A RECENT
POLICE CRACKDOWN THAT INJURED
HUNDREDS.
TWO WEEKS AFTER A MASSIVE
EARTHQUAKE IN MEXICO, SEARCH
TEAMS HAVE RECOVERED THE LAST
KNOWN BODY.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM THE MAYOR
OF MEXICO CITY AS RESEARCHERS
DUG THROUGH A COLLAPSED OFFICE
BUILDING.
OFFICIALS SAY 369 PEOPLE HAVE
DIED AFTER THE 7.1 MAGNITUDE
QUAKE.
AND E. COLI AND BACTERIA HAVE
BEEN FOUND AT A SWIMMING VENUE
FOR THE SUMMER OLYMPICS IN
TOKYO.
ORGANIZERS SAY WATER TESTING
SHOWED E. COLI LEVELS 20 TIMES
HIGHER THAN THE LIMITS.
ORGANIZERS HAVE PROMISED TO
IMPROVE THE WATER QUALITY.
THE NEWSES CONTINUES WITH
SHEPARD SMITH AFTER THIS.
>> Shepard: ACTUALLY, A LITTLE
BREAKING NEWS HERE.
WE MENTIONED THE PRESIDENT WAS
MEETING WITH FIRST RESPONDERS IN
LAS VEGAS.
WE'RE WAITING FOR HIM TO WALK IN
THE ROOM.
HE'S DONE SO.
NOTICE WE'RE USING AN INTERNET
CONNECTION HERE, THE WHITE HOUSE
POOL IS, BECAUSE OF WHERE IT IS.
IT'S A LITTLE GLITCHY.
IT TENDS TO CLEAR UP.
WE WANT YOU TO HEAR WHAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS TO SAY.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> THIS IS WHERE WE DO ALL THE
OPERATIONAL DECISIONS IN THE
AREA.
ALL INVESTIGATIVE LEADS,
EVERYTHING THAT YOU CAN IMAGINE
FUNNELS THROUGH HERE.
THIS IS WHERE -- ACTUALLY,
JOINING FORCES.
ALL OF THE DEPARTMENT OF PUBLIC
SAFETY REPRESENTATION HERE ALONG
WITH EMERGENCY MANAGERS AND
HOSPITAL SYSTEMS, THE FIRST
RESPONDER MEDICAL SYSTEMS AND
EVERYTHING THAT YOU CAN IMAGINE.
SO WE CAN SPEAK WITH ONE VOICE.
THAT'S THE IMPORTANT PIECE.
SO A LOT OF THESE FOLKS ARE NOT
SUPPOSED TO BE IN HERE BUT
YOU'RE HERE.
SO THESE ARE ALL THE PEOPLE THAT
ARE INSTRUMENTAL IN THE SUCCESS
OF OUR CRITICAL JOB.
THEY'RE ALL PART OF THE SUCCESS
FOR THE CONTINUANCE OF THE
INVESTIGATION.
IT'S IMPORTANT FOR YOU TO SEE
WHAT YOUR LEADERSHIP IS
PROVIDING YOU.
>> I CAN TELL YOU ON BEHALF OF
OUR COUNTRY, OUR GREAT, GREAT
COUNTRY, WE WANT TO THANK YOU.
YOU HAVE BEEN A REAL
INSPIRATION.
THIS IS A ROUGH TIME, BUT IF YOU
DIDN'T GET UP THERE SO QUICKLY,
COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE A LOT
WORSE.
WE JUST WANT TO THANK YOU.
THE WHOLE WORLD IS WATCHING.
THEY'VE SEEN PROFESSIONALISM
LIKE YOU RARELY SEE.
I WANT TO THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
I APPRECIATE IT VERY MUCH.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> Shepard: THIS IS A POOL
CAMERA.
THE WHITE HOUSE POOL WHICH
FOLLOWS THE PRESIDENT EVERYWHERE
HE GOES.
EACH OF THE NETWORKS AND THE
WHITE HOUSE POOL TAKES A DAY AND
TODAY THE POOL IS ONE OF THE SIX
OR SEVEN NETWORKS, SIX NETWORKS
THAT WERE PART OF THE WHITE
HOUSE POOL.
THEY'RE JUST FOLLOWING.
OH, LET'S LISTEN AS LONG AS HE'S
SAYING HELLO.
WE'LL GET THE WHITE HOUSE POOL
OUT OF THE ROOM ON THE
INSTRUCTIONS OF THE PRESS
SECRETARY.
JOHN ROBERTS FAMILIAR WITH THIS.
IN A COUPLE MOMENTS, HE'S GOING
TO A BIT MORE FORMAL SETTINGS
WHERE HE WILL MEET WITH POLICE
CHIEFS AND OTHERS.
>> YES, HE WILL BE MAKING BRIEF
REMARKS.
IT'S A FIVE NETWORK POOL.
IT'S UNDERSTAND, CNN, ABC AND
CBS AND US.
WE WERE HOPING HE WOULD COME
BACK IN TO TALK WITH US, GIVE US
THOUGHTS ABOUT TODAY AND MAYBE
TALK ABOUT OTHER NEWS OF THE DAY
AND THE ISSUES SWIRLING AROUND
THIS INCREASINGLY LOUD VOICES ON
CAPITOL HILL.
BUT HE HAD A LOT OF COMPANY WITH
HIM ON BOARD AIR FORCE ONE.
KEVIN McCARTHY WAS WITH HIM,
SENATOR HELLER AND HIS WIFE,
MELANIA WAS THERE WITH HIM.
SO THE PRESIDENT STAYED IN THE
FORWARD CABIN.
YOU CAN SEE THE BREAK-UP.
IT'S A UNIT THAT OPERATES ON
CELL SERVICE.
HOOKS IN TO A DIFFERENT OF CELL
NODES.
IF YOU'RE OUTSIDE, YOU GET
PRETTY GOOD RECEPTION.
SOMETIMES INSIDE, YOU LOSE
CONNECTIVITY AND THE PICTURE
GOES FUZZY LIKE THAT.
IT'S A WAY TO BRING YOU
IMMEDIATE PICTURES FROM
SOMETHING THAT NORMALLY WE
WOULDN'T HAVE ACCESS TOO.
LATER ON WHEN WE GET THE
FEEDBACK OVER THE SATELLITE,
YOU'LL SEE THE PICTURES IN THE
ENTIRETY AND CLARITY.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO MAKE
SPECIAL MENTION, SHEP, I'M TOLD
BY SARAH HUCKABEE SANDERS WHO
SAW IT ON THE WAY HERE BEFORE WE
LANDED, WANTS TO MAKE SPECIAL
MENTION OF THE CIVILIANS WHO AT
RISK TO THEIR OWN LIVES AND SOME
OF THEM DID DIE DOING THIS,
PROTECTED OTHER PEOPLE,
PROTECTED LOVED ONES, TRIED TO
GET PEOPLE OUT OF THE AREA, DID
WHATEVER THEY COULD TO GET
PEOPLE TO THE HOSPITALS.
THESE ARE CITIZEN HEROS, SHEP
THAT THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO
HONOR.
WE'LL SEE THEM IN A COUPLE
MINUTES.
HE'S TOURING THE COMMAND CENTER
THERE WITH THE SHERIFF WHO HAS
DONE AMAZING WORK IN THE WAKE OF
THIS HORRIBLE TRAGEDY.
YOU CAN IMAGINE, YOU CAN
PROBABLY COUNT ON ONE HAND THE
NUMBER OF HOURS OF SLEEP HE'S
HAD.
THE PRESIDENT TAKING THE TOUR OF
THE COMMAND CENTER, MEETING WITH
THE FIRST RESPONDERS AND WE'LL
HEAR FROM HIM SHORTLY WHERE HE
WILL PAY TRIBUTE TO THE BRAVE
MEN AND WOMEN OF LAW ENFORCEMENT
THAT PUT THEIR LIVES ON THE LINE
AND THE CIVILIANS THAT DID THE
SAME THING SUNDAY NIGHT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: JOHN, THANKS SO
MUCH.
THE ROOM BEGINNING TO FILL WHERE
THE PRESIDENT WILL GREET THOSE
FOLKS.
THEY'VE BEEN FILLING IN THE DOOR
ON THE LEFT TO OUR LEFT SIDE OF
THAT -- THE BLUE WALL BACK
THERE, THE BLUE CURTAIN.
YOU'LL SEE MORE COMING IN NOW.
IT'S OUR BELIEF THE PRESIDENT IS
ON HIS WAY RIGHT NOW.
THE OTHER STORY OF THE DAY HAS
BEEN THE REPORTS ON SECRETARY
TILLERSON.
IT WAS BACK IN THE SUMMER THAT
CNN REPORTED AND NBC REPORTED
OVERNIGHT AND INTO THIS MORNING,
I THINK THEY DEBUTED IT ON
MORNING JOE, THAT REX TILLERSON
SAID I'M DONE, I'M GOING TO
TEXAS.
BUT THE PRESIDENT INTERVENED IN
SOME WAY AND IT NEVER HAPPENED.
NOW SECRETARY TILLERSON HAS SAID
NONE OF THAT HAPPENED, IT'S FAKE
NEWS.
NBC NEWS STANDS BY ITS
REPORTING.
WITH THAT, WE RETURNED TO A.B.
STODDARD.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF
THIS.
I DON'T KNOW HOW MANY TIMES I
TRIED TO QUIT AROUND HERE.
EVERYBODY HAS BAD DAYS.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO MAKE OF
THIS.
SECRETARY TILLERSON SAYS IT'S
FAKE NEWS.
NBC NEWS STANDS BY IT.
I DON'T KNOW WHO TO MAKE OF IT.
>> THERE'S BEEN A LOT OF
REPORTING BETWEEN THE TENSION OF
THE WEST WING AND THE WHITE
HOUSE.
REX TILLERSON WAS THE MOST
POWERFUL MEN IN THE WORLD, HEAD
OF EXXON MOBIL.
HE DIDN'T HAVE TO HAVE REPORTERS
FOLLOWING HIM AROUND ASKING HIM
QUESTIONS IN HIS OLD LIFE ABOUT
GLOBAL CONFRONTATIONS, HAVING TO
DO WITH NATIONAL SECURITY.
HE'S NOT TOTALLY AT EASE IN ALL
THE ASPECTS OF THE JOB BUT HE
MADE COMMENTS TODAY THAT WERE
VERY COMPELLING ABOUT HIS
COMMITMENT TO THE PRESIDENT AND
THE PRESIDENT'S AGENDA AND THAT
AS A TEAM THEY'LL STICK
TOGETHER.
THEY'VE HAD SUCCESS.
HE COMPLIMENTED NIKKI HALEY THAT
SAID WOULD REPLACE HIM IF HE
LEFT.
THERE'S A LOT OF TALK ABOUT
WHETHER OR NOT HE HAS BEEN
PERFORMING A JOB THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP APPROVES OF.
THAT HE'S BEEN SLOW TO HIRE --
>> Shepard: THAT WAS THE POINT.
>> HE'S NOT DOING THINGS THE WAY
THAT THE WHITE HOUSE WANTS HIM
TO BE DOING THEM.
BUT ALL THIS GOSSIP ABOUT WHAT
HE'S CALLED THE PRESIDENT AND
ALL OF THAT STUFF OBVIOUSLY GETS
TO THE TOP OF THE HEADLINES.
THIS IS AN EXTRAORDINARY
SITUATION.
ALSO BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT SENT
OUT A TWEET UNDERMINING HIM
SAYING HIS WASTING HIS TIME IN
CHINA TALKING ABOUT HOW WE HAVE
PASSIVE NEGOTIATION OR DIALOGUE
WITH THE NORTH KOREANS.
HE'S WORKING ON A DIPLOMATIC
SOLUTION TO A GRAVE CRISIS.
MANY PEOPLE SAID ON SUNDAY LIKE
RICHARD HAAS, REPUBLICAN FOREIGN
POLICY EXPERT WITH EXPERIENCE,
THAT REX TILLERSON SHOULD RESIGN
AFTER THE WAY THE PRESIDENT
SPOKE ABOUT HIM.
IT'S OBVIOUSLY FILLED WITH
TENSION AND THEY BOTH SOUNDED
LIKE THEY WANT TO WORK.
THE VERY UPBEAT IS HONORED BY
TILLERSON'S COMMENTS, BUT
THERE'S MORE BEHIND THE SCENES
THAN WE UNDERSTOOD.
>> Shepard: THERE'S A LOT THERE.
WE HEAR FROM THE STATE
DEPARTMENT OFFICIALS THAT
THERE'S GREAT CONCERN AND GREAT
FRUSTRATIONS THAT THE POSITIONS
HAVE NOT BEEN FILLED.
ON THE MATTER OF THE PRESIDENT'S
TWEET REGARDING SECRETARY
TILLERSON IN NORTH KOREA, THE
PRESIDENT SAID DON'T WASTE YOUR
TIME, SECRETARY TILLERSON.
WE'RE GOING TO NEED WHAT NEEDS
TO BE DONE.
IN OTHER WORDS, STOP YOUR
DIPLOMACY.
IT'S HIS JOB TO HEAD UP THE
A LOT OF CONSERVATIVES THAT ARE
VERY UPSET ABOUT WHAT IT WAS
THAT THE PRESIDENT TWEETED
BECAUSE IF HE MEANT IT, IT'S
HARD TO SAY THAT HE MEANT
ANYTHING OTHER THAN WE'RE GOING
DO WHAT NEEDS TO BE DONE.
SOUNDS LIKE HE'S TALKING ABOUT
SOMETHING AGGRESSIVE.
>> ALSO JUST WHAT IT SHOWS TO
THE CHINESE WHEN REX TILLERSON
AS OUR SECRETARY OF STATE IS
OVER IN CHINA DOING THIS VERY
DIFFICULT WORK.
THIS IS VERY SENSITIVE WORK.
WHAT IT SHOWS WITH THE PRESIDENT
UNDERMINING HIM AND THROWING HIM
UNDER THE BUS AND UNDERMINING
THE IMPORTANCE OF DIPLOMACY
SENDS A WORRISOME SIGNAL ABOUT
HOW HE'S TREATING REX TILLERSON
AND HOW HE'S HANDLING THE
PROCESS IN TERMS OF WHAT HE'S
ASKING THE CHINESE TO DO TO TRY
TO MITIGATE THE THREAT OF NORTH
KOREA.
WE VERY MUCH OBVIOUSLY DEPEND ON
THE CHINESE IN THIS SITUATION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO HIS CREDIT
HAS GOTTEN THE CHINESE
GOVERNMENT TO STOP ALL CENTRAL
BANK ACTIVITY WITH THE NORTH
KOREANS.
THAT'S A HUGE STEP.
IT'S SOMETHING THAT COULD HAVE
GREAT -- COULD BE CONSEQUENTIAL
IF THEY ACTUALLY ENFORCE IT.
BUT IT'S A REAL QUESTION ABOUT
NOT ONLY TRUMP'S LEADERSHIP WHEN
HE DOES SOMETHING LIKE THAT
TWEET, BUT HOW LONG PEOPLE THAT
WORK UNDERNEATH HIM AND REPORT
TO HIM CAN ACTUALLY CONTINUE TO
DO THEIR JOBS IF THEY'RE TREATED
THAT WAY.
THAT'S A VERY CRITICAL JOB.
BEING SECRETARY OF STATE AND
TRYING TO HANDLE THE NORTH KOREA
CRISIS IS AT THE TOP OF THE
LIST.
>> Shepard: THERE'S A LOT ON THE
PLATE TODAY.
NOW THE PRESIDENT MAKING THE
ROUNDS OUT IN LAS VEGAS AND
SAYING WE'RE GOING TO DISCUSS
GUN CONTROL AT A LATER DAY.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT
SUGGESTED OVER TIME PRESIDENT
TRUMP THAT USED TO BE MUCH MORE
LIBERAL IN MANHATTAN WAS --
MIGHT HAVE BEEN MORE FOR GUN
CONTROL AT A TIME BEFORE HIS
PRESIDENCY.
I KNOW BECAUSE I READ THE MAIL
AND STUFF THAT THERE'S A LOT OF
CONSERVATIVES CONCERNED THAT HE
MIGHT BECOME MORE PRO GUN
CONTROL IN THE DAYS AHEAD.
>> THE SUPPORTERS THAT PUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN OFFICE ARE
LITTLE CONCERNED THAT HE'S NOT
GOTTEN OUT OF THE TRADE
AGREEMENTS EXCEPT FOR THE TRANS
PACIFIC PARTNERSHIP.
HE'S PUT MORE TROOPS IN
AFGHANISTAN.
AND THAT HE WAS WILLING TO TALK
ABOUT DOING AN AGREEMENT ON
IMMIGRATION WITH THE DEMOCRATIC
LEADERS IN CONGRESS.
SO THERE'S A LOT OF CONCERN
ABOUT HIS UNPREDICTABILITY AND
WHETHER OR NOT HE IS MORE TO A
SET OF IDEALOGICAL PRINCIPLES
THAT HE WILL STICK TO AS
PRESIDENT.
HE'S ON THE RECORD IN THE PAST
BEING SUPPORTING GUN CONTROL.
HE'S A WILD CARD, SHEP.
I DON'T THINK ANYBODY WILL
HAPPEN WITH HIM.
IF HE CREATES A BRIDGE,
SOMETHING COULD HAPPEN.
>> Shepard: WE'LL SEE.
HE SAYS HE WILL DISCUSS IT IN
THE DAYS AHEAD.
AS THAT HAPPENS, WE'LL FOLLOW
THE DEVELOPMENTS AS THEY COME.
IN ONCE AGAIN, FOX TELEVISION
STATIONS ACROSS THE NATION WILL
JOIN US RIGHT NOW.
GOOD AFTERNOON FROM FOX NEWS IN
NEW YORK.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THE PRESIDENT THIS AFTERNOON IS
IN LAS VEGAS WHERE HE'S ABOUT TO
MEET WITH FIRST RESPONDERS.
THESE ARE POLICE CHIEFS, FIRE
OFFICIALS AND OTHERS THAT WERE
INSTRUMENTAL IN ENDING THE
MASSACRE THAT HAPPENED OUTSIDE
THE MANDALAY BAY AND LUXOR
HOTELS ON THE STRIP DURING THE
COUNTRY MUSIC FESTIVAL.
59 KILLED.
A LOT OF QUESTIONS ABOUT DEATH
TOLL.
THE GUNMAN DIED, ACCORDING TO
AUTHORITIES, KILLED HIMSELF.
THERE'S 59 OTHERS THAT HAVE DIED
AS ANOTHER DIED IN THE HOSPITAL.
THAT BRINGS THE DEATH TOLL TO
59.
MORE THAN 540 INJURED.
THE PRESIDENT SPREADING THE LOVE
OF THE PEOPLE AND THANKS FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE AND FROM THE
AMERICAN FEEL IN LAS VEGAS.
ABOUT A MINUTE AGO, WE GOT A
TWO-MINUTE WARNING ON THIS.
OUR VIEWERS ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL
HAVE BEEN LISTENING DELONG AS WE
DISCUSS THE OTHER NEWS ITEMS OF
THE DAY.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN CLEAR.
WE'VE SEEN HIM AT THREE
DIFFERENT APPEARANCES IN
LAS VEGAS SINCE HE ARRIVED A FEW
SHORT HOURS AGO.
HE AND THE FIRST LADY ARE THERE.
THE ORDER OF THE DAY HAS BEEN TO
THANK PEOPLE TO ALLOW THEM TO
TELL THEIR STORIES OF WHAT
HAPPENED DURING THE MASSACRE.
WE'VE TALKED ABOUT HOW ORDINARY
PEOPLE STEP FORWARD AND BECOME
EXTRAORDINARY INDIVIDUALS OR WE
LEARNED OF THEIR EXTRAORDINARY
FORTITUDE AS THEY HELPED PEOPLE
OUT, STORIES OF PEOPLE PUTTING
FOLKS IN THE BACK OF THEIR
TRUCKS TO TAKE THEM TO
HOSPITALS.
PEOPLE PLUGGING WOUNDS, STOPPING
BLOOD FROM FLOWING OUT OF
PEOPLE'S BODIES.
THERE'S NO TELLING SPECIFICALLY
HOW MANY PEOPLE WERE SAVED AS A
RESULT OF THE ACTIONS OF PEOPLE
THAT WERE NOT DOCTORS.
THEY WERE JUST PEOPLE THAT
STEPPED IN TO TRY TO HELP AT A
MOMENT'S NOTICE.
JOHN ROBERTS IS THERE.
HE'S THE CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT.
JOHN, A LOT OF PEOPLE THAT NEED
REST IN THAT CITY, ESPECIALLY
THE ONES WE'VE BEEN LISTENING TO
HAVE BEEN MIGHTY GLAD TO SEE THE
PRESIDENT.
>> IT'S NOT JUST THE PHYSICAL
FATIGUE, EITHER.
THE MENTAL FATIGUE AS WELL.
LIVING EVERY DAY WITH WHAT
HAPPENED SUNDAY NIGHT AND IT
SPREADS ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THE MAJORITY OF PEOPLE WOULD
HAVE BEEN VISITORS FROM OUT OF
TOWN HERE FOR THE WEEKEND AND
JUST WANTED TO ENJOY SOME
COUNTRY MUSIC AND JASON ALDEAN
PACKING IN A CROWD OF 22,000
PEOPLE.
YOU CAN IMAGINE WHAT WAS GOING
ON IN THE CONCERT WHEN FROM THE
32nd FLOOR WINDOWS BEHIND ME,
THIS GUY PADDOCK TOOK THE
SEMIAUTOMATIC WEAPONS THAT WERE
CONVERTED TO FEAR NEW HAMPSHIRE
AUTOMATIC RATE OF FIRE AND START
RAINING HELLFIRE DOWN UPON
PEOPLE THERE JUST LISTENING TO
MUSIC.
SO MANY OF THEM RAN FOR THE EXIT
AS YOU WOULD EXPECT AS MANY
PEOPLE WOULD.
MANY OF THEM FELL TO THE GROUND
MORE TALLY WOUNDED OR SERIALLY
WOUNDED.
AND MANY DECIDED THEY WOULD
STAND AND HELP PEOPLE.
YOU CAN IMAGINE IN A STATE OF
FEAR AND SHOCK THAT THEY WOULD
DO THAT IS EXTRAORDINARY.
THAT'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT WILL
PAY TRIBUTE TOO.
>> Shepard: WE'RE WATCHING THE
CROWD MAKE ITS WAY IN THE ROOM.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN TOURING
THE COMMAND FACILITY THERE.
THIS IS A LAS VEGAS POLICE
DEPARTMENT COMMAND FACILITY.
IT'S MY UNDERSTANDING FROM THE
INFORMATION FROM LAS VEGAS
POLICE, AND THEY CALL THEM METRO
THERE, THAT WHAT THEY'RE TALKING
ABOUT, THIS IS THE PLACE WHERE
THE CALLS WERE INCOMING.
IMAGINE HOW MANY PEOPLE GOT ON
THE PHONE CALLING THE POLICE
DEPARTMENT.
AND THEN THE POLICE DEPARTMENT
ITSELF TRYING TO ORGANIZE ALL OF
THE FIRST RESPONDERS COMING.
AT ONE POINT WE HEARD ON POLICE
RADIOS THEM TELLING PEOPLE TO
GET OFF OF NORTH LAS VEGAS
BOULEVARD BECAUSE THEY REALIZED
WHERE THE SHOTS WERE COMING FROM
IN THE NORTH TOWER OF MANDALAY
BAY.
BUT THE POLICE AT THE TIME SAID,
YOU KNOW, DON'T USE THAT HIGHWAY
BECAUSE YOU'RE IN SIGHT OF HIM.
THEY WERE VERY CONCERNED THAT
AUTHORITIES AND OTHERS ARRIVING
TO HELP IN THIS SITUATION WOULD
BECOME VICTIMS.
WE KNOW A NUMBER OF LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICERS THAT WERE
OFF DUTY AND AT THAT CONCERT
WERE INJURED IN ONE WAY OR
ANOTHER.
EIGHT I BELIEVE FROM THE STATE
OF CALIFORNIA FROM DIFFERENT
JURISDICTIONS.
DIFFERENT POLICE DEPARTMENTS
WITH DIFFERENT PEOPLE INJURED.
THE AUTHORITIES TOLD US THIS
MORNING THAT THEY'VE BEEN ABLE
TO IDENTIFY ALL BUT THREE OF THE
VICTIMS.
SADLY THEY REPORTED TO US SOME
OF THE VICTIMS WITH REALLY --
WERE LEFT IN A POSITION TO
IDENTIFY THEM.
AUTHORITIES ARE WORKING ON
IDENTIFYING THREE OF THEM WHO
DIED ON THAT FATEFUL NIGHT.
IN ADDITION, THE HOSPITAL
WORKERS WERE CONGRATULATED BY
THE PRESIDENT AND THANKED BY THE
PRESIDENT ON BEHALF OF THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
THEY DISCUSS HOW THE HALLWAYS,
THE TRAUMA CENTER AND THE OTHER
HOSPITALS IN THE AREA WERE JUST
LITERALLY OVERFLOWING WITH
PEOPLE.
MEDICAL -- SOME PEOPLE GETTING
OUT OF THEIR HOSPITAL BEDS TO
MAKE ROOM FOR OTHERS THAT WERE
MORE GRAVELY WOUNDED.
THE SAME IN AMBULANCES AS THEY
WERE LOADING PEOPLE IN
AMBULANCES TO TAKE THEM TO
HOSPITALS FROM THE SHOOTING
SCENE.
WE GOT WORD OF I DON'T KNOW HOW
MANY DOZENS OF PEOPLE THAT
TRANSPORTED VICTIMS TO THE
HOSPITALS IN VANS, TRUCKS.
SOME PEOPLE INJURED THEMSELVES
HELPING TO STOP THE BLEEDING OF
OTHER PEOPLE.
THE STORIES ARE ENDLESS OF MAN
AND WOMAN HELPING MAN AND WOMAN.
THERE WERE TEENAGERS INVOLVED
THERE AS WELL.
A MATT RUSH TO TRY TO GET OUT.
DIFFERENT PEOPLE TELLING STORIES
OF IF I DIDN'T KNOW TO CROUCH
DOWN AND WAIT AND WAIT FOR
INSTRUCTIONS OR BE RUNNING FOR
THE EXITS WHERE THE HUGE CROWDS.
THINK OF WHEN YOU EXIT A CONCERT
VENUE HOW LONG YOU HAVE TO STAND
AND WAIT FOR PEOPLE TO GET UP
THE AISLES IN CASES LIKE THAT
WHERE THERE'S AN ACTIVE SHOOTER
SHOOTING DOWN FROM THE 32nd
FLOOR.
WELL, THEY WERE IN MANY CASES
JUST DEFENSELESS AND OUT IN THE
WIDE OPEN.
CLAUDIA COWAN IS IN LAS VEGAS
WITH THE STORY WITH SOME OF
THESE VICTIMS.
CLAUDIA?
>> WELL, WITH SHEPARD, EVERY
STORY OF A VICTIM IS A LIFE CUT
SHORT.
THERE WAS A MEMORIAL LAST NIGHT
IN MARIN COUNTY, CALIFORNIA FOR
50-YEAR-OLD STACY ECHABAR.
VINCENT PUT HIS WIFE IN A PLACE
THAT HE THOUGHT WOULD BE SAFE
FOR HER WHILE HE HELPED OTHER
PEOPLE TO SCRAMBLE FOR SAFETY.
ONLY TO LEARN LATER THAT SHE HAD
DIED.
I CAN TELL YOU A LAS VEGAS
POLICE OFFICER THAT WAS OFF DUTY
OUT ENJOYING THE MUSIC SUNDAY
NIGHT, HE PASSED AWAY AS WELL
AND A VIGIL SUNDAY NIGHT.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: THANKS.
THE GOVERNOR IS INTRODUCING THE
PRESIDENT.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
>> THE FIRST RESPONDERS AND HOW
THEY REACTED TO THIS SITUATION
PROVIDED SO MANY LOVE AND CARE
FOR THE PEOPLE THAT WERE HARMED
BY THIS HORRIBLE INCIDENT.
THE MEDICAL COMMUNITY, THOSE
THAT CAME TO THE AID OF THESE
PEOPLE.
THE EMPLOYEES AT MGM RESORTS AND
HOW THEY RESPONDED AS WELL.
AND EVERYONE ELSE, PERFECT
STRANGERS AND HOW THEY RESPONDED
TO THIS AND GAVE LOVE AND
ASSISTANCE TO THEIR FELLOW MAN.
I ALSO WANT TO THANK THE PEOPLE
FROM ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND
ACROSS THE WORLD FOR THEIR
OUTPOURING OF SUPPORT AND
GENEROSITY THAT HAS COME HERE.
IT'S UNPRECEDENTED IN OUR
HISTORY.
MAKES US FEEL LIKE WE'RE NOT
ALONE AND GIVES US STRENGTH.
BRIEFLY I ATTENDED A CANDLELIGHT
VIGIL LAST NIGHT AT THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA.
IT WAS AN IMPROMPTU EVENT.
OVER 1,500 PEOPLE SHOWED UP ON
SHORT NOTICE.
WE ALL HELD CANDLES, WE ALL
HUGGED ONE ANOTHER.
WE HELD HANDS.
WE HELD THOSE FLAMES OUT IN
FRONT OF US TO SHOW TRIBUTE TO
THE VICTIMS AND THEIR FAMILIES
OF THIS HORRIBLE EVENT.
AND TO -- AT THAT MOMENT,
DESPITE HOW DARK AND COLD IT WAS
I SAW AND WE ALL SAW THE
GREATEST DARKNESS CAN'T PUT OUT
THE SMALLEST LIGHT.
WE COLLECTIVELY FELT FOR THE
FIRST TIME THE FIRST PANES OF
HOPE.
WE SAW DESPITE THE SADNESS AND
GRIEF AROUND US THAT WE'RE
RESILIENT AND THAT WE'RE
COMMITTED TO FIGHT AND RECOVER
AND BEGIN THE LONG PROCESS OF
HEALING.
WE HAVE A LONG HISTORY OF
PULLING TOGETHER.
YES, WE'RE HURT, WE'RE HURT
BADLY, BUT WE'RE NOT BROKEN.
AS I SAID, WE'VE SEEN GENEROSITY
ON A SCALE THAT IS UNPRECEDENTED
IN NEVADA HISTORY.
WE KNOW THAT WE WILL NEVER EVER
FORGET THIS HORRIFIC EVENT.
WE WILL MARCH FORWARD AS A
FAMILY, GIVING EACH OTHER
COMFORT, SUPPORT AND LOVE.
FUTURE WILL COME ONE DAY AT A
TIME.
WE ALL HAVE A CHOICE HOW WE'RE
GOING TO LIVE EACH DAY.
WE MUST BE GLAD, WE MUST BE
GOOD, WE MUST BE BRAVE.
WE MUST HAVE FAITH.
WE WILL EMERGE AS A STRONGER,
KINDER, BETTER STATE AND NATION.
GOD BLESS THE VICTIMS AND THEIR
FAMILIES.
MAY THEY GIVE THEM PEACE, GOD
BLESS OUR STATE AND THE NATION,
THE GREATEST NATION ON EARTH.
WITH THAT, I'M VERY PRIVILEGED
AND HONORED TO INTRODUCE THE
FIRST LADY AND THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
I PERSONALLY WANT TO THANK THEM
ON BEHALF OF ALL OF THE PEOPLE
OF NEVADA FOR TAKING THE TIME TO
COME OUT HERE AND PROVIDE US
THEIR SUPPORT AND THEIR COMFORT
AND EVERYTHING ELSE THAT THEY'LL
BRING TO US.
WITH THAT, LADIES AND GENTLEMEN,
I'D LIKE TO INTRODUCE THE
PRESIDENT OF OUR GREAT NATION,
DONALD TRUMP.
THANK YOU.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
GOVERNOR.
WE APPRECIATE THAT.
I WILL TELL YOU, THE PEOPLE OF
NEVADA AND THE EXTRAORDINARY
CITY HAVE SHOWN THE WORLD THEIR
INCREDIBLE CHARACTER, COURAGE
AND RESOLVE.
NEVADA IS REALLY A SPECIAL
PLACE.
I'M HONORED TO BE HERE TODAY AT
THE LAS VEGAS METROPOLITAN
POLICE DEPARTMENT AND THE
COMPANY OF HEROS.
THANK YOU TO OUR POLICE, OUR
FIREFIGHTERS AND TO OUR FIRST
RESPONDERS AND OF COURSE TO
SHERIFF LOMBARDO.
INCREDIBLE JOB YOU'VE DONE.
MAYOR GOODMAN.
HELLO, MAYOR.
SENATOR HELLER.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
SENATOR CORTEZ, MAJORITY LEADER.
WHERE IS KEVIN.
KEVIN McCARTHY.
ADAM LAXAULT.
ALL OF THE GREAT CONGRESSMAN
WITH US TODAY FROM BOTH PARTIES.
WE JUST ARE VERY HONORED THAT
YOU COULD BE WITH US.
ON BEHALF OF THE GRATEFUL
NATION, MELANIA AND I THANK EACH
AND EVERY ONE OF YOU IN LAW
ENFORCEMENT IN THE DEPTHS OF
HORROR, WE WILL ALWAYS FIND HOPE
IN THE MEN AND WOMEN WHO RISK
THEIR LIVES FOR OURS.
THE MASS MURDER TOOK PLACE
SUNDAY NIGHT FILLS AMERICA'S
HEART WITH GRIEF.
AMERICA IS TRULY A NATION IN
MOURNING.
I VISITED THE HOSPITAL EARLIER
TODAY WHERE MANY VICTIMS ARE
STILL RECOVERS FROM THEIR
WOUNDS.
WE ASK GOD TO EASE THEIR
SUFFERING.
WE PRAY FOR THE RECOVERY OF THE
INJURED AND THOSE INJURED
OFFICERS THAT SO BRAVELY THROUGH
THEMSELVES INTO DANGER WHEN DUTY
CALLED.
AND WE GRIEVE THE LOSS OF THE
LAW ENFORCEMENT PERSONNEL WHO
WERE KILLED IN THIS VICIOUS
ATTACK.
MANY FAMILIES TONIGHT WILL GO TO
BED IN A WORLD THAT IS SUDDENLY
EMPTY, THE PEOPLE THEY SO DEARLY
LOVE WERE TORN AWAY FROM THEM
FOREVER.
OUR SOULS ARE STRIKEN WITH GRIEF
FOR EVERY AMERICAN WHO LOST A
HUSBAND OR A WIFE, A MOTHER OR A
FATHER, A SON OR A DAUGHTER.
WE KNOW THAT YOUR SORRY FEELS
ENDLESS.
WE STAND TOGETHER TO HELP YOU
CARRY YOUR PAIN.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
WE WILL NEVER LEAVE YOUR SIDE.
HERE AT THE POLICE DEPARTMENT,
WE REMEMBER ONE OF OUR OWN WHO
DIED THIS WEEK, CHARLES
HARTFIELD.
HE WAS A VERY, VERY SPECIAL
PERSON.
OFFICER HARTFIELD WAS A PROUD
VETERAN, A DEVOTED HUSBAND, A
LOVING FATHER.
HIS DEATH IS A TRAGIC LOSS FOR
THIS POLICE FORCE, FOR THIS CITY
AND FOR OUR GREAT NATION.
WE STRUGGLE FOR THE WORDS TO
EXPLAIN TO OUR CHILDREN HOW SUCH
EVIL CAN EXIST, HOW THERE CAN BE
SUCH CRUELTY AND SUCH SUFFERING.
WE CANNOT BE DEFINED BY THE EVIL
THAT THREATENINGS US OR THE
VIOLENCE THAT INCITES SUCH
TERROR.
WE'RE DEFINED BY THE LOVE, OUR
CARING AND OUR COURAGE.
IN THE DARKEST MOMENTS, WHAT
SHINES MOST BRIGHTLY IS THE
GOODNESS THAT THRIVES IN THE
HEARTS OF OUR PEOPLE.
THAT GOODNESS IS OUR LIGHT HOUSE
AND OUR SOLACE.
IS KNOWLEDGE.
THAT THE SOULS OF THOSE THAT
PASSED ARE NOW AT PEACE IN
HEAVEN.
HERE ON EARTH, WE'RE BLESSED TO
BE SURROUNDED BY HEROS.
AS ONE EYE WITNESS RECOUNTED
THIS WEEK, WHILE EVERYONE ELSE
WAS CROUCHING, POLICE OFFICERS
WERE STANDING UP AS TARGETS JUST
TRYING TO DISTRICT PEOPLE AND
TELL THEM WHERE TO GO.
THE OFFICERS WERE STANDING UP IN
THE LINE OF FIRE TO HELP THOSE
IN DANGER AND TO FIND OUT WHERE
THOSE HORRIBLE SHOTS WERE COMING
FROM.
WORDS CANNOT DESCRIBE THE
BRAVERY THAT THE WHOLE WORLD
WITNESSED ON SUNDAY NIGHT.
AMERICANS DENIED DEATH AND
HATRED WITH LOVE AND WITH
COURAGE.
WHEN THE WORD AND WORST OF
HUMANITY STRIKES, THE BEST OF
HUMANITY RESPONDS.
PARENTS AND SPOUSES USED THEIR
OWN BODIES AS SHIELDS TO PROTECT
LOVES ONES.
AMERICANS DASHED INTO A HAIL OF
BULLETS TO RESCUE TOTAL
STRANGERS.
JOINING US TODAY ARE MANY OF THE
HEROS THAT WERE HERE DURING THAT
HORRIBLE MOMENT, THAT HORRIBLE
NIGHT.
INCLUDING LAS VEGAS METROPOLITAN
POLICE OFFICE
POLICE OFFICERS.
OFFICER PETERSON WAS ON HIS
SECOND DAY ON THE JOB WHEN THE
SHOOTING BEGAN.
I JUST VISITED HIM IN THE
HOSPITAL.
WITHIN MINUTES, HE JOINED A
GROUP OF OFFICERS RUSHING
BETWEEN FLYING BULLETS TO CLEAR
THE FAIR GROUNDS AND SAVE LIVES.
OFFICER GURLET WAS OFF DUTY
ATTENDING THE CONCERT.
ALL THOSE S