I CAN'T SING IT.
WE HAVE TO PAY SOMEBODY.
TUCKER, GOD BLESS YOU.
HAVE FUN ON YOUR NEXT ADVENTURE
IN YOUR JOURNEY.
I'M HARRIS FAULKNER.
WE'RE STAYING ON THE NEWS ALL
DAY LONG, PARTICULARLY MEXICO
CITY WHERE THEY'RE TRYING TO
RESCUE KIDS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THE
WEST COAST, 3:00 IN THE EAST I
AND 2:00 P.M. IN MEXICO CITY.
TEAMS SAY THEY HAVE SPOKEN WITH
ONE GIRL TRAPPED BENEATH A
BUILDING.
SHE TOLD THEM THERE'S MORE
SURVIVORS WITH HER.
NOW WITH THE WRECKAGE SHIFTING
AND GROANING AND MORE AFTER
SHOCKS POSSIBLE, CREWS ARE
RISKING THEIR LIVES TO TRY TO
GET THOSE KIDS TO SAFETY.
HURRICANE MARIA ROARING ACROSS
THE CARIBBEAN NOW LEAVING BEHIND
ABSOLUTE DESTRUCTION.
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS IN PUERTO
RICO NOW GETTING AN IDEA OF JUST
HOW MUCH THEY LOST WHEN THE
STORM SCOURED THEIR ISLAND.
WINDS SO POWERFUL, THEY RIPPED
CONCRETE BALCONIES OFF OF WALLS
AND NOW MARIA HEADED FOR THE
TURKS AND CAICOS AND THE
BAHAMAS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ANNOUNCING BOLD
NEW MEASURES TARGETING THE
NUCLEAR NATION OF NORTH KOREA.
HE SAYS THEY'RE AIMED AT CUTTING
OFF CASH TO KIM JONG-UN AND HIS
WEAPONS PROGRAM.
MORE DETAILS EXPECTED IN A LIVE
EVENT IN JUST MOMENTS.
SO LET'S GET TO IT.
BREAKING NEWS THIS HOUR.
FIRST, THE TREASURY SECRETARY
STEVE MNUCHIN ABOUT TO BRIEF
REPORTERS ON THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S LATEST MOVE TO
CUT OFF NORTH KOREA'S CASH FLOW.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ANNOUNCING HIS
NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER HOURS AGO.
IT GIVES THE TREASURY DEPARTMENT
MORE POWER TO GO AFTER PEOPLE
THAT DO BUSINESS WITH KIM
JONG-UN'S GOVERNMENT.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS IT WILL LEAVE
THE DICTATOR WITH LESS MONEY FOR
HIS NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
>> NORTH KOREA'S NUCLEAR WEAPONS
AND MISSILE DEVELOPMENT IS A
GRAVE THREAT TO PEACE AND
SECURITY IN OUR WORLD AND IT IS
UNACCEPTABLE THAT OTHERS
FINANCIALLY SUPPORT THIS
CRIMINAL ROGUE REGIME.
OUR NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER WILL CUT
OFF SOURCES OF REVENUE THAT FUND
NORTH KOREA'S EFFORTS TO DEVELOP
THE DEADLIEST WEAPONS TO HUMAN
KIND.
>> Shepard: THE PRESIDENT MAKING
THE ANNOUNCEMENT WITH THE
LEADERS OF SOUTH KOREA AND
JAPAN.
THE PRESIDENT HELD SEPARATE
MEETINGS WITH EACH LEADER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP PRAISING CHINA
FOR REPORTEDLY TELLING ITS BANKS
TO STOP DOING BUSINESS WITH
NORTH KOREA.
THE REUTERS NEWS AGENCY SAID
THAT MESSAGE CAME FROM CHINA'S
CENTRAL BANK, WHICH MAKES IT
SIGNIFICANT.
ANALYSTS SAY IT WOULD BE A MAJOR
BLOW TO NORTH KOREA BECAUSE
CHINA IS ITS CLOSEST ALLY.
THE EXECUTIVE ORDER ALSO COMES
JUST A COUPLE OF DAYS AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S FIRST SPEECH
TO THE U.N.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THE UNITED
STATES WOULD TOTALLY DESTROY
NORTH KOREA IF IT HAD TO, BUT
HOPEFULLY HE SAID IT WON'T BE
NECESSARY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ALSO SAID KIM
JONG-UN OR ROCKETMAN, AS HE
CALLS HIM THESE DAYS IS ON A
SUICIDE ANYTHING.
NOW NORTH KOREA'S FOREIGN
MINISTER HAS SPOKEN BACK.
>> IF THEY THOUGHT THEY COULD
SCARE US WITH A SOUND OF A DOG
BARKING, IT'S A SILLY DREAM.
>> Shepard: SOUND OF A DOG
BARKING.
THE FOREIGN MINISTER SAYS HE
PITY'S PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
ADVISERS.
DESPITE THE RHETORIC, PRESIDENT
TRUMP DID NOT RULE OUT TALKING
WITH THE NORTH KOREANS.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, IS DIALOGUE
STILL POSSIBLE WITH NORTH KOREA?
>> Shepard: BREAKING RIGHT NOW,
THE TREASURY SECRETARY STEVE
MNUCHIN IS TALKING ABOUT THE NEW
ORDER.
LET'S LISTEN LIVE FROM NEW YORK
CITY.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S NEW
EXECUTIVE ORDER SIGNIFICANTLY
EXPANDS TREASURIES, AUTHORITIES
TO TARGET THOSE WHO ENABLE THIS
REGIME'S ECONOMIC ACTIVITY
WHEREVER THEY ARE LOCATED.
FOR TOO LONG, NORTH KOREA HAS
EVADED SANCTIONS AND USED THE
INTERNATIONAL FINANCIAL SYSTEM
TO FACILITATE FUNDING FOR
WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION AND
BALLISTIC MISSILE PROGRAMS.
NO BANK IN ANY COUNTRY SHOULD BE
USED TO FACILITATE KIM JONG-UN'S
DESTRUCTIVE BEHAVIOR.
THIS NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER WILL
AUTHORIZE TREASURY TO IMPOSE A
RANGE OF SANCTIONS LIKE
SUSPENDING U.S. CORRESPONDENT
ACCOUNT ACCESS TO ANY FOREIGN
BANK THAT KNOWINGLY CONDUCTS OR
FACILITATES SIGNIFICANT
TRANSACTIONS TIED TO TRADE WITH
NORTH KOREA.
THESE SANCTIONS WILL BE
FORWARD-LOOKING AND APPLIED TO
BEHAVIOR THAT OCCURS FOLLOWING
TODAY WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
SIGNED THE EXECUTIVE ORDER.
FOREIGN FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS
ARE NOW ON NOTICE THAT GOING
FORWARD, THEY CAN CHOOSE TO DO
BUSINESS WITH THE UNITED STATES
OR WITH NORTH KOREA, BUT NOT
BOTH.
THIS NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER ENABLES
TREASURY TO FREEZE ASSETS OF
ANYONE CONDUCTING SIGNIFICANT
TRADE IN GOODS, SERVICES OR
TECHNOLOGY WITH NORTH KOREA.
IT ALSO ALLOWS TO US FREEZE
ASSETS OF ACTORS SUPPORTING
NORTH KOREA'S TEXTILE, FISHING,
AND TECHNOLOGY INDUSTRIES.
WE CALL ON ALL COUNTRIES AROUND
THE WORLD TO JOIN US BY CUTTING
OFF ALL TRIED AND FINANCIAL TIES
TO NORTH KOREA IN ORDER TO
ACHIEVE A DE-NUCLEARIZED KOREAN
PENINSULA.
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP STATED IN HIS
SPEECH TO THE U.N., IT'S TIME
FOR ALL NATIONS TO WORK TOGETHER
TO ISOLATE KIM JONG-UN'S REGIME
UNTIL IT CEASES ITS HOSTILE
BEHAVIOR.
WE WILL WORK WITH OUR ALLIES AND
PARTNERS TO STOP FROM USING THE
GLOBAL FINANCIAL SYSTEM TO
FURTHER KIM'S RECKLESS BEHAVIOR.
THANK YOU AND I'D BE HAPPY TO
TAKE A FEW QUESTIONS.
>> CAN YOU EXPLAIN HOW THIS WILL
AFFECT -- WHAT KIND OF
DISCUSSIONS YOU AND YOUR COUNTER
PARTS HAVE HAD ABOUT THIS?
>> LET ME COMMENT.
I HAD A VERY PRODUCTIVE
CONVERSATION EARLY THIS MORNING
WITH GOVERNOR JOE AT THE PBOC,
THE PEOPLE'S BANK OF CHINA AND
HOW WE'RE GOING TO WORK
TOGETHER.
THIS ACTION IS DIRECTED AT
EVERYONE.
IT'S IN NO WAY DIRECTED AT
CHINA.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO WORKING
CLOSELY WITH THEM.
>> MR. SECRETARY, CAN I READ A
QUICK SECTION OF THE E.O.?
NO AIRCRAFT IN WHICH A FOREIGN
PERSON HAS AN INTERESTED HAS
LANDED AT A PLACE IN NORTH
KOREA, MAY LAND IN THE UNITED
STATES AFTER DEPARTURE FROM
NORTH KOREA.
THEN SIMILAR APPLICATIONS TO
SHIPS.
ANY IDEA ON HOW MANY SHIPS OR
AIRCRAFT WOULD BE HAVE BEEN
AFFECTED IN PICK A YEAR?
SO WE CAN GET A SENSE OF THE
SCALE OF THE IMPACT.
>> AGAIN, ANOTHER IMPORTANT
ASPECT OF THE E.O. BESIDES FOR
US BEING ABLE TO BLOCK FINANCIAL
TRANSACTIONS.
WE'LL WORK CLOSELY WITH THE
COAST GUARD AND OTHERS ON THIS.
I'M NOT PREPARED TO GIVE YOU A
NUMBER.
IT'S VERY SIGNIFICANT.
FURTHER, WE CAN PUT ACTIONS
AGAINST PORTS AS WELL.
>> A COUPLE QUESTIONS.
FIRST ONE, WHY WILL THIS ROUND
OF SANCTIONS WORK WHEN OTHERS
HAVE FAILED?
>> AGAIN, LET ME BE CLEAR.
I DON'T THINK OTHER SANCTIONS
HAVE FAILED.
THESE SANCTIONS ARE SIGNIFICANT.
NOT ONLY DOES IT ALLOW US TO
SANCTION INDIVIDUALS OR
ENTITIES, BUT IT ALLOWS US TO
FREEZE OR BLOCK ANY TRANSACTIONS
WITH ANY FINANCIAL INSTITUTIONS
ANYWHERE IN THE WORLD THAT
FACILITATES ANY TRANSACTIONS
WITH THE BLOCKED PERSON.
>> DO THESE SANCTIONS INCLUDED A
PLAN TO TARGET NORTH KOREAN
BUSINESSES AROUND THE WORLD?
>> YES, IT DOES.
>> ANY FUTURE SANCTIONS?
>> I WON'T COMMENT ON FUTURE
SANCTIONS.
WE'LL REVIEW ALL OPTIONS.
>> DOES THIS REPRESENT A
REJECTION OR A MOVING PATH TO
THE U.N. SECURITY COUNCIL?
>> NO, I DON'T THINK IN ANY WAY.
WE APPRECIATE THE U.N. SECURITY
COUNCIL RESOLUTION AND THE
UNANIMOUS SUPPORT TO THAT.
THIS GOES BEYOND IT.
AS I'VE MENTIONED, THIS ALLOWS
US TO BLOCK ANY FINANCIAL
INSTITUTION THAT DOESN'T
FOLLOW-THROUGH ON THE U.N.
SANCTIONS OR ADDITIONAL
SANCTIONS.
>> WHEN DO YOU EXPECT TO MAKE
DESIGNATIONS --
>> WE'LL DO DESIGNATIONS ON A
ROLLING BASIS.
THIS STARTS TODAY.
IT'S FORWARD LOOKING, NOT
BACKWARDS LOOKING.
>> CAN YOU SAY MORE ABOUT YOUR
DISCUSSIONS WITH THE CENTRAL
BANK OF CHINA?
WHAT DO YOU UNDERSTAND --
>> AGAIN, THOSE CONVERSATIONS
ARE CONFIDENTIAL.
AS I SAID, I HAD A VERY
PRODUCTIVE CONVERSATION WITH
THEM THIS MORNING.
>> PIGGYBACKING ON THAT, THE
TIMELINE, HAS THERE BEEN
PREVIOUS NEGOTIATIONS WITH THE
BANK OF CHINA?
>> NO, THERE WERE NO PREVIOUS
DISCUSSIONS.
THE FIRST TIME WE DISCUSSED IT
WAS THIS MORNING.
I CALLED THEM TO ALERT THEM OF
THIS IN ADVANCE GIVEN THEIR
CLOSE COOPERATION WITH US.
>> THANK YOU.
SO I WANT TO ASK PART OF THE
SAME QUESTION.
THAT CHINA HAD GIVEN SOME
INDICATION 1 1/2 WEEKS AGO OF
SOME ACTIONS.
WHAT DID THEY TODAY IS SEPARATE
FROM WHAT THEY INDICATED
EARLIER --
>> I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE
COMMENTS ABOUT WHAT THEY DID
EARLIER.
WHAT THEY DID TODAY IS I ASSUME
AS A RESULT OF OUR CONVERSATION.
>> CAN I ASK --
>> LET'S COME BACK TO YOU SO WE
CAN GET OTHER PEOPLE.
>> CAN YOU -- DO YOU BELIEVE
THAT CHINA'S ACTIONS TODAY
REDUCE THE NEED FOR FURTHER
SECONDARY SANCTIONS ON CHINESE
ENTITIES --
>> I JUST COMMENTED WE LOOK
FORWARD TO WORKING WITH THEM AS
WELL AS ALL OF OUR PARTNERS.
WHAT IS IMPORTANT ABOUT THIS IS
THE ADDITIONAL AUTHORITIES THE
TREASURY HAS.
>> CAN YOU PUT THIS IN THE
CONTEXT OF THE PRESIDENT'S
SPEECH EARLIER IN THE WEEK WHEN
HE TALKED ABOUT MORE MILITARY
ACTION?
HOW DO THESE THINGS WORK
TOGETHER AND WHAT DO YOU EXPECT
NORTH KOREA TO DO IN RESPONSE?
>> I'M NOT GOING TO COMMENT ON
WHAT I EXPECT NORTH KOREA TO DO.
OBVIOUSLY WHAT WE'VE SAID IS THE
OBJECTIVE, FOR THEM TO STOP
THEIR MISSILE TESTS AND GIVE UP
THEIR NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
THIS IS SOMETHING THAT HAS BEEN
IN THE WORKS FOR A WHILE.
I ALLUDED TO THIS ABOUT TWO
WEEKS AGO, THAT I HAD BEEN
DISCUSSING THIS WITH THE
PRESIDENT AND THIS IS ALL PART
OF THE PRESIDENT'S STRATEGY AT
THE U.N. THIS WEEK.
>> SECRETARY TILLERSON SAID IT
TOOK AWHILE FOR THE LAST ROUND
OF SANCTIONS TO HAVE AN IMPACT
OR FOR NORTH KOREA TO BE ABLE TO
FEEL THEM IS.
THERE A TIMELINE THAT YOU'RE
LOOKING AT IN WHICH CASE --
>> AGAIN, THERE'S NO TIME LINE.
THIS IS FORWARD ACTION ON THIS.
AGAIN, I WOULD EMPHASIZE THAT WE
HOPE THAT THERE'S VOLUNTARY
COOPERATION, BUT TO THE EXTENT
THAT WE HAVE TO CUT OFF BANKS
FROM THE BANKING SYSTEM IN THE
UNITED STATES, WHICH OBVIOUSLY
WOULD BE SIGNIFICANT, WE NOW
HAVE THOSE TOOLS TO DO THAT.
>> DO YOU RECALL ANY OTHER
COUNTRIES, CENTRAL BANKS --
>> I'M NOT GOING TO MAKE ANY
COMMENTS ON CONFIDENTIAL
DISCUSSIONS WITH OTHER
COUNTRIES.
AGAIN, I'M CONFIRMING THAT I DID
SPEAK TO THEM THIS MORNING.
I'M NOT GOING TO COMMENT ON
OTHER DISCUSSIONS THAT ARE
CONFIDENTIAL.
>> THE PRESIDENT EARLIER THANKED
PRESIDENT XI FOR HIS ACTIONS.
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE ENOUGH?
DID YOU CALL ON RUSSIA --
>> AGAIN, WE'LL CALL ON RUSSIA
TO DO MORE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND PRESIDENT XI
HAVE HAD PRODUCTIVE
CONVERSATIONS AND WE APPRECIATE
THE WAY THEY'RE WORKING WITH US.
I'M GOING TO TAKE ONE MORE.
>> I'D FOLLOW UP ON MY INITIAL
QUESTION.
YOU SAID THIS WAS NOT TARGETED
AT CHINA SPECIFICALLY.
BUT CHINA IS THE LARGEST TRADING
PARTNER WITH NORTH KOREA.
SO CAN YOU SPELL OUT HOW THIS
WILL AFFECT THEM AND HOW IT WILL
AFFECT THE U.S. AND THEIR
RELATIONSHIP WITH CHINA WITH
REGARD TO NORTH KOREA?
>> AS I EMPHASIZED EARLIER, THIS
IS TARGETED AT NORTH KOREA AND
ANYBODY THAT WANTS TO DO TRADE
OR BUSINESS WITH THEM.
WE APPRECIATE THE RELATIONSHIP
WITH CHINA AND LOOK FORWARD TO
WORKING WITH THEM.
THANK YOU, EVERYBODY.
>> Shepard: STEVE MNUCHIN
DISCUSSING THE NEW SANCTIONS BY
THE PRESIDENT THROUGH NORTH
KOREA WITH PARTNERSHIP IT WOULD
APPEAR FROM A NUMBER OF NATIONS.
HE WOULDN'T BE SPECIFIC ABOUT
DISCUSSIONS.
BIG PICTURE WITH THE SANCTIONS
AND THE NATIONS COMING TOGETHER
WHAT IS THE GOAL?
JOHN ROBERTS TRAVELLING WITH THE
PRESIDENT IN NEW YORK AND IN THE
STUDIO WITH US TODAY.
BIG PICTURE?
>> BIG PICTURE, THIS IS DESIGNED
TO GET KIM JONG-UN TO THE
NEGOTIATING TABLE.
THE PRESIDENT WAS ASKED, IS
THERE STILL ROOM FOR DIALOGUE?
HE SAID WHY NOT.
ALL OF THIS THAT YOU'VE HAVE
SEEN IS DESIGNED TO TRY TO GET
KIM JONG-UN TO THE NEGOTIATING
TABLE TO TALK ABOUT NOT JUST
FREEZING IT BUT TO GIVE IT UP.
THE PRESIDENT'S GOAL IS TO
DENUCLEARIZE THE KOREAN
PENINSULA.
IT MEANS FREEZING IT AND ROLLING
IT BACK TO NOTHING.
ONE OF THE BIG DEVELOPMENTS IS
THE FACT THAT CHINA FINALLY
STEPPED UP TO THE PLATE.
LISTEN TO WHAT THE PRESIDENT
SAID CHINA DECIDED TO DO TODAY.
>> CHINA, THEIR CENTRAL BANK,
HAS TOLD THEIR OTHER BANKS, A
MASSIVE BANKING SYSTEM, TO
IMMEDIATELY STOP DOING BUSINESS
WITH NORTH KOREA.
I THANK PRESIDENT XI OF CHINA
FOR THE BOLD MOVE HE MADE TODAY.
THIS IS A SOMEWHAT UNEXPECTED
MOVE AROUND WE APPRECIATE IT.
>> RIGHT NOW THE PRESIDENT IS
SPEAKING WITH PRESIDENT ERDOGAN
FROM TURKEY.
THEY'RE HAVING A BILATERAL
MEETING AND THE POOL IS THERE.
LET'S WATCH.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
A GREAT HONOR AND PRIVILEGE.
HE'S BECOME A FRIEND OF MINE.
I WANT TO INTRODUCE PRESIDENT
ERDOGAN OF TURKEY.
HE'S RUNNING A VERY DIFFICULT
PART OF THE WORLD.
HE'S INVOLVED VERY STRONGLY AND
HE'S GETTING HIGH MARKS FRANKLY.
HE'S ALSO BEEN WORKING WITH THE
UNITED STATES.
WE HAVE A GREAT FRIENDSHIP.
AS COUNTRIES WE'RE AS CLOSE AS
WE HAVE EVER BEEN.
A LOT OF THAT HAS TO DO WITH THE
PERSONAL RELATIONSHIPS.
SO PRESIDENT, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
A GREAT HONOR TO HAVE YOU HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
THANK YOU.
[SPEAKING TURKISH].
>> Shepard: THE TURKISH PRIME
MINISTER EDWARD SPEAKING WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
ERDOGAN, A VERY COMPLICATED
RELATIONSHIP.
LET'S LISTEN.
>> WE ARE GETTING TOGETHER WITH
YOU AS A DELEGATION AND WE WILL
COME BACK TO BILATERAL
MEETINGS-WE'LL ASSESS THE
CURRENT RELATIONSHIPS BETWEEN
THE UNITED STATES AND TURKEY AND
HAVE THE OPPORTUNITY TO DISCUSS
REGIONAL DEVELOPMENTS AS A
WHOLE.
I WOULD LIKE TO ONCE AGAIN THANK
YOU FOR THIS OPPORTUNITY.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
MR. PRESIDENT.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
THANK YOU ALL VERY MUCH.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, WHEN IS THE
LAST TIME YOU SPOKE WITH PAUL
MANAFORT.
>> THANK YOU, THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: A DIFFICULT SET OF
CIRCUMSTANCES HERE WITH THE
PRIME MINISTER ERDOGAN.
HE'S JAILED PEOPLE BY THE
THOUSANDS FOR SPEAKING OUT
AGAINST HIS GOVERNMENT.
HE'S JAILED MORE THAN 120
JOURNALISTS, DENOUNCED AROUND
THE WORLD.
THERE'S A WIDELY-HELD BELIEF
THAT HE'S TURNING WHAT APPEARED
TO BE A COUNTRY ON THE WAY TO
DEMOCRATIZATION INTO SOMETHING
AKIN TO A DICTATORSHIP.
>> THE PROBLEM HERE, HE'S A NATO
MEMBER AND TURKEY IS THE GATEWAY
FROM TURKEY TO THE MIDDLE EAST.
YOU SAID IT'S A COMPLICATED
RELATIONSHIP.
A DIPLOMATIC WAY OF PUTTING UP.
>> Shepard: I DON'T KNOW HOW YOU
RESOLVE IT.
SEEING HIM UP THERE, AS A
JOURNALIST IT AFFECTS YOU THE
SAME WAY IT DOES ME.
IT'S A SCARY PROPOSITION WHAT IS
HAPPENING IN TURKEY, IT'S
AGAINST EVERYTHING WE BELIEVE IN
THE UNITED STATES.
>> IT IS.
UNFORTUNATELY, THIS PRESIDENT,
THIS NATION NEEDS TO HAVE A
RELATIONSHIP WITH HIM BECAUSE OF
WHERE HIS COUNTRY IS AND WHERE
THEY REPRESENT.
IT'S ONE OF THOSE LINES THAT YOU
HAVE TO HOLD YOUR NOSE TO DEAL
WITH THE PEOPLE YOU HAVE TO DEAL
WITH.
THAT'S PROBABLY THE CASE IN THIS
POINT.
BACK TO WHAT WE TALKED ABOUT
PRIOR TO GOING HERE, CHINA.
THE MOVE THAT CHINA MADE IN
TERMS OF THE CENTRAL BANK
TELLING CHINESE BANKS, DON'T DO
ANY BUSINESS WITH NORTH KOREA
ANYMORE, THAT'S BIG.
THE PRESIDENT SAID CHINA NEEDS
TO STEP UP TO THE PLATE.
WHEN I SPOKE WITH THE PRESIDENT
LAST THURSDAY, I ASKED HIM ABOUT
NORTH KOREA AND CHINA.
HE SAID THEY'RE PLANNING SOME
MOVES WITH CHINA HE COULDN'T
TELL US ABOUT.
IT WOULD CLEARLY SEEM THIS IS
IT.
WHY IT'S SO IMPORTANT IS BECAUSE
THIS DOESN'T WORK WITHOUT
CHINA'S COOPERATION AND CHINA
TAKING STRINGENT MEASURES.
ALWAYS LOTS OF POSSIBILITIES FOR
CHEATING, BUT MAYBE THIS IS A
STEP DOWN THE RIGHT DIRECTION.
>> Shepard: CHINA HAS BEEN CLEAR
TO SAY FROM THEIR PERSPECTIVE,
WE'VE DONE WHAT WE CAN DO.
THE WORLD IS PUSHING US.
>> THE CHINESE CAN DO MORE THAN
THEY'VE BEEN DOING.
>> Shepard: OBVIOUSLY.
I WONDER IF THIS IS A CHANGE.
>> IT WOULD APPEAR TO BE A
CHANGE.
ALTHOUGH THERE'S ROOM FOR
CHEATING.
IS THIS CHINA JUST SAYING THIS
IS WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO OR IS
THIS CHINA DOING WHAT THEY SAY
THEY'RE GOING TO DO?
>> Shepard: THE U.S.,
SANCTIONING BANKS, THIS IS A
WIDE EXPANSION?
>> IT BROADENS THE TARGET
ENVIRONMENT.
THERE WAS ONE CHINESE BANK BEING
SANCTIONED.
THIS LAST TARGETED INDIVIDUALS
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
THE FACT THAT THEY'RE LOOKING AT
NORTH KOREA AND GOING TO TARGET
THE NORTH KOREAN TEXTILE
INDUSTRY AND THE FISHING
INDUSTRY.
OTHER SMALLER INDUSTRIES THAT
HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH THE
DEFENSE MINISTRY, THIS IS TRYING
TO PUT A CHOKE HOLD ON NORTH
KOREA.
THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID HE
DOESN'T WANT TO SETTLE FOR
ANYTHING SHORT OF
DENUCLEARIZATION OF THE
PENINSULA.
THERE COULD BE WIGGLE ROOM
THERE.
I DON'T THINK NORTH KOREA WOULD
FREEZE IT UP.
>> Shepard: THANKS, JOHN
ROBERTS.
GORDON CHANG WROTE THE BOOK ON
NORTH KOREA.
HE'S OUR GUEST LIVE NEXT.
WILL THIS WORK?
THAT'S NEXT.
When my doctor told me
I have age-related macular
degeneration, AMD,
he told me to look at this
grid every day.
And we came up with a plan
to help reduce
my risk
of progression,
including PreserVision
AREDS 2.
My doctor said
PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
the National Eye
Institute recommends
to help reduce
the risk of progression of
moderate to advanced AMD
after 15 years
of clinical studies.
PreserVision
AREDS 2.
Because my eyes
are everything.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
>> Shepard: NEW SANCTIONS ON
NORTH KOREA WITH CHINESE HELP.
LET'S GO TO GORDON CHANG, AUTHOR
OF "NUCLEAR SHOW DOWN: NORTH
KOREA TAKES ON THE WORLD."
GORDON, THANK YOU.
>> THANKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: A BIT OF A MUTED
RESPONSE.
SOMETHING ABOUT DOGS BARKING.
YOUR THOUGHTS?
>> YEAH, THIS IS EXTREMELY
SIGNIFICANT.
WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP DID AND
WHAT TREASURY SECRETARY MNUCHIN
IS NOW DOING IS SHUTTING OFF THE
MONEY TO THE NORTH KOREAN
REGIME.
EVERY BANK GETS A FREE PASS FOR
WHAT THEY DID IN THE PAST WITH
THEIR RELATIONS WITH PYONGYANG.
WHAT MNUCHIN SAID, LOOK, GOING
FORWARD, IF A BANK VIOLATES U.S.
LAW, IT WILL BE DESIGNATED.
YOU HEARD THAT WORD
"DESIGNATION" IN THE PRESS
CONFERENCE.
THAT'S UNDER 311 OF THE PATRIOT
ACT.
IF A BANK IS SO DESIGNATED, IT'S
CUT OFF FROM THE GLOBAL
FINANCIAL SYSTEM BECAUSE IT CAN
NO LONGER TRANSACT BUSINESS IN
DOLLARS.
WHAT THE NORTH KOREANS NOW WILL
DO IS TRY TO TRANSACT BUSINESS
IN OTHER CURRENCIES, WHAT THE
UNITED STATES IS GO AROUND THE
WORLD AND MAKE SURE THEY CAN'T
USE OTHER CURRENCIES.
>> Shepard: THE NORTH KOREANS
DIDN'T SAY MUCH.
THEY WAIT AWHILE.
YOU WONDER IF THEY WON'T WAIT
UNTIL ALL OF THESE WORLD LEADERS
GO BACK TO THEIR HOMES.
>> OH, ABSOLUTELY.
THE LAST THING THEY WANT TO DO
IS ENGAGE IN A PROVOCATION THAT
GIVES UP TRUMP TO TALK TO OTHER
WORLD LEADERS.
I EXPECT THE NORTH KOREANS TO BE
QUIET A WORK OR SO.
YOU HEARD WHAT NORTH KOREA SAY
ABOUT THE WORDS OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP, LIKE A DOG BARKING.
THEY'RE SEEING THAT THE U.S. CAN
EXERT PRESSURE ON THEIR PRIMARY
BACKER.
NORTH KOREA IS IN A WORLD OF
HURT.
>> Shepard: JOHN ROBERTS REPORTS
THE BIG PICTURE IS TO GET NORTH
KOREANS TO THE NEGOTIATING
TABLE.
DOES THIS HELP?
>> OBVIOUSLY NEGOTIATIONS ARE
THE PREFERRED WAY OF SOLVING
THIS.
I BELIEVE WE SHOULD START THE
DISCUSSIONS ONLY WHEN THE NORTH
KOREANS UNDERSTAND THAT THEY
HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO DISARM.
IF WE START THEM EARLIER THAN
THAT, THEY WILL USE THEM TO
DELAY TO PERFECT THEIR MISSILES
AND NUKES.
THAT'S WHAT WE DID IN THE
SIX-PARTY TALKS IN THE
ADMINISTRATION OF GEORGE W.
BUSH.
WE DON'T WANT TO DO THAT AGAIN.
THE PRESIDENT, OUR PRESIDENT
UNDERSTANDS THAT, AND I THINK
WE'LL SEE MAXIMUM PRESSURE,
MAXIMUM ENGAGEMENT, WHICH IS THE
BUZZ PHRASE IN WASHINGTON.
IT MIGHT WORK THIS TIME IF THE
ADMINISTRATION IS ABSOLUTELY
DETERMINED TO CARRY FORWARD ON
THIS.
>> Shepard: SHORT ON TIME.
LESS LIKELY OR MORE LIKELY TO
GET ANOTHER MISSILE TEST?
>> THERE WILL BE ANOTHER MISSILE
TEST.
THE NORTH KOREANS NEED TO
IMPROVE THEIR CAPABILITIES.
THEY WANT A DETERRENT.
THEY WANT TO SELL THESE THINGS
TO THE IRANIANS, THIS IS WHERE
WE COME IN.
THE IRANIANS PAY THE NORTH
KOREANS $2 BILLION TO $3 BILLION
A YEAR.
WHAT MNUCHIN IS DOING WILL CUT
OFF THAT FLOW OF CASH IF HE'S
SUCCESSFUL.
WE HAVE TO BE CONCERNED THAT THE
NORTH KOREANS DON'T SWITCH TO
OTHER CURRENCIES.
THE ONE CURRENCY WE CAN'T
CONTROL IS THE CHINESE CURRENCY.
>> GORDON CHANG FROM WASHINGTON.
THANK YOU.
>> THANK YOU, SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: THERE'S BREAKING
NEWS FROM THE EARTHQUAKE IN
MEXICO.
MOMENTS AGO, WORD THAT THERE ARE
NO CHILDREN STILL ALIVE IN THAT
SCHOOL THAT COLLAPSED THERE
AFTER TUESDAY'S POWERFUL
EARTHQUAKE.
THAT CAME FROM THE MEXICAN NAVY.
EARLIER REPORTS HAD INDICATED
THAT UP TO SIX CHILDREN MIGHT BE
ALIVE IN THE RUBBLE.
THE ASSOCIATED PRESS QUOTING AN
OFFICIAL FROM THE MEXICAN NAVY
SAYS THERE MAY STILL BE AN ADULT
ALIVE IN THE WRECKAGE.
THEY BELIEVE THERE IS, BUT NO
CHILDREN.
THE PILE OF WRECKAGE SHIFTED
DRAMATICALLY THIS MORNING.
WORKERS HAVE BEEN TRYING TO PROP
IT UP WITH IRON BEAMS.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW MANY SETS OF
HUMAN REMAINS MAY BE UNDERNEATH.
A SEARCH AND RESCUE TEAM FROM
LOS ANGELES IN MEXICO TO HELP, A
PHOTO OF THEM HERE ON A CARGO
PLANE.
THE U.S. AMBASSADOR TO MEXICO
SAYS THEY HAVE EXPERTS AND TONS
OF EQUIPMENT.
MEXICAN OFFICIALS SAY SO FAR THE
QUAKE HAS KILLED 245 PEOPLE AND
INJURED MORE THAN 2,000.
OUR CHIEF CORRESPONDENT,
JONATHAN HUNT IS LIVE AT THE
SCHOOL.
JONATHAN?
>> SHEP, IT'S A VERY TENSE SCENE
HERE AT THE SCHOOL RIGHT NOW.
THE SCHOOL IS ABOUT 50 YARDS OR
SO BEHIND ME.
IT'S A HIVE OF ACTIVITY AND
REMAINS SO.
RUBBLE BEING BROUGHT OUT FROM
THE SCENE, LOADED ON TO THE
TRUCKS YOU CAN SEE HERE.
AS WE COME LEFT AND DOWN A BIT,
YOU CAN SEE THE SUPPLY TENTS.
THESE ARE SET UP TO SUPPORT THE
RESCUE WORKERS IN THEIR HUNDREDS
IF NOT THOUSANDS OF VOLUNTEER
CIVILIANS DOING WHAT THEY CAN DO
HELP IN THIS VERY INTENSE RESCUE
EFFORT, SHEP.
WE HAVE BEEN GETTING CONFLICTING
REPORTS ALL DAY AS YOU JUST
POINTED OUT ABOUT WHETHER OR NOT
THERE MAY BE ANY SURVIVORS
UNDERNEATH THE RUBBLE OF THAT
SCHOOL AND WHETHER, IF THERE
ARE, THEY ARE CHILDREN OR
ADULTS.
THE LATEST AS YOU SAID FROM THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS, HEARING FROM
THE MEXICAN NAVY, WHICH IS ONE
OF THE INSTITUTIONS INVOLVED IN
THE RESCUE EFFORT, THAT THEY DO
NOT BELIEVE THERE ARE ANY
SURVIVING CHILDREN.
THEY DO BELIEVE THERE MAY BE AN
ADULT ALIVE.
WE HAVE HEARD DIRECTLY FROM OUR
SOURCES CLOSER IN TO THE SCHOOL
THAT A HEAT-SEEKING CAMERA HAS
PICKED UP A SIGNAL THAT MAY
INDICATE THAT THERE MAY BE
SOMEBODY ALIVE.
I WANT TO CAUTION EVEN WITH THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS HEARING THIS
FROM THE MEXICAN NAVY, THERE'S
SO MANY CONFLICTING REPORTS
FLOATING AROUND WHO MAY OR MAY
NOT BE ALIVE UNDERNEATH THAT
RUBBLE.
IT'S DIFFICULT TO TAKE ANYTHING
WITH ANY CERTAINTY AT THIS
POINT.
OBVIOUSLY THE PARENTS THAT ARE
STILL GATHERED HERE, THE PARENTS
OF THE CHILDREN WHO ARE STILL
MISSING ARE HOPING AGAINST HOPE
THAT THEIR CHILD MAY STILL BE
ALIVE, MAY COME OUT FROM
UNDERNEATH THAT RUBBLE.
OBVIOUSLY, SHEP, WE'RE SOME 48
HOURS ON FROM THAT 7.1
EARTHQUAKE AND WITH EVERY
PASSING MINUTE, HOPES OF FINDING
SURVIVORS HERE OR ANY OF THE
OTHER SITES BEGIN TO DIM.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: MUCH OF THE FOCUS
HAS BEEN ON THE SCHOOL.
BUT YOU MENTIONED THE OTHER
SITES.
IT APPEARS THERE'S DOZENS AND
DOZENS.
ANY PROGRESS?
>> INDEED THERE'S BEEN SOME
PROGRESS, SHEP.
WE WERE AT AN OFFICE BUILDING
THAT COLLAPSED.
YOU MIGHT HAVE LIVE PICTURES, IF
NOT, VIDEO FROM THAT BUILDING.
THAT IS IN DOWNTOWN MEXICO CITY,
AN AREA KNOWN AS ROMA.
IT COLLAPSED OVERNIGHT.
A MIRACLE THERE.
TWO WOMEN AND ONE MAN PULLED OUT
ALIVE.
THE SEARCH AND RESCUE EFFORT
GOES ON THERE.
WE'RE TOLD BY FAMILIES OF PEOPLE
WHO THEY BELIEVE WERE IN THE
OFFICE BUILDING AND STILL
MISSING, THERE MAY BE 14 PEOPLE
STILL TRAPPED IN THERE.
WHETHER THEY ARE DEAD OR ALIVE,
WE DON'T KNOW.
AS THE PRESIDENT SAID, IT'S A
RESCUE OPERATION.
THEY WON'T GIVE UP UNTIL THEY'RE
CERTAIN THERE'S NO CHANCES OF
ANYBODY ELSE SURVIVING.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THANKS, JONATHAN.
SADLY WE'RE WATCHING ANOTHER
UNFOLDING CATASTROPHE AND WORD
THAT PARTS OF PUERTO RICO COULD
BE WITHOUT POWER FOR NOT WEEKS
BUT MONTHS.
THAT'S AS HURRICANE MARIA
CONTINUES ITS DEADLY TREK
THROUGH THE CARIBBEAN.
THE LATEST STORM TRACK AND HOW
THE UNITED STATES' MAINLAND MAY
BE AFFECTED.
THAT'S AHEAD.
QUIET CONFIDENCE...
AT THE PUSH OF A BUTTON.
FOR 480 BUCKS...
ELECTRICITY WITHOUT THE SHOCK.
CABELA'S OUTDOORSMAN
REMOTE START GENERATOR.
GREAT PRICE.
EVERY DAY.
ONLY AT CABELA'S.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
RUSSIA THREATENING TO STRIKE
BACK IF THE U.S. MILITARY OR
ALLIES FIRE AT RUSSIAN SOLDIERS
IN SYRIA.
THE KREMLIN WARNING THAT SPECIAL
FORCES ARE DEPLOYEDED IN SYRIA
WHERE U.S. BACKED FIGHTERS, ISIS
AND THE RUSSIAN-SUPPORTED SYRIAN
REGIME ARE BATTLING IT OUT.
AN EXPLOSION IN LOS ANGELES.
A BLAST DESTROYED A GARAGE AND
SEVERAL SURROUNDING HOMERS.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE RULED OUT
ILLEGAL DRUG MAKING OR OTHER
CRIMINAL ACTIVITIES.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
A RUN-AWAY GOAT WANDERED INTO A
HOTEL IN MASSACHUSETTS.
COPS SAY THE GOAT WAS ON THE
LOSE 24 HOURS BEFORE POLICE
BROUGHT HIM HOME.
HE JUMPED THE FENCE AND TOOK OFF
LIKE A CRIMINAL.
THE NEWS CONTINUES WITH SHEPARD
SMITH AFTER THIS.
I count on my
Dell Small Business Advisor
for tech advice.
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪
So we sent that sample
I doff to Ancestry. I
was from ethnically.
My Ancestry DNA results
are that I am 26% Nigerian.
I am just trying to
learn as much as I can
about my culture.
I put the Gele on my
head and I looked
into the mirror and I
was trying not to cry.
Because it's a hat,
but it's like the most
important hat I've
ever owned.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
when I feel controlled
by frequent,
unpredictable abdominal pain
or discomfort
and diarrhea.
I tried lifestyle changes
and over-the-counter treatments,
but my symptoms keep
coming back.
It turns out I have
Irritable Bowel Syndrome
with Diarrhea,
or IBS-D.
A condition that's really
frustrating.
That's why I talked to my
doctor about VIBERZI...
...a different way
to treat IBS-D.
VIBERZI is a
prescription medication
you take every day
that helps proactively manage
both abdominal pain and
diarrhea at the same time.
So I can stay ahead of
my symptoms.
VIBERZI can cause new or
worsening abdominal pain.
Do not take VIBERZI
if you have no gallbladder,
have pancreas or
severe liver problems,
problems with alcohol abuse,
long-lasting or
severe constipation,
or a bowel or
gallbladder blockage.
Pancreatitis may occur
and can lead to
hospitalization and death.
If you are taking VIBERZI,
you should not take medicines
that cause constipation.
The most common side effects of
VIBERZI include constipation,
nausea, and abdominal pain.
Stay ahead of IBS-D
with VIBERZI.
>> Shepard: HURRICANE MARIA IS
GAINING STRENGTH AS IT'S MOVING
ACROSS THE CARIBBEAN.
AS PUERTO RICANS LOOK AT THE
DAMAGE THAT THE MAYOR OF THE
CAPITOL CITY SAYS SOME PLACES
COULD BE WITHOUT POWER FOR SIX
MONTHS.
MARIA IS BRINGING CATASTROPHIC
FLOODING TO PUERTO RICO.
THE STORM HIT THE ISLAND AS A
CATEGORY FOUR STORM, 155 MILES
AN HOUR SUSTAINED WINDS.
THE STRONGEST HURRICANE
ACCORDING TO THE NATIONAL
HURRICANE CENTER TO HIT PUERTO
RICO IN MORE THAN 80 YEARS.
RESCUE WORKERS TODAY DEALING
WITH DOWNED STREETS AND FLOODING
STREETS AS THEY TRY TO REACH
VICTIMS THAT NEED HELP.
THE STORM DESTROYED HUNDREDS OF
HOMES AND KNOCKED OUT
ELECTRICITY TO THE ISLAND AND
BROUGHT DOWN CELL PHONE TOWERS
AND LEAVING MOST PEOPLE UNABLE
TO CALL FOR HELP OR CALL FOR
FAMILY MEMBERS.
MORE IMAGES TO SHARE IN THE
SLIDE SHOW THIS AFTERNOON.
THIS IS TYPICAL DAMAGE, I'M
TOLD.
A FLOODED GAS STATION ON THE
ISLAND'S EAST COAST.
THE SAME AREA, AMBULANCES
TRAPPED UNDER THE COLLAPSED
ROOF.
THE ROAD LITTERED WITH POLES AND
POWER LINES.
LOOK AT THAT.
THINK HOW LONG IT WOULD TAKE TO
FREE UP THIS ROAD AND FREE UP
THE POWER LINES?
THERE'S A WHOLE ISLAND LIKE
THAT.
HERE'S WHAT'S LEFT OF A HOUSE
NEXT TO THE SOUTHERN COAST.
THE ENERGY MANAGEMENT DIRECTOR
SAID IT WILL BE A HISTORIC
EVENT.
AND THIS IS NEAR PUNTA CANA.
YOU CAN SEE A DAMAGED RESTAURANT
IN THE AREA.
A CATEGORY THREE STORM BY THE
TIME IT BATTERED THAT ISLAND
TODAY WITH WINDS SUSTAINED AT
NEARLY 115 MILES AN HOUR.
FORECASTERS SAY MARIA REGAINED
MAJOR HURRICANE STATUS AS IT
MOVED OFF THE COAST OF THE
DOMINICAN REPUBLIC TODAY.
THE NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER
HERE IN THE U.S. REPORTS THAT
MARIA IS EXPECTED TO BRING
DANGEROUS WINDS, HEAVY WIND TO
THE TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS AND
THE BAHAMAS LATER TODAY.
MORE AHEAD IN THE FORECAST.
WE'RE LOOKING AT THE WHITE
SPREAD DAMAGE IN ST. CROIX AND
THE U.S. VIRGIN ISLANDS.
IT WAS A CAT FIVE MONSTER WHEN
IT PASSED OVER-TUESDAY.
THERE'S MORE FLOODING IN
ST. THOMAS.
STEVE HARRIGAN IN SAN JUAN WITH
MORE.
>> A COUPLE OF FEET OF FLOODING
AROUND THESE APARTMENTS.
MANY PEOPLE IN THEIR BALCONIES.
THEY'RE WITHOUT ELECTRIC POWER.
PEOPLE TRUDGING THROUGH THIS
WATER WITH STICKS AS GUIDES.
OLDER PEOPLE GETTING HELP.
IT'S TOUGH TO SEE PEOPLE WALK
THROUGH WITH CHILDREN ON THEIR
BACKS OR CARRYING THEIR ITEMS IN
PLASTIC.
SOME WOMAN OVER HERE CHOP UP
WOOD WITH MACHETES AND HAMMERS
AND BUILD A COOKOUT.
IT'S OUTDOOR LIVING AT THE MOST
PRIMITIVE.
WE'VE SEEN A HYDRANT USED AS A
BATH THIS MORNING, SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: STEVE, ARE THEY
GETTING THE HELP IN THE EARLY
GOING?
>> WHEN YOU TALK ABOUT PEOPLE
INSIDE THEIR APARTMENTS OFTEN
WITH FLOOD WATER AND HOLES IN
THE ROOFS, THEY SAY THEY'RE NOT
GETTING ANYTHING.
IT'S A DO-IT-YOURSELF OPERATION.
IT'S PEOPLE TAKING RUBBISH FROM
HURRICANE IRMA AND TRYING TO USE
IT TO PROP UP A POWER LINE THAT
WAS DOWNED BY HURRICANE MARIA.
USING ONE HURRICANE TO HELP
ANOTHER.
HELP IS ON THE WAY FROM FEMA AND
FROM THE COAST GUARD.
RIGHT NOW MOODS ARE GOOD HERE.
THE PEOPLE ARE RESILIENT.
WITHOUT HELP QUICKLY, THAT COULD
CHANGE, SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: I SUSPECT SO.
STEVE HARRIGAN IN SAN JUAN.
LET'S GET MORE ON THE
HURRICANE'S PATH.
IT'S STILL ON THE MOVE AND HEAD
ADD CROSS THE CARIBBEAN.
CHIEF METEOROLOGIST RICK
REICHMUTH IN THE EXTREME WEATHER
CENTER.
RICK?
>> TURKS AND CAICOS WILL BE SPOT
THAT TAKES THE WORST OF IT.
WINDS 20 TO 50 MILES AN HOUR.
STILL MORE RAIN HERE.
FLOODING.
THE TURKS AND CAICOS, IT WILL
GET THERE CLOSE TONIGHT AND
TOMORROW.
THAT SAID, WE'RE WATCHING
TROPICAL STORM JOSE.
UP HERE ACROSS THE NORTHEAST.
THAT HAS CREATED A WEAKNESS IN
THE ATMOSPHERE.
IT'S GOING TO ALLOW MARIA TO
MOVE TO THE NORTH.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT OUR RELIABLE
COMPUTER GUIDANCE RIGHT NOW,
PULLS THIS UP BETWEEN BERMUDA
AND THE U.S.
AT THIS POINT IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S
GOING TO STAY BETWEEN THAT AREA.
IT'S A SLOW-MOVING STORM.
WE'RE GOING TO BE TALKING ABOUT
A WEEK OR SO BEFORE IT GETS INTO
THIS AREA.
MORE PROBLEMS FOR THE COAST.
CERTAINLY BEACH EROSION.
AS LONG AS WE THREAT THIS NEEDLE
BETWEEN BERMUDA AND THE EAST
COAST, I THINK WE'LL BE LOOKING
GOOD.
THE OFFICIAL TRACK FROM THE
NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER SHOWS
THAT.
KEEPING THIS WELL OFFSHORE AND
THEN EVENTUALLY BY THURSDAY TO
FRIDAY OUT TO SEE.
ANY BIG IMPACTS ACROSS THE U.S.
WON'T BE FELT.
>> Shepard: FINGERS CROSSED.
THANKS, RICK.
OFFICIALS IN FLORIDA HAVE
CONFIRMED A TENTH PERSON FROM A
NURSING HOME THERE HAS DIED
AFTER HURRICANE IRMA KNOCKED OUT
AIR CONDITIONING IN THE BUILDING
FOR THREE DAYS.
HEALTH OFFICIALS ARE SUSPENDING
THAT CENTER'S LICENSE SAYING
WORKERS ACTED WITH GROSS MEDICAL
AND CRIMINAL RECKLESSNESS.
WHY DIDN'T THEY CALL 911 WHEN
THE TEMPERATURES SOARED INTO THE
TRIPLE DIGIT AND ELDERLY PEOPLE
LEFT TO COOK.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
(AVO)it off with Contrave.
It's FDA-approved
to help adults who
are overweight or
struggle with obesity.
CONTRAVE is believed to work on
two areas of the brain:
Your hunger center...
I'm so hungry.
(AVO) To reduce hunger. And your
reward system...
Ice cream.
French fries.
(AVO) To help control cravings.
One ingredient in CONTRAVE may
increase suicidal thoughts or
actions in some children, teens,
and young adults in the
first few months.
Serious side effects are mood
changes like depression
and mania, seizures, increased
blood pressure or heart rate,
liver damage, glaucoma, allergic
reactions and hypoglycemia.
Not for patients with
uncontrolled blood pressure,
seizure history, anorexia,
bulimia, drug or alcohol
withdrawl, on bupropion,
opioids, MAOIs, allergy to the
ingredients, or pregnant.
May cause nausea, constipation,
headache and vomiting.
Reduce hunger, help control
cravings with Contrave.
Now you can talk to a doctor
online and get free shipping
at getcontravenow.com
>> Shepard: WORKERS AT THE
NURSING HOME IN FLORIDA AFTER
TEN PEOPLE DIED AFTER HURRICANE
IRMA.
HEALTH OFFICIALS ORDERED THE
FACILITY TO CLOSE.
THIS HAPPENED IN HOLLYWOOD,
FLOOR NORTH OF MIAMI.
NURSING HOME OFFICIALS HAVE
FILED A LAWSUIT DENYING ANY
WRONG DOING.
TRACE GALLAGHER WITH THE
DETAILS.
TRACE?
>> SHEP, FLORIDA HEALTH
OFFICIALS ARE ACCUSING THE
NURSING HOME OF GROSS CRIMINAL
AND RECKLESSNESS SAYING THE
TRAINED MEDICAL PROFESSIONALS AT
THE CITY OVERWHELMINGLY DELAYED
CALLING 911.
THE OFFICIALS SAY A WOMAN SHOWED
UP TO THE HOSPITAL WITH A
TEMPERATURE OF 108.3, BUT AT THE
VERY SAME TIME, SHE WAS DYING AT
THE HOSPITAL, THE NURSING HOME
RECORDED HER TEMPERATURE AT 101.
A 70-YEAR-OLD WOMAN SHOWED UP
WITH A BODY TEMPERATURE OF
109.9.
SHE DIED TEN MINUTES LATER.
JUST HOURS EARLIER, THE NURSING
HOME DESCRIBED HER OF BEING
ALERT, RECORDING HER TEMPERATURE
AT 101.
AN ELLED EARLY MAN ARRIVED AT
THE HOSPITAL WITH A BLUISH LIP
LOOK AND A BODY TEMPERATURE OF
107.
THE STATE OF FLORIDA SAYS THIS
FACILITY CANNOT CONTINUE TO HAVE
ACCESS TO PATIENTS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: NURSING HOME
OFFICIALS, I UNDERSTAND, ARE
FIGHTING BACK, TRACE.
>> YEAH, THEY ARE.
THE FACILITY HAS FILED A LAWSUIT
DENYING ANY WRONG DOING AND
ASKING A JUDGE TO ALLOW THEM TO
REOPEN.
THE NURSING HOME CONTENDS THEY
SPENT CONSIDERABLE TIME ASKING
FOR HELP, SAYING THEY CALLED THE
EMERGENCY LINE AND LEFT MULTIPLE
MESSAGES TO GOVERNOR SCOTT AND
MADE NUMEROUS REQUESTS WITH
FLORIDA POWER AND LIGHT.
REPORTS WITH THE GOVERNOR'S
OFFICE SHOW TWO DOCTORS FROM
SOUTH FLORIDA VISITED THE
RESIDENTS THE DAY BEFORE THE
TRAGEDY AND DID NOT FIND ANYONE
IN DISTRESS.
THE NURSING HOME SAYS ITS
EMPLOYEES TOOK REASONABLE
ACTIONS IN REAL TIME AND THEY'RE
UNFAIRLY BEING CRITICIZED BASED
ONLY ON HINDSIGHT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER,
THANK YOU.
SOMETHING NEW HAS JUST HAPPENED.
POTENTIALLY SOMETHING VERY
IMPORTANT.
FACEBOOK HAS JUST CONFIRMED THAT
IT WILL INDEED SHARE ADS THAT
THE RUSSIANS PURCHASED WITH
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATORS.
THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS OF
ADVERTISEMENTS DURING OUR
POLITICAL SEASON PURCHASED BY
THE RUSSIANS.
THIS IS PART OF LAWMAKERS'
INQUIRY TO RUSSIAN MEDDLING IN
OUR ELECTION AND DETAILS ARE
NEXT.
'Member that
accident I got in,
with the pole, and I had to
make a claim and all that?
Is that whole thing
still draggin' on?
No, I took some pics with
the app and filed a claim,
But, you know how they send you
money to cover repairs and -
-they took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid right away,
But, at the very end
of it all, my agent-
-wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy,
But, if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience,
for any reason...
...they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim
satisfaction guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>> Shepard: WE GOT BREAKING NEWS
JUST A MOMENT AGO.
THE FACEBOOK CEO, MARK
ZUCKERBERG THAT FACEBOOK JUST
STRUCK A DEAL WITH CONGRESS TO
REACH DETAILS ABOUT ADS THAT THE
RUSSIANS PURCHASED TO INFLUENCE
THE 2016 ELECTION.
MORE THAN 3,000 ADS APPEARED TO
HAVE COME FROM A RUSSIAN LINKED
FIRM.
FACEBOOK REPORTS THEY WILL
HAPPENED OVER THE ADS.
LET'S BRING IN CHAD DAY FROM THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS.
THIS IS A REVERSAL ON FACEBOOK'S
PART.
ZUCKERBERG IS SAYING WE HAVE TO
DO THIS, IT'S VITAL FOR THE
NATION AND ALL OF YOU OTHER
MEDIA COMPANIES YOU NEED TO DO
THE SAME THING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
SO THIS IS A BIG REVERSAL FOR
THEM.
PREVIOUSLY THEY DECIDED THEY
WEREN'T GOING TO TURN OVER THE
CONTENTS OF THE ADS THAT THEY
TRACED BACK TO RUSSIAN FIRMS
THAT WRITE POLITICAL, ON TOPICS
THAT WERE POLITICAL AND SOCIAL
ISSUES TARGETED DURING THE
CAMPAIGN.
A BIG TOPIC OF INTEREST FOR THE
COMMITTEES AND LEADERS OF THE
SENATE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
HAD BEEN TURNING OVER FOR THEM
TO TURN OVER THE CONTENTS TO ARE
YOU VERY THEM AND SEE IF THE ADS
WERE TARGETED AT SPECIFIC
GROUPS.
>> AND HOW THEY MIGHT HAVE BEEN
TARGETED TOWARDS SPECIFIC
GROUPS, WHETHER SOMEBODY LED THE
RUSSIANS TOWARD THAT.
THAT IS THE HEART OF THIS
INVESTIGATION, IS IT NOT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AS THE INVESTIGATIONS ARE
LOOKING AT THE RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN THE ELECTION BUT
LOOKING TO SEE IF THERE IS
ANYBODY ON THE AMERICAN SIDE TO
DIRECT WHERE THE ADS WOULD BE
TARGETED.
ONE OF THE MAIN THING THEY'RE
LOOKING AT, IF THEY'RE TARGETED
AT SPECIFIC GROUPS THAT COULD
DECREASE VOTER TURNOUT FOR
HILLARY CLINTON OR INCREASE
TURNOUT FOR TRUMP.
SO WHAT THE COMMITTEES
PARTICULARLY LOOKED AT, THAT'S
SOMETHING THAT AN AMERICAN
POLITICAL OPERATIVE WOULD KNOW.
SO THAT'S OF PARTICULAR INTEREST
TO THEM AND LOOKING FOR WHETHER
THERE WAS ANY COORDINATION
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
RUSSIANS IS PART OF THIS RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE.
SO FAR THE COMMITTEES HAVE SAID
WE'VE SEEN EVIDENCE OF
COORDINATION BUT THEY HAVEN'T
SAID ANYTHING CONCLUSIVELY.
>> Shepard: WHICH TAKES US BACK
TO PAUL MANAFORT WHO WAS WITH
THE CAMPAIGN FOR A SHORT PERIOD
OF TIME.
AT ANY RATE, IT'S CLEAR TO
INVESTIGATORS THAT HE OFFERED A
PRIVATE BRIEFING TO A RUSSIAN
BILLIONAIRE WITH CLOSE TIES TO
VLADIMIR PUTIN.
IT APPEARS THE FEDS WANT TO KNOW
WHY HE DID THAT AND A LOT ELSE.
>> RIGHT.
SO YOU KNOW, THIS IS AN OFF OF A
BRIEFING FOR A RUSSIAN
BILLIONAIRE WHO HAS BEEN
DESCRIBED AS BEING CLOSE TO
PUTIN.
THIS WAS SOMETHING THAT WAS
DESCRIBED IN AN E-MAIL BETWEEN
POWELL MANAFORT AND A FORMER
WORKER OR FORMER EMPLOYEE OF HIS
A UKRAINIAN NATIONAL THAT WORKED
WITH HIM ON POLITICAL CONSULTING
IN THE UKRAINE.
SO WE DON'T KNOW -- WHAT WE
DON'T KNOW YET, A LOT WE DON'T
KNOW ABOUT THIS POINT, WHETHER
THAT OFFER WENT TO THE RUSSIANS.
THE STORY WAS BROKE YET AND IT
WAS NOTED THERE WERE NO
BRIEFINGS THAT OCCURRED OR
WHETHER THIS OFFER WAS ACTUALLY
PASSED TO THE RUSSIANS.
WHAT WE DO KNOW IS THAT THE
E-MAILS ARE LEGITIMATE AND
ROBERT MUELLER HAS THEM IN HIS
POSSESSION AS WELL AS
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEES.
THEY'LL LOOK AT THIS WHEN THEY
LOOK AT DIRECT TIES OR LINKS
BETWEEN THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
RUSSIANS.
>> Shepard: THE BIG PICTURE
QUESTION, WAS SOMEONE WITHIN THE
CAMPAIGN DIRECTING THE RUSSIANS
WHERE TO PLACE THE ADS TO HELP
DONALD TRUMP GET ELECTED AND
HURT HILLARY CLINTON'S CHANCES
TO THAT WE DON'T KNOW THE
ANSWER.
BUT THE SPECIAL PROSECUTOR IS
WORKING ON IT NOW.
CHAD DAY FROM ASSOCIATED PRESS.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Dynamic performance,
Track tuned handling,
and aggressive styling.
The bold Lexus IS.
Lease the 2017 IS Turbo for
$299 a month for 36 months.
Experience Amazing at
your Lexus dealer.
You totaNobody's hurt, new car.
but there will still be pain.
It comes when your insurance
company says they'll only pay
three-quarters of what
it takes to replace it.
What are you supposed to do?
Drive three-quarters of a car?
Now if you had Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
you'd get your whole car back.
I guess they don't want you
driving around on three wheels.
Smart.
With Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
we'll replace the full
value of your car.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>> Shepard: ON THIS DAY IN 1938,
ONE OF THE MOST DESTRUCTIVE
HURRICANES ON RECORD HIT THE
NORTHEAST.
IT CRASHED INTO NEW YORK'S LONG
ISLAND AND WENT TO CONNECTICUT.
HAD WINDS 186 MILES AN HOUR.
THE STORM DOWNED POWER LINES
WHICH STARTED CATASTROPHIC FIRES
AND FLOODING.
FORECASTERS CALLED IT THE GREAT
NEW ENGLAND HURRICANE THAT HIT
79 YEARS AGO TODAY.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
BREAKING NEWS CHANGES EVERYTHING
ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
THE DOW WITH A DOWNED DAY.
DON'T BLAME AIR AERO SPACE AND
DEFENSE STOCKS.
TEN OF THEM HIT ALL-TIME HIGHS
AFTER THE PRESIDENT'S REMARKS.
"YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL CAVUTO
STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>> Neil: THANK YOU.
I'M NEIL CAVUTO, THIS IS "YOUR
WORLD."
WHAT IN THE WORLD WAS THE
PRESIDENT ABLE TO DO THAT SO
MANY OF HIS PREDECESSORS IN BOTH
PARTIES WERE NOT?
EVER SINCE NORTH KOREA STARTED
AGITATING WITH A NUCLEAR FUTURE,
THE PRESIDENTS GOING BACK TO
GEORGE BUSH SR. TRIED TO REIGN
THEM IN BY GETTING THE CHINESE
TO REIGN THEM IN BUT THEY
FAILED.
AGAIN AND AGAIN THROUGH GEORGE
BUSH SR. AND BILL CLINTON AND
GEORGE W. BUSH AND BARACK OBAMA.
THEY FAILED.
AGAIN AND AGAIN.
THAT WAS UNTIL TODAY.
INDICATIONS FROM THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES THAT
CHIN