HAS ALL THE STORY WRAP-UP.
I CONTRIBUTE TO IT.
IT'S CALLED BAIR TRACKS.
THAT'S IT FOR THIS "SPECIAL
REPORT," FAIR, BALANCED,
UNAFRAID.
>> TONIGHT WALL STREET CHAOS AS
SOME KIND OF GLITCH LOCKS UP
TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS.
AND NOW WORD ON WHAT CAUSED IT.
PLUS THE FORMER NFL PLAYER TODAY
INDICTED FOR MURDER.
PROSECUTORS MAKE THEIR CASE
AGAINST AARON HERNANDEZ.
>> WE'RE ABOUT GETTING JUSTICE
FOR VICTIMS.
>> THE DEFENSE IS VOWING TO
CLEAR HIS NAME.
>> AARON HERNANDEZ IS AN
INNOCENT MAN AS WE STAND HERE
TODAY.
>> TONIGHT THE SHOWDOWN IN
COURT.
EGYPT'S FORMER LEADER LEAVES
PRISON MORE THAN TWO YEARS AFTER
THE REVOLUTION THAT TOPPLED HIM.
AND A THREAT OF POSSIBLE FORCE
AGAINST SYRIA AFTER A CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK REPORTEDLY KILLED
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE, INCLUDING
CHILDREN.
PLUS A GIANT SINKHOLE SWALLOWS A
BUNCH OF TREES IN A MATTER OF
SECONDS.
FIRST FROM FOX THIS THURSDAY
NIGHT, A GRAND JURY TODAY
INDICTED THE EX-FOOTBALL STAR
AARON HERNANDEZ ON CHARGES OF
MURDER IN THE FIRST DEGREE.
PROSECUTORS SAY HE SHOT AND
KILLED HIS FRIEND IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT LESS 18-MILE FROM
THE ATHLETE'S MILLION DOLLAR
MANSION.
OUR PRODUCENER THE COURTROOM
SAYS HERNANDEZ APPEARED TO SMIRK
AS THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY WENT
THROUGH THE INDICTMENT, WHICH
ALSO INCLUDES CHARGES RELATED TO
GUN POSSESSION.
PROSECUTORS SAY AARON HERNANDEZ
GUNNED DOWN HIS FRIEND, A SEMI
PRO FOOTBALL PLAYER NAMED ODIN
LLOYD EXECUTION STYLE IN JUNE.
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO FROM AARON
HERNANDEZ'S HOME IS SAID TO SHOW
HIM CARRYING A GUN JUST MOMENTS
AFTER THAT SHOOTING HAPPENED,
BUT HIS DEFENSE LAWYER SAYS
PROSECUTORS STILL DO NOT HAVE
THE EVIDENCE TO PROVE THEIR CASE
BEYOND A REASONABLE DOUBT.
>> WE BELIEVE THAT BURDEN WILL
NOT BE CARRIED.
AARON HERNANDEZ IS AN INNOCENT
MAN AS WE STAND HERE TODAY.
>> WE WANTED TO PRESENT AS MUCH
EVIDENCE TO THE GRAND JURY AS WE
COULD BEFORE WE ASKED FOR THE
VOTE.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT WE DID.
>> Shepard: KEEP IN MIND, THE
FORMER NEW ENGLAND PATRIOT'S
LEGAL TROUBLES MAY BE JUST
BEGINNING.
ACCORDING TO OUR STATION IN
BOSTON, MY FOX BOSTON, POLICE
FOUND A GUN THAT SOMEBODY USED
IN TWO OTHER MURDERS BACK IN
2012.
INVESTIGATORS ARE REPORTEDLY
TRYING TO LINK AARON HERNANDEZ
TO THOSE MURDERS AS WELL.
MOLLY LYON IS OUTSIDE THE
COURTHOUSE IN ATTLEBOROUGH.
MOLLY?
>> THE CASE AGAINST AARON
HERNANDEZ WILL GO FORTH IN
SUPERIOR COURT, BUT TODAY HE
FACED A DISTRICT COURT JUDGE, A
COURTROOM FULL OF REPORTERS, AND
ALSO THE FAMILY MEMBERS OF THE
MAN HE'S ALLEGED TO HAVE KILLED.
THE BODY OF 27-YEAR-OLD ODIN
LLOYD WAS DISCOVERED ON JUNE
17th.
HIS MOTHER AND NUMEROUS OTHER
RELATIVES WORE PINS TODAY IN HIS
MEMORY.
>> I DON'T THINK HAPPY IS THE
RIGHT WORD.
THIS WAS A VERY GRAVE CASE.
MY HEART GOES OUT TO THE LLOYD
FAMILY.
I JUST MET WITH SOMEWHERE AROUND
10 OF HIS FAMILY MEMBERS.
THIS IS A GRIM PROFESSION.
>> AN ATTORNEY REPRESENTING
HERNANDEZ INSISTED HE'S INNOCENT
TODAY.
>> THERE HAS BEEN AN INCREDIBLE
RUSH TO JUDGMENT IN THIS CASE.
IT HAS BEEN BASED ON INNUENDO,
MISREPRESENTATION OF FACTS,
HEARSAY AND OPINION HAS BEEN
REPRESENTED AS FACT AND AS
EVIDENCE, AND IT IS NOT.
>> ALSO INDICTED TODAY, EARNEST
WALLACE, 47 YEARS OLD, FOR
ACCESSORY AFTER THE FACT OF
FIRST-DEGREE MURDER, AND A
COUSIN FROM HERNANDEZ'S HOMETOWN
OF BRISTOL, CONNECTICUT, WAS
INDICTED, 37-YEAR-OLD TANYA
SINGLETON FOR REFUSING TO
TESTIFY BEFORE THE GRAND JURY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: MOLLY, THERE MAY BE
SEVERAL IMPORTANT PLAYERS IN
THIS CASE.
FROM FRIENDS OF AARON HERNANDEZ
TO HIS RELATIVES.
TODAY ON STUDIO B, THE CRIMINAL
DEFENSE ATTORNEY HEATHER HANSON
EXPLAINED HOW PROSECUTORS MAY BE
TRYING TO GET ONE OR MORE OF
THOSE PEOPLE TO TURN ON
HERNANDEZ.
>> THE COUSIN WAS ALSO INDICTED
TODAY, BECAUSE SHE REFUSED TO
TESTIFY AT THE GRANDURY.
WALLACE, ONE OF THE PEOPLE WHO
WERE WITH HIM, WAS INDICTED
TODAY AS AN ACCESSORY AFTER THE
FACT.
THERE ARE A LOT OF PEOPLE
INVOLVED IN THIS.
THE FIANCEE WILL HAVE MORE
INVESTIGATION AFTER HER, BECAUSE
THERE'S THOUGHT HE HAD HELPED TO
GET RID OF THE GUN.
THERE'S A LOT OF PEOPLE WHO
COULD BE INVOLVED, A LOT OF
PEOPLE WHO SEEM TO BE AFRAID OF
HIM.
>> Shepard: THE FIANCEE LEFT THE
COURTHOUSE IN TEARS TODAY.
SO FAR SHE DOES NOT FACE CHARGES
IN CONNECTION WITH THE SHOOTING.
MINUTES AGO WE GOT WORD THAT
JURORS DECIDING THE CASE OF THE
ACCUSED FORT HOOD SHOOTER ARE
HEADED HOME TONIGHT, NO VERDICT
TODAY.
JURORS SPENT FOUR HOURS TEED
DELIBERATING THE FATE OF ARMY
MAJOR NIDAL HASSAN.
JURORS RETURNED TO COURT ABOUT
15 MINUTES AGO TO ASK A COUPLE
OF QUESTIONS, BUT AGAIN NO
VERDICT TONIGHT.
PROSECUTORS SAY THERE IS NO
QUESTION THAT MAJOR HASSAN
PLANNED AND CARRIED OUT THE
ATTACK IN 2009 AT THAT POST IN
TEXAS.
HE'S NEVER EVEN DISPUTED IT.
WHILE HE'S BEEN REPRESENTING
HIMSELF THROUGHOUT THE TRIAL,
HE'S HAD VERY LITTLE TO SAY, PUT
UP NO DEFENSE VIRTUALLY, JUST
ABOUT THE ONLY WORDS SPOKEN
TODAY WERE, "THE DEFENSE CHOOSES
NOT TO MAKE A CLOSING
STATEMENT."
THE 13-MEMBER JURY NEEDS ONLY
A 2/3 MAJORITY TO FIND MAJOR
HASSAN GUILTY OF THE CHARGES,
BUT IF THEY WANT THE MILITARY TO
EXECUTE HIM THEY WILL HAVE TO
ALL BE ON BOARD.
CASEY STEGALL WITH THE NEWS
TONIGHT.
CASEY?
>> EVERY SINGLE PERSON ON THAT
PANEL IS A SENIOR RANKING ARMY
OFFICIAL, AN OFFICER, A RANK IN
FACT OF MAJOR OR HIGHER.
THEY WERE CAREFULLY SELECTED,
YOU'LL REMEMBER, AT THE
BEGINNING OF JULY FROM U.S. ARMY
POSTS ALL AROUND THE WORLD.
THEY HAVE NOT BEEN SEQUESTERED
SINCE THIS COURT MARTIAL BEGAN
ON AUGUST 6th, BUT CLEARLY
INSTRUCTED NOT TO READ ANYTHING
ABOUT THIS EXTREMELY
HIGH-PROFILE CASE, WATCH ANY
NEWS REPORTS ABOUT IT OR TALK
WITH ANYONE ABOUT THEIR
INVOLVEMENT.
AT THIS HOUR THEY'RE GOING
THROUGH THE LONG LIST OF 45
CHARGES, 13 PREMEDITATED MURDER
FOR THOSE WHO DIED, AND 39
ATTEMPTED PREMEDITATED MURDER.
THE PANEL RELEASE RECESSED FOR E
NIGHT, CONTINUING TOMORROW
MORNING.
>> Shepard: IF HE'S FOUND
GUILTY, THEN IN HIS SENTENCING A
FAMILY MEMBER FROM EACH OF THE
13 VICTIMS WILL SPEAK ABOUT WHAT
THIS TRAGIC ACT DID TO THEIR
LIVES.
MEANTIME THE U.S. SOLDIER WHO
PLEADED GUILTY TO MURDERING 16
VILLAGERS IN AFGHANISTAN LAST
YEAR SAID TODAY IN COURT, I'M
TRULY, TRULY SORRY.
REMEMBER A JURY IS WORKING TO
DETERMINE WHETHER THE STAFF
SERGEANT ROBERT BALES SHOULD
HAVE ANY CHANCE OF PAROLE.
HE ALREADY FACES LIFE IN PRISON
AS A RESULT OF HIS PLEA DEAL.
TODAY IN COURT, THE SOLDIER
CALLED HIS PREDAWN MASSACRE AN
ACT OF COWARDICE AND ADDED
NOTHING MAKES IT RIGHT.
"SO MANY TIMES I'VE ASKED
MYSELF, I DON'T KNOW WHY, SORRY
ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH."
HE HOPES SOMEBODY WILL TRANSLATE
HIS REMARKS FOR THE AFGHAN
VILLAGERS WHOSE LOVED ONES DIED.
SOME OF THOSE SURVIVORS FACED
HIM IN COURT THIS WEEK AND SAID
THEY, TOO, STILL WISH TO KNOW
WHY HE WENT ON THE RAMPAGE.
>>> TRADING RESUMED ON THE
NATION'S LARGEST STOCK EXCHANGE
THIS AFTERNOON AFTER OFFICIALS
SAY A COMPUTER GLITCH FORCED A
THREE-HOUR SHUTDOWN OF THE
TECH-HEAVY NASDAQ, ALL TRADING
STOPPED.
IT HAPPENED SHORTLY AFTER THE
NOON HOUR TODAY ON THE EAST
COAST.
WHEN IT DIDN'T, TRADING OF SOME
OF THE BIGGEST TECH GIANTS,
INCLUDING APPLE, GOOGLE,
MICROSOFT, ALL SCREECHED TO A
HALT.
INVESTORS DIDN'T SEEM TOO
BOTHERED, BECAUSE THE NASDAQ
STILL CLOSED MORE THAN A PERCENT
HIGHER.
WE'RE LIVE IN OUR NEW YORK
NEWSROOM.
JO?
>> HI, SHEP.
NEARLY TWO HOURS AFTER THE
TRADING DAY ENDED, NASDAQ
FINALLY EXPLAINED THAT THE FLASH
FREEZE WAS CAUSED BY A GLITCH IN
ITS PROCESSOR USED TO DISTRIBUTE
STOCK QUOTES TO INVESTORS.
YOU CAN SEE HOW THE NASDAQ
FLATLINED HERE.
FULL TRADING DID NOT ROOM UNTIL
3:25 EASTERN TIME.
DURING THE TIME $5.7 TRILLION
WORTH OF SHARES WERE PARALYZED
AND INACCESSIBLE TO TRADERS.
NASDAQ SAID IN A STATEMENT THAT
WE WILL, QUOTE, WORK WITH OTHER
EXCHANGES TO INVESTIGATE THE
ISSUES OF TODAY AND WILL SUPPORT
ANY NECESSARY STEPS TO ENHANCE
THE PLATFORM.
EXPERTS SAY THERE'S LITTLE TO
WORRY WHEN IT COMES TO YOUR
401(K) OR IRA BECAUSE AS TRADING
NETWORKS HAVE BECOME MORE
INTERCONNECTED THE MARKET HAS
COME TO EXPECT GLITCHES LIKE
THESE.
EVEN PRESIDENT OBAMA HEARD ABOUT
THE ISSUE TODAY.
SHEP.
>> Shepard: THE SO-CALLED FLASH
CRASH OF 2010 CAUSED A DROP IN
THE DOW OF 1,000 POINTS.
WHILE A COMPUTER GLITCH CAUSED
TODAY'S PROBLEMS, BACK IN
DECEMBER OF 1987 A SQUIRREL
REPORTEDLY CAUSED A
SHORT-CIRCUIT THAT SHUT DOWN THE
NASDAQ FOR MORE THAN AN HOUR.
WALL STREET SURVIVED.
THE SQUIRREL DID NOT.
AND SEVEN YEARS LATER ANOTHER
SQUIRREL FORCED THE EXCHANGE TO
CLOSE WHEN IT CHEWED THROUGH
POWER CABLES.
AFTER ALL THAT, STOCKS CLOSED
HIGHER FOR THE FIRST TIME IN SIX
TRADING SESSIONS.
BESIDES THE NASDAQ'S GAIN, THE
DOW WAS UP 66, THE S&P UP 14.
THIS COMES DESPITE A REPORT THAT
SHOWS MORE AMERICANS ARE FRESH
OUT OF WORK, OR WERE LAST WEEK.
THE LABOR DEPARTMENT REPORTS
13,000 MORE PEOPLE FILED THEIR
FIRST CLAIMS FOR JOBLESS
BENEFITS, BUT THE TREND IS
CLEARLY HEADING IN THE OTHER
DIRECTION, AT LEAST FOR THE
MOMENT.
CLAIMS HAVE BEEN DROPPING IN
RECENT WEEKS, AND THEY'RE ABOUT
HALF OF WHAT THEY WERE DURING
THE WORST DAYS OF THE GREAT
RECESSION.
>>> DRAMATIC DETAILS ABOUT THE
FINAL MOMENTS BEFORE A GUNMAN
SHOT A BABY IN THE FACE RIGHT IN
FRONT OF HIS MOTHER.
THE ACCUSED KILLER'S CODEFENDANT
TALKS ABOUT HEARING THE SHOT
THAT HIT CHILD BETWEEN THE EYES.
>>> PLUS, THERE'S WORD THE MAYOR
ACCUSED OF SEXUALLY HARASSING 18
WOMEN NOW HAS CUT SOME SORT OF
DEAL WITH THE CITY.
THE LATEST ON THE FUTURE OF BOB
FILNER AND THE MONSTER HE SAYS
IS INSIDE HIM.
THAT'S COMING FROM THE
JOURNALISTS OF FOX NEWS ON THIS
THURSDAY "FOX REPORT."
♪
Reinforced with scratch-
resistant glass
and a unibody
Made Kevlar Strong.
Okay Google Now.
Call My Droid.
The new
Droid Ultra by Motorola.
When strength matters,
Droid Does.
I put in the hours
and built a strong reputation
in the industry.
I set goals and worked
hard to meet them.
I've made my success happen.
So when it comes
to my investments,
I'm supposed to just hand it
over to a broker and back away?
That's not gonna happen.
AVO: When you work with a
Schwab financial consultant,
you'll get the guidance you need
with the control you want.
Talk to us today.
but you had to leave rightce to
now, would you go? world,
Man: 'oh I can't go tonight'
Woman: 'I can't.'
Hero : That's what
Expedia asked me.
Host: Book the flight but
you have to go right now.
Hero: (Laughs) And I just go?
This is for real right?
This is for real?
I always said one day
I'd go to China,
just never thought
it'd be today.
ANNCR: We're giving away
a trip every day.
Download the Expedia app and
your next trip could be on us.
Expedia, find yours.
ICAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEVING HEARTBURN,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES
24-HOUR HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL
PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
>> Shepard: THERE'S WORD THIS
AFTERNOON THAT THE SAN DIEGO
MAYOR BOB FILNER MAY BE HOURS
AWAY FROM STEPPING DOWN.
A CITY ATTORNEY SAYS MAYOR
FILNER CUT A DEAL AND THE CITY
COUNCIL COULD APPROVE IT AS SOON
AS TOMORROW.
WE DON'T HAVE WORD YET ON THE
DETAILS, BUT LOCAL MEDIA DO
REPORT THAT THE MAYOR HAS AGREED
TO RESIGN.
18 WOMEN HAVE ACCUSED HIM OF
SEXUAL HARASSMENT, INCLUDING
GROPING, GRABBING, AND
SLOBBERING ON THEM.
A FORMER AIDE IS SUING MAYOR
FILNER, CLAIMING HE ONCE PUT HER
IN A HEADLOCK AND ASKED HER TO
WORK WITHOUT HER UNDERWEAR.
HER LAWYER SAYS THEY HAVE NOT
SIGNED OFF ON ANY DEAL.
A PHOTO REPORTEDLY SHOWS THE
DEMOCRATIC MAYOR LEAVING CITY
HALL LAST NIGHT AND PUTTING
BOXES INTO HIS CAR.
TODAY MAYOR FILNER'S FORMER
FIANCEE SAYS SHE HOPES THE CITY
CAN GET PAST THIS.
>> I'M HOPEFUL THAT THE IDEAS
AND THE VISION THAT CAPTURED THE
IMAGINATION AND VOTE OF SAN
DIEGOANS LAST NOVEMBER WILL
CONTINUE TO MOVE FORWARD THROUGH
NEW LEADERSHIP.
>> BOB FILNER HAS APOLOGIZED,
CLAIMINGS HE'S A HUGGER OF MEN
AND WOMEN.
HE SAYS HE RECENTLY UNDERWENT
INTENSIVE THERAPY FOR WHAT HE
ONCE CALLED A MONSTER INSIDE
HIM.
>>> JURORS FOM THE FIRST TIME
HAVE HEARD THE WORDS OF THE
TEENAGER CHARGED WITH SHOOTING
AND KILLING A BABY IN GEORGIA AS
THAT CHILD'S MOTHER PUSHED HIM
IN A STROLLER.
MORE ON THAT IN A MOMENT.
AT TEENAGER'S ALLEGED
ACCOMPLICE WHO I GUESS ALSO
CHARGED WITH MURDER, GAVE
DRAMATIC COURTROOM TESTIMONY
TODAY DETAILING THE SHOOTING.
DOMINIQUE LANG TOOK THE STAND
AND SAID THAT DEMARCUS ELKINS,
WHO YOU SEE HERE, TRIED TO ROB
THE BABY'S MOTHER AND THREATENED
THE CHILD.
LANG SAID ELKINS FIRED AT THE
GROUND, SHOT THE WOMEN IN THE
LEG, AND LET OFF A THIRD-ROUND.
AS THAT
BULLET THAT STRUCK THE BABY IN
THE FACE.
LANG ALSO TESTIFIED THAT HE AND
ELKINS HAD ESSENTIALLY JUST MET
EACH OTHER EARLIER THAT DAY.
>> SAY ANYTHING TO YOU AFTER
THAT?
>> YES, MA'AM.
>> WHAT DID HE SAY?
>> HE ASKED ME, DID I EVER OFF
SOMEBODY BEFORE.
>> WHAT DID YOU TELL HIM?
>> NO.
>> LANG SAYS HE WENT WITH
ELKINS, BECAUSE THE TEEN HAD
SHOWN HIM A GUN AND HE WAS
SCARED.
JOHN ROBERTS IS COVERING THE
AFFAIR LIVE IN MARIETTA,
GEORGIA.
JOHN?
>> SHEP, IN THAT INTERROGATION
VIDEO PRESENTED BY THE
PROSECUTION TODAY, DeMARCUS
ELKINS SAYS ON THE DAY OF THE
MURDER HE WOKE UP AT 10:00, LEFT
THE HOUSE AT 11:00, WENT
STRAIGHT TO SCHOOL.
POLICE THEN TELL ELKINS THEY
HAVE SURVEILLANCE VIDEO OF HIM
EARLIER IN THE DAY, AND HE'S A
PRIME SUSPECT IN THE MURDER OF
13-YEAR-OLD ANTONIO SANTIAGO.
HERE'S HOW ELKINS REACTED.
>> DUDE, I DON'T KNOW WHAT Y'ALL
TALKING ABOUT.
I DON'T CAREW!Ñ
ABOUT.
I GOT NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
>> AND HERE'S HOW THE DEFENSE
RESPONDS TO ALL OF THAT, BY
TRYING TO BLOW HOLES IN THE
CREDIBILITY OF ANYBODY WHO
TESTIFIED AGAINST ELKINS.
IN THE CROSSHAIRS TODAY WAS
DOMINIQUE LANG, WHO ADMITTED
UNDER WITHERING
CROSS-EXAMINATION, THAT HE LIED
TO INVESTIGATORS AT LEAST 15
TIMES.
>> WOULD YOU AGREE THAT RIGHT
BEFORE YOU SAY, I'M TELLING THE
TRUTH, SIR, I'M NOT FIXING TO
LIE TO YOU, THE INVESTIGATOR
TELLS YOU THIS IS YOUR LAST
OPPORTUNITY TO TELL ME THE EXACT
TRUTH, AND THAT'S ANOTHER
EXAMPLE OF WHERE YOU LIED DURING
THIS INTERVIEW, ISN'T IT?
>> OKAY, I LIED, I LIED, I LIED.
THE PROSECUTION IS EXPECTED TO
CALL BETWEEN 30 AND 35
WITNESSES.
SO FAR THEY'VE ONLY GOTTEN
THROUGH EIGHT.
SHEP, THIS COULD GO ON FOR A
LONG TIME, BECAUSE THE DEFENSE
WILL CALL ITS OWN SET OF
WITNESSES AS WELL.
>> Shepard: JOHN, DOMINIQUE LANG
ALSO SAID HE DOES NOT HAVE A
DEAL WITH PROSECUTORS AND THAT
HE AGREED TO TESTIFY, BECAUSE HE
JUST WANTS TO GO HOME.
>>> A 16-YEAR-OLD GIRL FROM
CALIFORNIA IS THANKING HER
RESCUERS AFTER INVESTIGATORS SAY
A FAMILY FRIEND KILLED HER
MOTHER AND BROTHER AND KIDNAPPED
HER.
HANNAH ANDERSON SPOKE WITH NBC
NEWS IN HER FIRST INTERVIEW
SINCE HORSEBACK RIDERS SPOTTED
HER WITH JAMES DIMAGGIO IN THE
WILDERNESS OF IDAHO AND AN FBI
TEAM SAVED HER.
SHE CORRECTED A REPORT THAT SHE
CALLED DIMAGGIO 13 TIMES BEFORE
HE GRABBED HER.
>> THE PHONE CALLS WEREN'T PHONE
CALLS.
THEY WEREN'T TEXTS, BECAUSE HE
WAS PICKING ME UP FROM CHEER
CAMP, AND HE DIDN'T KNOW THE
ADDRESS, LIKE, WHERE I WAS, SO I
HAD TO TELL HIM THE ADDRESS,
TELL HIM THAT I WAS GOING TO BE
IN THE GYM, NOT IN FRONT OF THE
SCHOOL, YOU SAY SO HE KNEW WHERE
TO COME GET ME.
>> Shepard: DIMAGGIO DIED AFTER
A SHOOTOUT WITH FBI AGENTS
NEARLY TWO WEEKS AGO NOW.
>>> INVESTIGATORS REPORT THAT
TEENAGERS ACCUSED OF KILLING A
MAN FOR FUN WERE ESSENTIALLY
RAISING THEMSELVES.
A LIVE REPORT ON THAT NEXT.
PLUS, WHY BOTHER WHY CHOPPING
DOWN TREES WHEN THE EARTH CAN
JUST SWALLOW THEM?
HOW THIS HAPPENED COMING UP.
CAN SAVE BY SHARING.
LIKE CARPOOLS...
POLLY WANTS TO KNOW
IF WE CAN PICK HER UP.
YEAH,
WE CAN MAKE ROOM.
YEAH.
[ Male Announcer ]
...OFFICE SPACE.
YES, WE'RE LOVING THIS
COMMUNAL SEATING. IT'S GREAT.
[ Male Announcer ]
THE BEST THING TO SHARE?
A DATA PLAN.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
ONE BUCKET OF DATA
FOR EVERYONE ON THE PLAN,
UNLIMITED TALK AND TEXT
ON SMART PHONES.
NOW, EVERYONE'S IN THE SPIRIT
OF SHARING.
HEY, CAN I BORROW YOUR BOAT
THIS WEEKEND?
NO.
[ Male Announcer ]
SHARE MORE. SAVE MORE.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
♪
ARE YOU FLO?
YES.         IS THIS THE THING
YOU GAVE MY HUSBAND?
WELL, YEAH, YES.
THE "NAME YOUR PRICE" TOOL.
YOU TELL US THE PRICE
YOU WANT TO PAY,
AND WE GIVE YOU A RANGE
OF OPTIONS TO CHOOSE FROM.
CAREFUL, THOUGH -- THAT KIND
OF POWER CAN GO TO YOUR HEAD.
THAT EXPLAINS
A LOT.
YO, BUDDY!
I GOT THIS.
GIMME ONE, GIMME ONE,
GIMME ONE!
THE POWER OF
THE "NAME YOUR PRICE" TOOL
ONLY FROM PROGRESSIVE.
>> Shepard: WE'RE LEARNING MORE
TONIGHT ABOUT THE THREE OKLAHOMA
TEENAGERS WHO INVESTIGATORS
ACCUSE OF MURDERING A MAN OUT OF
BOREDOM.
THE PROSECUTORS SAYS THE BOYS
AGE 15, 16 AND 17 DIDN'T HAVE
MUCH ADULT SUPERVISION.
HE SAYS THEY RAN AROUND THE
APARTMENT COMPLEX WHERE THEY
LIVED, QUOTE, PLAYING VIOLENT
VIDEO GAMES AND PRETTY MUCH
RAISING THEMSELVES.
OF COURSE NONE OF THAT IS MUCH
CONSOLATION TO THE VIETNAM OF FF
THIS MAN, CHRIS LANE, AN
AUSTRALIAN BASEBALL CLEAR
ATTENDING OKLAHOMA'S EAST
CENTRAL UNIVERSITY.
THEY DROVE UP BEHIND HIM,
INVESTIGATORS SAY, SHOT HIM, AND
DROVE OFF, MURDERING HIM FOR THE
FUN OF IT.
WE'RE LIVE IN CHICAGO TONIGHT.
GARRETT?
>> YES, SHEP.
JUST A FEW MONTHS AGO, THE
YOUNGEST OF THOSE THREE TEENS,
JAMES EDWARD JR. ALLEGEDLY
POSTED THIS ON TWITTER, "90% OF
WHITE APPLE ARE NASTY."
#HATETHEM A FEW DAYS AFTER THE
TRIAL OF GEORGE ZIMMERMAN, THERE
WAS THIS MESSAGE, USING SLANG,
HE BRAGGED ABOUT KNOCKING OUT
FIVE WHITE PEOPLE SINCE THE
VERDICT WAS READ.
WHEN WE SPOKE TO THE DISTRICT
ATTORNEY THIS AFTERNOON, THOUGH,
HE SAID AS OF RIGHT NOW THEY ARE
NOT FOCUSING ON THE CRIME --
FOCUSING ON THE MURDER RATHER AS
A HATE CRIME, BUT INSTEAD AS A
HOMICIDE.
WHILE POLICE ARE STILL SEARCHING
FOR THE MURDER WEAPON, SCHOOLS
ARE NOW BACK IN SESSION IN
DUNCAN, OKLAHOMA, BUT WITH
ADDITIONAL SECURITY AFTER
SEVERAL THREATS OF VIOLENCE
EARLIER IN WEEK.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: SOMEBODY SET UP AN
ONLINE FUND TO RAISE MONEY TO
HELP CHRIS LANE'S FAMILY FLY HIS
BODY HOME.
THE GOAL WAS TO RAISE ABOUT 15
GRAND.
AS OF THIS HOUR, PEOPLE HAVE
DONATED MORE THAN $110,000.
>>> BRADLEY MANNING NOW.
HE SAYS HE WANTS TO LIVE OUT THE
REST OF HIS LIFE AS A WOMAN.
HE SAYS HE IS FEMALE, AND HIS
NEW NAME IS CHELSEA MANNING.
JUST YESTERDAY A JUDGE SENTENCED
THE ARMY FIVE-DAY FORECAST 35
YEARS FOR GIVING WIKILEAKS
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF SECRET
U.S. GOVERNMENT DOCUMENTS.
BRADLEY MANNING'S LAWYER
RELEASED THIS PHOTO OF MANNING
DURING THE TRIAL, USED MANNING'S
GENDER IDENTITY DISORDER AS PART
OF HIS DEFENSE.
THE ATTORNEY SAYS HE'LL FIGHT TO
GET THE MILITARY TO GIVE MANNING
HORMONE TREATMENT IN PRISON.
RIGHT NOW OFFICIALS SAY THE ARMY
DOES NOT PROVIDE THAT TREATMENT.
MANNING'S LAWYER SAYS THE
PRIVATE WROTE A LETTER TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA, SAYING MANNING
KNOWS HE BROKE THE LAW, BUT THAT
HE DID IT OUT OF LOVE FOR HIS
COUNTRY.
>>> PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS A YEAR
AGO THAT THE USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS WOULD BE A RED LINE IN
SYRIA.
BUT NOW THAT THERE ARE DRAMATIC
NEW CLAIMS THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
IS HAPPENING AGAIN.
OTHER NATIONS APPEAR TO BE
TAKING A MUCH HARDER LINE.
JONATHAN HUNT REPORTS.
AND IT'S A FAMILIAR DRILL FOR
ANYBODY WHO'S EVER CONSIDERED
WHICH COLLEGE TO ATTEND.
YOU MAKE A LIST OF SCHOOLS, YOU
COMPARE THEM.
NOW THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT MIGHT
DO THE SAME THING.
NOT TO PLAN FOR A NEW COLLEGE
RATING SYSTEM AS WE APPROACH THE
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR AND THE TOP
OF THE NEWS.
MEET THE NEWEST MEMBER
OF THE Quicken Loans FAMILY:
J.D. Power and Associates
HAS RANKED Quicken Loans
HIGHEST IN THE NATION
IN CUSTOMER SATISFACTION...
I SAY "FAMILY,"
BECAUSE WE'VE BEEN BLESSED
WITH THIS HONOR
FOR 3 YEARS IN A ROW...
REST ASSURED WE'LL TREAT
ALL OF YOUR MORTGAGE NEEDS
WITH TENDER LOVING CARE.
AMAZING CLIENT SATISFACTION:
IT'S A Quicken Loans
FAMILY VALUE.
CALL 800-Quicken
OR GO TO QuickenLoans.com
TO EXPERIENCE IT FOR YOURSELF.
NO-CHARGE SCHEDULED MAINTENANCE.
CHECK.
AND HERE'S THE KICKER...
0% APR FOR 60 MONTHS.
AND WHO GOT IT?
THIS GUY.
THAT'S RIGHT...
[ Male Announcer ]
IT'S THE CAR YOU WON'T STOP
TALKING ABOUT. EVER.
HURRY IN TO THE VOLKSWAGEN
BEST. THING. EVER. EVENT.
AND GET 0% APR FOR 60 MOHS,
NOW UNTIL SEPTEMBER 3RD.
THAT'S THE POWER
OF GERMAN ENGINEERING.
THE NEXT POWERFUL STORM
IS GOING TO HIT...
BUT IT WILL...
THAT'S WHY
THERE'S A NEW DURACELL BATTERY.
INTRODUCING DURACELL QUANTUM.
WITH ITS HIGH DENSITY CORE,
IT'S A QUANTUM LEAP
IN BATTERY POWER.
THE NEXT STORM IS OUT THERE.
BUT SO ARE THE HEROES.
SO WE'RE GIVING
A MILLION DURACELL QUANTUM
TO FIRST RESPONDERS EVERYWHERE.
POWER. IN THE HANDS
OF THE MOST POWERFUL.
DURACELL.
TRUSTED EVERYWHERE.
EVERY DAY WE'RE WORKING TO
AND TO KEEP OUR COMMITMENTS.
AND WE'VE MADE A BIG
COMMITMENT TO AMERICA.
BP SUPPORTS NEARLY
250,000 JOBS HERE.
THROUGH ALL OF OUR
ENERGY OPERATIONS,
WE INVEST MORE IN THE U.S. THAN
ANY OTHER PLACE IN THE WORLD.
IN FACT, WE'VE INVESTED
OVER $55 BILLION HERE
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS -
MAKING BP AMERICA'S
LARGEST ENERGY INVESTOR.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS
NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
♪
(Train Horn)
VO: Wherever our trains go,
the economy comes to life.
Norfolk Southern.
One line,
infinite possibilities.
>> Shepard: SOME CRAZY VIDEO NOW
OF AN UNDER WATER SINKHOLE THAT
SWALLOWED A BUNCH OF TREES IN A
LOUISIANA BAYOU.
IT HAPPENED YESTERDAY IN A
WATERWAY WEST OF NEW ORLEANS.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY NOTICED THE
SINKHOLE LAST YEAR AND ORDERED A
MANDATORY EVACUATION OF THE
YEAR.
LOOK AT THIS.
STATE AND FEDERAL AGENCIES HAVE
REPORTEDLY BEEN MONITOR BEING IT
EVER SINCE.
CAMERAS HAPPENED TO BE ROLLING,
THEY TELL US, WHEN THE HOLE
OPENED UP AND SUCKED DOWN THE
TREES.
NOBODY GOT HURT.
>>> AT LEAST 30 PEOPLE ARE HURT
AFTER A MASSIVE WAVES CRASHED
INTO A COASTLINE.
THEY TOP OUR NEWS AROUND THE
WORLD IN 80 SECONDS.
>> Shepard: CHINA.
THOSE WAVES THE RESULT OF A
MAJOR STORM SWELLING THE
INCOMING TIDE THAT RUSHED INTO A
NARROW INLET, SMASHING A
RIVERBANK AND RIPPED UP PART OF
A SEAWALL IN THE EAST.
STATE MEDIA REPORT THE WATER
SHOT UP TO 60 FEET HIGH.
CREWS RUSHED THE INJURED
ONLOOKERS TO HOSPITALS.
>>> GREECE.
CREWS BATTLED A HUGE WILDFIRE
THAT CHARRED SOME 1500 ACRES ON
A POPULAR VACATION ISLAND.
AN OFFICIAL SAYS THIS COULD BE
THE LATEST IN A SERIES OF FIGHTS
THAT ARSONISTS HAVE STARTED THIS
SUMMER.
>>> HAITI.
FOLKS IN PUERTO PRINC
GROCERY STORE WORKER IS
MOONLIGHTING AS A SO-CALLED
SUPERHERO AT A SUBWAY IN TOKYO.
THE GUY DRESSES UP IN A GREEN
POWER RANGER SUIT AND VOLUNTEERS
TO CARRY COMMUTERS' BABY
STROLLERS AND HEAVY LUGGAGE UP
AND DOWN THE LONG FLIGHTS OF
STAIRS.
THE TRAVELERS LOVE THE SERVICE,
SINCE THEY'RE NO ELEVATOR AT THE
STATION.
THE GUY WANTS TO PUT TOGETHER A
FULL TEAM OF SUBWAY RANGERS TO
HELP OUT WHILE HE'S AT HIS DAY
JOB.
THAT'S A WRAP ON THIS FOX TRIP
AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 SECONDS.
>> Shepard: I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS THE "FOX REPORT."
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR,
TIME FOR THE TOP OF THE NEWS.
WE'RE BEING EXTERMINATED.
THAT'S WHAT ONE SYRIAN TOLD THE
REUTERS NEWS SERVICE TODAY.
OPPOSITION FORCES CLAIM THE
GOVERNMENT KILLED HUNDREDS OF
ITS OWN PEOPLE IN A CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK OUTSIDE DAMASCUS.
THEN THIS.
ACTIVISTS SAY THIS IS AMATEUR
VIDEO OF SYRIA SHELLING THE SAME
AREA AGAIN TODAY.
THERE IS VIDEO THAT PURPORTS TO
SHOW VICTIMS OF YESTERDAY'S
POISON GAS ATTACK.
THE GOVERNMENT DENIES USING
CHEMICAL WEAPONS, BUT IS
REFUSING TO LET UNITED NATIONS
INSPECTORS SEE IT FOR
THEMSELVES, EVEN THOUGH THOSE
INSPECTORS ARE ALREADY IN
DAMASCUS A FEW SHORT MILES AWAY
TO INVESTIGATE EARLIER CLAIMS OF
CHEMICAL ATTACKS.
JONATHAN HUNT IS LIVE IN NORTH
WITH AN UPDATE.
U.S. OFFICIALS ARE REFUSING TO
POINT FINGERS DESPITE THE VIDEO
AND ALL THE EVIDENCE.
>> YEAH, NOT JUST REFUSING TO
POINT FINGERS IN TERMS OF BLAME,
SHEP, BUT ACTUALLY SAYING THEY
HAVE NOT DEFINITIVELY CONCLUDED
THERE WAS A CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACK.
LISTEN HERE.
>> WE ARE UNABLE TO CONCLUSIVELY
DETERMINE CW USE, BUT WE'RE
FOCUSED ON DOING EVERYTHING
POSSIBLE WITHIN OUR POWER TO
NAIL DOWN THE FACTS.
>> NAILING DOWN THE FACTS WILL
INCLUDE LOOKING AT THIS VIDEO,
WHICH APPEARS TO SHOW SCORES OF
PEOPLE KILLED AND BEING TREATED
WITH NO SIGNS OF THE SORT OF
PHYSICAL TRAUMA THERE MIGHT BE
IF IT HAD BEEN A NORMAL SORT OF
BOMB ATTACK.
NOW, THE UNITED NATIONS AND
SECRETARY-GENERAL HAS ALSO
CALLED FOR AN URGENT
INVESTIGATION.
THOSE INSPECTORS, THE UNITED
NATIONS ONES ALREADY IN
DAMASCUS, AS YOU SAID, SHEP,
JUST 15 MINUTES AWAY FROM THE
SCENE OF THE ALLEGED ATTACK, BUT
UNABLE TO GET THERE WITHOUT
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT ASSISTANCE,
NOT FORTHCOMING RIGHT NOW.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THERE'S VIDEOS OF
DOZENS AND DOZENS AND DOZENS OF
CHILDREN DEAD ON THE FLOOR WITH
NO WOUNDS, JUST LYING DEAD.
SOME NATIONS HAVE LOOKED AT THIS
AND SAID, WE'VE GOT TO ACT.
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY.
THE FRENCH AMONG THE LEADING
NATIONS IN TERMS OF ISSUING
STRONG STATEMENTS.
THE FOREIGN MINISTER SAID TODAY
THAT IF INDEED IT IS
DEFINITIVELY DETERMINED THIS WAS
CHEMICAL WEAPONS USED BY THE
SYRIAN REGIME, THEN THERE MUST
BE A REACTION OF FORCE AS HE PUT
IT.
I SPOKE TO ONE LEADING MIDDLE
EAST EXPERT OF THE UNIVERSITY OF
SOUTH CAROLINA TODAY TO ASK HIM
WHAT EXACTLY HE BELIEVED
HAPPENED.
HE SAID 100% THIS IS THE WORK OF
THE GOVERNMENT REGIME.
HE SAID ASSAD TRIES TO CREATE A
NEW BALANCE OF FEAR WITH THE BYF
GAS AND CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
HE FEELS HE CAN DO IT.
THIS IS WHERE STRONG AMERICAN
REACTION CAN DETER HIM, BUT THAT
STRONG AMERICAN REACTION RIGHT
NOW SEEMS SOME WAY OFF.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: ANALYSTS BELIEVE
SYRIA HAS ONE OF THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST STOCKPILES OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS INCLUDING SARIN GAS,
MUSTARD GAS, AND MANY EXPERTS
WHO LOOKED THAT THE VIDEO
BELIEVE IT MAY HAVE BEEN SARIN.
OF COURSE IT'S NOT BEEN
CONFIRMED.
>>> MEANTIME IN EGYPT, A CRUCIAL
U.S. PARTNER IN THE MIDDLE EAST,
THE FORMER LEADER HOSNI MUBARAK
IS OUT OF PRISON.
THE GOVERNMENT REPORTS HE'S
UNDER HOUSE ARREST AND OFFICIALS
SAY HE COULD END UP BACK BOARD
OBEHINDBARS.
HE WAS FORCED OUT OF POWER MORE
THAN TWO YEARS AGO.
LAST MONTH THE MILITARY FORCED
OUT HIS REPLACEMENT, MOHAMED
MORSI, EGYPT'S FIRST
DEMOCRATICALLY-ELECTED
PRESIDENT.
MORSI SUPPORTERS CAMPED OUT FOR
WEEKS TO PROTEST, AND LAST WEEK
OFFICIALS SAY HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE
DIED AFTER THE MILITARY CLEARED
OUT THOSE CAMPS AND SOME
PROTESTERS FOUGHT BACK.
NOW MORSI'S SUPPORTERS ARE
PLANNING MORE PROTESTS TOMORROW,
CALLING IT A FRIDAY OF MARTYRS.
JAMES ROSEN AT THE STATE
DEPARTMENT.
JAMES?
>> SHEP, GOOD EVENING.
FEW HERE REGARD THE RELEASE OF
EX-PRESIDENT BUT MAKER AS A MUBA
STABILIZER.
HE FLASHED A QUICK SMILE AS HE
WAS REMOVED FROM THE CAIRO
PRISON TO THE MILITARY HOSPITAL
WHERE HE HAS PREVIOUSLY SPENT
TIME DURING HIS TWO YEARS OF
DETENTION.
>> WITH RESPECT TO THE MUBARAK
TRIAL, DECISIONS MADE, THIS IS
AN INTERNAL EGYPTIAN LEGAL
MATTER WORKING ITS WAY THROUGH
THE EGYPTIAN LEGAL SYSTEM.
BEYOND THAT, I DON'T HAVE MORE
FOR YOU.
I REFER TO YOU THE EGYPTIAN
GOVERNMENT.
>> WHILE THE COUNTRY HE RULED
FOR 30 YEARS REMAINS IN TURMOIL,
MUBARAK EMERGES AS A MAN WITHOUT
A COUNTRY AS BOTH PARTIES IN
EGYPT'S CURRENT CONFLICT, THE
MILITARY AND THE ISLAMIST MUSLIM
BROTHERHOOD FACTION HELPED BRING
ABOUT MUBARAK'S DOWNHILL.
STATE DEPARTMENT OFFICIALS
DECLINED TO SAY WHETHER THE U.S.
WOULD CONTINUE ITS PRESENCE
RELATIONSHIP WITH EGYPT IF THE
MILITARY DOES NOT TAKE IMMEDIATE
STEPS TO RESTORE DEMOCRACY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: HOSNI MUBARAK
SUPPORTERS SAY HE HAD A STROKE.
>>> PRESIDENT OBAMA FOCUSED ON
DOMESTIC ISSUES TODAY, TO
HIGHLIGHT A NEW EDUCATION PLAN
HE RODE A BUS TO SCHOOL.
IT WAS THE START OF A TWO-DAY
BUS TOUR THROUGH NEW YORK AND
PENNSYLVANIA.
HE STOPPED AT TWO SCHOOLS,
UNVEILED A PLAN TO CREATE A
RATINGS SYSTEM TO EVALUATE
UNIVERSITIES AND COLLEGES.
HE SAYS HE WANTS TO RATE SCHOOLS
BASED ON FACTORS LIKE TUITION
COST AND GRADUATION RATES, THEN
REWARD STUDENTS AT THE
HIGHEST-RATED COLLEGES WITH
LARGER GRANTS, MORE AFFORDABLE
STUDENT LOANS.
WE'RE LIVE IN D.C.
RICH?
>> SHEP, PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS HE
WANTS THAT NEW COLLEGE RATINGS
SYSTEM UP AND RUNNING BY 2015,
WANTS TO TIE FEDERAL STUDENT AID
TO THOSE RATINGS BY 2018.
HE SAYS THAT WILL DRIVE DOWN
COST BY REWARDING EFFICIENCY.
>> WHAT WE WANT TO DO IS RATE
THEM ON WHO'S OFFERING THE BEST
VALUE SO STUDENTS AND TAXPAYERS
GET A BIGGER BANG FOR THEIR
BUCK.
>> HE HAS OPPOSITION.
THE PRESIDENT OF THE ASSOCIATION
OF AMERICAN COLLEGES AND
UNIVERSITIES SAYS THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT HAS NEITHER
COMPETENCE TO MAKE ITS OWN
METRICS.
THE CHAIRMAN OF THE HOUSE
EDUCATION AND FORK WORRIES
COMMITTEE SAYS I REMAIN
CONCERNED THAT IMPOSING AN
ARBITRARY COLLEGE RANKING SYSTEM
COULD CURTAIL THE VERY
INNOVATION WE HOPE TO ENCOURAGE
AND EVEN LEAD TO FEDERAL PRICE
CONTROLS.
THE ADMINISTRATION SAYS IT
ALREADY HAS THE AUTHORITY TO
PUBLISH THESE SCHOOL VALUE
RATINGS, BUT TO TIE THEM TO
FEDERAL FUNDING, THAT TAKES AN
OKAY FROM CONGRESS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: THE PRESIDENT IS
SCHEDULED TO SPEAK AT ANOTHER
STATE UNIVERSITY IN NEW YORK
TOMORROW BEFORE JOINING VICE
PRESIDENT BIDEN IN SCRANTON,
P.A.
>>> YAHOO! WAS THE MOST VISITED
WEBSITE IN JULY BEATING OUT
GOOGLE FOR THE FIRST TIME IN TWO
YEARS, ACCORDING TO A NEW REPORT
ACCORDING TO COMSCORE WHICH
TRACKS UNIQUE VISITORS.
NEARLY 179 MILLION PEOPLE
VISITED YAHOO! IN JULY COMPARED
TO 192 MILLION FOR GOOGLE.
YAHOO!'S CURRENT CEO, MARISSA MA
MEYER, HAS BEEN RUNNING THINGS
FOR MORE THAN A YEAR, AND SHARES
HAVE NEARLY DOUBLED IN PRICE IN
THAT TIME.
HER LAST JOB, BY THE WAY, WAS AT
GOOGLE.
>>> A HUSBAND AND WIFE SAY THEY
WENT ON A CRUISE OVERSEAS AND
RAN INTO SERIOUS TROUBLE.
THE WIFE SAYS SHE WAS AFRAID HER
INJURED HUSBAND WOULD DIE AFTER
THE CRUISE SHIP TOOK OFF WITHOUT
THEM.
>>> PLUS, THE TOWER THREAT THAT
FORCED THE U.S. TO CLOSE DOZENS
OF EMBASSIES AROUND THE GLOBE.
TONIGHT WE HAVE WORD FROM THE
HEAD OF THE FBI THAT THE DANGER
HAS NOT PASSED.
ENACTS.
THAT'S NEXT.
I GO AHEAD OF YOU?
INSTEAD WE HAD SOMEONE
GO AHEAD OF HIM
AND WIN FIY THOUSAND DOLLARS.
CONGRATULATIONS YOU ARE
OUR ONE MILLIONTH CUSTOMER.
NOBODY LIKES TO MISS OUT.
THAT'S WHY ALLY TREATS ALL
THEIR CUSTOMERS THE SAME.
WHETHER YOU'RE THE
FIRST OR THE MILLIONTH.
IF YOUR BANK DOESN'T THINK
YOU'RE SPECIAL ANYMORE,
YOU NEED AN ALLY.
ALLY BANK.
YOUR MONEY NEEDS AN ALLY.
EVEN IN STUPID LOUD PLACES.
TO PROVE IT, WE SET UP
OUR CALL CENTER RIGHT HERE...
[ chirp ]
ALL GOOD?
GETTY UP.
CALL ME.
SERIOUSLY,
THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING!
[ cellphone rings ]
HELLO?
IT'S A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.
[ Male Announcer ] GET IT DONE
[ chirp ]
WITH THE ULTRA-RUGGED
Kyocera Torque,
ONLY FROM Sprint
Direct Connect.
TRBLE HEARING ON THE PHONE?
BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE
FOR YOUR BUSINESS.
VISIT SPNTCAPTEL.COM
ONLY FROM Sprint
Direct Connect.
TRBLE HEARING ON THE PHONE?
Over 20 million drivers are
insured with GEICO.
So get a free rate quote
today.
I love it!
How much do you love it?
Animation is hot...and I
think it makes GEICO's
20 million drivers message very
compelling, very compelling.
This is some really strong
stuff!
So you turned me into a
cartoon...lovely.
GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could
save you
fifteen percent or more on
car insurance.
>> Shepard: AT LEAST 50 PEOPLE
GOT HURT WHEN A TOUR BUS
OVERTURNED ALONG A SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA FREEWAY THIS MORNING
ABOUT 20 MILES OR SO EAST OF LOS
ANGELES.
THAT BUS APPARENTLY WENT THROUGH
A CHAINLINK FENCE.
LOOK AT THIS.
IT LANDED ON ITS SIDE BETWEEN
THE FREEWAY AND THE RAILROAD
TRACKS.
ACCORDING TO THE CALIFORNIA
HIGHWAY PATROL, INITIAL FINDINGS
SHOW THE BUS HIT ANOTHER
VEHICLE, BUT IT'S SIMPLY NOT
CLEAR YET HOW IT ALL HAPPENED.
EMERGENCY CREWS SAY THEY
AIRLIFTED FIVE PEOPLE TO A
TRAUMA CENTER.
MOST OTHERS HAD MINOR INJURIES.
THE BUS WAS TAKING FOLKS TO AN
INDIAN CASINO.
FIRE OFFICIALS SAY MOST
PASSENGERS WERE SENIOR CITIZENS.
>>> ONE ELDERLY COUPLE FROM
FLORIDA CLAIMS THE POPULAR
CRUISE LINE ESSENTIALLY
ABANDONED THEM IN TURKEY.
HERE'S A PICTURE OF THE COUPLE.
THE HUSBAND APPARENTLY FELL AND
BROKE HIS HIP WHILE ON A SHIP
WHICH ROYAL CARIBBEAN OWNS.
ROYAL CARIBBEAN ARRANGED FOR
TREATMENT AT A NEARBY HOSPITAL.
THE WIFE SAYS THE PLACE WAS
DIRTY AND NOBODY SPOKE ENGLISH
THERE.
SHE SAYS SHE PAID FOR AN
AMERICAN TRANSFER TO THE COMPANY
IN ISTANBUL BECAUSE THE COMPANY
TOLD THEM TO FILE A CLAIM.
SHE SAYS SHE FEARED FOR HER
HUSBAND'S LIFE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF HE WOULD
SURVIVE.
>> Shepard: ROYAL CARIBBEAN
ISSUED A STATEMENT THAT READS IN
PART, "WE HELPED ARRANGE
TRANSPORTATION BY AMBULANCE TO
THE CLOSEST AREA HOSPITAL.
ONCE ASHORE, WE WORKED CLOSELY
WITH THE TRAVEL INSURANCE
PROVIDER AS THEY HAVE THE
EXPERIENCE TO DEAL WITH LOCAL
AUTHORITIES AND MEDICAL
FACILITIES."
>>> THE THREAT WHICH PROMPTED
THE UNITED STATES GOVERNMENT TO
CLOSE SOME TWO DOZEN EMBASSIES
EARLIER THIS MONTH HAS NOT
PASSED AND TERROR GROUPS HAVE
ONLY POSTPONED WHATEVER THEY
WERE PLANNING, OR THAT'S THE
WORD FROM THE FBI DIRECTOR,
ROBERT MULLER.
HE IS THE DOWN TODAY FOR RARE
INTERVIEWS AS HE PREPARES TO
LEAVE AFTER 12 YEARS IN OFFICE.
CATHERINE HARRIDGE SPOKE WITH
HIM.
CATHERINE?
>> SHEP, MULLER WAS CANDID ABOUT
THE THREATS.
>> WE ARE CLOSELY MONITORING THE
SITUATION.
I WOULD SAY THAT IT MAY WELL
HAVE BEEN POSTPONED.
ONE OF THE CONTRIBUTING FACTORS,
I BELIEVE, IS THE FACT THAT WE
RAMPED UP, AND PRECAUTIONS WERE
TAKEN, AND THAT THE OPPORTUNITY
THEY THOUGHT THEY MAY HAVE HAD
AT JUNCTURE WAS NO LONGER THERE.
>> AS FOR A REPORTED CONFERENCE
BETWEEN TERRORIST LEADERS --
>> WE'RE SEEING DIALOG BETWEEN
CORE AL-QAEDA AND THE AFFILIATES
AS THE COUNTRIES ARE GOING
THROUGH THE ARAB SPRING THAT
WILL TERRITORIALLY PRESENT A
SUBSTANTIAL THREAT DOWN THE
ROAD.
>> SO AL-QAEDA IS NOT DEAD?
>> NO.
>> THE THREAT CONNECTING MOST
HOMEGROWN PLOTS FROM THE FORT
HOOD MASSACRE IN 2009 TO THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBING EARLIER
THIS YEAR IS THAT THE SUSPECTS
ARE FOLLOWERS OF ANWAR
AL-AWLAKIY, THE FIRST AMERICAN
TARGETED BY DEATH BY THE CIA.
>> THE INCREASE IN INDIVIDUALS
RADICALIZED ON THE INTERNET, AND
CAN GAIN KNOWLEDGE HOW TO
DEVELOP A EXPLOSIVE DEVICE ON
THE INTERNET IS THE BIGGEST
THREAT AT THAT JUNCTURE.
THEN AL-QAEDA IN THE ARABIAN
PENINSULA OUT OF YEMEN.
>> FOX'S ONGOING REPORT OF THE
CLERIC IN NEWLY DECLASSIFIED
DOCUMENTS ARE RAISING QUESTIONS
OVER WHETHER THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
TRIED TO RECRUIT HIM.
>> I'M NOT AWARE OF THAT, BUT
THAT DOES NOT THERE WAS NOT
OTHER AGENCY THAT DID SO.
>> Shepard: THE STANDARD TERM
FOR AN FBI DIRECTOR IS 10 YEARS.
MULLER PUT IN AN EXTRA TWO AT
THE REQUEST OF THE PRESIDENT.
>>> THE FEDS ARE SUING THE STATE
OF TEXAS NOW TO TRY TO BLOCK ITS
NEW VOTER ID LAW, THE ONE THAT
REQUIRES A PHOTO ID FROM THE
GOVERNMENT TO REGISTER TO VOTE.
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT ACCUSES
TEXAS OF TRYING TO KEEP
MINORITIES FROM FOREHEAD.
THE GOVERNOR, RICK PERRY, SAID,
THE FILING IN AN EFFORT TO
OBSTRUCT THE WILL OF THE PEOPLE
OF TEXAS IS WHAT WE'VE COME TO
EXPECT FROM ATTORNEY GENERAL
ERIC HOLDER AND PRESIDENT OBAMA.
>>> A MAN WHO DOCTORS DECLARED
DEAD FOR 45 MINUTES SUDDENLY
CAME BACK TO LIFE.
WAIT TILL YOU HEAR WHAT HIS SON
SAID TO HIM JUST BEFORE HE
STARTED SHOWING SIGNS OF LIFE.
>>> PLUS, LEGAL MARIJUANA MAY BE
THE CASE IN COLORADO, BUT MANY
FOLKS THERE SHOULD NOT EXPECT TO
PICK IT UP ON THEIR WAY TO WORK.
THE PUSHBACK OVER POT STORES.
THAT'S NEXT.
Reinforced with scratch-
resistant glass
and a unibody
Made Kevlar Strong.
Okay Google Now.
Call My Droid.
The new
Droid Ultra by Motorola.
When strength matters,
Droid Does.
FEMALE NARRATOR:
The mattress
price wars are on
at Sleep Train.
We challenged the manufacturers
to offer even lower prices.
Now it's Posturepedic
versus Beautyrest
with big savings of
up to $400 off.
Serta iComfort
and Tempur-Pedic
go head-to-head
with three years'
interest-free financing.
Plus, free same-day
delivery, set-up,
and removal of your
old set.
When brands compete,
you save.
Mattress Price Wars
are on now at Sleep Train.
♪ Your ticket
to a better night's sleep ♪
>> THE FATHER WHO REPORTEDLY
CAME BACK FROM THE DEAD AFTER
HIS SON TOLD HIM, YOU'RE NOT
DYING TODAY, SAYS HE DOESN'T
REMEMBER A THING.
COMING UP, TONY YALEY WITH HIS
WIFE AND SON.
THE OHIO FAMILY SAYS EARLIER
THIS MONTH, TONY'S WIFE WOKE UP
EARLY IN THE MORNING, REALIZED
HE WASN'T BREATHING RIGHT.
EMERGENCY CREWS THEN BROUGHT HIM
TO THE HOSPITAL WHERE HIS HEART
STOPPED BEATING FOR 45 MINUTES.
I SPOKE WITH TONY TODAY IN
STUDIO B.
>> THEY GAVE UP.
THEY HAD ACTUALLY WENT TO MY
FAMILY, DECLARED ME DEAD.
EVERYTHING WAS UNHOOKED FROM ME
EXCEPT FOR THE HEART MONITOR.
THE NURSE THAT WAS WORKING ON ME
ACTUALLY SAID FOR SOME REASON
SHE FELT SHE SHOULD LEAVE THE
HEART MONITOR ON.
>> TONY LAY THERE MOTIONLESS IN
HIS HOSPITAL BED.
HE SAYS HIS SON GOT WORD OF WHAT
HAPPENED AND RAN TO HIS ROOM.
>> HE WAS ACTUALLY BACK THERE,
IAND THE PASTOR OF OUR CHURCH WS
BACK THERE.
HE'S THE ONE THAT SAID, YOU'RE
NOT DYING TODAY, DAD.
THEN AFTER THAT HE STOOD THERE
FOR A MINUTE OR TWO, TURNED TO
WALK OUT OF THE ROOM, AND THE
PASTOR SAW THE HEART MONITOR
START UP.
>> THE POWER OF PRAYER THEY SAY.
HE'S EVEN REPORTEDLY SET TO
RETURN TO WORK ON MONDAY.
>>> COLORADO VOTED TO APPROVE
LEGAL MARIJUANA LAST YEAR, BUT
THAT DOES NOT NECESSARILY MEAN
POT RETAIL STORES WILL BE
POPPING UP ALL OVER THE STATE
ANYTIME SOON.
DRIVER AROUND TO THE FIRST
WINDOW.
THAT'S BECAUSE THE
CONSTITUTIONAL AMENDMENT GAVE
CITIES THE OPTION TO BAN
STOREFRONT MARIJUANA SALES.
LAST MONTH THE STATE'S SECOND
LARGEST CITY, COLORADO SPRINGS,
DID JUST THAT.
NOW DENVER'S MAYOR HAS ALSO
CALLED FOR A TEMPORARY DELAY IN
OPENING RECREATIONAL MARIJUANA
OUTLETS.
SOME CITY OFFICIALS SAY
RESIDENTS -- OR I SHOULD SAY
SOME CITY OFFICIALS AND
RESIDENTS SAY NO MATTER HOW MUCH
REVENUE LEGAL POT GENERATES THEY
DON'T WANT TO BE ASSOCIATED WITH
THE BUSINESS OF WEED.
>> SHEP, COLORADO SPRINGS
OFFICIALS SAY THE AMOUNT OF
REVENUE PROMISED FROM RETAIL POT
SALES, $3.9 MILLION, IS DWARFED
BY THE AMOUNT THEY SAY THEY
COULD LOSE IF SHOPS OPENED UP.
>> CITY LEADERS IN OTHER PLACES
LIKE HUNTSVILLE, OMAHA, THAT WE
COMPETE AGAINST, WOULD USE THAT
AGAINST US AS THEY WALK THE
HALLS OF THE PENTAGON, SAYING
KEEP O HERE, WE DON'T
ALLOW RECREATIONAL MARIJUANA
SALES.
>> DEFENSE CONTRACTS ARE BIG IN
COLORADO SPRINGS.
PUEBLO COUNTY HAS A DIFFERENT
TAKE, WELCOMING THE OPPORTUNITY.
>> MAYBE WE'LL BE THE HUB OF
COLORADO WHERE THEY HAVE THE
TESTING LABS, A LOT OF WHITE
COLLAR, GOOD PROFESSIONAL JOBS
CONTRIBUTING TO OUR ECONOMY.
>> THROUGHOUT COLORADO, ANYONE
OVER 21 CAN POSSESS 1 OUNCE OR
LESS, EVEN IF THEY MUST DRIVE TO
GET IT.
>> THE MARIJUANA SALES WILL BE
JUST LIKE ALCOHOL WITH DRY
COUNTIES.
YOU KNOW, IF I WERE TO LIVE IN A
DRY COUNTY, I CAN DRIVE ACROSS
THE COUNTY LINE, PURCHASE
ALCOHOL, AND BRING IT HOME.
WE'LL SEE THE SAME THING WITH
MARIJUANA.
>> MORE THAN 70 CITIES AND
COUNTIES HAVE PROHIBITED OR
DELAYED POT SHOPS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: WASHINGTON STATE'S
RECREATIONAL MARIJUANA LAW DOES
NOT PROVIDE A WAY FOR CITIES TO
OPT OUT, BUT THAT HASN'T STOPPED
SOME FROM TRYING.
>>> WE RECENTLY LEARNED IF YOU
BUILD A MOUNTAIN ON TOP OF A
HIGH-RISE IN CHINA, COMPLAINING
NEIGHBORS WILL EVENTUALLY FORCE
YOU TO TEAR IT DOWN.
NOW WORD OF ANOTHER HIDDEN
STRUCTURE ON A DIFFERENT ROOFTOP
IN CHINA.
THE CONTROVERSY OVER ONE GUY'S
TEMPLE IN THE SKY.
[ Dog ]
We found it together.
On a walk, walk, walk.
Yeah, we found
that wonderful thing.
Anyou smiled. And threw it.
And I decided I would never,
ever leave it anywhere.
Because that wonderful,
bouncy, roll-around thing...
had made you play.
And that...
had made you smile.
[ Announcer ] Beneful.
Play. It's good for you.
Beneful is awarding a $500,000
dog park makeover...
In the 2013 Dream Dog Park
Contest.
Enter now.
STILL RUNNING
IN THE MORNING?
YEAH.
GETTING YOUR VEGETABLES
EVERY DAY?
WHEN I CAN.
[ BOP ]
[ Male Announcer ]
COULD'VE HAD A V8.
TWO FULL SERVINGS OF VEGETABLES
FOR ONLY 50 DELICIOUS CALORIES.
For a strong bag that
grips the can...
♪
get Glad ForceFlex.
Small change,
big difference.
[ Male Announcer ]
STAYING WARM AND DRY
HAS NEVER BEEN OUR PRIORITY.
♪
CATERING TO
THE CONVENIENTLY LATED
HAS NEVER BEEN OUR PRIORITY.
OUR PRIORITY IS, WAS
AND ALWAYS WILL BE
SERVING YOU,
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
WE GET TO SEE EVERYONE
IN AMERICA ALMOST EVERY DAY.
AND WE'VE NOTICED THAT YOU'RE
SENDING AND RECEIVING
MORE PACKAGES THAN EVER.
SO WE WANTED TO GIVE YOU
A MORE RELIABLE WAY
TO SHIP THEM.
WITH IMPROVED PRIORITY MAIL
FLAT RATE.
DON'T JUST TAKE OUR WORD
FOR IT --
NOW WE'LL PROVE IT
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY
WITH TRACKING
UP TO ELEVEN SCANS,
SPECIFIED DELIVERY DATES,
AND FREE INSURANCE UP TO $50
ALL FOR THE SAME LOW RATE.
WE'LL NEVER STOP DELIVERING
FOR EVERY PERSON
IN THIS COUNTRY.
[ Woman ] WE ARE THE
UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.
[ Man ] WE ARE THE
[ Woman #2 ] WE ARE THE
UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.
[ Male Announcer ] WE ARE THE
AND OUR PRIORITY IS YOU.
GO TO USPS.COM®
AND TRY IT TODAY.
LOOKIN' GOOD, FLO!
FEELIN' GOOD!
FEELIN' REAL GOOD!
[ ENGINE REVS ]
BOAT PROTECTION PEOPLE LOVE.
NOW, THAT'S PROGRESSIVE.
CALL OR CLICK TODAY.
>> Shepard: A COUPLE OF
COSMONAUTS STRUGGLED WITH FAULTY
EQUIPMENT DURING A SPACEWALK AT
THE SPACE STATION.
THEY SAY THEY FOUND A PROBLEM
WITH A PLATFORM THEY WERE
INSTALLING, OR TRYING TO,
OUTSIDE THE STATION.
THE DEVICES WILL REPORTEDLY HOLD
A NEW TELESCOPE.
MISSION CONTROL TOLD THEM TO
GIVE UP, BUT AFTER TAKING
ANOTHER LOOK AT THE THING, THE
SPACEWALKERS WENT AHEAD AND
INSTALLED IT ANYWAY.
THEY SAY THEY CAN ALWAYS FIX IT
LATER.
>>> SURVEILLANCE VIDEO CAPTURED
A GUY PISTOL-WHIPPING A DUNKIN'
DONUTS EMPLOYEE.
IT ALL APPARENTLY HAPPENED
BECAUSE THE WORKER GAVE HIS WIFE
THE WRONG COFFEE DRINK.
THE "MIAMI HERALD" NEWSPAPER IS
REPORTING THE COUPLE ORDERED
SOME DRINKS AT THE DRIVE-THRU
THERE, BUT THEN REALIZED THE
WIFE GOT CARAMEL IN HER COFFEE,
CARAMEL INSTEAD OF VANILLA.
I MEAN, DRONED THEM.
THAT'S WHEN COPS SHE WENT INSIDE
THE PLACE TO DEMAND TO SPEAK TO
A MANAGER, BUT BEFORE HE CAME
OUT, THE WOMAN REPORTEDLY TRIED
TO HIT THE WORKER WHO TOOK THE
ORDER.
HER HUSBAND JUMPED IN TO BREAK
UP THE SCUFFLE, PULLED OUT A
HANDGUN AND HIT THE WORKER WITH
IT.
COPS ARRESTED THEM.
THERE'S ANOTHER CASE OF AN
ILLEGALLY BUILT ROOFTOP
MASTERPIECE IN CHINA.
THIS ONE MAY BE BETTER THAN THE
LAST ONE.
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU DECIDE.
RESIDENTS ARE DEMANDING A
PENTHOUSE OWNER TEAR DOWN HIS
TEMPLE.
SEE HERE.
THE GUY REPORTEDLY BUILT IT ATOP
A HIGH-RISE IN THE SOUTH OF
CHINA, ABOUT SIX, SEVEN YEARS
AGO.
RESIDENTS SAY THEY'VE BEEN
COMPLAINING ABOUT THE THING FOR
A LONG TIME, BUT THEY ALSO SAY
THE OWNER HAS POLITICAL
CONNECTIONS, SO THEY JUST, YOU
KNOW, GAVE UP.
AT LEAST UNTIL LAST WEEK, WHEN
THE NEWS BROKE OF THAT AWESOME
SITUATION IN BEIJING.
REMEMBER THIS?
AUTHORITIES FORCED A WEALTH
BUSINESSMAN WHO BUILT THIS
MONSTROSITY TO TEAR DOWN HIS
ILLEGALLY-CONSTRUCTED PENTHOUSE
MOUNTAIN PEAK.
>>> THE JURY BEGAN DELIBERATIONS
TODAY IN THE TRIAL OF THE
ACCUSED FORT HOOD SHOOTER, MAJOR
NIDAL HASSAN.
JURORS WENT HOME WITHIN THE LAST
HOUR, SET TO RETURN TOMORROW.
MAJOR NIDAL HASSAN STANDS
ACCUSED OF KILLING 13 PEOPLE AND
WOUNDING MORE THAN 30 OTHERS IN
THE SHOOTING AT THE ARMY POST
WHICH HAPPENED BACK IN 2009.
THE DEFENDANT CHOSE TO REPRESENT
HIMSELF IN COURT AND DOES NOT
PRESENT MUCH OF A CASE AT ALL.
HE DIDN'T CALL ANY WITNESSES,
AND HE DIDN'T GIVE A CLOSING
ARGUMENT.
>>> A GRAND JURY INDICTED THE
FORMER NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS
TIGHT END AARON HERNANDEZ TODAY
ON SEVERAL CHARGES, CHARGES
INCLUDING MURDER AND CARRYING A
GUN WITHOUT A LICENSE.
PROSECUTORS SAY HE KILLED HIS
FRIEND ODIN LLOYD BACK IN JUNE.
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO APPARENTLY
SHOWED HERNANDEZ WITH THAT GUN
AFTER THE SHOOTING, OR WITH A
GUN ANYWAY, BUT THE DEFENSE
CLAIMS THE PROSECUTION HAS NOT
PRODUCED SUFFICIENT EVIDENCE TO
PROVE ITS CASE BEYOND A
REASONABLE DOUBT.
>>> AND WEIRDNESS ON WALL STREET
TODAY.
ACTUALLY NOT WALL STREET,
BECAUSE IT'S NASDAQ, DOESN'T
BELONG ON THE STREET, JUST IN
THE DIGITAL WORLD.
THEY'RE BLAMING A TECHNICAL
GLITCH FOR A THREE-HOUR TRADING
FREEZE TODAY.
BY THE END OF THE SESSION, THE
NASDAQ WAS UP 38 POINTS, MORE
THAN A WHOLE PERCENTAGE POINT.
THE DOW UP 66, S&P 15 WITH
POSITIVE SIGNS FROM TRADERS IN
EUROPE AND ASIA.
>>> ON THIS DAY IN 1950, A
TENNIS PHENOM NAME ALTHEA GIBSON
BECAME THE FIRST AFRICAN
AMERICAN PLAYER TO PLAY IN A
U.S. NATIONAL COMPETITION.
ALTHEA CAME FROM HARLEM, A
NATIVE THERE, SHOWING A NATURAL
TALENT FROM THE VERY START.
AT 15 YEARS OLD, ALTHEA WON HER
FIRST STATE TITLE.
THEN 10 MORE CHAMPIONSHIPS.
BUT OFFICIALS STILL REJECTED HER
ENTRY INTO THE NATIONAL GRASS
COURT CHAMPIONSHIPS, BECAUSE,
AFTER ALL, SHE WAS BLACK.
A TENNIS CHAMPION WROTE AN ESSAY
SUPPORTING GIBSON.
IN ADDITION, THE ASSOCIATION
INVITED HER TO QUALIFY, WHICH
SHE DID, AND EARNED A SPOT IN
THE BIG TOURNAMENT.
ALTHEA GIBSON WOULD VIL WIN
MAJOR EVENTS THROUGHOUT HER
CAREER, INCLUDING WIMBLEDON AND
THE FRENCH AND U.S. OPENS, BUT
SHE ACED THE TENNIS COLOR
BARRIER 63 YEARS AGO TODAY.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS FOR
THIS THURSDAY, AUGUST 22nd,
2013.
I'M STO SHEPARD SMITH.
THE "FOX REPORT" IS BACK
TOMORROW NIGHT.
"STUDIO B" TOMORROW AFTERNOON.
"O'REILLY" COMES ON NOW.
>> Bill: TONIGHT --
>> THEY DON'T HAVE MALE FIGURES
IN THEIR LIVES.
YOU CAN'T GIVE KIDS LIBERTY TO
DO WHAT THEY WANT TO DO WITH NO
RESTRAINTS WHATSOEVER.
>> Bill: THE THREE TEENAGERS
CHARGED WITH MURDERING A YOUNG
AUSTRALIAN MAN IN OKLAHOMA ARE
UNDER INTENSE SCRUTINY TONIGHT.
NOW THERE'S CHARGES OF RACISM
AGAINST ONE OF THE BOYS.
WE'LL HAVE THE LATEST.
>> I'D LIKE TO INVITE YOU TO THE
STATE DINNER NEXT WEEK.
NOT AS A BUTLER, CECIL.
I'M INVITING YOU AS A GUEST.
>> SOME CONSERVATIVES WANT
MOVIEGOERS TO BOYCOTT "THE
BUTLER" BECAUSE JASON FONDA
POSTERIOR TRACES NANCY REAGAN.
IS THAT FAIR?
>>