HE PHYSICALLY CANNOT DO IT ANY
MORE.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
SPENDING YOUR DAY WITH US, I AM
ARTHEL NEVILLE.
>> I AM ERIC SHAWNS, HAVE A
GREAT EVENING.
EVENING.
HARRIS: YOUNGER TRUMP IS FACING
A SERIES OF FOREIGN POLICY
TESTS.
JUST AS HOLY WEEK OF EASTER
BEGINS, I AM HARRIS FAULKNER
REPORTING LIVE.
>> LET'S BEGIN IN EGYPT, ISIS,
ISLAMIST STATE TERROR ARMY IS
NOW CLAIMS RESPONSIBILITY FOR
TWO BOMBINGS AT COPTIC CHRISTIAN
CHURCHES, 100 INJURIES, 47
PEOPLE KILLED.
REMEMBER, PRESIDENT OF THAT
COUNTRY WAS JUST AT THE WHITE
HOUSE LAST WEEK.
ALSO UNFOLDING U.S. MAKING MOVES
IN TWO MAJOR GLOBAL HOT SPOTS,
SYRIA AND NORTH KOREA, PRESIDENT
TRUMP ARRIVING BACK IN
WASHINGTON D.C. AFTER A FEW DAYS
IN FLORIDA MEETING WITH
PRESIDENT OF CHINA.
THEY TALKED ABOUT NORTH KOREA.
AND RECENT PROVOCATIONS
INCLUDING BANNED MISSILE TESTING
BY NORTH KOREA, PRESIDENT IS
SENDING A STRONG MESSAGE BY
DELAYING A U.S. CARRIER STRIKE
GROUP.
USS CARL VINSON AND ITS
SUPPORTING CHIP, THAT MASSIVE
FIGHTING FORCE IS BEING DIVERTED
TO WATERS OFF OF THE KOREAN
PENINSULA.
>> WHEN I WAS AMBASSADOR IN
KUWAIT IN 1990s, I REFERRED TO
CARRIER BATTLE GROUP AS A
100,000 TONS OF DIPLOMACY.
I WORKED CLOSELY WITH CENTRAL
COMMAND THEN TO MAKE SURE WE
HAVE CARRIER PRESENT IN NORTHERN
GULF WHEN WE NEEDED IT.
I THINK THAT PRESIDENT HAS MADE
THE RIGHT MOVE BOTH IN SYRIA AND
IN KOREA.
BUT, THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING.
HARRIS: 100,000 POUNDS OF
DIPLOMACY,R WE BRING IN DAVID LE
MILLER TO START COVERAGE WITH
LATEST FROM MIDDLE EAST
BOMBINGS.
REPORTER: HARRIS, EGYPT'S
PRESIDENT DECLARING A 3-MONTH
STATE OF EMERGENCY, FOLLOWING
TWO TERROR ATTACKS ON COPTIC
ORTHODOX CHURCHES, DOZENS DIED,
AND OVER 100 WOUNDED.
DEATH TOLL COULD HAVE BEEN
HIGHER.
BOTH OF THE INCIDENTS WERE
CAUGHT ON CAMERA, WE CAUTION,
SOMEWHAT OF YOU ABOUT TO SEE AND
HERE IS DISTURBING.
SURVEILLANCES VIDEO SHOWS A
SUICIDE BOMBER.
BOMBER IS TURNED AWAY FROM THE
MAIN GATE, AND DIRECTED TO A
METAL DETECTOR, HE THEN WALKED
PAST A FEMALE OFFICER IRK --
TALKING TO A WOMAN, AND
DETONATES THAT BOMB.
EARLIER, LEADER OF THE COPTIC
CHURCH FINISHES SERVICES.
LOCAL REPORTS SAID HE WAS STILL
IN THE BUILDING AT THE TIME OF
THE BLAST BUT NOT HURT, 11
PEOPLE WERE KILLED, INCLUDE
THREE POLICE, THE CATHEDRAL IS
CONSIDERED SACRED.
TODAY'S FIRST ATTACK WAS IN
TANTA, 26 WORSHIPPERS WERE
KILLED.
CHURCH'S YOUTUBE CHANNEL WAS
TRANSMITTING AS THE BOMB REPORT
OFF, AND VIDEO ABRUPTLY ENDS.
A WITNESS WHO LIVED ACROSS THE
STREET, DESCRIBED CHURCH DEACONS
IN BLOOD-STAINED WHITE ROBES
RUNNING FROM THE SCENE, AND
OTHER SERIOUSLY INJURED VICTIMS
WERE RUSHED TO HOSPITALS IN
PRIVATE CARS, ISIS CLAIMS
RESPONSIBILITY FOR BOTH DEADLY
BLASTS, AND THREATEN TO INCREASE
ATTACKS TARGETING EGYPT
MINORITIES, CHRISTIANS, THEY
REFER TO AS INFIDELS, THERE HAVE
BEEN OVER 2 GO DOZEN ATTACKS OFE
COPTIC ORTHODOX COMMUNITY.
HARRIS: LET'S GET TO U.S. NAVY
CARRIER STRIKE GROUP, HEADED TO
THE KOREAN PENINSULA, THE NEXT
MOVE BY TRUMP ADMINISTRATION.
OFFICIALS SAY THIS IS A SHOW OF
FORCE IN THAT REGION FOLLOWING
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S PHONE CALL
WITH SOUTH KOREA PRESIDENT
YESTERDAY.
WHITE HOUSE SAID THAT TWO MEN
AGREED TO KEEP AN EYE ON THE
NORTH.
THAT COUNTRY APPEARS TO BE
CONTINUING WITH NUCLEAR PROGRAM
AND IS NEARING ANOTHER TEST.
IN A INTERVIEW TODAY, SECRETARY
OF STATE REX TILLERSON HAD A
MESSAGE FOR COUNTRIES WHICH
VIOLATE INTERNATIONAL LAW.
>> IF YOU FAIL TO LIVE UP TO
COMMICOMMITMENTS, IF YOU BECOMEA
THREAT TO OTHERS, AT SOME POINT
A RESPONSE IS LIKELY TO BE
UNDERTAKEN.
HARRIS: LUCAS WITH MORE.
REPORTER: GOOD EVENING HARRIS,
McMASTER TOLD CHRIS WALLACE
THIS DECISION TO SEND THE CARL
VINSON STRIKE GROUP WAS THE
PRUDENT THING TO DO.
>> THIS SAY ROGUE REGIME.
THAT IS NOW A NUCLEAR CAPABLE
REGIME.
THE PRESIDENT HAS ASKED US TO BE
PREPARED TO GIVE HIM A FULL
RANGE OF OPTIONS TO REMOVE THAT
THREAT TO THE EMERGENCY PEOPLE,
AND TO OUR ALLIES AND PARTNERS
IN THE REGION.
REPORTER: LAST MONTH BATTLE
GROUP TOOK PART IN ANNUAL
MILITARY EXERCISES WITH SOUTH
KOREAN AND JAPANESE ALLIES,
SATURDAY, IN ADDITION TO HIS
CALL WITH SOUTH KOREA ACTING
PRESIDENT, PRESIDENT TRUMP SPOKE
TO JAPAN'S PRIME MINISTER TO
DISCUSS THE NORTH KOREA THREAT.
THAT SAME DAY, HEADS OF PACIFIC
COMMAND ORDERS AIRCRAFT CARRIER
DO REVERSE COURSE.
CANCELING A PORT CALL IN
AUSTRALIA, AMONG THE STRIKE
GROUP ARE TWO DESTROYERS AND A
CRUISER.
DEFENSE OFFICIALS TELL FOX THIS
ABILITY TO LAUNCH MISSILES TO
NORTH KOREA MAY BE A BIGGER
MESSAGE TO SEND NORTH KOREA THAN
THE AIRCRAFT CARRIER.
PENTAGON SEES SIGN THAT ROGUE
COMMUNIST REGIME IS PREPARING
FOR ANOTHER NUCLEAR TEST, AND I
AM TOLD THAT DESCRIBE GROUP WILL
ARRIVE LATER THIS WEEK.
THERE IS ALSO A SUBMARINE
LURKING, BUT U.S. OFFICIALS DO
NOT LIKING ABOUT THOSE
OPERATIONS.
>> NO DOUBT, ANYBODY WHO SEES
OUR FIGHTING FORCE, 100,000
POUNDS OF DIPLOMACY TOWARD IT,
THEY KNOW THEY NEED TH THE REPO.
>> NEW QUESTIONS SURROUNDING
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION AND WHETHER
HIS TEAM ARE ACTUALLY ON THE
SAME PAGE, AMBASSADOR TO UNITED
NATIONS NIKKI HALEY SIGNALS THAT
PRESIDENT MAY BE IN FAVOR OF
REGIME CHANGE IN SYRIA, WE GO TO
THAT NOW, BUT SECRETARY OF SAY
THE TILLERSON SAID IT IS UP TO
THE SYRIAN PEOPLE, NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER McMASTER
CLEAR FI FID THOSE COMMENTS.
>> AMBASSADOR HALEY POINTING OUT
IT IS DIFFICULT TO UNDERSTAND
HOW A POLITICAL SOLUTION.
WE ARE NOT SAY WE'RE THE ONES
WHO WILL AFFECT THAT CHANGE,
WE'RE SEEING OTHER COUNTRY HAVE
TO ASK THEMSELVES HARD
QUESTIONS, RUSSIA SHOULD ASK
THEMSELVES, WHAT ARE WE DOING
HERE.
HARRIS: PETER IS AT THE WHITE
HOUSE NOW WITH MORE ON THIS,
WHAT IS THE BIGGEST CONCERN FOR
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS NOW TRYING
TO PUT TOGETHER A SERIOUS
STRATEGY?
REPORTER: THEY KNOW THEY WANT
PRESIDENT BASHAR AL-ASSAD TO GO
AWAY, BUT NOW THEY ARE TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT WHO WOULD TAKEOVER IF
HE WAS TO GO.
AND IF THAT IS EVEN THEIR
RESPONSIBILITY TO CONDUCT A
REGIME CHANGE OR PUSH FOR ONE.
AND REASON THEY ARE CONCERNED IS
BECAUSE THEY REMEMBER HOW
QUICKLY THINGS WENT SOUTH IN
LIBYA WITH GADHAFI WAS TOPPLED.
>> WE HAVE TO LEARN LESSONS OF
PAST AND WHAT WENT WRONG IN
LIBYA WHEN YOU CHOOSE THAT
PATHWAY OF REGIME CHANGE.
WE KNOW THIS WILL BE HARD WORK.
BUT WE THINK IT IS ALSO A
PROCESS THAT WILL LEAD TO A
DURABLE AND LASTING STABILITY IN
SYRIA.
REPORTER: WHICH WEEK'S
AIRSTRIKES WERE MEANT TO WEAKEN
THE ASSAD REGIME AS A RESPONSES
TO THEIR USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPON,
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION KNOWS THAT
ISIS FIGHTERS WHO SET UP SHOP IN
SYRIA ARE A MAJOR NATIONAL
SECURITY CONCERN AS WELL.
>> GETTING ASSAD OUT IS NOT ONLY
PART, WE HAVE TRYING TO DEFEAT
ISIS.
SECONDLY WE DON'T SEE A PEACEFUL
SYRIA WITH ASSAD IN DPLSM THEREE
MOVE TOWARD A POLITICAL
SOLUTION, AT END OF THE DAY THIS
IS A COMPLICATED SITUATION.
REPORTER: NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER McMASTER SAYING THAT
MAIN OBJECTIVE OF U.S. WITH
AIRSTRIKES AGAINST THE AADD
REGIME, WAS -- ASSAD REGIME WAS
TOO SEND A STRONG POLITICAL
MESSAGE.
HARRIS: I KNOW THERE ARE CHANGES
MADE AT NATIONAL SECURITY LEFT
THIS NEWS DEVELOPING, K.T.
McFARLAND HAS BEEN REASSIGNED
AS U.N. AMBASSADOR TO SINGAPORE.
REPORTER: SHE WAS MICHAEL BLIN'S
FLYNN'S DEPUTY, AND PRESIDENT
TRUMP IS EXPECTED TO NOMINATE
HER TO AMBASSADOR OF SINGAPORE,
THAT WOULD BE A PROPORTION FOR
HER, SHE JOINS STEVE BANNON AS
SECOND OFFICIAL TO LEAVE
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISE
COUNCIL.
SINCE MICHAEL FLYNN RESIGNED.
WE HEARD FROM PRESIDENT TRUMP
ABOUT A NATIONAL SECURITY
CONCERN BUT ON A DIFFERENT
TOPIC, TALKING ABOUT CHURCH
BOMBINGS IN THE MIDDLE EAST,
TWEETING, SO SAD TO HEAR OF
TERRORIST ATTACK IN EGYPT, U.S.
STRONGLY CONDEMNS, I HAVE GREAT
CONFIDENCE THAT PRESIDENT ASEE
-- WILL HANDLE THOSE PROPERLY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP BACK AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HE HAS SERIOUS BUSINESS TO GET
DOWN TO.
HARRIS: WELL, AS EVERYONE CAN
APPRECIATE, YOU KNOW, WE NEARED
THAT LONGER HOUR DAY, IT IS
LIGHTER OUT.
PEOPLE CAN SEE WITH MORE
DAYLIGHT, WE'RE SEEING QUITE A
BIT OF SUPPORT FROM BOTH
POLITICAL PARTIES FOR TRUMP'S
MOVE ON SYRIA MILITARY FOR
UNLEASHING CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON
CITIZENS THERE WHAT HAPPENS NEXT
TO GETTING A CRITICAL LOOK ON
CAPITOL HILL.
I'LL TALK WITH ONE LAW MAKER WHO
BACKS THE PRESIDENT ON SYRIA,
BUT SAID HOW HE JUSTIFIED IT
LEGALLY WAS FLAWED.
AND SAID THAT CONGRESS NEEDS TO
GET INVOLVED IMMEDIATELY, SCOTT
TAYLOR A FORMER NAVY SEAL, AND
MEMBER OF HOMELAND SECURITY, HE
WILL JOIN ME LATER THIS HOUR,
STAY CLOSE.
>> AND RIGHT NOW, FOX NEWS IS
LEARNING NEW DETAILS ABOUT THE
MAN ACCUSED OF PLOWING A BEER
TRUCK INTO A CROWD OF PEOPLE IN
STOCKHOLM, WE'D SWEDEN, WHEN HIS
REASON FOR DOING THIS MAY HAVE
DONE.
>> A DOMESTIC FOCUS FOR THE
PRESIDENT LAST YEAR, URBAN
BLIGHT AND CREATING JOBS FOR
POOR AMERICANS IN THE CITIES,
HEAD SECRETARY.
YOU SEE HIM THERE BEN CARSON
WILL JOIN US LIVE ON THE "FOX
REPORT" WITH A CHECK IN FROM HIS
LISTENING TOUR ACROSS AMERICA.
o,
gas or bloating?
She does.
Help defend against
those digestive issues.
Take Phillips' Colon Health
Probiotic Caps daily
with three types of
good bacteria.
400 likes? Wow!
Try Phillips'
Colon Health.
gives you a reason to slow down
and pull up a seat to the table.
That's why she takes the time to
season her turkey to perfection,
and make stuffing from scratch.
So that you can spend time
on what really matters.
Marie Callender's.
It's time to savor.
DearThere's no other
way to say this.
It's over.
I've found a permanent
escape from monotony.
Together, we are
perfectly balanced,
our senses awake,
our hearts racing as one.
I know this is sudden,
but they say: If you
love something...
set it free.
See you around, Giulia
♪
Or keeping a hotel's guests
cuttinconnected.i to 35,000
fans...
Businesses count on
communication,
and communication counts on
CenturyLink.
of your brain can make it hard
to lose weight?
CONTRAVE is an FDA-approved
weight-loss medicine that may
. .. .
. .
Other serious side effects
include seizures, increase in
blood pressure or heart rate,
liver damage, manic episodes,
glaucoma and allergic reactions.
Do not take with opioids.
Reduce hunger, help control
cravings.
CONTRAVE. The #1 prescribed
weight-loss brand.
Go to CONTRAVE.com.
>> SECRETARY OF HOUSING AND
URBAN DEVELOPMENT, DOCTOR BEN
CARSON RETURNED TO THE DETROIT
NEIGHBORHOOD.
THAT TRIP TO SHOW, THEN
CANDIDATE DONALD TRUMP TO SHOW
THE MORE IMPOVERISHED AREAS.
NOW, HE SAYS HE WANTS TO DO MORE
THAN JUST PUT ROOFTOPS OVER THE
HEADS OF AMERICANS.
HE HOPES TO EMPOWER THEM AS
WELL.
SECRETARY CARSON IS HERE TO TELL
US ABOUT THE PLAN.
IT IS ALWAYS GOOD TO SEE YOU.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
MY FIRST QUESTION FOR YOU HAS TO
DO WITH WHAT YOU ARE DOING TO
GATHER INFORMATION.
YOU HAVE BEEN DOING THIS
LISTENING TO HER.
I'M CURIOUS TO SEE WHERE YOU
HAVE GOTTEN WHAT YOU HAVE HEARD.
>> THE FIRST PLACE I STARTED WAS
IN THE HUD BUILDING.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN WORKING THERE
FROM 10 - OF 40 YEARS AND THEY
HAVE A LOT OF IMPORTANT
INFORMATION.
I'M STILL GETTING INFORMATION
FROM THEM.
AS I HAVE GONE TO SOME OF THE
CITIES, ONE OF THE THINGS THAT
HAS IMPRESSED ME AND WORKED
EXTRAORDINARY WHILE WAS THE
PUBLIC PRIVATE PARTNERSHIPS AND
THE ABILITY TO LEVERAGE FEDERAL
DOLLARS IN SOME PLACES LIKE
DETROIT, AT A RATE OF 8 - 1.
THIS GETS THE LOCAL COMMUNITY
INVESTED IN A WAY THAT THEY HAVE
A VESTED INTEREST IN MAKING SURE
THE PROJECT SUCCEEDS.
SO YOU DON'T HAVE JUST THESE
FEDERAL PEOPLE LOOKING OVER
EVERYBODY'S SHOULDER.
I THINK THAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
>> YOU KNOW IT'S INTERESTING?
WE'VE BEEN TALKING ABOUT FOREIGN
POLICY THAT WE HAVE NOT TALKED
AS MUCH ABOUT DOMESTIC POLICY
THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP, THEN
CANDIDATE WANTED TO FOCUS ON IN
URBAN AREAS.
CREATING JOBS IS AN AREA HE
THOUGHT HE COULD WIN VICTORY.
GOING FORWARD, WHAT YOU SEE IS
THE PLAN?
I HAVE BEEN READING THAT YOU
WILL BE LEANING ON RICH URBAN
HOMEOWNERS TO BE HELPING OUT
THEIR NEIGHBORS.
HAVE YOU TALK TO THE PRESIDENT
TO SEE WHAT YOU THINK ABOUT
THAT?
>> THE PRESIDENT AND I ARE VERY
WELL ALIGNED.
WE ARE LOOKING AT THINGS ALREADY
IN PLACE, LIKE SECTION THREE
WHICH REQUIRES THOSE PEOPLE
RECEIVING HOUSING FUNDS TO
EMPLOY SOME OF THE LOW INCOME
PEOPLE IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
IT HAS BEEN LARGELY NEGLECTED
ACROSS THE COUNTRY BECAUSE
PEOPLE FREQUENTLY DO NOT HAVE
THE SKILLS.
WHAT WE ARE LOOKING AT IS A WAY
TO, AHEAD OF TIME, MAYBE A YEAR
AHEAD OF TIME BEFORE MAJOR
PROJECT, GO IN AND TRAIN PEOPLE.
NOW YOU DON'T HAVE THAT EXCUSE.
WE HAVE MORE EMPLOYMENT OF
PEOPLE WHO CAN HELP WITH
INFRASTRUCTURE PROJECTS.
NOW THEY HAVE A SKILL THAT
TRAINS THEM.
THESE ARE THINGS WE NEED TO DO
WITH TO DEVELOP OUR PEOPLE.
NOT JUST PUT A ROOF OVER THEIR
HEAD.
DEVELOPING THE WHOLE PERSON.
THAT MEANS WORKING WITH THE
DEPARTMENT OF EDUCATION, THE
DEPARTMENT OF LABOR,
TRANSPORTATION, HHS, A NUMBER OF
THINGS TO CREATE VIBRANT
COMMUNITIES.
>> YOU MENTIONED THAT 8 - 1 WHEN
YOU LOOK AT THE PRIVATE PUBLIC
PARTNERSHIP AND HOW FAR PUBLIC
DOLLARS WOULD GO.
I IMAGINE THAT'S IMPORTANT.
PART OF THE WHITE HOUSE BUDGET
PROPOSAL WOULD CUT THE
DEPARTMENT AT HUD BY MORE THAN
13%.
WHAT IS YOUR REACTION TO HAVING
TO DO THE JOB ON LESS MONEY FOR
YOUR DEPARTMENT?
>> WE ARE LOOKING AT
EFFICIENCIES.
HOW DO WE CARVE OUT AND GET THE
BANK FOR OUR BUCK.
ALSO, THE ADMINISTRATION IS NOT
INTERESTED IN HURTING PEOPLE AND
PUTTING PEOPLE OUT ON THE
STREET.
WE ARE VERY INTERESTED IN MAKING
SURE THAT WE ARE EFFICIENT AND
THAT WE ARE COMPASSIONATE, NOT
ONLY TO THE PEOPLE TODAY BUT THE
PEOPLE TOMORROW.
EVERY SINGLE AMERICAN OWES
$60000 IN TERMS OF OUR NATIONAL
DEBT.
WE HAVE TO START LOOKING OUT FOR
THE PEOPLE WHO ARE COMING AFTER
US.
WE CANNOT JUST IGNORE THAT.
MANY NATIONS HAVE TRIED THAT IN
THE PAST AND IT HAS BEEN
DETRIMENTAL TO THEM.
>> THE VIDEO WE SHOWED AT THE
TOP WAS YOU AND YOUR FORMER HOME
OF DETROIT.
WE KNOW THE STATE OF MICHIGAN
HOW MUCH THEY HAVE SUFFERED BOTH
ECONOMICALLY AND EVEN IN TERMS
OF WHAT HAPPENED IN FLINT WITH
THE DRINKING WATER AND SOME OF
THE PROBLEMS THERE.
OVER YEARS AND DECADES OF
LIBERAL LEADERSHIP AND DEMOCRATS
IN OFFICE.
POLITICS COME UP IN YOUR
LISTENING TO HER?
>> NOT VERY MUCH.
I HAVE DEALT WITH BOTH
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS.
THE ISSUES THAT FACE US ARE NOT
REPUBLICAN OR DEMOCRAT ISSUES.
WE HAVE 3 - 4 TIMES THE NUMBER
OF PEOPLE WHO NEED AFFORDABLE
HOUSING THE WHAT WE CAN PROVIDE.
WE HAVE AN AGING POPULATION,
BABY BOOMERS WHO NEED TO RETIRE
BUT DON'T HAVE THE FINANCES TO
DO SO BECAUSE THEIR 4O1 KAYS
HAVE NOT DONE MUCH IN THE PAST
TEN YEARS.
WE HAVE GOT TO BE CREATIVE AND
THINK OUT-OF-THE-BOX IN ORDER TO
MAINTAIN A REASONABLE LIFESTYLE
FOR THESE INDIVIDUALS.
THIS CERTAINLY CANNOT BE A PART
OF SOMETHING.
>> REAL QUICK, BEFORE I LET YOU
GO YOU SEEM TO BE RIGHT ON
TARGET WITH THIS I KNOW YOU TO
CRITICISM EARLY ON, BUT THIS IS
IN YOUR WHEELHOUSE, YOU'VE GONE
BACK TO THE URBAN AREAS.
I WANT TO GIVE YOU THE LAST
WORD.
>> OKAY.
THE LAST WORD IS THAT WE ONLY
HAVE 330 MILLI- PEOPLE IN
AMERICA.
ONE QUARTER WHAT CHINA HAS, ONE
QUARTER OF WHAT INDIA HAS.
WE HAVE GOT TO DEVELOP ALL OF
OUR PEOPLE IF WE ARE GOING TO
COMPETE IN THE FUTURE.
THAT MEANS TAKING A HOLISTIC
APPROACH.
>> NEXT, WHERE YOU GOING?
>> HEADING OFF TO MIAMI.
I WILL BE GOING THERE THIS WEEK.
I'M SURE WE'LL SEE A LOT OF
GREAT THINGS THERE.
WERE LOOKING NOT ONLY THE
POSITIVE THINGS BUT THE NEGATIVE
THINGS BECAUSE WE CAN LEARN FROM
BOTH.
>> YOU HEARD IT HERE HERE FIRST.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH DOCTOR
CARSON.
POLICE IN SWEDEN ARE RELEASING
INFORMATION ABOUT THE DEADLY
TRUCK ATTACK IN STOCKHOLM.
WHY POLICE SAY HE WAS ALREADY
BEING SOUGHT.
HE WAS ABLE TO SLIP THROUGH
THEIR FINGERS.
Make sure the germs they
bring home don't stick around.
Use Clorox
disinfecting products.
Because no one kills germs
better than Clorox.
I USE WHAT'S
ALREADY INSIDE ME
TO REACH MY GOALS.
SO I LIKED WHEN
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
THAT I MAY REACH
MY BLOOD SUGAR
AND A1C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING
WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS
NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE
MY BODY TO DO WHAT
IT'S SUPPOSED TO DO
RELEASE ITS
OWN INSULIN.
TRULICITY RESPONDS WHEN
MY BLOOD SUGAR RISES.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN.
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS ITCHING, RASH,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING;
A LUMP OR SWELLING IN YOUR NECK;
OR SEVERE PAIN IN
YOUR STOMACH AREA.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS,
WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE,
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS WORSE.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING YOUR
A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR NUMBERS
WITH A NON-INSULIN OPTION,
CLICK TO ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
>> POLICE HAVE ARRESTED A SECONT
WEEKEND'S DEADLY TRUCK ATTACK.
LEARNING ABOUT THE MAN WHO WAS
ACCUSED OF CARING THAT OUT.
HE WAS ORDERED TO LEAVE THE
COUNTRY AFTER HIS REQUEST FOR
RESIDENCY WAS DENIED.
INSTEAD, HE STAYED AND DODGED
DEPORTATION BY GIVING THEM THE
WRONG ADDRESS.
AS FOR THE MEMORIAL, ORGANIZERS
ARE RELOCATING IT AFTER NEARBY
FENCE THREATENED TO COLLAPSE.
>> PASSWORD AND LOOKING AHEAD TO
A BIG STORY THIS WEEK.
JUDGE NEIL GORSUCH WILL BE SWORN
IN AS THE 113th A SUPREME
COURT JUSTICE, TOMORROW MORNING
AFTER BEING CONFIRMED BY THE
SENATE LAST WEEK.
COURSES WILL GET RIGHT TO WORK
AS THE HIGH COURT IS EXPECTED
TO'S HERE TO CASES AND THE NEW
COMING WEEKS.
HERE IS MORE ON THE SUPREME
COURT'S NEWEST MEMBER.
>> NOW THAT THE SENATE HAS
CONFIRMED NEIL GORSUCH TO BE THE
NEXT SUPREME COURT JUSTICE
REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS ARE
WAITING TO SEE HOW GORSUCH VOTES
ON THE BET.
HOW CLOSELY HE FALLS IN LINE
WITH PRESIDENT TRUMP SUMMI IDEA.
>> THE NOMINATION OF NEIL M
GORSUCH OF COLORADO TO BE AN
ASSOCIATE JUSTICE OF THE SUPREME
COURT OF THE UNITED STATES, IS
CONFIRMED.
>> HITTING THE GROUND RUNNING ON
THURSDAY, THE NEW JUSTICE WILL
MEET WITH HIS COLLEAGUES TO
DECIDE WHETHER OR NOT TO HEAR
NUMBER OF CASES IN THE FALL
TERM.
THERE ARE STILL A COUPLE OF
MONTHS IN THE CURRENT TERM FOR
THE COURT WHICH ENDS IN JUNE.
HE FEELS THE CONSERVATIVE SEAT
LEFT VACANT BY THE LATE JUSTICE
ANTONIN SCALIA.
HIS NEW VOICE COULD BE THE
TIEBREAKER VOTE.
UNDER CONSIDERATION BY THE
HIGHEST COURT WHETHER OR NOT TO
HEAR THE CASES ABOUT SECOND
AMENDMENT RIGHTS AS WELL AS OF
BUSINESS OWNERS MAY REFUSE TO
OFFER SERVICES TO SAME-SEX
COUPLES.
I CASE BOTH PARTIES WILL BE
CLOSELY WATCHING, HOW INSTEP THE
NEW JUSTICE IS WITH THE
PRESIDENT AND HIS REVISED TRAVEL
BAN ON REFUGEES.
GETTING GORSUCH ON THE BENCH HAS
NOT BEEN EASY FOR THE PRESIDENT
OR GOP LEADERS.
AFTER BETTER CONFIRMATION BATTLE
IN THE SENATE WHICH PRONTO
REPUBLICANS TO USE THE NUCLEAR
OPTION, NOW BLAMED FOR THE
HISTORIC MOVE BEING TOSSED
BETWEEN BOTH PARTIES.
>> BOTH DEMOCRATS AND
REPUBLICANS HAVE BLAME.
BOTH DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS
HAVE HANDLED THINGS IN A WAY
THAT SHOULD NOT HAVE BEEN DONE.
WE SHOULD CHANGE OUR RULES BY
BIPARTISAN.
WE SHOULD NOT CHANGE OUR ROLES
TO ACCOMPLISH A PURPOSE.
>> TOMORROW MORNING, NEIL
GORSUCH WILL BECOME THE NINTH
JUSTICE ON THE SUPREME COURT AND
THE 114th IN HISTORY.
HE WILL BE SWORN IN IN A ROSE
GARDEN CEREMONY.
>> Harris: WILL WATCH HISTORY
BEING MADE HERE ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
WE'LL BRING A COMPLETE COVERAGE
OF THE CEREMONY, AND WE WILL LET
YOU KNOW WHAT YOU JUST HEARD
LAUREN TALKING ABOUT, THE
PRIVATE ONE AS WELL.
THE COUNTRY WILL BE ABLE TO
WATCH THAT PLAY OUT THAT IS
PUBLIC.
STAY WITH THE FOX NEWS CHANNEL
AT 9:00 A.M. EASTERN.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS TAKING ACTION
ON FORM POLICY.
WE HAVE BEEN TALKING ABOUT AT
THIS HOUR.
SCREEN LEFT, THE AIRSTRIKE ON
THE SYRIAN AIRBASE IN RESPONSE
TO THAT CHEMICAL ATTACK.
THE RIGHT SCREEN, THE AIRCRAFT
CARRIER, THE PINNACLE OF
AMERICAN FORCE PROJECTION,
100,000 TONS OF DIPLOMACY AS WE
HAVE HEARD AN EARLIER GUEST
STAY.
IT IS STEAMING TOWARD THE KOREAN
PENINSULA TO SEND A STRONG
MESSAGE.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT WHAT IT MEANS
FOR THE PRESIDENT, THE NATION,
AND WHAT COMES NEXT.
CONGRESSMAN SCOTT TAYLOR FROM
VIRGINIA IS COMING UP NEXT.
I was given warfarin
in the hospital,
but wondered, was this the
best treatment for me?
So I asked my doctor.
And he recommended ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots
and reduces the risk of
them happening again.
Yes, ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots.
ELIQUIS also had
significantly
less major
bleeding
than the
standard
treatment.
Both made me
turn around my
thinking.
Don't stop ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal injection
while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling,
numbness, or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
...and it may take longer
than usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned
medical or dental
procedures.
ELIQUIS treats
DVT and PE
blood clots.
Plus had
less major
bleeding.
Both made ELIQUIS
the right treatment for me.
Ask your doctor if switching
to ELIQUIS is right for you.
Various: (Shouting) Heigh!
Ho!
( ♪ )
It's off to work we go!
Woman:
On the Gulf Coast,
new ExxonMobil projects
are expected to create
over 45,000 jobs.
And each job created
by the energy industry
supports two others
in the community.
Altogether,
the industry supports over
9 million jobs nationwide.
These are jobs that natural
gas is helping make happen,
all while reducing
America's emissions.
HIM
.
>> Harris: THE U.S. MISSILE
STRIKES IN SYRIA ARE RAISING
QUESTIONS AMONG LAWMAKERS IN
WASHINGTON OVER WHAT ROLE WE
SHOULD PLAY IN THE SIX YEARS
CIVIL WAR GOING FORWARD.
ONE SURVIVOR OF THE CHEMICAL
ATTACK THAT SPURRED THAT
OPERATION SAID PEOPLE SHOULD
FORGET THE POLITICS.
THAT MAN LOST HIS WIFE.
YOU PROBABLY SEEN THE PICTURE
GONE VIRAL OF HIM HOLDING HIS
TWIN BABIES.
THE ASSAD REGIME TOOK THEM OUT
WITH CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
HE SAID THE U.S. SHOULD DO MORE
NOW, NOT JUST ONE STRIKE.
NOT ALL SYRIANS AGREE.
ENGINEMEN HALL HAS THE STORY
FROM TURKEY.
>> IT WAS WATCHING VIDEOS OF
THIS HORRIFIC CHEMICAL ATTACK
WHICH DROVE PRESIDENT TRUMP TO
INTERVENE.
WHILE SPEAKING TODAY PEOPLE ARE
DIVIDED UP IT IS EASY TO
UNDERSTAND WHAT DROVE HIM.
IT WAS ALSO AN INCREDIBLY
SOBERING MOMENT.
AMONG THE FAMILIES WE SPOKE TO
WAS ABDUL, HE HAS BECOME THE
FACE OF THE TRAGEDY.
HE WAS REUNITED WITH FAMILY
MEMBERS WHO DID SURVIVE, THOUGH
HE LOST 22.
HE DESCRIBED SOME OF THE THINGS
HE SAW.
>> AS I ENTERED THE HOUSE, THE
WHOLE FAMILY WAS DEAD.
GROWN-UPS, DEAD.
FAMILY ON TOP OF EACH OTHER.
MY WIFE, MY CHILDREN, MY
BROTHER, HIS WIFE, THEIR
CHILDREN, MY NIECES, ALL OF THEM
DEAD.
AFTER A FEW MINUTES, I FAINTED.
>> AMONG THE DEAD, HIS 11 MONTH
OLD TWINS.
HE BURIED THEM IN HIS WIFE WITH
HIS OWN HANDS, BUT CANNOT BEAR
TO PUT THEM IN THE GROUND,
GRIPPING THEM TILL THE BITTER
END.
HE SPOKE TO US ABOUT THE
AMERICAN STRIKES.
>> I WANT TO TELL PRESIDENT
TRUMP, THE FIRST STRIKE WAS
GOOD, IT SAVED US.
BUT JUST A FEW HOURS LATER THE
AIRBAGS CONTINUED WORKING, IT'S
LIKE A CHALLENGE FROM ASSAD.
I CAN STILL ATTACK FROM THE SAME
BASE YOU ATTACKED.
>> NOT ONLY A PLANE STILL TAKING
OFF FROM THE AIRBASE, THERE
STILL BOMBING THE TOWN.
APPARENTLY ADD A GREATER PACE
THAN BEFORE, WITH NOBODY TO STOP
THEM.
>> ASSAD IS A CRIMINAL.
HE IS KILLING NOT ONLY HUMAN
BEINGS AND CHILDREN, BUT ANIMALS
AS IF THEY WERE THE SAME.
HE IS A WAR CRIMINAL.
>> THE FEELING IS ONE OF
GRATITUDE TOWARD THE U.S.
THE STRIKES GIVE THE SYRIAN BITE
AT THE END OF THE TUNNEL AND
OPTIMISM FOR THE FUTURE.
BUT THE LESS THEY HAVE DONE TO
BACK UP THE ASSAD REGIME, HE
WILL CONTINUE TO KILL HIS PEOPLE
LIKE HE HAS DONE FOR THE LAST
SIX YEARS.
>> Harris: MY NEXT GUEST,
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S DECISION TO
LAUNCH THE MISSILE STRIKE ON
SYRIA.
HE OPPOSES THE LEGAL BASIS ON
WHICH YOU ORDER THAT MISSION.
VIRGINIA REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN,
SCOTT TAYLOR IS A MEMBER OF THE
HOUSE APPROPRIATION ON HOMELAND
SECURITY.
THE U.S. NAVY SEAL, HE HAS
SERVED HIS COUNTRY IN THAT WAY.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
I WANT TO START WITH WHERE YOU
ARE IN TERMS OF SUPPORTING THE
PRESIDENT AND WHY YOU SAY
CONGRESS NEEDS TO IMMEDIATELY
GET INVOLVED NOW?
>> LET'S BE CLEAR.
OUT OF THE CONSTITUTION THEY
SHOULD HAVE THE ABILITY AND
FLEXIBILITY AS A PRESIDENT THAT
HE OR SHE SEE SOMETHING AS A
THREAT TO OUR NATIONAL SECURITY
TOWARD TROOPS AND INTEREST THEY
HAVE HAVE THE FLEXIBILITY TO
ASK.
WITH THAT BEING SAID, CONGRESS
DECLARES WAR OR CREATE STATUTORY
LAWS THAT ALLOW FOR USE OF
FORCE.
THIS PRESIDENT, AND THE PREVIOUS
PRESIDENT, TWO ADMINISTRATIONS
OPERATING OFF USE OF MILITARY
FORCE FROM 16 YEARS AGO FROM A
THIRD ADMINISTRATION.
CONGRESS DOES NEED TO LEAD AND
THAT NEED TO HAVE A VOICE IN
THIS.
I'VE SEEN MANY CONGRESSMEN AND
WOMEN ON NATIONAL NEWS IN THE
PAST FEW DAYS BECAUSE OF THE
STRIKE.
THE BEST THING WE CAN DO AS
LEADERS IN CONGRESS IS TO TAKE
IT UP IN DEBATE AND TALK ABOUT
IT.
THE PRESIDENT DID HAVE THE
ABILITY TO ACT.
HE HAS THAT TIME AND FLEXIBILITY
TO DO SO.
UNDER THE UN CHEMICAL WEAPONS
TREATY, YOU CANNOT PRODUCE,
DEVELOP, OR USE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS, I DO SUPPORT THE
PRESIDENT AND HIS ACTION.
I THINK THE WORLD WAS WATCHING
WHEN THAT HAPPENED AND I SUPPORT
HIS DECISION TO TAKE ACTION AND
SAY THAT WILL NOT STAND.
>> Harris: PEOPLE HERE YOU AND I
CAN SEE EYES GLAZING OVER.
CONGRESS CUT SEEM TO AGREE ON
ANYTHING.
I UNDERSTAND WHAT YOU HAVE SAID,
THAT IT IS UNACCEPTABLE THAT YOU
ARE WORKING OFF A 16-YEAR-OLD
AUTHORIZATION OF MILITARY FORCE
TO GET THIS DONE.
DO YOU REALLY HAVE CONFIDENCE
THAT IN A BIPARTISAN MANNER YOU
CAN MOVE FORWARD AND GIVE THE
PRESIDENT SUPPORT HE NEEDS?
>> THAT THE NEXT ONE QUESTION.
BECAUSE CONGRESS IS SLOW TO
DEBATE AND THERE'S DIVERGING
INTEREST THERE, THERE THE
PEOPLE'S REPRESENTATIVE.
THAT'S WHEN EXECUTIVE HAS
FLEXIBILITY IN TIME TO TAKE
ACTION IF THEY DEEM FIT.
BUT, LEADERS MUST ACT.
LEADERS MUST LEAVE.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE HAVE TO HAVE
A SAY IN USE OF MILITARY FORCE
AROUND THE WORLD.
THAT BEING SAID, HOW TO HAVE A
SAY?
TO THE REPRESENTATIVES IN
CONGRESS.
IT'S IMPORTANT THEIR VOICES LIKE
MYSELF FOR SPEAKING OUT SAME
CONGRESS MUST TAKE THIS OUT AND
DEBATED.
THEY NEED TO COME TOGETHER
BIPARTISAN AND SAY WHAT WERE
GOING TO DO.
IF WERE GOING TO AUTHORIZE THE
USE OF MILITARY FORCE FOR LONGER
TIME ARE NOT.
>> Harris: HAVE ANOTHER QUESTION
THAT HAS BEEN LINGERING, THAT IS
OUR COMPLETE MISSION.
AS A FORMER NAVY SEAL YOU KNOW
WHEN YOU HAVE AN ENDGAME IT
SAVES PEOPLE'S LIVES AND KEEPS
OUR VISION CRISP.
IT KEEPS THINGS FROM VEERING UP
AND BECOMING OTHER THINGS.
WHAT IS THE ENDGAME HERE?
TO WE KNOW WHAT IT IS?
>> THAT'S NEXT LINE POINT.
WERE NOT GOOD TO BE TALKING
ABOUT TACTICS, STRATEGY -WISE
IT'S IMPORTANT.
THE EXECUTIVE BRANCH SHOULD COME
TO CONGRESS AND TALK ABOUT THE
INTELLIGENCE, THE GOALS, THE END
STATE.
I'M CONCERNED ABOUT SYRIA, IT'S
A POWDER CAKE, ANYTHING THAT I'M
AWARE OF SINCE WORLD WAR II YOU
HAVE TURKEY, US, ISRAEL, RUSSIA,
OTHERS IN THAT SPACE AS WELL.
IT'S VERY DANGEROUS.
I RAN AS WELL, HEZBOLLAH.
YOU HAVE TREMENDOUS POTENTIAL
FOR FLASHPOINT.
AND NOT ENOUGH TO COMPLEXION A
POTENTIALLY GREATER CONFLICT.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY IMPORTANT THAT
PEOPLE UNDERSTAND THE ENDGAME
AND THE STRATEGY AND THE GOAL OF
THE UNITED STATES.
>> Harris: WE ARE WAITING TO
HEAR THAT IS GOING TO BE.
YOU HEARD THAT FATHER IN SYRIA
WHO LOST HIS TWINS, AMERICA DO
MORE THAN ONE STRIKE.
ARE YOU CONCERNED THE EMOTION
BASED UPON THE NEED FOR POLICY?
HOW DO YOU KEEP THEM SEPARATE?
>> IT IS A HORRIBLE TRAGEDY AND
WATCHING THE IMAGES AND
LISTENING TO THAT FAMILY.
IT DOES TUG AT THE HEARTSTRINGS.
IT IS IMPORTANT FOR LEADERS TO
BE ABLE TO SEE CLARITY THROUGH
CHAOS.
UNDERSTAND WHAT THE STRATEGY AND
THE GOALS ARE.
WE CANNOT SOLVE EVERY PROBLEM
BUT THERE'S NO DOUBT THAT EVEN
SYRIA SIGNED ONTO THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS CONVENTION AS WELL.
IT'S IMPORTANT THE WORLD'S LEAD
AND THEY SAY SOMETHING LIKE THAT
CANNOT AND WILL NOT STAND.
THE PRESIDENT TOOK DECISIVE
ACTION AND THIS IS A COMPLETELY
DIFFERENT PRESIDENT THAN THE
LAST ONE.
WHEN YOU HAVE DIPLOMACY THAT THE
WORLD AGREES WITH YOU HAVE TO
BACK IT UP WITH FORCE.
THAT'S IMPORTANT.
>> Harris: YOU SAY YOU ARE READY
TO STEP UP AND BEGIN THAT
LEADING IN CONGRESS TO MAKE SURE
YOU GIVE THE PRESIDENT SUPPORT
HE NEEDS.
WHEN YOU COME BACK, I WANT TO
TALK ABOUT VETERANS AFFAIRS.
YOU ACTUALLY GET SOME THINGS
DONE AND YOU MIGHT BE ABLE TO
WORK WITH THE PRESIDENT ON THAT
PART OF DOMESTIC POLICY.
WE'LL BRING YOU BACK.
AND WE CAN TALK ABOUT ANOTHER
TIME, DOES THAT SOUND GOOD?
>> I'M OPTIMISTIC AND POSITIVE
THAT WERE GONNA GET STUFF DONE
AT THE VIRGINIA.
THANK YOU.
>> Harris: THANK YOU FOR YOUR
TIME.
POPE FRANCIS IS WEIGHING IN ON
THE DEADLY BOMBING SAID TO
CHRISTIAN CHURCHES IN EGYPT.
THE POPE IS CONDEMNING THE
ATTACKS HAS THAT HAPPENED AS HE
WAS HOLDING HIS PALM SUNDAY MASS
AT THE VATICAN.
HE OFFERED HIS CONDOLENCES AND
SAID HE IS PAYING FOR THOSE WHO
DIED.
THE BOMBING BECAME'S WEEKS BE
FOR HIS VISIT TO CAIRO.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS SEARCHING FOR
AN END WITH DOMESTIC ISSUES.
WE'RE GOING TO TALK MORE ABOUT
THE VIRGINIA IN COMING WEEKS AS
WELL.
THE PRESIDENT IS NOW TURNING
TOWARD TAX REFORM.
WE'LL HAVE TO TURN TO DEMOCRATS
TO GET SOMETHING DONE, TO HELP
HIS PRIORITIES BECOME A REALITY?
WE'LL TALK WITH MY NEXT GUEST,
DEMOCRAT.
NEW DETAILS ON A MANHUNT FOR A
SUSPECT POLICE CALL A NATIONAL
THREAT.
STAY WITH US
Maybe you should've done
more research on them.
For drivers with
Accident Forgiveness,
Liberty Mutual won't raise
your rates
due to your first accident.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Aleve with
DTENS Device,y
a relief from
lower back pain.
That's good, cause I need it.
I put it on my back.
Ok, this is interesting.
There we go.
There's the little tingle.
I feel this electrical pulse
grabbing at my muscles.
Level 3. 5.
I'm pleasantly surprised.
It was more powerful
than I was expecting it to be.
It worked. What can I say?
I believe Aleve.
Learn more and read
Reviews at Aleve.com.
At Red Lobster's Lobsterfestime.
any of these 9 lobster dishes
could be yours.
So don't resist delicious new
Lobster Mix and Match
or Lobsterfest Surf and Turf
because you won't have this
chance for long.
WHY PAUSE A
SPONTANEOUS MOMENT?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
>> HIM
.
>> Harris: PROTESTERS TAKEN TO
THE STREET OF DOWNTOWN DALLAS TO
SPEAK OUT OF AGAINST PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S IMMIGRATION POLICY.
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE INCLUDING
IMMIGRANTS AND REFUGEES AREN'T
MARCHING TO MILES WHAT IS CALLED
THE MEGA MARCH.
THEY'RE PACKED INTO SAID HE
HALTED AND THE DEMONSTRATION.
THEY EXPECT ABOUT 100,000
PEOPLE.
THEY DID THAT BEFORE IN 2006, I
THINK IT WAS.
BACK TO WASHINGTON WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS LOOKING TO
MOVE ON WITH HIS DOMESTIC
AGENDA.
AFTER FAILING TO REPEAL OBAMA
CARE, HE AND CONGRESS ARE
GEARING UP TO TACKLE TAX REFORM.
EARLY SIGNS INDICATE A TOUGH
FIGHT AHEAD.
WITH EVEN REPUBLICANS
DISAGREEING OVER KEY PARTS OF A
PROPOSED PLAN.
CAN PRESIDENT TRUMP GET
DEMOCRATS ON HIS SIDE?
MY NEXT GUEST HAS EXPERIENCE
WORKING WITH THE OTHER SIDE OF
THE POLITICAL AISLE FROM THE
WEST WING.
HE SPENT SIX YEARS WITH
PRESIDENT BILL CLINTON IN THE
1990s, DOUG SHOWING.
FORMER ADVISOR TO BILL CLINTON
AND A FOX NEWS CONTRIBUTOR AND
FRIEND, GOOD TO SEE YOU.
YOU HAVE BEEN TRAVELING ABOUT
GLAD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
PRESIDENT CLINTON PROBABLY
TEACHES A FEW THINGS ABOUT
DEALING WITH DIFFICULT PEOPLE,
RIGHT?
HE HAD FOUR DIFFERENT
CONGRESSES, THE FIRST ALL
DEMOCRAT, THE NEXT THREE FOR THE
REST OF HIS PRESIDENCIES HE WAS
STACKED AGAINST REPUBLICANS.
WHAT DID YOU TELL HIM?
>> BIPARTISANSHIP.
WHAT WAS I CALL TRIANGULATION.
CANDIDLY, WITH DONALD TRUMP
FIGHTING WITH REPUBLICANS, HE
HAS TO IF HE IS GOING TO
SUCCEED, BUILD ON THE SUCCESS OF
LAST WEEK'S RAID AND BEGIN
BIPARTISAN OUTREACH TO THE
DEMOCRATS.
>> Harris: LAST WEEK'S RAID?
WHAT YOU MEAN?
>> THE ATTACK ON SYRIA FOLLOWI
FOLLOWING.
>> BECAUSE HE HAS BIPARTISAN
SUPPORT ON THAT.
>> YES, NANCY PELOSI AND CHUCK
SCHUMER.
NOW, GIVEN THE FACT THAT
REPUBLICANS ON HEALTHCARE ARE
DIVIDED BETWEEN THE FREEDOM
CAUCUS, THE ESTABLISHMENT, THE
REPUBLICANS AND MODERATES, HE
REALLY HAS TO IF HE IS GOING TO
SUCCEED.
WHETHER IT BE A TAX REFORM,
HEALTHCARE, OR INFRASTRUCTURE.
>> Harris: LET'S STAY WITH TAX
REFORM NOW.
THAT WAS AN ISSUE THAT PRESIDENT
CLINT OUT WITH.
I WANT TO DO APPLES AND APPLES.
WHO DOES THE PRESIDENT REALLY
NEED TO REACH OUT TO?
>> THERE IS A CONSENSUS THAT WE
NEED TO DO CORPORATE TAX REFORM.
WE NEED TO REPATRIATE THE MONEY
THAT MAY BE TRILLIONS OF DOLLARS
THAT ARE OVERSEAS AND LOWER THE
RATE.
>> Harris: AND HE HAS SAID THAT,
HUNDRED DEMOCRATS FEEL?
>> DEMOCRATS FEEL FINE ABOUT IT.
THEY DON'T WANT TO REDUCE TAXES
ON THE WEALTHY WHICH IS ONE OF
HIS SIGNATURE INITIATIVES AS
WELL.
IF THEY CAN BE BROKEN UP AND BE
DONE AS BITE-SIZE INITIATIVES
MAYBE WE CAN GET SUCCESS.
>> Harris: WHO TAKES A BITE IN
TERMS EVERY PETRI MONEY
OVERSEAS?
>> IF THE PRESIDENT GOES TO
CHUCK SCHUMER AND SAID CHUCK, WE
HAVE TO GET SOMETHING DONE ON
CORPORATE TAX REFORM BEFORE WE
DO INDIVIDUAL TAX REFORM.
JUST MAYBE WE CAN BEGIN TO GET
SOME MOMENTUM TO GET OTHER
ISSUES.
>> Harris: CAN ASK YOU, WHY DOES
THE PRESIDENT HAVE TO GO TO
SENATOR SCHUMER?
WHY NOT THE OTHER WAY AROUND?
AND I'LL TELL YOU WHY.
YOU SAW WITH THE NOMINATION OF
NEIL GORSUCH, YOU SAW THAT
DEMOCRATS DO WANT TO PLAY BALL,
THEY WANTED TO FILIBUSTER.
WE BASICALLY GOT TWO SIDES NOT
WINNING BUT WE GOT A SUPREME
COURT JUSTICE WHICH I THOUGHT
EVERYBODY AGREED ON UNTIL CAME
TO POLITICS.
THAT MIGHT BE GREAT FOR THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE BUT AWFUL FOR
CAPITOL HILL.
MY QUESTION FOR YOU IS, WHY
CAN'T DEMOCRATS OFFER SOMETHING?
DOESN'T MAKE THEM LOOK WEAK?
>> ONE WORD, POLITICS.
THE DEMOCRATIC POLITIC PARTY ITS
DIVIDED.
THE ONLY THING THEY AGREE ON IS
OPPOSING DONALD TRUMP.
THEY WILL CONTINUE WITH THE
STRATEGY AS WE JUST SAW,
DEMONSTRATIONS, RESISTANCE,
OPPOSITION.
THAT IS WHY THE PRESIDENT WHO
HASN'T SPOKEN TO SCHUMER IN
ABOUT TWO MONTHS HAS TO REACH
OUT.
>> Harris: THIS ISN'T A WINNING
STRATEGY FOR DEMOCRATS.
YOU HAVE LOST 1000 SEATS BETWEEN
HOUSES, PRESIDENCY, CONGRESS,
IT'S NOT WORKING FOR YOU.
>> RIGHT.
THAT IS THE REASON WHY DEMOCRATS
HAVE COME TO THIS.
ADVOCACY OF IDEAS.
WE SOUGHT WAS SECRETARY CLINTON,
WE SOUGHT IN STATE AFTER STATE,
DOES NOT WORK.
WHAT THE DEMOCRATS HAVE FOUND
RECENTLY IS THE OPPOSITION
STRATEGY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT I WOULD DO, AS
YOU ARE SUGGESTING, URGE
BIPARTISANSHIP.
FOR THE PARTY BASE, THE
LEFT-WING, THIS RESPONSE
RESONATES.
>> Harris: REMEMBER THE GANG OF
EIGHT?
ON THAT WAS CHUCK SCHUMER.
THERE IS SOME DONATION DOLLARS
IN THE HISTORY WITH THEIR
CURRENT PRESIDENT WHEN HE WAS A
PRIVATE CITIZEN THAT WENT TO THE
GANG OF EIGHT.
A FEW DOLLARS, NOT A LOT WENT TO
SENATOR SCHUMER AT THE TIME FOR
THE CAUSE THEY WERE WORKING ON.
THEY HAVE SOME HISTORY TOGETHER.
DOES THAT GIVE YOU SOME HOPE
THAT WE CAN GO FORWARD WITH SOME
SORT OF BIPARTISANSHIP?
>> IT DOES GIVE ME HOPE.
SENATOR SCHUMER HAS MOVED AWAY
FROM WHERE HE WAS IN DECEMBER
WHICH WAS TO WORK WITH THE
PRESIDENT.
>> Harris: WHERE IS HE NOW?
>> HE'S IN THE OPPOSITION CAN.
RESIST, RESIST, RESIST.
I THINK OF THE PRESIDENT REACHES
OUT WE CAN GET A DEAL
POTENTIALLY ON HEALTHCARE, TAX
REFORM, EVEN IMMIGRATION.
>> Harris: WOULD YOU BE WILLING
TO BROKER THAT?
I'M NOT KIDDING.
YOU HAVE EXPERIENCE.
>> I WOULD DO ANYTHING I COULD
TO GET THAT DONE FOR THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
>> Harris: I WISCONSIN MAN WHO
PLEASE CONSIDER NATIONAL THREAT
IS AT LARGE AT THIS HOUR.
THE DETAILS ON THE HUNT FOR THIS
PERSON INVESTIGATORS BELIEVE HAS
A BEEF FOR POLITICIANS.
So she makes her pie crust
from scratch.
And sprinkles on brown sugar
streusel.
So that you can spend more time
making special moments with
your family.
Marie Callender's
It's time to savor
What twisted ankle?ask
What muscle strain?
Advil makes pain a distant
memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
I love how USAA gives me
the and the security
just like the Marines did.
At one point, I did change
to a different company
with car insurance,
and I was not happy with the
customer service.
We have switched back over
and we feel like
we're back home now.
The process through USAA
is so effortless,
that you feel like
you're a part of the family.
I love that I can pass the
membership to my children,
and that they can be protected.
We're the Williams family,
and we're USAA
members for life.
Call USAA today
to talk about
your insurance needs.
>> Harris: 161 PAGE MANIFESTOBAS
WHAT ONE MAN SAID TO DONALD
TRUMP.
NOW THE SEARCH IS ON TO FIND
HIM.
THEY'RE CALLING HIM A NATIONAL
THREAT.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS A NATIONAL MANHUNT.
THIS WISCONSIN RESIDENTS ARE ON
EDGE THIS WEEKEND AND
AUTHORITIES ARE KEEPING A CLOSE
EYE OUT ON CHURCHES AFTER
DISCOVERING ALARMING DETAIL IN
THE MANIFESTO.
THIS COMES AFTER POLICE WORKING
ON A TIP RATED AT JANESVILLE
HOME LAST NIGHT.
NOTHING TERMED UP FROM THAT.
150 MEMBERS OF LAW-ENFORCEMENT
ARE SEARCHING AROUND THE CLOCK.
THE STARTED TUESDAY WHEN JOSEPH
-- MAILED HIS LENGTHY MANIFESTO
TO DONALD TRUMP.
IT HAD HATRED FOR
LAW-ENFORCEMENT AND A CALL FOR
REBELLION IN THE CELL PHONE
VIDEO BE FOR PUTTING THE
MANIFESTO IN THE MAIL.
>> ANYBODY QUÉBEC THAT THIS
LETTER MIGHT WANT TO READ IT.
IT'S A REVOLUTION.
IT'S TIME FOR CHANGE.
>> LATER THAT NIGHT HE ALLEGEDLY
STOLE 16 FIREARMS FROM A GUN
SHOP, TORTIOUS CAR AND THEN
DISAPPEARED.
PLEASE HAVE BEEN GOING THROUGH
HIS MANIFESTO AND SAY IT MAKES
GENERIC THREATS AT SCHOOLS,
POLICE AND POSSIBLY PLACES OF
WORSHIP.
IT HAS CAUSED LAW-ENFORCEMENT TO
STEP UP PATROL TO CHURCHES AND
OTHER RELIGIOUS OF VENUES.
ONE CHURCH CANCELED ITS PALM
SUNDAY SERVICES THIS WEEKEND.
WE LEARNED HE IS NOT A STRANGER
TO LAW-ENFORCEMENT.
PAST CHARGES INCLUDE BATTERY,
MULTIPLE CHARGES FOR RESISTING
ARREST.
>> THERE IS ONE SPECIFIC CASE
WHERE HE ATTEMPTED TO DISARM A
POLICE OFFICER.
NOT FOR THE VERY SECURE HOLSTER
OF THIS OFFICER HE WOULD MOST
CERTAINLY DISARMED THAT POLICE
OFFICER.
FOR THAT CRIME HE WAS SENT TO
PRISON.
>> THE FBI IS OFFERING A
10000-DOLLAR REWARD FOR
INFORMATION THAT LEADS TO HIS
ARREST.
>> Harris: THANK YOU.
GREAT BRITAIN IS PAYING RESPECTS
TO A POLICE OFFICER KILLED IN
LAST MONTH'S TERROR ATTACK.
QUEEN ELIZABETH GAVE PERMISSION
FOR THE OFFICER COFFIN TO LIE IN
A CHAPEL IN PARLIAMENT.
HE WAS STABBED AND KILLED
ACCORDING TO BRITISH AUTHORITIES
AFTER HE DROVE AN SUV INTO A
CROWD.
PALMER WILL BE LAID TO REST
TOMORROW AFTER FULL POLICE
FUNERAL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
When heartburn hits,
fight back fast
with TUMS Smoothies.
It starts dissolving
the instant it
touches your tongue.
And neutralizes
stomach acid at the source.
♪ TUM -TUM -TUM -TUM
Smoothies! Only from TUMS
DearThere's no other
way to say this.
It's over.
I've found a permanent
escape from monotony.
Together, we are
perfectly balanced,
our senses awake,
our hearts racing as one.
I know this is sudden,
but they say: If you
love something...
set it free.
See you around, Giulia
♪
the slopes like I used to.
I even accept I have a higher
risk of stroke due to AFib,
a type of irregular heartbeat
not caused by a heart valve
problem.
But whatever trail I take,
I go for my best.
So if there's something better
than warfarin,
I'll go for that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS reduced the risk of
stroke better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS unless
your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
...and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care for
sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about all
planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor about ELIQUIS.
TECH: When your windshield
needs to be fixed...
trust Safelite AutoGlass.
For these parents, driving
around was the only way to get
their baby to sleep.
So when their windshield
got cracked...
CUSTOMER: We can't
drive this car.
TECH: ...they wanted it
fixed right.
So they scheduled with Safelite.
Our exclusive TrueSeal
technology means a strong,
reliabe bond,
every time.
At Safelite,
we stand behind our work.
Bye, bye.
Because the ones you love,
sit behind it.
(PARENTS WHISPER JINGLE)
Safelite repair, Safelite
replace.
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night.
Hold on Dad...
Liberty did what?
Yeah, Liberty Mutual 24-Hour
Roadside Assistance
helped him to fix his flat
so he could get home safely.
My dad says our insurance
doesn't have that.
Don't worry - I know what a
lug wrench is, Dad.
Is this a lug wrench?
Maybe?
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Ito treat your toughy
nasal allergies...
...listen up.
Unlike pills that don't
treat congestion,
Clarispray covers 100 percent of
your nasal allergy symptoms.
Clarispray. From the
makers of Claritin.
HARRIS: THIS IS AWESOME.
AN EYE CATCHING PICTURE HIT
TWITTER, IN PAST HOUR, OLD
POLITICAL RIVALS SHARING A GOOD
TIME, FORMER PRESIDENT BILL
CLINTON TWEETING OUT THIS
PICTURE WITH GEORGE H.W. BUSH ON
A VISIT TO HOUSTON, THEY TALKED
ABOUT GROWN KIDS, GRAND KIDS,
CLINTON GAVE BUSH A GIFT, A
GREEN PAIR OF SOCKS WITH
LABRADORS AND A BLUE PAIR WITH
BEES.
AND IT TOOK LONGER THAN EXPECTED
BUT WE HAVE A WINNER AT THE
MASTERS, SERGIO GARCIA IS TAKING
HOME THE FAMOUS GREEN JACKET,
EPIC FASHION.
HE WON TOURNAMENT AFTER A
PLAY-OFF HOLE AGAINST JUSTIN
ROSE.
THIS IS GARCIA'S FIRST EVER
MASTERS WIN.
WATCH THIS, IT WAS SOMETHING TO
SEE, HIS FIRST MAJOR
CHAMPIONSHIP, AS WELL.
SO WEARING OF THE GREEN, AND THE
WEARING OF THE SOCKS, IT HAS
BEEN A GOOD HOUR, I'LL SEE YOU
BACK HERE TOMORROW, NOON
EASTERN.
MY FRIEND JESSE WATTERS' WORLD
IS NEXT, WE'RE ABOUT TO BE IN
IT, HAVE A GREAT WEEK.
♪
>> TONIGHT --
>> TONIGHT I ORDERED A TARGETED
MILITARY STRIKE ON AIRFIELD IN
SYRIA.
JESSE: PRESIDENT TRUMP FINALLY
ENFORCING PRESIDENT OBAMA'S RED
LINE.
BUT IS IT ENOUGH?
AND WHAT DOES THIS MEAN FOR
RUSSIA?
SEAN SPICER, MARK STEYN AND NEWT
GINGRICH ALL HERE TO DISCUSS.
>> WE'VE SEEN NO EVIDENCE THAT
SHE'S DONE ANYTHING IMPROPER,
AND IT SEEMS LIKE AN EFFORT TO
TAR AND FEATHER HER.
JESSE: THE MEDIA CIRCLING THE
WAGONS AROUND SUSAN RICE, BUT
ARE OUR OWN INTELLIGENCE
AGENCIES HELPING THEM?
>> GOES OUT FIRST BECAUSE, LET'S