OR THIS
"SPECIAL REPORT," FAIR,
BALANCED AND INSPIRED BY
STAFF SERGEANT CARTER AND
SOLDIERS LIKE HIM TRULY
UNAFRAID.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT,
TONIGHT, OF THE EVIDENCE OF
A CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK
IN SYRIA IS UNDENIABLE.
THAT FROM SECRETARY OF
STATE JOHN KERRY.
NOW, HE SAYS THERE MUST BE
CONSEQUENCES.
IST WARSHIPS IN STRIKING
DISTANCE OF SYRIA.
>> UNITED STATES IS LOOKING
AT ALL OPTIONS.
>> PRESIDENT OBAMA BELIEVES
THERE MUST BE
ACCOUNTABILITY FOR THOSE
WHO WOULD USE THE WORLD'S
MOST HEINOUS WEAPONS NOW
SYRIA IS THREATENING TO
STRIKE BACK AS UNITED
NATIONS INSPECTORS DODGE
SNIPER FIRE AT THE SCENE OF
A POSSIBLE CHEMICAL ATTACK.
PLUS:
>> WHAT IS THIS WORLD
COMING TO ANYWAY?
POLITICIAN ARRESTED A
SECOND TEENAGER IN THE
BRUTAL KILLING OF A WORLD
WAR II VETERAN AND:
>> THEY JUST BROKE THE
WINDOW NOW.
>> A LITTLE BOY HOME ALONE
WHEN BURGLARS BREAK IN.
>> STAY RIGHT THERE.
>> HE HIDES IN THE CLOSET
AND CALLS 911 TONIGHT WHY
THE BOY IS A HOMETOWN HERO.
I'M JON SCOTT IN FOR
SHEPARD SMITH.
FOUR U.S. NAVY DESTROYERS
ARE CLOSE ENOUGH TO SYRIA
TO LAUNCH A MISSILE STRIKE
AT A MOMENT'S NOTICE.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM
PENTAGON OFFICIALS.
DEFENSE SECRETARY CHUCK
HAGEL SAYS THE U.S. IS
LOOKING AT ALL OPTIONS TO
RESPOND TO A SUSPECTED
CHEMICAL ATTACK IN SYRIA
THAT REPORTEDLY KILLED
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE
INCLUDING CHILDREN.
BUT HE SAYS THE U.S. WILL
NOT GO IT ALONE IF THERE IS
ANY ACTION TAKEN IT WILL
BE IN CONCERT WITH
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY AND
WITHIN FRAMEWORK OF LEGAL
JUSTIFICATION.
>> JOHN KERRY SAYS EVIDENCE
IS REAL AND COMPELLING, HE
SAYS THERE MUST BE
CONSEQUENCES.
"THE FOX REPORT'S"
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
LIVE IN OUR NEW YORK
NEWSROOM.
JOHN, THAN THE U.N. WEAPON
INSPECTORS ARE IN SYRIA.
BUT U.S. OFFICIALS HAVE
ALREADY MADE THEIR OWN
CONCLUSIONS.
>> YEAH, THEY MAY HAVE
DECIDED TO DO THAT JON,
SIMPLY BECAUSE OF THE
DIFFICULTY THOSE YATIONS
WEAPONS INSPECTORS HAVE
FACED IN DOING THEIR JOB
INSIDE SYRIA.
TODAY FOR INSTANCE THEIR
CONVOY LEFT HOTEL IN
CENTRAL DAMASCUS TO HEAD TO
THE SIGHT OF THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK FOR THE
FIRST TIME AND THE CONVOY
WAS FIRED ON BY AT LEAST
ONE SNIPER.
ONE VEHICLE WAS HIT.
NO INJURIES REPORTED.
AND THE WEAPONS INSPECTORS
DID THEN GO ON TO THE
HOSPITAL WHERE THEY
INTERVIEWED SOME OF THE
ALLEGED VICTIMS OF THE
ATTACK AND SOME DOCTORS WHO
HAD TREATED THEM.
BUT SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN
KERRY WAS QUICK TO POINT
OUT TODAY THAT THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT HAS BEEN
ANYTHING BUT HELPFUL TO
THOSE INSPECTORS.
LISTEN.
INSTEAD FOR FIVE DAYS THEY
REFUSED INVESTIGATORS TO
THE SITE OF THE ATTACK THAT
WOULD ALLEGEDLY EXONERATE
THEM.
INSTEAD IT ATTACKED THE
AREA FURTHER SHELLING IT
AND SYSTEMATICALLY
DESTROYING EVIDENCE.
THAT'S NOT THE BEHAVIOR OF
A GOVERNMENT THAT HAS
NOTHING TO HIDE.
>> NOW, THERE IS NO
INDICATION AT THIS MOMENT
WHEN THOSE UNITED NATIONS
INSPECTORS MIGHT LEAVE
SYRIA FOR ANYONE READING
THE TEA LEAVES THAT ACT
MIGHT BE ANOTHER IMPENDING
MILITARY ACTION.
>> PRESIDENT ASAN AS
DEFIANT AS EVER?
>> IT SEEMS THAT WAIT A
MINUTE HE SAT DOWN
APPARENTLY FOR INTERVIEW
WITH THE RUSSIAN DAILY
NEWSPAPER.
THE STILL PHOTOGRAPHS OF
THAT INTERVIEW WERE
RELEASED BY STATE RUN
SYRIAN MEDIA WE CANNOT
INDEPENDENTLY CONFIRM THEM.
IN THE INTERVIEW PRESIDENT
ASSAD SAID QUOTE:  THINK
MEANING THE UNITED STATES
CAN START A WAR BUT THEY
WILL NOT KNOW WHERE IT WILL
SPREAD OR HOW IT WILL END.
ASKED HOW HE BELIEVES IT
MIGHT END FOR THE U.S., HE
SAID WHAT IT SUFFERED IN
ALL ITS WARS FROM VIETNAM
UNTIL NOW FAILURE.
THOSE QUOTES APPEAR TO BE
AFFIRMATION OF WHAT WE HAVE
SAID MANY TIMES HERE BEFORE
RK JON THAT LONG AGO
PRESIDENT ASSAD DECIDED HE
WILL FIGHT TO WHAT WILL
INEVITABLY BE A BITTER AND
BLOODY END.
JON?
>> Jon: JONATHAN, I
MENTIONED U.S. WARSHIPS ARE
READY TO STRIKE AT SYRIA AT
ANY MOMENT.
AT LEAST ONE REPUBLICAN IS
CALLING FOR MORE THAN JUST
A MISSILE LAUNCH.
WE WILL WILL GO LIVE TO THE
WHITE HOUSE FOR THE LATEST
ON THE MILITARY OPTIONS
COMING UP ON "THE FOX
REPORT."
THE NEWS OUT OF SYRIA HURT
YOUR 401(K)S AND IRA'S
TODAY STOCKS SLID IN THE
RED AFTER SOARING EARLIER
THIS THE DAY.
JOHN KERRY SPOKE ABOUT
SYRIA.
THE DOW FINISHED THE DAY
DOWN 65 POINTS.
NASDAQ AND S&P ALSO FELL.
YOU A THREE MAJOR INDICES
HAD BEEN HOLDING ON TO
SLIGHT GAINS IN THE FINAL
HOUR OF TRADING.
THAT'S WHEN KERRY'S SPEECH
OCCURRED.
POLICE OFFICERS REPORT THEY
HAVE SOLVED THE KILLING OF
A WORLD WAR II VETERAN IN
SPOKANE, WASHINGTON.
THEY SAY THEY ARRESTED A
SECOND TEENAGE SUSPECT
EARLY THIS MORNING.
>> TODAY, I WOULD LIKE TO
ASSURE OUR COMMUNITY THAT
THE TWO INDIVIDUALS WE
BELIEVE WERE RESPONSIBLE
FOR THE ROBBERY AND MURDER
OF MR. BELTON HAD BEEN
TAKEN INTO CUSTODY.
SINCE RECEIVING THE INITIAL
CALL ON WEDNESDAY NIGHT,
THE SPOKANE POLICE
DEPARTMENT HAS WORKED
TIRELESSLY TO IDENTIFY AND
APPREHEND THE SUSPECTS IN
THIS HOMICIDE.
>> Jon: INVESTIGATORS
REPORT TWO TEENS RANDOMLY
TARGETED THIS 88-YEAR-OLD
MAN LAST WEEK, ROBBING HIM
IN THE PARKING LOT OF AN
EAGLES LODGE BEATING HIM
AND LEAVING HIM TO DIE.
TRACE GALLAGHER IS LIVE IN
OUR WEST COAST NEWS HUB.
TRACE, WHAT DO WE KNOW
ABOUT THIS SECOND SUSPECT?
>> WELL, WE ARE LEARNING,
JON,JUST LIKE THE FIRST
SUSPECT, HE IS ALSO 16
YEARS OLD AND JUST LIKE THE
FIRST SUSPECT HE IS ALSO
HAD A CRIMINAL RECORD FOR
ASSAULT.
HE IS BEING IDENTIFIED AS
16-YEAR-OLD KEENAN ADAM
KENNARD.
HE WAS ARRESTED AT 3:00
THIS MORNING AT A FRIEND'S
HOUSE IN SPOKANE.
IT TURNS OUT HIS FAMILY
ACTUALLY HAPPENED LEAD
POLICE TO HIM.
THE POLICE CHIEF SAYS
KENNARD WAS A STANDOUT
BASKETBALL PLAYER BUT
NEITHER ONE OF THESE
SUSPECTS HAD ANY PROPER
SUPERVISION.
HERE IS THE CHIEF.
WE HAVE A VERY TROUBLED
GROUP OF YOUNG PEOPLE NOT
JUST IN SPOKANE OR
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY THAT
REALLY NEED THE ASSISTANCE,
THE GUIDANCE, THE
MENTORSHIP OF THE WHOLE
COMMUNITY.
>> BOTH MEN OR TEENS ARE
BEING HELD ON MILLION
DOLLARS BOND.
THE FIRST SUSPECT WILL
APPEAR IN COURT TOMORROW.
JON?
>> WE ARE LEARNING MORE
ABOUT THIS HORRIBLE CRIME
AS WELL.
>> YEAH, THE CHIEF SAYS THE
TWO SUSPECTS WERE NOT
INVOLVED IN ANY GANG
ACTIVITY HE SAYS THIS
APPEARS TO BE SOLELY
MOTIVATED BY THE ROBBERY
ASPECT NOT RACE.
BOTH BOYS THERE WERE
CAPTURED ON VIDEO ARRIVING
OR A NEARBY STORE THAT WAS
NEAR THE CRIME SCENE
BELTON WAS SITTING IN HIS
CAR.
HE WAS WAITING FOR A FRIEND
TO PICK HIM UP WHEN THE
ATTACK HAPPENED.
FAMILY BELIEVES HE WAS
TARGETED FOR HIS AGE AND
THE FACT THAT HE WAS JUST
OVER 5 FEET TALL.
POLICE SAY HE THOUGHT BACK
AND THAT MAY HAVE
CONTRIBUTED TO THE SEVERITY
OF THE ATTACK.
HERE NOW IS BELTON'S
NEPHEW.
>> I DON'T UNDERSTAND LIKE
THREE LIVES WERE LOST THAT
NIGHT.
IT'S OVER FOR THEM.
THEY HAVE NOTHING NOW.
AND YOU TOOK A VERY SPECIAL
PERSON AWAY FROM OUR
FAMILY.
AND FOR THAT I CAN'T
FORGIVE YOU.
GOD WILL HAVE TO FORGIVE
YOU FOR THAT I CAN'T.
>> YOU MENTIONED THAT
BELTON WAS A WORLD WAR II
VETERAN.
HE WAS SHOT AND WOUNDED
DURING THE BATTLE OF OAK
KIN THAT WHAT YOU.
JON?
>> Jon: TRACE, THAT WORLD
WAR II VETERAN'S FAMILY IS
PLANNING TO BURY HIM AFTER
A MILITARY FUNERAL LATER
THIS WEEK.
WILDFIRE ALERT NOW.
ONE OF THE LARGEST
WILDFIRES IN CALIFORNIA
STATE HISTORY IS NOW THE
HIGHEST PRIORITY FIRE IN
THE NATION.
THAT'S WHAT A U.S. FORREST
INDUSTRY SERVICE SPOKESMAN
SAYS ABOUT THE FIRE STILL
RAGING THROUGH YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK.
THE RIM FIRE BACK ON
AUGUST 17TH.
OFFICIALS SAY SO FAR IT'S
BURNED AT LEAST
15,000 ACRES IN YOSEMITE
ALONE.
AND THAT'S ONLY 10% OF THE
TOTAL FIRE.
THE WHOLE THING IS SPREAD
TO NEARLY 250 SQUARE MILES
IN SIZE, COVERING MORE
GROUND THAN THE CITY OF
CHICAGO NOT ONLY DOES IT
THREATEN MOVER THE PARK BUT
POWER AND WATER SUPPLIES IN
THE SAN FRANCISCO BAY AREA.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
THE WEST ON FIRE.
THE RIM FIRE ONE OF DOZENS
BURNING THROUGHOUT THE
WEST.
AT LEAST AT LAST REPORT I
SHOULD SAY.
OFFICIALS SAID IT WAS JUST
15% CONTAINED.
CLAUDIA COWAN IS LIVE NEAR
THE EDGE OF THE FIRE
FIREFIGHTERS ARE MAKING A
STAND WHERE YOU ARE TONIGHT
IN HUH?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE ARE IN A CITY JUST A FEW
MILES AND ONE RIDGE LINE
AWAY FROM THE FIRE'S
LEADING EDGE.
FOLKS IN THIS AREA READY TO
EVACUATE AT A MOMENT'S
NOTICE AS NEARLY 4,000
FIREFIGHTERS BATTLE THOSE
FLAMES ON THE GROUND AND
FROM THE AIR.
IN FACT, TAKE A LOOK AT
THIS.
ONE RESIDENT TOOK SOME
AMAZING VIDEO OF A DROP
THAT HAPPENED JUST BEHIND
HIS HOUSE.
PRETTY EXCITING.
HUGE TONS OF RETARDANT.
>> AFTER MEETING WITH FIRE
OFFICIALS TODAY JERRY BROWN
WILL BE HELPING ASK FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT TO HELP COVER
THIS FIRE SEASON.
ATTACK ON THIS RIM FIRE
ALONE MORE THAN
$20 MILLION.
>> MORE PROBLEMS ASH FROM
THAT FIRE FALLING INTO A
MAJOR DRINKING WATER
SUPPLY?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE FIRE HAS INCHED CLOSER
AND IS NOW WITHIN A MILE OF
THE HETCHY, HECHY.
THAT DRINKING WATER COMES
FROM THE DEPTHS OF THE
RESERVOIR SO THE ASH NOW
FALLING ON THE SURFACE HAS
NOT TAINTED THE WATER
QUALITY JUST YET AUTHORITY
ARE SCRAMBLING TO FILL
OTHER NEARBY RESERVOIRS
WITH THE CLEAN WATER FROM
HECH HECHY WHERE THE INTAKE
VALVES ARE LOCATED.
JOHN, IN SO MANY WAYS THIS
FIRE FIGHT IS A RACE
AGAINST THE CLOCK.
>> CLAUDIA THE CALIFORNIA
DEPARTMENT OF FORREST
INDUSTRY REPORTS THAT THE
RIM FIRE NOW RANKS 13TH ON
THE STATE'S LARGEST
WILDFIRE LIST THAT DATES
BACK TO 1932.
MODERN AREA BURNED 427
SQUARE MILES OF SAN DIEGO
COUNTY BACK IN 2003.
AN EMOTIONAL DAY AT FORT
HOOD AS SURVIVORS OF THE
2009 MASSACRE FACE THE
CONVICTED KILLER IN COURT.
SHOOTING VICTIMS AND HEART
BROKEN FAMILY MEMBERS
TELLING THEIR STORIES TO
THE JURY THAT WILL DECIDE
WHETHER THE GUNMAN SHOULD
LIVE OR DIE.
PLUS, POLICE SAY A MAN WHO
WENT ON A DEADLY SHOOTING
SPREE OVER THE WEEKEND WENT
BEHIND A NOTE AND HIT LIST.
THAT'S COMING UP ON "THE
FOX REPORT."
LIKE A NEW DEEPWATER WELL CAP
AND A STATE-OF-THE-ART  MONITORING
CENTER, WHE EXPERTS
WATCH OVER ALL DRILLING  ACTIVITY
TWENTY-FOUR-SEVEN.
AND WE'RE SHARING  WHAT WE'VE LEARNED
SO WE CAN ALL PRODUCE  ENERGY MORE
SAFELY.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS  NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
Getting theight nutrition  during
your busy day can be a  challenge.
Take control of your nutrition  with
Each delicious bar provides    BOOST
Bars are perfect with a  meal or as
a nutritious snack.  Plus, they are
available in  Chocolate and Peanut
Butter  Chocolate flavors.  A great-tasting
way to get the  nutrition you need.
Brand Power. Helping you buy  better.
♪ ♪  ♪ WE GO, GO  WE DON'T HAVE TO
GO SOLO ♪  ♪ FIRE, FIRE,  YOU CAN
TAKE ME HIGHER ♪  ♪ TAKE ME TO THE
MOUNTAINS,  START A REVOLUTION ♪
♪ HOLD MY HAND, WE CAN MAKE  WE CAN
MAKE A CONTRIBUTION ♪  ♪ BRAND-NEW
SEASON,  KEEP IT IN MOTION ♪  ♪ 'CAUSE
THE RHYME  IS THE REASON ♪  ♪ BREAK
THROUGH, MAN, IT DOESN'T  MATTER WHO
YOU'RE TALKING TO ♪    [ Male Announcer
]    COMPLETELY REDESIGNED    FOR
WHATEVER YOU LOVE TO DO.    THE ALL-NEW
NISSAN VERSA NOTE.    YOUR DOOR TO
MORE.  ♪ ♪
ANY LAST REQUESTS  MR. BALDWIN?  DO
YOU MIND  GRABBING MY PHONE  AND OPENING
THE Capital One  Purchase Eraser?
I NEED TO REDEEM SOME  Venture MILES
BEFORE MY DEMISE.  OKAY.  IT'S EASY
TO ERASE ANY  RECENT TRAVEL EXPENSE
I WANT.  JUST PICK THAT FLIGHT  RIGHT
THERE.  MMM HMMM.  GIVE IT A FEW TAPS
AND...IT'S TAKEN CARE OF.  THIS IS
PRETTY EASY, AND I SEE  IT WORKS ON
HOTELS TOO.  YOU BET. NOW IF YOU LIKE
THAT,  PRESS THE RED BUTTON ON TOP.
♪ ♪  HOW DID HE NOT SEE THAT COMING?
WHAT'S IN YOUR WALLET?
Hero:  If you had a chance to  go
anywhere in the world  but you had
to leave right  now, would you go?
Man:  'oh I can't go tonight'
Woman:  'I can't.'
Hero  : That's what  Expedia asked
me.
Host:  Book the flight but  you have
to go right now.
Hero:  (Laughs) And I just go?
This is for real right?  This is for
real?
I always said one day  I'd go to China,
just never thought  it'd be today.
ANNCR:  We're giving away  a trip
every day.
Download the Expedia app and  your
next trip could be on us.
Expedia, find yours.
>> Jon: GUT WRENCHING
TESTIMONY IN THE FORT HOOD
SHOOTER AS JURORS MUST
DECIDE WILL MAJOR NADAL
WILL DIE FOR HIS CRIMES OR
SPEND THE REST OF HIS LIFE
IN PRISON.
VICTIMS FAMILIES TESTIFIED
INCLUDING THE WIDOW AND
MOTHER OF THIS SPECIALIST.
WIDOW SAYS SHE HAS SINCE
TRIED TO KILL HERSELF TWICE
AND MOTHER SAID WHEN
OFFICERS ARRIVED TO INFORM
HER OF HER SON'S DEATH SHE
CALLED HER DAUGHTER PUT THE
PHONE ON THE TABLE AND
COULD HEAR HER SCREAMING ON
THE PHONE AS THE OFFICERS
TOLD HER THE NEWS.
THIS ARMY PRIVATE WAS
PREGNANT WHEN SHE DIED IN
THE MASSACRE.
HER FATHER TODAY TOLD
JURORS QUOTE THAT MAN DID
NOT KILL 13 THAT KAY.
HE KILLED 15.
HE KILLED MY GRANDSON AND
HE KILLED ME SLOWLY.
CASEY STEGALL LIVE FROM
FORT HOOD.
DID THE PROSECUTOR GET
THROUGH ALL THE WITNESSES?
>> THEY DID NOT.
COURT WENT INTO UNEXPECTED
RECESS AT 3:30 LOCAL TIME,
4:30 EASTERN.
THAT WAS NOT LONG AFTER WE
HAD JUST BEEN TOLD BY
PUBLIC AFFAIRS THAT
EVERYONE WOULD LIKELY BE
WORKING LATE TONIGHT.
THE ONLY REASON WE WERE
GIVEN FOR THIS DELAY WAS
BECAUSE OF LOGISTICAL
ISSUES.
THEY WOULDN'T ELABORATE.
THIS FOLLOWED A DAY OF ODD
BEHAVIOR FROM HASAN WHO
ASKED FOR TWO RECESSES
THROUGHOUT THE MORNING AND
ALSO ASKED TO BREAK EARLY
FOR LUNCH WHICH THE JUDGE
DENIED.
THIS IS ODD BECAUSE IT'S
THE FIRST TIME HE HAS MADE
SUCH REQUESTS.
THIS ENTIRE COURT MARTIAL
AND HE MADE THEM AFTER
FAMILY MEMBERS SOBBED ON
THE STAND.
ONE WIDOW TESTIFYING SHE
ONLY DISCONNECTED HER LATE
HUSBAND'S CELL PHONE JUST A
FEW MONTHS AGO BECAUSE SHE
WOULD CALL IT, JON JUST TO
HEAR HIS VOICE ONE MORE
TIME.
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT?
>> ONCE THE PROSECUTION'S
REMAINING SEVEN WITNESSES
TAKE THE STAND WE HOPE
TOMORROW.
THEN HASAN HITS THE FLOOR.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT HE HAS
UP HIS SLEEVE.
IS HE ABLE TO TALK A LITTLE
BIT MORE FREELY IN THIS
PART OF THE COURT MARTIAL.
IT'S NOT THE GUILTY
INNOCENT PHASE ANYMORE.
IN THE SENTENCING THERE
AREN'T AS MANY RESTRICTIONS
ON WHAT HE CAN SAY.
SOME MILITARY LAW EXPERTS
HAVE SUGGESTED THIS WHEN HE
IS GOING TO TRY TO DEFEND
WHY HE CARRIED OUT THE
ATTACK.
WHICH HAS A LOT TO DO WITH
HIS RADICALIZATION, JON.
>> Jon: CASEY HASAN
REPORTEDLY HAS EARNED ABOUT
$300,000 IN PAY SINCE THE
MASSACRE.
LEGAL ANALYSTS TELL US ONCE
HE GETS SENTENCED, THAT
STOPS.
AN ARMY SPOKESMAN TOLD THE
"WALL STREET JOURNAL" SOME
OF THAT MONEY COULD BE USED
TO PAY FINES AND COMPENSATE
VICTIMS.
POLICE IN FLORIDA SAY THE
MAN BEHIND THIS WEEKEND'S
SHOOTING RAMPAGE WROTE OUT
THE NAMES OF HIS INTENDED
VICTIMS IN ADVANCE.
AND THEY SAY ALL FOUR
VICTIMS WERE FORMER
TRUCKING COMPANY CO-WORKERS
OF THE 72-YEAR-OLD SHOOTER.
COPS SAY THEY FOUND THE
NOTE AT THE GUNMAN'S HOUSE.
IT DID NOT MENTION A
MOTIVE.
TWO OF THE SHOOTING VICTIMS
DIED.
FRIENDS OF THE GUNMAN'S
FAMILY SAY THEY HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT MADE HIM DO IT.
THE SUSPECT LATER KILLED
HIMSELF AT HIS HOME.
THE FBI IS NOW OFFERING A
$50,000 REWARD TO HELP
TRACK DOWN THE KILLER OF A
POLICE OFFICER IN KENTUCKY.
THAT BRINGS THE TOTAL
REWARD MONEY TO MORE THAN
$200,000.
INVESTIGATORS SAY SUSPECT
SHOT OFFICER JASON ELLIS
THREE MONTHS AGO AS HE WAS
CLEARING DEBRIS FROM A
HIGHWAY EXIT RAMP.
OFFICER ELLIS LEFT BEHIND A
WIFE AND TWO YOUNG SONS.
HE WORKED WITH THE POLICE
DEPARTMENT'S DRUG SNIFFING
DOGS ONE OF HIS FORMER
CANINE PARTNERS WAS THERE
TO SAY GOODBYE AT HIS
FUNERAL.
TERRIFYING MOMENTS FOR A
CHILD WHO WAS HOME ALONE
WHEN BURGLARS BROKE INTO
HIS HOUSE.
HOW THE BOY MANAGED TO KEEP
HIS COOL AND HELP PUT THE
CROOKS BEHIND BARS.
PLUS, A LITTLE GIRL LIKELY
WOULD NOT BE -- LIKELY
WOULD NOT BE ALIVE NOW IF
HER PARENTS HAD NOT WON
THEIR FIGHT TO GET HER NEW
LUNGS.
WELL NOW YOUNG SARAH IS
ABOUT TO CELEBRATE ANOTHER
VICTORY.
SHE IS GOING HOME.
BEGINS WITH BACK PAIN, WHEN...  HEY
PAM,  YOU SHOULD TAKE ADVIL.  WHY?
YOU CAN TAKE FOUR ADVIL  FOR ALL DAY
RELIEF.  SO I SHOULD GIVE UP MY TWO
ALEVE  FOR MORE PILLS WITH ADVIL?
YOU'RE JOKING RIGHT?  FOR MY BACK
PAIN  I WANT MY ALEVE.
[ Male Announcer ]    RUNNING OUT
OF STEAM?  ♪ ♪    NOW YOU CAN GIVE
YOURSELF    A KICK IN THE REAR!
V8 V-FUSION PLUS ENERGY.    NATURAL
ENERGY FROM GREEN TEA    PLUS FRUITS
AND VEGGIES.    NEED A LITTLE KICK?
OOH!    COULD'VE HAD A V8.    IN THE
JUICE AISLE.
Alert.  The beach on your TV is much
closer than it appears.
Dive into Labor Day with up  to 50%
off hotels
at Travelocity.
[ Male Announcer ]    THESE DAYS,
A SMALL BUSINESS    CAN SAVE BY SHARING.
LIKE CARPOOLS...  POLLY WANTS TO KNOW
IF WE CAN PICK HER UP.  YEAH  WE CAN
MAKE ROOM.  YEAH.    [ Male Announcer
]    ...OFFICE SPACE.  YES, WE'RE
LOVING THIS  COMMUNAL SEATING. IT'S
GREAT.    [ Male Announcer ]    THE
BEST THING TO SHARE?    A DATA PLAN.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
ONE BUCKET OF DATA    FOR EVERYONE
ON THE PLAN    UNLIMITED TALK AND
TEXT    ON SMART PHONES.    NOW, EVERYONE'S
IN THE SPIRIT    OF SHARING.  HEY,
CAN I BORROW YOUR BOAT  THIS WEEKEND?
NO.    [ Male Announcer ]    SHARE
MORE. SAVE MORE.    AT&T MOBILE SHARE
FOR BUSINESS.  ♪ ♪
[PHONE RINGING.
[911 WHERE IS THE
EMERGENCY, HELLO?
>> SOMEONE IS TRYING TO
BREAK INTO MY HOUSE.
>> Jon: SOMEONE IS TRYING
TO BREAK INTO HIGH HOUSE.
THE VOICE YOU JUST HEARD IS
THAT OF A 12-YEAR-OLD BOY.
POLICE REPORT HE WAS ALONE
IN HIS FAMILY'S HOME AT
PORT ARTHUR TEXAS WHEN TWO
BURGLARS BUSTED.
IN THE BOY HID IN A CLOSET
AS HE SPOKE TO A 911
DISPATCHER.
DAVID LEE MILLER IS LIVE
WITH WITH THAT.
DAVID?
>> JEN, DION MURDOCK IS
ONLY 12 YEARS OLD BUT IS HE
COURAGEOUS BEYOND HIS
YEARS.
NOT ONLY DID HE CALL 911
AFTER HEARING SOMEONE BREAK
INTO HIS HOME BUT HE KEPT
HIS COOL HIDING IN A CLOSET
WITH THE INTRUDERS ONLY A
FEW FEET AWAY.
>> I'M GOING TO HAVE TO
WHISPER BECAUSE I CAN TELL
THEY ARE COMING.
>> IN DO YOU HAVE ANY
WEAPONS INSIDE THE CLOSET?
>> NO, MA'AM.
PLEASE HURRY.
>> THEY ARE.
>> THEY ARE TURNING ON YOUR
STREET.
>> STAY RIGHT THERE.
>> THEY ARE INSIDE THE ROOM
NOW.
>> THEY ARE INSIDE THE
BEDROOM WHERE IS HE AT.
ARE YOU THERE?
DION?
>> YES.
>> OKAY.
JUST STAY THERE.
THE OFFICER -- I THINK THEY
ARE GOING TO CATCH THE GUY.
OKAY?
>> Jon: AS POLICE
APPROACHED THE HOUSE, THEY
WERE APPARENTLY SPOTTED BY
ONE OF THE INTRUDERS AND
THAT'S WHEN THEY DECIDED TO
MAKE A RUN FOR IT.
ALL THE WHILE DION REMAINED
ON THE PHONE.
THE DISPATCHER REASSURING
THE YOUNG BOY EVERYTHING
WAS GOING TO BE ALL RIGHT.
DION CONTINUED TO DESCRIBE
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
>> IT SOUNDS LIKE THERE ARE
MULTIPLE PEOPLE.
>> OKAY.
BE QUIET.
>> IS THE POLICE OFFICER
OUTSIDE THE HOUSE?
>> YEAH.
BUT STAY INSIDE THE CLOSET.
BECAUSE THEY ARE TRYING TO
FIND THE BAD GUYS OKAY?
YOU ARE DOING GOOD.
YOU ARE DOING REAL GOOD.
DOING PERFECT.
YOUR MOM'S GOING TO BE SO
PROUD OF YOU.
>> THE TWO ALLEGED
INTRUDERS TWO MEN IN EARLY
20'S FOUND BY POLICE USING
TRACKER DOGS A QUARTER MILE
AWAIT A MINUTE THEY WERE
UNARMED.
TONIGHT THEY ARE BEHIND
BARS CHARGED WITH BURGLARY.
DION IS A HOMETOWN HERO
DESCRIBED BY LOCAL POLICE
AS COURAGEOUS AND
DETERMINED.
JON?
>> Jon: DAVID LEE, POLICE
SAY THE TWO SUSPECTS BOTH
HAVE CRIMINAL RECORDS.
THEY BELIEVE THAT THEY
RANDOMLY PICKED THAT HOUSE.
ANOTHER BRAVE CHILD WHO HAS
CAPTURED THE HEARTS OF THE
ENTIRE NATION IS FINALLY
GOING HOME.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM A
FAMILY SPOKESMAN WHO SAYS
DOCTORS WILL RELEASE LITTLE
SARA MURNAGHAN TOMORROW.
REMEMBER, SARAH WAS DYING
OF CYSTIC FIBROSIS WHEN HER
FAMILY SUCCESSFULLY FOUGHT
THE RULES THAT KEPT HER OFF
THE ADULT TRANSPLANT LIST.
THE 11-YEAR-OLD HAS BEEN IN
THE HOSPITAL FOR MONTHS
RECOVERING FROM A DOUBLE
LUNG TRANSPLANT.
HER MOTHER SAYS DOCTORS
HAVE NOW TAKEN SARAH OFF
OXYGEN.
SHE SAYS SARAH STILL USES A
MACHINE THAT HELPS HER TO
BREATHE BUT THAT SHE IS NOW
WALKING SHORT DISTANCES
WITH A WALKER.
SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN
KERRY DID NOT MINCE WORDS
TODAY WHEN TALKING ABOUT
SYRIA'S ALLEGED USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
WORDS ARE ONE THING.
ACTION IS ANOTHER.
FOX REPORTS LIVE FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE WHERE THE
PRESIDENT IS CONSIDERING
POSSIBLE ACTIONS.
OF COURSE, THE U.S. IS ALSO
WORKING CLOSELY ON THE
ISSUE WITH THE UNITED
NATIONS BUT THINGS COULD
GET A LITTLE AWKWARD FOR
OUR DIPLOMATS AFTER A
REPORTED THAT THE U.S.
SPIED ON THE GLOBAL
ORGANIZATION.
THAT'S COMING UP AS WE
APPROACH THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR AND THE TOP OF THE
NEWS.
NEED A SPOON, DEAR?  NOT ANYMORE.
WHAT? MY SILVERWARE  ISN'T GOOD ENOUGH
FOR YOU?  HAVE --  HAVE YOU SEEN IT?
YES, I HAVE SEEN IT  AND IT LOOKS
--  YOU GOTTA LOOK BETTER.  LADIES,
BREATHE.  SCADE KITCHEN COUNSELOR
HERE.  IT'S NOT YOUR SILVERWARE.
IT'S LIKELY YOUR DETERGENT.  SEE,
OVER TIME,  CASCADE PLATINUM'S  TRIPLE
CLEANING FORMULA  DELIVERS BRILLIANT
SHINE  FINISH GEL CAN'T BEAT.  IT
EVEN HELPS KEEP  YOUR DISHWASHER SPARKLING.
FIND SOMETHING,  MOTHER?  NO.  [ Counselor
] CASCADE PLATINUM  IS CASCADE'S BEST.
Peace of mind is important when  you're
running a successful  business.  So
we provide IT services you  can rely
on.  With CenturyLink as your trusted
IT partner  you'll experience reliable
uptime for the network and  services
you depend on.  Multi-layered security
solutions  keep your information safe,
and  secure.  And responsive dedicated
support  meets your needs, and eases
your  mind.  CenturyLink.  Your link
to what's next.
SHE LOVES A LOT OF  THE SAME THINGS
YOU DO.  IT'S WHAT YOU LOVE ABOUT
HER.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A  QUESTION OF BLOOD
FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME  THE MOMENT'S
RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT  IN YOUR
ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS  THE ONLY DAILY
ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED  AND SYMPTOMS
OBPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO  FREQUENTLY OR
URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT  ALL YOUR MEDICAL
CONDITIONS AND MEDICATIONS
AND ASK  YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY  ENOUGH
FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU  TAKE NITRATES
FOR CHEST PAIN
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE  DROP
IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL  IN EXCESS WITH
CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE  HEADACHE,
UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,  SEEK IMMEDIATE
MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING  MORE THAN
4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE  OR
LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION
OR IYOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC  REACTIONS
SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS  TONGUE OR THROAT
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING  OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET  MEDICAL
HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT  CIALIS FOR
DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
>> Jon: WE'RE HEARING AN
EMOTIONAL STORY AND A
COUPLE MARRIED 65 YEARS WHO
RECENTLY DIED JUST HOURS
APART.
THEIR FAMILY SAYS THE TWO
MET BACK IN 3RD GRADE AND
HAD BEEN TOGETHER EVER
SINCE.
THE COUPLE WAS LIVING
TOGETHER AT A NURSING HOME
IN OHIO WHEN EARLIER THIS
MONTH THEIR CHILDREN TOLD
THEIR FATHER THAT HIS
WIFE'S HEALTH WAS QUICKLY
DETERIORATING.
DAD HAD A SLEEPLESS NIGHT
AND A SUDDEN CALM ABOUT
HIM.
HE DIED A FEW DAYS LATER.
JUST 11 HOURS BEFORE HIS
WIFE DID.
THEIR CHILDREN CREDITS THE
COUPLE'S STRONG FAITH AND
LOVE FOR WHAT THEY CALL A
MIXED BLESSING.
AT LEAST FIVE PEOPLE ARE
DEAD AND DOZENS MORE HURT
AS A TRAIN NOTORIOUS FOR
CARRYING UNDOCUMENTED
MIGRANTS GOES OFF THE
RAILS, OUR TOP STORY AS WE
GO AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
MEXICO.
OFFICIALS SAY THE FREIGHT
TRAIN WAS HEADING NORTH OF
THE GUATEMALAN BORDER
TRACKS IN THE REMOTE AREA
TO THE SOUTH.
SOME 250 MIGRANTS WERE
REPORTEDLY ON THE ROOFS OF
THE TRAIN'S CARS.
AUTHORITIES SAY HEAVY RAIN
HAD LOOSENED THE GROUND
BENEATH THE TRACKS AND
SHIFTED THE RAILS.
RESCUERS BROUGHT IN TWO
CRANES TO LEFT THE
OVERTURNED CARS AND SEARCH
FOR VICTIMS.
CHINA.
A MASSIVE FIRE TORE THROUGH
A FOOD PROCESSING PLANT IN
A CENTRAL PROVINCE.
THE FLAMES REPORTEDLY BROKE
OUT IN THE MORNING JUST AS
WORKERS ARRIVED.
CREWS SAY EVERYBODY ESCAPED
BEFORE THE FIRE CHARRED
SOME 21,000 SQUARE FEET.
NO WORD ON THE CAUSE.
AUSTRALIA.
POLICE RECOVERED THE BODY
OF A SWIMMER KILLED IN AN
APPARENT CROCODILE ATTACK
AT A POPULAR TOURIST
RETREAT IN THE AUSTRALIAN
OUTBACK.
WITNESSES SAY THE VICTIM
AND A FRIEND WERE SWIMMING
ACROSS A RIVER WHEN A
15-FOOT CROC BIT HIM AROUND
THE CHEST.
THE SWIMMER DIED FROM CHEST
WOUNDS OR DROWNED WHEN THE
CROCK DRAGGED IMUNDER THE
WATER.
TORNADO DAMAGED BUILDINGS
AND BOATS AS IT RIPPED
NORTH OF ROME.
THE TWIST TWISTER SCATTERED
DEBRIS ON THE ROADS AND
BLOCKED TRAFFIC.
NOBODY HURT.
AND THAT'S A WRAP ON THIS
FOX TRIP AROUND THE WORLD
IN 80 SECONDS.
>> Jon: I'M JON SCOTT IN
FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS "THE FOX REPORT."
IT IS UNDENIABLE, THAT'S
WHAT SECRETARY OF STATE
JOHN KERRY SAID TODAY ABOUT
LAST WEEK'S CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK IN SYRIA.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS THERE
IS VERY LITTLE DOUBT THE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT LAUNCHED
THAT ATTACK.
AND PRESIDENT OBAMA IS
CONSIDERING THE OPTIONS FOR
A POSSIBLE MILITARY
RESPONSE.
AS WE REPORTED AT THE TOP
OF THIS NEWSCAST, OFFICIALS
SAY THE U.S. NOW HAS FOUR
WARSHIPS OFF THE COAST OF
SYRIA READY TO STRIKE AT A
MOMENT'S NOTICE.
ED HENRY LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
SO, ED, WHAT IS NEXT FOR
THE PRESIDENT ON THIS
ISSUE?
>> THAT'S THE BIG QUESTION
JON.
THESE WERE THE STRONGEST
COMMENTS YET FROM ANYONED
IN THE ADMINISTRATION.
SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN
KERRY CAME OUT TODAY AND
RATHER DRAMATICALLY
DECLARED THAT IN FACT THE
U.S. GOVERNMENT BELIEVES
THAT THERE WAS A CHEMICAL
ATTACK AND THAT THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT WAS RESPONSIBLE
FOR IT.
THEY FLATLY DECLARED THAT
AND JOHN KERRY WENT ON TO
TO SAY THAT THE PRESIDENT
WANTS TO HAVE
ACCOUNTABI   HINTING AT U.S. MILITARY
ACTION.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> WHAT WE SAW IN SYRIA
LAST WEEK SHOULD SHOCK THE
CONSCIENCE OF THE WORLD IT.
IT DEFIES ANY CODE OF
MORALITY.
LET ME BE CLEAR.
THE INDISCRIMINATE
SLAUGHTER OF CIVILIANS, THE
KILLING OF WOMEN AND
CHILDREN AND INNOCENT
BYSTANDERS BIOCHEMICAL
WEAPONS IS IMMORAL
OBSCENITY.
>> NOW WE'RE TOLD THAT
GENERAL MARTIN DEMPSEY, THE
CHAIR OF THE JOINT CHIEFS
HAS PRESENTED THE PRESIDENT
WITH ONE PLAN THAT WOULD
INCLUDE GROUND TROOPS,
COULD INCLUDE HALF A
MILLION U.S. GROUND TROOPS,
BILLIONS OF U.S. DOLLARS.
THAT'S ABOUT THE ONLY
OPTION THE PRESIDENT HAS
RULED OUT.
HE SAID PUBLICLY MANY TIMES
HE WOULD NOT COMMIT U.S.
GROUND TROOPS.
THERE IS ANOTHER OPTION
INVOLVING CREWS MISSILES
THAT WOULD BE SHOT FROM
SUBMARINES.
ALSO PRECISION GUIDED
MISSILES.
FIRED FROM AIRPLANES THAT
WOULD BE FLYING BELOW
SYRIAN RADAR.
THAT'S AN OPTION ON THE
TABLE.
IT COULD VERY WELL BE ONE
OF THE OPTIONS THE
PRESIDENT USES JON.
>> Jon: THE PRESIDENT IS
UNDER PRETTY HEAVY PRESSURE
FROM REPUBLICANS TO ACT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, JON IT WAS
ONE YEAR AGO THIS MONTH AT
A NEWS CONFERENCE HERE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE THAT THE
PRESIDENT FIRST DREW THAT
RED LINE FAMOUSLY IN TERMS
OF THE USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS BY PRESIDENT ASSAD
IN SYRIA.
AND JUST AS IMPORTANTLY IN
THE NEXT LINE AT THAT NEWS
CONFERENCE SAID THERE WOULD
BE QUOTE, ENORMOUS
CONSEQUENCES IF THAT LINE
WAS CROSSED.
THAT'S WHY REPUBLICAN JOHN
MCCAIN TODAY DECLARED THE
PRESIDENT BETTER BACK UP
THESE WORDS.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> IF THE UNITED STATES
STANDS BY AND DOESN'T TAKE
VERY SERIOUS ACTION.
NOT JUST LAUNCHING CREWS
MISSILES, THEN AGAIN OUR
CREDIBILITY IN THE WORLD IS
DIMINISHED EVEN MORE IF
THERE IS ANY LEFT.
>> NOW, WHITE HOUSE
SPOKESMAN JAY CARNEY TODAY
REFUSED TO GET INTO ANY
HYPOTHETICALS ABOUT WHAT'S
THE NEXT MOVE FROM THE
PRESIDENT.
THEY OBVIOUSLY WANT TO KEEP
AS MUCH AS THIS BEHIND
CLOSE THE DOORS AS THEY
CAN.
BUT HE DID SAY THAT THERE
WILL BE SOME SORT OF A
RESPONSE THAT IT DEMANDS A
RESPONSE, BUT HE SAID THE
PRESIDENT HAS NOT MADE A
FINAL DECISION YET JON.
>> Jon: ED HENRY, THANK
YOU.
A NEW BOMBSHELL ALLEGATION
THAT OUR GOVERNMENT HAS
BEEN SPYING ON THE UNITED
NATIONS.
ACCORDING TO DOCUMENTS, NSA
LEAKER ED SNOWDEN GAVE TO
GERMANY'S DER SPIEGEL
MAGAZINE THE NATIONAL
SECURITY AGENCY HACKED INTO
THE U.N.'S CLOSED VIDEO
FEED.
THAT LET AGENTS TAP INTO
MEETINGS PRIVATE DIPLOMATS.
THE DOCUMENTS CLAIM THAT
THE NSA BUGGED THE EUROPEAN
UNION OFFICES IN D.C. AND
EVEN HACKED INTO ITS
COMPUTER NETWORK.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE WITH THE
NEWS LIVE FROM D.C. NOW.
CATHERINE, WHAT MORE ARE
YOU LEARNING ABOUT THIS?
>> WELL, THANK YOU, JON
ACCORDING TO THE NEW NSA
DOCUMENTS THE NATIONAL
SECURITY AGENCY NOT ONLY
INFILTRATED BUT CRACKED THE
CODE OF THE U.N. INTERNAL
VIDEO CONFERENCING NETWORK
LEADING TO IT A SIGNIFICANT
JUMP IN THE NSA'S
INTELLIGENCE REPORTING ON
THE U.N. BODY.
TODAY A U.N. SPOKESMAN
SAYING THE REPORTED BUGGING
VIOLATES INTERNATIONAL
AGREEMENTS.
>> THE VIABILITY OF
DIPLOMATIC MISSIONS
INCLUDING THE UNITED
NATIONS AND OTHER
INTERNATIONAL MISSIONS
WHOSE FUNCTIONS ARE
PROTECTED BY THE RELEVANT
INTERNATIONAL CONVENTIONS
LIKE THE VIENNA CONVENTION
HAS BEEN WELL ESTABLISHED
INTERNATIONAL LAW.
>> DER SPIEGEL ALSO
REPORTING THAT THE NSA
SURVEILLANCE OF 80
EMBASSIES AND CONSULATES IS
PART OF A SPECIAL PROGRAM
KNOWN AS A SPECIAL
COLLECTION SERVICE JON.
>> Jon: SO WHAT ARE WE
HEARING FROM THE
ADMINISTRATION?
>> WELL, GIVEN THE
SENSITIVE NATURE OF THE
ALLEGATIONS, THE STATE
DEPARTMENT SPOKESWOMAN READ
FROM HER NOTES PROVIDING A
SCRIPTIVE RESPONSE.
>> WE SAID THIS REPEATEDLY
THAT WE'RE NOT GOING TO
COMMENT PUBLICLY ON EVERY
SPECIFIC ALLEGED
INTELLIGENCE ACTIVITY AS A
MATTER OF POLICY.
WE HAVE MADE CLEAR THAT THE
U.S. GATHERS FOREIGN
INTELLIGENCE OF THE TYPE
GATHERED BY ALL NATIONS.
>> THE NEWEST LEAKS FROM
FORMER NSA CONTRACTOR
EDWARD SNOWDEN APPEARED TO
UNDERCUT THE PRESIDENT'S
MOST EXPENSIVE DEFENSE OF
THE NSA PROGRAMS.
>> I DON'T HAVE AN INTEREST
AND THE PEOPLE OF THE NSA
DON'T HAVE AN INTEREST IN
DOING ANYTHING OTHER THAN
MAKING SURE THAT WHERE WE
CAN PREVENT A TERRORIST
ATTACK.
>> THE NSA HAD NOTHING TO
ADD TODAY BEYOND THE STATE
DEPARTMENT'S SCRIPTED
COMMENTS.
JON.
>> Jon: AND CATHERINE, WE
ARE LEARNING THAT SNOWDEN'S
DECISION TO FLY TO RUSSIA
MIGHT NOT HAVE BEEN THE
SURPRISE THAT PRESIDENT
VLADIMIR PUTIN PUTIN
CLAIMED.
ACCORDING TO A RESPECTED
RUSSIAN NEWSPAPER SNOWDEN
SPENT TWO DAYS AT RUSSIA'S
CONSULATE IN HONG KONG
BEFORE HE FLEW TO MOSCOW.
THE PAPER REPORTS SNOWDEN
SHOWED HIS PLANE TICKET AND
ASKED FOR HELP.
HE EVENTUALLY FLEW TO
RUSSIA WHERE OFFICIALS
GRANTED HIM TEMPORARY
ASYLUM.
A NEW STOCK EXCHANGE COULD
SOON REPLACE THE NASDAQ AS
THE SECOND LARGEST IN THE
U.S.
THE DEAL WAS ANNOUNCED
TODAY AND IF REGULATORS
APPROVE IT IT, IT WOULD
UNITE THE THIRD AND FOURTH
LARGEST EQUITY EXCHANGE
OWNERS THE BATS GLOBAL
MARKETS AND DIRECT EDGE.
THE NEW EXCHANGE WOULD TAKE
THE BATS GLOBAL MARKET
NAME.
THE CURRENT CEO CALLED IT
AN IMPORTANT MILESTONE FOR
THE U.S. EQUITIES MARKET.
THE DEAL COMES ALMOST A
WEEK AFTER A TECHNICAL
GLITCH AT THE NASDAQ CAUSED
A FLY HOUR TRADING HALT.
IF APPROVED THE DEAL IS
EXPECTED TO CLOSE FOR THE
FIRST HALF OF 2014.
AFGHAN WAR VETERAN HAS
BECOME THE NEWEST RECIPIENT
OF OUR NATION'S HIGHEST
MILITARY AWARD FOR BRAVERY.
DETAILS OF THE DEADLY FIRE
FIGHT THAT HE SAID WAS LIKE
FACING A WALL OF SPIKES.
MEANWHILE, DISABLED
VETERANS ARE WAITING LONGER
THAN EVER TO RECEIVE THEIR
BENEFITS AND NOW THERE IS
WORD THAT FEDERAL WORKERS
ARE ESSENTIALLY GETTING
PAID EXTRA WHILE LEAVING
SOME OF THOSE VETS IN THE
LURCH.
THE Kyocera Torque  LETS YOU HEAR
AND BE HEARD  EVEN IN STUPID LOUD
PLACES.  TO PROVE IT, WE SET UP  OUR
CALL CENTER RIGHT HERE...  [ chirp
]  ALL GOOD?  [ chirp ]  GETTY UP.
CALL ME.  SERIOUSLY,  THIS IS REALLY
HAPPENING!  [ cellphone rings ]  HELLO?
IT'S A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.
[ Male Announcer ] GET IT DONE  [
chirp ]    WITH THE ULTRA-RUGGED
Kyocera Torque    ONLY FROM Sprint
Direct Connect.  TRBLE HEARING ON
THE PHONE?    BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE
FOR YOUR BUSINESS.  VISIT SPNTCAPTEL.COM
YOU HAVE TIME TO SHOP  FOR CAR INSURANCE
TODAY?  YEAH.
I HEARD ABOUT PROGRESSIVE'S  "NAME
YOUR PRICE" TOOL?
I GUESS YOU CAN TELL THEM  HOW MUCH
YOU WANT TO PAY
AND IT GIVES YOU A RANGE OF  OPTIONS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
HUH? I'M LOOKING  AT IT RIGHT NOW.
OH, YEAH?
YEAH.
WHAT'S THE...  GUEST ROOM SITUATION?
THE "NAME YOUR PRICE" TOOL
MAKING THE WORLD    A LITTLE MORE
PROGRESSIVE.
>> Jon: IN A WHITE HOUSE
CEREMONY TODAY PRESIDENT
OBAMA BESTOWED THE NATION'S
HIGHEST MILITARY VALOR
MEDAL OF HONOR ON STAFF
SERGEANT TY CARTER.
FOUR YEARS AGO IN
AFGHANISTAN HE RISKED HIS
LIFE TO PULL A WOUNDED
SOLDIER FROM THE LINE OF
FIRE AND RESUPPLY AMMO TO
HIS COMRADES.
THEY HAD BEEN AMBUSHED.
THE KIND OF PLACE THE
MILITARY NO LONGER SENDS
TROOPS BECAUSE OF WHAT
HAPPENED THAT DAY IN
OCTOBER OF 2009.
THE PRESIDENT TODAY
DESCRIBED SERGEANT
CARTEDDER AS THE ESSENCE OF
TRUE HEROISM.
>> BEFORE THEY CAME, TY
SAID HE WAS HOPING TO TAKE
HIS CHILDREN AROUND
WASHINGTON TO SHOW THEM THE
SITES AND THE HISTORY.
BUT JADEN MADISON IF YOU
WANT TO KNOW WHAT MAKES OUR
COUNTRY GREAT AND WHAT A
TRUE AMERICAN HERO LOOKS
LIKE THEN YOU DON'T HAVE TO
LOOK TOO FAR, YOU JUST HAVE
TO LOOK AT YOUR DAD.
>> SERGEANT CARTER IS THE
FIFTH LIVING RECIPIENT TO
RECEIVE THE MEDAL OF HONOR
FOR ACTIONS IN IRAQ OR
AFGHANISTAN.
IS HE FROM WASHINGTON
STATE.
DAN SPRINGER IS IN OUR
SEATTLE BUREAU WITH THE
NEWS.
DAN?
>> JON, WHEN I INTERVIEWED
SERGEANT TY CARTER, I FOUND
HIM TO BE A RELUCTANT HERO.
HUMBLE.
IN MANY WAYS HE WAS A QUIET
ORDINARY SOLDIER WHO ENDED
UP DOING THE EXTRAORDINARY.
>> ARMY STAFF SERGEANT TY
CARTER IS AN AMERICAN HERO,
STILL HAUNTED BY WHAT HE
COULD NOT DO IN HIS BRAVEST
HOUR.
CARTER IS THE FOURTH LIVING
RECIPIENT OF THE
CONGRESSIONAL MEDAL OF
HONOR FROM THE WAR IN
AFGHANISTAN.
>> I WOULD NEVER WISH FOR
SOMEONE TO RECEIVE THIS
MEDAL BECAUSE, IN ORDER TO
RECEIVE IT MEDAL, YOUR
FAMILY IS PRETTY MUCH DYING
AROUND YOU EVERYTHING IS --
EVERYTHING IS GETTING
DESTROYED.
IT WAS OCTOBER 3RD, 2009.
53 U.S. SOLDIERS AT COMBAT
OUTPOST KEATING IN THE
LAWLESS MOUNTAINS NEAR THE
PAKISTAN BORDER, WERE
ATTACKED BY SEVERAL HUNDRED
MILITANTS.
UNDER HEAVY FIRE.
CARTER RAN AMMUNITION TO
FELLOW SOLDIERS.
HE KILLED SEVERAL OF THE
ENEMY AND HE HEROICALLY
RISKED HIS LIFE TO GIVE
FIRST AID TO SPECIALIST
STEPHAN MAYES WHO LAY
GRAVELY WOUNDED IN THE
OPEN.
AFTER SLOWING THE BLEEDING
AND PUT A TOURNIQUET ON
MASON'S LEG, HE CARRIED HIM
TO SHELTER.
AFTER THE DAY LONG BATTLE
AS HE WAS GOING INTO
SURGERY, STEPHAN MAYES
DIED.
YET, HIS MOTHER REMAINS
BEYOND GRATEFUL FOR
CARTER'S COURAGE.
>> TY GAVE MY SON PEACE.
HE GAVE HIM SAFETY.
HE GAVE HIM COMFORT.
HE GAVE -- HE ALLOWED
STEPHAN TO HAVE THE
THOUGHTS THAT HE WOULD BE
COMING HOME TO US.
COMING HOME TO HIS FAMILY.
>> IN ALL, 8 SOLDIERS WERE
KILLED IN THE BATTLE AND 25
WERE INJURED.
TY CARTER WHO PRESIDENT
OBAMA CALLED AS TOUGH AS
THEY COME PLANS ON STAYING
IN THE ARMY AND GOING
AROUND THE BASES TALKING TO
SOLDIERS ABOUT
POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS WHICH
HE STILL OCCASIONALLY
STRUGGLES WITH JON?
>> Jon: AND, DAN TY CARTER
IS THE SECOND LIVING
SOLDIER TO RECEIVE THE
MEDAL OF HONOR FROM THE COP
KEATING BATTLE.
THAT'S WORKERS AT THE
DEPARTMENT OF VETERANS
AFFAIRS RECEIVED MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS IN PERFORMANCE
BONUSES FOR PERFORMANCES
THAT REPORTEDLY INVOLVED
AVOIDING CERTAIN CLAIMS
THAT ACCORDING TO THE "THE
WASHINGTON POST."
AS WE REPORTED OUR NATION'S
HEROS HAVE HAD TO WAIT
LONGER THAN EVER IN RECENT
YEARS TO RECEIVE
COMPENSATION.
TO GIVE YOU A SENSE OF HOW
SIRIUS THE BACKLOG OF
CLAIMS IS AT THE DEPARTMENT
OF AFFAIRS.
AS OF NOVEMBER DEFENDING
BONUSES SAYING THEY ARE
WELL SCERVED AND WORKING
HARD TO WEIGHT TIMES AND
IMPROVE ACCURACY OF CLAIMS.
MOSTLY BY PAPER DIGITAL
FILES.
EVEN THAT TRANSITION HALLS
HAD HAD SHARE OF PROBLEMS
WHICH KIND OF CASES ARE
GETTING THE BRUSH OFF?
>> A WORD, JOHN.
THE TOUGHEST ONCE.
BONUS STRUCTURES AT THE
V.A. IN RECENT YEARS ARE
INVENT SIZING CLAIMS
PROCESSORS TO MORE
DOCUMENTATION OR FOLLOW UP.
>> THIS DEPARTMENT CHARGED
WITH COMPLEX CLAIMS FROM A
HIGH VOLUME OF VETERANS AND
THINGS THAT HAPPEN IN THE
ENVIRONMENT.
YOU BETTER HAVE THE RIGHT
SET OF HIFER AND FIRE GOOD
AND BAD EMPLOYEES.
>> THE NUMBER OF CLAIMS
THAT LANG WISH GISHED FOR
MORE THAN FOUR MONTHS
DOUBLED FROM 2010 TO 2011.
WHAT'S THE V.A. SAYING
ABOUT THIS.
>> IN ESSENCE THAT THEY'RE
CHIPPING AWAY AT THE
BACKLOG.
V.A. OFFICIALS NOTE THAT
ALL THOSE RETURNING IRAQ
AND AFGHAN WAR VETS HAVE
CONTRIBUTED TO THE DOUBLING
OF THE CASE LOAD FOR VA
CLAIMS WORKERS.
AND THAT THOSE WORKERS NONE
THE LESS HAVE PROCESSED
MORE THAN A MILLION CASES A
YEAR FOR THE LAST THREE
YEARS.
STILL, THEY SAID SENIOR
EXECUTIVES IN THE VETERANS
BENEFITS ADMINISTRATION
WILL NOT BE RECEIVING ANY
PERFORMANCE AWARDS FOR
FISCAL YEAR 2012.
THOSE INSTEAD BEING
INVESTED TO ACCELERATOR
BACKLOG, JOHN JON.
>> Jon: THE V.A. OFFICE
LONGEST CLAIMS GAVE BONUSES
AVERAGING $1,100 EACH TO
40% OF ITS WORKFORCE.
THE FEDS JOINED IN TO SAVE
HUNDREDS OF DOGS ACROSS THE
SOUTHEAST IN ONE OF THE
LARGEST DOGFIGHTING
CRACKDOWNS THIS COUNTRY HAS
EVER SEEN.
TAKE A LOOK AT JUST A FEW
OF THE 367 PIT BULLS THEY
SEIZED DOG FIGHTS.
MANY FACE GAMBLING CHARGES.
ANIMAL WELFARE OFFICIALS
SAY SOME OF THE DOGS WERE
SO MAL-NOURISHED THEIR RIBS
WERE STICKING OUT.
OTHERS NEEDED EMERGENCY
CARE FOR INJURIES.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY HOPE TO
RETRAIN THE DOGS AND FIND
THEM GOOD HOMES.
A STRING OF VIOLENCE
CONTINUES TO PLAGUE ONE
MAJOR CITY.
KIDS THERE ARE NOW GETTING
ESCORTED TO SCHOOL.
PARENTS SAY THAT IS STILL
NOT ENOUGH.
PLUS MORE LEGAL TROUBLE
FOR THE DONALD.
WE'RE TELL YOU WHAT ONE NEW
YORK STATE OFFICIAL IS
ACCUSING HIM OF NOW IT'S
ALL AHEAD WHEN THE FOX
REPORT CONTINUES.
Reinforced with scratch-  resistant
glass
and a unibody  Made Kevlar Strong.
Okay Google Now.  Call My Droid.
The new  Droid Ultra by Motorola.
When strength matters,  Droid Does.
>> Jon: IT'S BEEN MORE THAN
THREE MONTHS SINCE AN
ARIZONA JURY CONVICTED JODI
ARIAS OF MURDERING HER
BOYFRIEND.
SHE HAS BEEN WAITING TO
FIND OUT WHAT THE SENTENCE
WILL BE.
TODAY SHE FOUND OUT SHE
WILL HAVE TO IT WAITED A
LITTLE WHILE LONGER.
APPEARED BEFORE A JUDGE WHO
DECLINED TO SET A DATE REDO
OF SENTENCING.
NEED MORE TIME TO RESPOND
TO DEFENSE REQUESTS.
AREAS WORE PRISONER STRIPES
ON AN OUTFIT THAT READ
SHERIFF'S INMATE
UNSENTENCED.
JURY LAST SPRING FAILED TO
REACH A DECISION ON WHETHER
SHE SHOULD GET THE DEATH
PENALTY SO PROSECUTORS PLAN
TO ASK A NEW JURY TO
CONSIDER THE SAME THING.
MORE DRAMATIC TESTIMONY OF
A TRIAL SHOOTING AND
KILLING IN GEORGIA AS A
CHILD'S MOTHER PUSHED HIM
IN A STROLLER.
A WOMAN WHO SAYS SHE GREW
UP WITH THE SUSPECT DARR
MARQUISE ELKINS TODAY
TESTIFIED HE ASKED HER
COULD HIDE HIS GUN
UNDERNEATH HER COUCH THE
DAY AFTER THE MURDER.
ALSO SAID MOTHER AND SISTER
CAME AND TOOK THE WEAPON
LATER THAT DAY.
REMEMBER, PROSECUTORS SAY
ELKINS TRIED TO ROB THAT
BABY'S MOTHER BACK IN
MARCH, FOUGHT OVER HER
PURSE AND SHOT HER IN THE
LEG AND SHOT THE BABY IN
THE FACE.
A SINGLE BULLET BETWEEN THE
EYES.
ELKINS MOTHER AND SISTER
BOTH STAND CHARGED WITH
EVIDENCE TAMPERING.
TOLL CHICAGO WHERE POLICE
ARE STRUGGLING TO KEEP UP A
SURGE OF VIOLENCE.
GUNMAN SHOT 10 PEOPLE IN
VARIOUS ATTACKS ACROSS THE
CITY, KILLING A 14-YEAR-OLD
BOY.
IT COMES A WEEK AFTER
SOMEONE SHOT FIVE PEOPLE
OUTSIDE A CHURCH IN WHAT
INVESTIGATORS SAY MAY HAVE
BEEN A GANG-RELATED ATTACK.
CHICAGO IS HOME TO FEWER
PEOPLE THAN L.A. OR NEW
YORK.
BUT THERE WERE MORE MURDERS
THERE LAST YEAR.
512 OF THEM.
THAT'S ABOUT 19 FOR EVERY
100,000 PEOPLE.
MORE THAN DOUBLE THE MURDER
RATE OF THE LARGER CITIES.
STARTING TODAY ON THE FIRST
DAY OF SCHOOL HUNDREDS OF
NEW SAFETY GUARDS ARE
WATCHING OVER CHILDREN AS
THEY WALK THROUGH GANG
AREAS.
THE PARENTS SAY THEIR NEEDS
TO BE MORE DONE.
MIKE TOBIN IS LIVE IN THE
CITY.
MIKE?
>> A LOT OF KIDS WALKED TO
SCHOOL FLANKED BY GUARDS
WITH FRANKED VESTS.
A HALF BLOCK AWAY FROM SAFE
PASSAGE ROUTES A BODY WAS
FOUND IN A DUMPSTER THAT
MAN APPARENTLY KILLED
OVERNIGHT AND CHICAGO
REMAINS PLAGUED WITH
VIOLENCE.
>> A GUY LAYING IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE STREET.
LOOKS LIKE HE IS SHOT.
>> WHEN THE GUNSHOTS RANG
OUT ON CHICAGO'S TROUBLED
SOUTH AND WEST SIDE.
SOMEONE KNOWS THEY ARE
COMING WHETHER THE VIOLENCE
IS DRIVEN BY DRUG VAD OR
VENTRICLE NATE THAT.
WORD HITS THE STREET BEFORE
BULLETS FLY.
>> EVERYONE KNOWS WHO HAS
GUNS WHO IS RUNNING THE
STREETS.
EVERYONE KNOWS.
IT'S A MATTER OF THE
NEIGHBORHOOD GETTING
INVOLVED.
>> NATED PENDLETON IS THE
FATHER OF THAT DEA
PENDLETON WHO MADE NATIONAL
HEADLINES BEING KILLED BY A
STRAY BULLET JUST AFTER A
WEEK AFTER PERFORMING AT
THE PRESIDENT'S
INAUGURATION.
THE FIRST LADY ATTEND ITED
HER FUNERAL.
[GUNFIRE]
>> WHEN THE GUN RULES THE
STREET SNITCHES PAY A HARSH
PENALTY.
>> GOT TO GET OPEN ARMS
COMMUNITY.
>> ANETE FREEMAN WHO LOST
HER SON TO IT A STRAY
BULLET SAYS THE
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE
PEOPLE IN THE VIOLENT
NEIGHBORHOOD AND CHICAGO
COPS IS NOT GOOD.
THERE IS NO TRUST.
>> I HAVE CALLED POLICE
BEFORE.
YOU KNOW, IT MADE ME FEEL
LIKE I WAS THE CRIMINAL.
POLICE SUPERINTENDENT GARY
McCARTY SAYS THE LOCAL
DEPARTMENTS NEED TO DO MORE
TO BUILD RELATIONSHIPS AND
TRUST IN THOSE TROUBLED
NEIGHBORHOODS, JON?
>> Mike: MIKE, A POLICING
EXPERT SAYS CRIME GROWS
FASTEST IN NEIGHBORHOODS
WHERE FOLKS HIDE IN THEIR
HOMES AND GIVE CRIMINALS
FREE REIGN OF THE STREETS.
HE SAYS THE ANSWER IS TO BE
OUTSIDE AND TO BE SEEN TO
MAKE IT KNOWN THAT
NEIGHBORS ARE WATCHING OUT
FOR EACH OTHER.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL OF NEW
YORK STATE SAYS TRUMP
UNIVERSITY IS NOT AN ACTUAL
UNIVERSITY.
HE CALLS IT A SCAM.
IS HE SUING REAL ESTATE
MOGUL DONALD TRUMP ACCUSING
HIM OF COMMITTING FRAUD BY
PROMISING TO MAKE ONLINE
STUDENTS RICH THROUGH
MOSTLY USELESS SEMINARS.
TRUMP DENIES THAT HE CALLS
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL QUOTE
A POLITICAL HACK LOOKING TO
GET PUBLICITY.
WHAT WILL STEPHEN COLBERT
THING END WITHIN OA RANT
AFTER GROUP PUNK CANCELLED
HIS SHOW.
THEY DID IT SO THEY COULD
PERFORM EXCLUSIVELY ON THE
MTV VIDEO MUSIC AWARDS.
SO WAS IT WORTH THE WAIT?
HERE IS A HINT.
NO.
I HAVE LOW TESTOSTERONE.  THERE, I
SAID IT.  SEE, I KNEW TESTOSTERONE
COULD AFFECT SEX DRIVE  BUT NOT ENERGY
OR EVEN MY MOOD.  THAT'S WHEN I TALKED
WITH MY DOCTOR.  HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD
TESTS...  SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.  THAT'S
IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.    [ Male Announcer
]    TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T    HAVE
ANDROGEL    1.62% TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED    TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY    INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.    WOMEN AND CHILDREN
SHOULD AVOID    CONTACT WITH APPLICATION
SITES.    DISCONTINUANDROGEL    AND
CALL YOUR DOCTOR    IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED
SIGNS    OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,    WHICH MAY
INCLUDE    CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE    POSSIBLY
DUE    TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER    OR WHO HAVE
OR MIGHT HAVE    PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.    SERIOUS
SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE    WORSENING
OF AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,    POSSIBLE
INCREASED RIS    OF PROSTATE CANCER
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING    OF
ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY    ENLARGED
OR PAINFUL BREASTS,  PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP    AND BLOOD CLOTS IN
THE LEGS.    TELL YOUR DOCTOR    ABOUT
YOUR MEDICAL CONDITION    AND MEDICATIONS
ESPECIALLY IULIN    CORTICOSTEROIDS,
OR MEDICINES    TO DECREASE BLOOD
CLOTTING.    IN A CLINICAL STUDY,
OVER 80%    OF TREATED MEN HAD THEIR
T LEVELS RESTORED TO NORMAL.    TALK
TO YOUR DOCTOR    ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.    CHANGE YOUR
NUMBER. TURN IT UP.    ANDROGEL 1.62%.
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]    [ Male Announcer
]    FROM THE LAST DAY OF SCHOOL,
BACK TO THE FIRST.    THEY'RE GONNA
MAKE EVERYTHING    FROM POSTERS
TO DO IT YOURSELF TATTOOS.    SO MAKE
SURE THEY'VE GOT THE    SHARPIES TO
MAKE THEIR MARK.    THIS WEEK ONLY
GET SHARPIE    FIVE PACKS FOR A DOLLAR.
STAPLES HAS IT.    STAPLES.    THAT
WAS EASY.
WHEN WE MADE OUR COMMITMENT TO  THE
GULF, BP HAD TWO BIG GOALS:  HELP
THE GULF  RECOVER AND LEARN  FROM
WHAT HAPPENED
SO WE COULD BE  A BETTER, SAFER  ENERGY
COMPANY.
I CAN TELL YOU - SAFETY IS AT  THE
HEART OF EVERYTHING WE DO.
WE'VE ADDED CUTTING-EDGE  TECHNOLOGY
LIKE A NEW DEEPWATER WELL CAP
AND A STATE-OF-THE-ART  MONITORING
CENTER, WHE EXPERTS
WATCH OVER ALL DRILLING  ACTIVITY
TWENTY-FOUR-SEVEN.
AND WE'RE SHARING  WHAT WE'VE LEARNED
SO WE CAN ALL PRODUCE  ENERGY MORE
SAFELY.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS  NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
Check it out...  Over 20 million drivers
are  insured with GEICO.
So get a free rate quote  today.
I love it!
How much do you love it?
Animation is hot...and I  think it
makes GEICO's
20 million drivers message very  compelling,
very compelling.
This is some really strong  stuff!
So you turned me into a  cartoon...lovely.
GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could  save you
fifteen percent or more on  car insurance.
Max and Penny kept our bookstoreexciting
and would always me  to my rescue.
But as time passed, I stted to  notice
Max just wasn't himself.
And I knew he'd feel better if  heost
a little weight.
So I switched to Purina Cat ow  Healthy
Weight formula.
I just fed the recommended  amount...
And they both loved the taste.
After a few months Max's  "speal powers"
returned...
And I got my hero back.
Purina Cat Chow Healthy Weight.
>> Jon: ALL KINDS OF
OUTRAGE DURING MILEY CYRUS
DANCE MOVES.
SOME SEEMED TO BE
SCRATCHING THEIR HEADS
WONDERING WHAT HAPPENED TO
PUNK'S SO-CALLED SURPRISE
PERFORMANCE.
EARLIER THIS MONTH THE
FRENCH ELECTRO POP DUO
APPARENTLY CANCELLED A
SCHEDULED APPEARANCE ON
COMEDY CENTRAL'S COLBERT
RESPONSE.
IN RESPONSE HOST STEPHAN
COLBERT LEAKED THAT THE
GROUP WAS SET TO BE A
SURPRISE MUPG MUSICAL GUEST
AT THE VMA'S.
YOU MIGHT REMEMBER COLBERT
HAD FUN WITH THAT LAST
NIGHT THEY DID TAKE THE
STAGE BUT ONLY TO PRESENT
AN AWARD.
FOLKS HOPING TO HEAR THE
GROUP'S HIT SONG DID NOT
GET LUCKY.
REALTY TV STAR KATE
GOSSELIN HAS FILED A
LAWSUIT AGAINST EX-HUSBAND
JOHN GOSSELIN ACCUSING HIM
OF STEALING HER COMPUTER'S
HARD DRIVE AND HACKING INTO
HER PHONE TO GET EMAIL --
TO GET MATERIAL I SHOULD
SAY FOR A TELL ALL BOOK.
THAT ACCORDING TO NEW COURT
DOCUMENTS.
THE LAWSUIT ACCUSES JON
GOSSELIN OF IDENTITY THEFT
WIRETAPPING AND INVASION OF
PRIVACY IT SEEKS
UNSPECIFIED DAMAGES.
OF COURSE, THE TWO STARRED
IN THE TV SHOW JON AND KATE
PLUS 8 WITH THEIR TWINS AND
SEX IT
SEXTUPLETS.
NO WORD FROM JOHN JOSS
GOSSELIN'S LEGAL TEAM.
UPDATING SOME OF OUR TOP
STORIES TONIGHT.
SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN
KERRY TODAY ACCUSED SYRIANS
PRESIDENT OF DESTROYING
EVIDENCE OF A CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK.
THAT PURPORTEDLY KILLED
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE
INCLUDING HUNDREDS OF
CHILDREN.
HE ALSO SAID THERE MUST BE
CONSEQUENCES FOR THE
STRIKE.
STOCKS PLUMMETED AFTER
SECRETARY KERRY MADE THOSE
COMMENTS.
THAT DOTTED RED LINE THERE
MARKS THE TIME THAT HE
SPOKE.
AN EMOTIONAL TESTIMONY
TODAY FROM FAMILIES OF THE
VICTIMS OF THE FORT HOOD
MASSACRE.
BEFORE JURORS DECIDE
WHETHER TO GIVE MAJOR NIDAL
HASAN THE DEATH PENALTY OR
LIFE IN PRISON.
A.M. AND ON THIS DAY IN
1939 THE BROOKLYN DODGERS
HOSTED THE REDS MAJOR
LEAGUE.
IT DID NOT YET EXIST BUT
THE SPRING OF '39 MARKED
THE WORLD EXPO IN QUEENS,
NEW YORK AND NBC HAD BEEN
USING THE FAIR TO BROADCAST
EVENTS ON ITS LOCAL NEW
YORK CITY STATION.
ORGANIZERS AGREED TO
POSITION CAMERAS AT THE
FIELD FOR DODGERS RED
DOUBLE HEADER HOPING TO
SHOWCASE THE UP AND COMING
TECHNOLOGY.
THE COVERAGE WAS A SUCCESS
AND IT WOULD HELP LAUNCH
THE NOW MULTIBILLION-DOLLAR
DEAF ADVISED SPORTS
INDUSTRY.
BUT THE NATIONAL PAST TIME
FIRST HIT THE SMALL SCREEN
74 YEARS AGO TODAY.
AND NOW THAT IS THE FOX
REPORT FOR MONDAY,
AUGUST 26TH, 2013.
I'M JON SCOTT IN FOR
SHEPARD SMITH.
WE'LL BE BACK TOMORROW, THE
FACTOR IS UP NEXT BE HAVE A
GOOD NIGHT.
>> Bill: THE O'REILLY
FACTOR IS ON.
TONIGHT.
>> I WANT TO GO BACK FOR A
SECOND TO THE TRAYVON
MARTIN CASE BECAUSE I THINK
THAT IS SPAWNED THIS SORT
OF DESIRE FOR REVENGE
ALMOST FROM PEOPLE ON THE
RIGHT.
>> Bill: NOW THE FAR LEFT
IS SAYING THAT REPORTING ON
STORIES LIKE THE MURDERS IN
OKLAHOMA AND SPOKANE ARE
REVENGE FOR THE TRAYVON
MARTIN CASE.
IN SANE, YOU BET.
WE WILL CONTINUE OUR
REPORTING.
>> WHAT WE SAW IN SYRIA
LAST WEEK SHOULD SHOCK THE
CONSCIENCE OF THE WORLD IT
DEFIES ANY CODE OF
MORALITY.
WHAT WILL THE U.S.A. DO TO
SYRIA.
WE HAVE TO PUNISH THAT
COMPANY.
KARL ROVE WILL TELL US WHAT
HE THINKS WILL HAPPEN.
>> WHO IS YOUR