-- STARTS IN 10 SECONDS.
>> Shepard: THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT, I'M SHEPARD SMITH
ABOVE MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
ABOVE THE SCHOOL ON WHICH
WE HAVE BEEN FOCUSING FOR
THE PAST 48 HOURS.
COMING UP, WE'LL SHOW YOU
THE ENTIRE PATH OF THE
TORNADO THAT RAKED ACROSS
THIS OKLAHOMA CITY SUBURB.
WE WILL SHOW YOU THE
DAMAGE, THE DESTRUCTION,
THE RECOVERY EFFORTS AND
YOU WILL MEET THE PEOPLE IN
THE MIDDLE OF IT ALL.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
AND THE NEWS BEGINS NOW.
>> Shepard: LIVE ON THE
GROUND NOW, MOORE
OKLAHOMA, WHERE TODAY THE
MEDICAL EXAMINER ANNOUNCED
HIS OFFICE HAS IDENTIFIED
ALMOST ALL OF THE 24 PEOPLE
WHO DIED IN THE TORNADO
MONDAY.
10 OF THOSE VICTIMS,
CHILDREN.
TWO OF THOSE INFANTS, LESS
THAN A YEAR OLD.
ONE MAN WHOSE DAUGHTER WAS
AMONG THOSE KILLED AT PLAZA
HILLS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
SAYS HE ARRIVED THERE 10
MINUTES AFTER THE TWISTER
HIT AND HE SAYS WHEN HE
FINALLY RETURNED TO HIS
HOUSE, WITHOUT HIS CHILD
HIS HOME WAS GONE.
THE LATEST OFFICIAL
ESTIMATES INDICATE THIS
TORNADO MAY HAVE DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED UP TO 13,000
HOMES.
I MENTIONED EARLIER WE GOT
A LOOK FROM THE SKY AND A
LENGTHY ONE.
WE WERE UP FOR HOURS
LOOKING AT THE DESTRUCTION
THE TORNADO INFLICTED.
IT IS A BROKEN LINE OF
OBLITERATION.
A SCAR ACROSS AMERICA'S
HEART LAND.
ONE THAT STRETCHES FOR MANY
MILES.
>> WE'RE STARTING IN PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
THIS IS THE SPOT WHERE THE
SEVEN CHILDREN DIED.
AND THIS IS THE SPOT WHERE
WE WATCHED FROM THE
HELICOPTER TWO DAYS AGO AS
RESCUE WORKERS AND
NEIGHBORS WERE PULLING AWAY
ALL OF THE -- WHAT WAS LEFT
OF THE SCHOOL TO TRY TO GET
TO THE CHILDREN.
IN HOPES, IN HOPES THAT
THEY COULD GET SOME OUT
ALIVE.
AS IT TURNED OUT, IT WAS AN
AWFUL SCENE THERE.
BUT THEY ARE HARD AT WORK
TODAY, TRYING TO REMOVE
WHAT'S THERE.
BECAUSE THE GOAL NOW IS TO
GET ON WITH THEIR LIVES.
OVER THE NEXT FEW MINUTES
WE ARE GOING TO TAKE YOU
ALONG THE PATH OF THE
STORM.
I'M GOING TO TAKE YOU FROM
THE SCHOOL ACROSS ABOUT A
FOUR TO FIVE MILE AREA OF
THE WORST OF DESTRUCTION.
YOU WILL SEE HOW THE WIDTH
OF THE STORM THE WIDTH OF
THIS TORNADO CHANGES AS WE
MOVE ACROSS THE LANDSCAPE.
SCOTT, TAKE US OUT THERE IF
YOU COULD.
AND THIS -- WE'RE IN THE
SCHOOL AREA NOW AND AS HE
ZOOMS, IN YOU WILL BE ABLE
TO SEE IN THIS PARTICULAR
AREA HOMES WERE REDUCED TO
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING.
THIS IS ONE OF THE AREAS
WHERE THE STORM WAS AT ITS
WIDEST.
THINK OF THIS AS A FUNNEL
LIKE YOU WOULD USE IN YOUR
KITCHEN.
THE TIP OF THE FUNNEL IS
VERY THIN.
THE TOP IS VERY WIDE.
BUT IF YOU COULD PUSH THAT
FUNNEL DOWN INTO THE
GROUND, THE AREA WHICH IS
CONCENTRATED ON THE GROUND,
IT'S WIDER.
THAT'S WHAT HAPPENED HERE.
THAT'S WHY IN THIS AREA
THE WIDTH OF THE STORM THE
WIDTH OF THE TORNADO WAS
ABOUT TWO MILES.
SO THE AREA OF DESTRUCTION
IS MASSIVE AND THE DENSITY
OF IT IS REALLY INCREDIBLE.
YOU DON'T SEE A BUNCH OF
HOUSES STILL THAT MIGHT BE
ABLE TO BUILD AROUND.
YOU SEE NOTHING BUT DEBRIS.
IT'S AS IF SOMEBODY -- AS
IF A GIANT CAME IN AND
SQUISHED IT IN HIS HAND AND
DROPPED IT IT ON THE
GROUND.
THROUGHOUT THIS AREA, NOW
THE PATH OF THE DESTRUCTION
IS THINNER.
THE CLOUDS LIFTED UP SOME.
AND THE AREA OF THE FUNNEL
CLOUD THAT WAS TOUCHING THE
GROUND IS SMALLER.
YOU WILL SEE SOME THE
DESTRUCTION ISN'T QUITE AS
SEVERE.
IN SOME OF THESE AREAS YOU
WILL SEE BLUE TARPS ON TOP
OF HOUSE AFTER HOUSE.
THOSE ARE AREAS WHERE THEY
ARE GOING TO BE ABLE TO
SALVAGE THE HOME.
BUT, BEHIND US, IT WASN'T
LIKE THAT AT ALL.
SCOTT, PULL OUT AND SHOW
FORWARD IF YOU WOULD, AND
YOU WILL SEE AHEAD OF US
THE PATH OF THE STORM WAS
MUCH THINNER, MEANING THE
CLOUDS HAD LIFTED HIGHER
AND THE PART OF THE CONE
THAT'S ACTUALLY ON THE
GROUND IS MUCH SMALLER.
THE WINDS GET STRONGER AND
WEAKER AS THE STORM MOVES
ALONG LIKE ANYTHING ELSE
IT PICKS UP ENERGY AND IN
SPURTS IT WILL BE STRONGER
THAN IT WAS BEFORE.
WE ARE A LITTLE MORE THAN
HALFWAY THROUGH THE
DESTRUCTION OF THIS NOW.
AND YOU CAN SEE AGAIN I'M
TRYING TO GIVE YOU AN IDEA
OF HOW WIDESPREAD THIS IS.
WE ARE FLYING ALONG A
STRAIGHT LINE.
AND AS YOU LOOK ALONG THAT
NEIGHBORHOOD AFTER
NEIGHBORHOOD HOUSE AFTER
HOUSE, JUST COMPLETELY
OBLITERATED.
IF HE PULLS OUT JUST A
LITTLE BIT, YOU WILL SEE
THAT TO THE LEFT AND RIGHT
OF THE SHOT, THERE ARE
HOUSES THAT ARE JUST FINE.
THIS ISN'T A TWO MILE WIDE
PATH IN THIS AREA.
IT'S MUCH THINNER THAN THAT
IN SOME AREAS IT'S JUST A
FEW HUNDRED YARDS WIDE.
BUT IF YOUR HOME WAS IN
THAT AREA, YOUR HOME IS
DESTROYED.
IF YOU WERE JUST TO THE
LEFT OR RIGHT OF IT YOU
MIGHT HAVE SOME ROOF DAMAGE
AND THEN THE NEXT SERIES OF
HOUSES OVER, THERE MIGHT BE
DEBRIS FROM YOUR NEIGHBOR'S
HOME, WHAT USED TO BE YOUR
NEIGHBOR'S HOME ON TOP OF
YOUR HOUSE OR IN YOUR YARD.
BUT YOUR HOUSE ITSELF IS
FINE.
THAT'S THE NATURE OF THIS
STORM.
NOW, BACK TO THE PATH OF IT
ITSELF.
AND WE ARE COMING INTO AN
AREA THAT'S MORE -- THAT'S
LESS POPULATED.
YOU WILL SEE AN AREA WHERE
IT JUST SORT OF DUG UP THE
DIRT AND REPLACED THE GRASS
WITH DIRT.
AND THEN THERE WILL BE A
HOME HERE AND A HOME THERE.
AND JUST AHEAD OF US IS THE
SPOT WHERE THE TORNADO
ACTUALLY LIFTED BACK INTO
THE SKY.
LIFTED BACK NOT TO BE SEEN
AGAIN AND THEN THE
RESIDENTS CAME BACK TO TRY
TO ASSESS WHAT HAD
HAPPENED.
THE DAMAGE WAS EXTENSIVE.
THE WORK THAT THEY HAVE
AHEAD IS WEEKS AND MONTHS.
BUT THEY HAVE VOWED THEY
WILL REBUILD AND WHEN YOU
LOOK DOWN BELOW, YOU WONDER
CAN THOSE PEOPLE FEEL SAFE
IN THE YEARS TO COME?
OKLAHOMANS TELL US THEY
CAN.
>> Shepard: OUR THANKS TO
JIM JOHNSON WHO GAVE US
THAT TWO AND A HALF HOUR
TOUR TODAY.
WE FLEW BACK AND FORTH AND
BACK AND FORTH.
JIM WAS IN THAT SAME
CHOPPER 14 YEARS AGO AND
FLYING THAT SAME PATH WHEN
THE LAST HUGE STORM HIT
HERE.
HE SAYS IN AREAS THE
DESTRUCTION IS WORSE, BUT
THE ACTUAL LENGTH OF THE
DESTRUCTION IN 1999 WAS
LONGER.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS
PRESIDENT OBAMA WILL HEAD
HERE ON SUNDAY TO SEAT
DAMAGE FOR HIMSELF.
HE IS SET TO MEET WITH
SURVIVORS AND THANK THE
RESPONDERS.
WE HAVE A LOT MORE FROM THE
HEARTLAND NEWSCAST.
YOU WILL MEET A TEACHER
FROM BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY.
NOW JUST A PILE OF BROKEN
CHALK BOARDS AND SCATTERED
ARTWORK AND PILES WHERE
DESKS USED TO BE.
HOW SCIEWNTS GOT OUT ALIVE.
HOW THE BRAVE KIDS GOT INTO
ACTION LIFT THE CONCRETE TO
SAVE THEIR OWN LITTLE KIDS.
WE HAVE SEEN THE HARD HIT
NEIGHBORHOODS LIKE THIS BUT
ONLY FROM ABOVE.
NOW WE ARE ABLE TO SEE THEM
FROM THE GROUND, GIVING
THIS A WHOLE NEW
PERSPECTIVE.
OUR CASEY STEGALL HAS JUST
GOTTEN ACCESS.
HE WILL TAKE US ON A LIVE
DRIVING TOUR WITH MAWLT
PELL CAMERAS IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
ONE OF THE BIGGEST STARS IN
ALL OF COUNTRY MUSIC COMES
HOME.
TOBY KEITH GREW UP RIGHT
HERE IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
HIS NAME IS ON THE WATER
TOWER.
HE WAS IN TOWN BEFORE THE
STORM HIT.
HE TELLS ME HOW HE HOPES TO
USE HIS STAR POWER TO HELP
HIS HOMETOWN.
WE WILL TELL YOU HOW YOU
CAN HELP TOO AS LIVE TEAM
FOX COVERAGE CONTINUES JUST
AHEAD.
FIRST A STUNNING ATTACK IN
BROAD DAYLIGHT TODAY AND
TONIGHT OFFICIALS SAY IT
LOOKED TO THEM LIKE A
TERRORIST HAS STRUCK.
WE HAVE AMATEUR VIDEO
SHOWING A MAN WITH BLOOD
ALL OVER HIS HANDS HOLDING
A BLOODY KNIFE AND A MEAT
CLEAVER.
HE REPORTEDLY IS ONE OF THE
ATTACKERS WHO HACKED TO
DEATH A BRITISH SOLDIER
TODAY IN LONDON.
FOX NEWS CANNOT CONFIRM
THAT BUT THE MAN IN THE
VIDEO REPORTEDLY SAYS THE
KILLING IS PAY BACK FOR,
QUOTE:  WHAT'S GOING ON IN
OUR COUNTRIES.
A TERROR ATTACK GREG
PALKOT WITH THE NEWS LIVE
IN LONDON TONIGHT, GREG?
>> YEAH, SHEP THERE ARE
GROWING SIGNS TONIGHT
ACCORDING TO OFFICIALS THAT
THERE WAS A BRUTAL TERROR
ATTACK HERE.
TWO MEN ATTACKED ONE IN THE
STREETS OF SOUTHEAST LONDON
IN MID AFTERNOON.
IT'S GOTTEN EVERYBODY
CONCERNED AS THE REAL
INDICATION THAT THE VICTIM
COULD HAVE BEEN A SERVING
SOLDIER.
IT HAPPENED NEAR A BRITISH
MILITARY BARRACKS.
THE DEFENSE MINISTRY
TONIGHT SAY THEY ARE
URGENTLY TRYING TO CONFIRM
THAT IT'S GOT EVERYBODY
CONCERNED HERE TOO THE
BLOODY NATURE OF THE
INCIDENT.
EYEWITNESSES SAY THE VICTIM
WAS ATTACKED AGAIN AND
AGAIN AND THEN ONE OF THE
ATTACKERS REPORTEDLY
PRONOUNCED ISLAMIST
POLITICAL SLOGANS.
TAKE A LOOK AND LISTEN TO
THIS AMATEUR AND VERY
GRAPHIC VIDEO.
>> WE MUST FIGHT THEM AS
THEY FIGHT US.
AN EYE FOR AN EYE AND A
TOOTH FOR A TOOTH.
I APOLOGIZE THAT WOMEN HAD
TO WITNESS THIS TODAY, BUT
IN OUR LAND OUR WOMEN HAVE
TO SEE THE SAME.
YOUR PEOPLE WILL NEVER BE
SAFE.
THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT YOU.
>> WORDS POSSIBLY COMING
FROM A HOMEGROWN TERRORIST.
POSSIBLY SOMEONE WITH
JIHADI LINKS.
AGAIN WE CAN'T CONFIRM THE
VIDEO.
THESE TWO STOOD AROUND THE
BODY LEFT IN THE STREET FOR
ABOUT 20 MINUTES UNTIL THE
POLICE CAME.
THE POLICE SHOT THEM.
TOOK THEM AWAY.
THEY ARE UNDER ARREST
TONIGHT.
EMERGENCY SECURITY MEETING
U.K. GOVERNMENT CONVENED
TONIGHT AS WELL.
THEY ARE BEEFING UP
DEFENSES ALL AROUND LONDON.
INCLUDING AT THE MILITARY
BARRACKS.
U.K. DAVID CAMMERON'S WORDS
WE WILL NEVER BUCKLE
AGAINST TERRORISM.
MAYBE PEOPLE ARE TAKING
THINGS IN THEIR OWN HANDS
THOUGH TONIGHT TWO
DIFFERENT MOSQUES WE HAVE
REPORT HAVE BEEN ATTACKED
AND THERE ARE NATIONALISTS
DEMONSTRATORS OUT ON THE
STREETS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: GREG PALKOT
LIVE TONIGHT FOR US FROM
LONDON.
THE CONVICTED MURDERER JODI
ARIAS IS WAITING TO FIND
OUT HER INCIDENCE SENTENCE,
LIFE IN PRISON OR THE DEATH
PENALTY.
THE JURORS TOLD THE JUDGE
TODAY WE ARE HAVING TROUBLE
DECIDING AND JODI ARIAS
HERSELF HAS SOMETHING TO
SAY.
>> I CAN NEVER MAKE UP FOR
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> DO YOU WANT TO SAY I'M
SORRY RIGHT NOW TO TRAVIS
ALEXANDER'S FAMILY?
>> Shepard: JODI ARIAS
SPEAKING BEFORE THE VERDICT
AND EXPLAINING WHY SHE
CHANGED HER MIND ABOUT WHAT
SHE WANTS.
>> YOU TOLD ME TWO WEEKS
AGO THAT YOU WOULD RATHER
DIE THAN GO TO JAIL FOR
LIFE.
IS THAT A LIE?
>> NO I MEANT THAT WHEN I
SAID IT.
>> Shepard: WHAT NOW.
>> REGARDLESS OF WHICH WAY
THE VERDICT GOES, THERE IS
A LONG ROAD AHEAD OF ME.
>> Shepard: TONIGHT JODI
ARIAS ON HER CRIME AND THE
PUNISHMENT.
PLUS, LAWMAKERS TRYING TO
GET ANSWERS ABOUT HOW THE
IRS TARGETED CONSERVATIVE
GROUPS.
BUT NOT HAVING MUCH LUCK
WITH ONE WITNESS.
>> I HAVE NOT DONE ANYTHING
WRONG.
I WILL NOT ANSWER ANY
QUESTIONS OR TESTIFY ABOUT
THE SUBJECT MATTER THIS
COMMITTEE'S MEETING.
>> Shepard: LAWMAKERS
DIDN'T LIKE THAT ONE BIT.
>> SHE WAIVED HER RIGHT TO
FIFTH AMENDMENT PRIVILEGE
BY ISSUING AN OPENING
STATEMENT.
SHE OUGHT TO STAND HERE AND
ANSWER OUR QUESTIONS.
>> Shepard: BUT THE WOMAN
AT THE CENTER OF THE
SCANDAL REFUSES TO TALK.
THAT'S COMING UP FROM THE
JOURNALISTS OF FOX NEWS ON
THIS WEDNESDAY FOX REPORT.
FROM MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
[ bop ]
[ Male Announcer ]    COULD'VE HAD
A V8.    100% VEGETABLE JUICE    WITH
THREE OF YOUR DAILY    VEGETABLE SERVINGS
IN EVERY LITTLE BOTTLE.
[ man ]  ON DECEMBER 17, 1903  THE
WRIGHT BROTHERS BECAME  THE FIRST
IN FLIGHT.  [ Goodall ] I THINK  THE
MOST AMAZING THING  IS HOW LIKE US
THESE CHIMPANZEES ARE.  [ LAUGHING
]  [ woman ]  CAN YOU HEAR ME?  AND
YOU HEAR YOUR VOICE?  OH, IT'S EXCITING!
[ man ] TOUCHDOWN CONFIRMED.  WE'RE
SAFE ON MARS.  [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE
]  ♪ ♪  HI.  [ BABY FUSSING ]  ♪ ♪
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.  HERE YOU GO. YOU,
TOO.  I'M GOING TO DREAM  OUT THAT
STEAK.  I'M GOING TO DREAM  ABOUT
THAT TIRAMISU.
WHAT A NIGHT, HUH?  BUT, UM, CAN THE
TEST DRIVE  BE OVER NOW?  HEAD BACK
TO THE DEALERSHIP?    [ Male Annocer
]    IT'S PRACTICALLY YOURS.    BUT
WE STILLEED    UR SIGNATURE.    VOLKSWAGEN
SIGN THEN DRIVE    IS BACK.    AND
IT'S NEVER BEEN EASIER    TO GET A
PASSAT.    THAT'S THE POWER    OF
GERMAN ENGINEERING.    GET $0 DOWN,
$0 DUE AT SIGNING    $0 DEPOSIT
AND $0 FIRST MONTH'S PAYMENT    ON
ANY NEW VOLKSWAGEN.    VISIT VWDEALER.COM
TODAY.
What makes the Sleep
Number store different?  You walk
into a  conventional mattress
store, it's really not  about you.
They say, "Well, if you  wanted a
firm bed you can
lie on one of those.
We provide the exact  individualization
that
your body needs.
Oh, yeah!
Wow.
Once you experience it  there's no
going back.
At the Sleep Number  Memorial Day
Sale,
save on the closeout of  our Classic
Special
Edition bed set.
Now just $1299-a savings  of $600.
Only at the Sleep Number  store.
Sleep Number.
Comfort Individualized.
AS OUT MIGHT IMAGINE.
HE WAS HERE ONMOND AND FLEW
FROM NASHVILE HOURS BEFORE
THE DISASTER.
I KNEW YOU WERE HERE
BECAUSE I SAW YOUR NAME ON
THE WATER TOWER.
>> HOW ABOUT THAT.
I'M PROUD OF THAT.
>> Shepard: GREW UP THERE.
>> GREW UP FOUR BLOCKS FROM
WHERE WE ARE AT.
>> MOVED HERE.
>> MOVED OUT HERE THREE
MILES.
>> Shepard: NOW YOU HAVE
GOT A BIG SPREAD OUT THERE.
>> EAST OF TOWN.
>> Shepard: HIS SISTER
LIVES RIGHT HERE.
>> SHE LIVES A COUPLE MILES
DOWN FOURTH STREET HERE IN
THIS PATH WE ARE STANDING
IN GOT HER HOUSE RIGHT
HERE.
>> Shepard: TOBY SPENT THE
MORNING BOARDING UP.
>> WE SPENT THE LAST TWO
DAYS MAKING SURE SHE GOT
HER STUFF, SAVED THE SHELL,
ALL THE GARAGE DOORS AND
WINDOWS OF THE GARAGE IS
GONE.
THANK GOD SHE GOT TO KEEP
HER STUFF.
>> Shepard: ONE THING THAT
HAS STRUCK OUR TEAM IS THE
NUMBER OF PEOPLE WHO HAVE
COME HERE TO HELP.
EVERYTHING FROM PASSING OUT
WATER BOTTLES, OFFERING
FOOD TO RESCUE WORKERS AND
THE MEDIA FOR THAT MATTER.
AND THE FAMILIES WHO ARE
LEFT WITH NOTHING.
TOBY KEITH TOLD ME THAT IS
SOMETHING THAT COMES
NATURAL TO SOONERS.
>> LAST TORNADO MAYBE THE
PEOPLE THAT GOT HIT THIS
TIME WERE HELPING THOSE
PEOPLE WHEN THEY GOT HIT.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THAT YOU
COME TOGETHER AS ONE AND
PUT EVERYTHING ASIDE AND
YOU GET IT BACK UP AND
RUNNING.
IT'S OUR HOME, YOU KNOW.
AND WHEN YOU CALL SOME
PLACE HOME, YOU CAN TELL
THAT PEOPLE ALREADY
STARTING TO PICK THEMSELVES
UP.
THE NEIGHBORS ARE COMING
AROUND PASSING FOOD OUT
BRINGING BLANKETS AND
WATER.
THEY ARE RESOURCEFUL AND
GOT THAT SPIRIT.
OKLAHOMA MADE IT THROUGH
THE DUST BOWL.
TORNADO IS JUST ANOTHER BAD
DAY BLOOD ROCK WE ARE RIGHT
BACK IN THE MIDDLE.
>> Shepard: RIGHT BACK IN
THE MIDDLE.
TOBY KEITH SAID HE WOULD
ALSO LIKE TO HELP BY
DONATING WHAT HE DOES BEST.
HE SAYS HE IS PLANNING A
BENEFIT CONCERT.
HE SAYS FIRST THE COMMUNITY
NEEDS SOME TIME TO HEAL.
>> RIGHT NOW WE ARE TRYING
TO GET EVERYBODY, YOU KNOW
GET WOOD ON PEOPLE'S HOUSES
GET THEM SCREWED IN AND
GETS THE TARPS ON.
GET EVERYTHING UP AND
RUNNING AND THEN GET PAST
THE FUNERALS AND THE SHOCK
OF THING THIS AND ONCE WE
TURN THE CORNER THEN WE
WILL ALL DIVE IN AND TRY TO
RAISE A BUNCH OF MONEY FOR
THEM BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
PEOPLE IN THE MUSIC LOVE TO
DO.
BUT RIGHT NOW WE ARE JUST
RIGHT NOW I'M JUST GOING TO
FOCUS ON GETTING THE
INFRASTRUCTURE PUT BACK IN
PLACE.
GETTING CELL TOWERS UP.
GETTING THE PEOPLE BACK IN
THEIR HOUSES.
GETTING THEIR POSSESSIONS
SAVED.
AS SOON AS WE FIND OUT MORE
DETAILS ABOUT THE BENEFIT
CONCERT IS HE WORKING ON WE
WILL GET BACK TO YOU.
>> DECIDING THE FATE OF THE
JODI ARIAS HAVING TROUBLE
MAKING THE   TRACE GALLAGHER HAS THAT
FROM OUR WEST COAST
NEWSROOM.
>> AFTER THREE HOURS OF
DELIBERATIONS THE JURY TOLD
THE JUDGE THEY WERE
DEADLOCKED.
THEY COULD NOT COME TO A
UNANIMOUS DECISION.
THE JUDGE SENT THEM BACK TO
DELIBERATE AGAIN.
NOW THEY HAVE BEEN BACK AT
IT FOUR FOUR AND A HALF
HOURS.
WE HAVE HEARD NOTHING.
NOW, IF THEY CANNOT COME TO
A DECISION, THERE ARE TWO
CHOICES.
ONE, THEY CAN EITHER
IMPANEL A BRAND NEW JURY
AND START THE PENALTY PHASE
ALL OVER AGAIN OR TWO THE
COUNTY ATTORNEY CAN TAKE
DEATH OFF THE TABLE AND
AGREE TO LIFE IN PRISON.
FOX NEWS ASKED JODI ARIAS
HOW SHE FEELS ABOUT THE
POSSIBILITY OF A DEATH
SENTENCE.
LISTEN.
>> I'M AS PREPARED AS I CAN
BE, I GUESS HE, IN A
SITUATION LIKE THIS.
I'M NOT ANTICIPATING IT OR
EXPECTING IT.
BUT IF IT COMES THEN THAT'S
A BRIDGE I WILL JUST HAVE
TO CROSS.
SO, IF IT HAPPENS, I'M
GOING TO FEEL REALLY BAD
FOR WHAT I HAVE DONE TO MY
FAMILY.
>> Trace: DID NOT ASK THE
JURY FOR THE DEATH PENALTY
IS BECAUSE THAT IS ASSISTED
SUICIDE AND THAT WOULD
CAUSE HER FAMILY GREAT PAIN
AND THEY HAVE BEEN THROUGH
ENOUGH.
SHE SAYS IF SHE GETS LIFE
SHE WILL TEACH INMATES
SPANISH AND SIGN LANGUAGE
AND POSSIBLY HAVE A BOOK
CLUB.
IF SHE GETS LIFE, THERE IS
NO POSSIBILITY OF PAROLE
BUT APPARENTLY SOMEONE
FORGOT TO TELL THAT TO JODI
ARIAS.
LISTEN.
>> IF I GET LIFE I DESERVE
TO HAVE A SECOND SHOT AT
FREEDOM SOME DAY BECAUSE I
KNOW I WOULD BE VERY
RESPONSIBLE WITH IT.
HOWEVER, AND I CAN'T
PREDICT THE FUTURE, BUT
BASED ON SOME OF THE
RULINGS THAT HAVE BEEN MADE
PREVIOUSLY, CAN I SEE THE
JUDGE LEANING TOWARD
NATURAL LIFE AS OPPOSED TO
GIVING ME ANY SHOT OF A
CHANCE LATER.
>> THEN JODI ARIAS TOLD
REPORTERS WHAT SHE NEVER
TOLD THE FAMILY OF TRAVIS
ALEXANDER.
LISTEN.
>> CAN I NEVER MAKE UP FOR
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> DO YOU WANT TO SAY I'M
SORRY RIGHT NOW TO TRAVIS
ALEXANDER'S FAMILY?
>> CERTAINLY I'M
DEFINITELY SORRY.
>> THE JURY SHEP SHOULD
BE DONE FOR THE DAY IN
ABOUT 10 OR 15 MINUTES.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE
GALLAGHER, THANK YOU SIR.
BACK HERE IN OKLAHOMA WE
ARE GETTING NEW ACCESS TO
ONE OF THE MOST DEVASTATING
NEIGHBORHOODS.
CASEY STEGALL IS DRIVING
LIVE IN ONE OF THOSE NOW
HARDLY RECOGNIZABLE STREETS
AS POLICE LET JOURNALISTS
IN FOR THE FIRST TIME.
THAT'S COMING UP LIVE AND
ON THE ROAD FROM AMERICA'S
HEARTLAND.
♪ ♪  [ engine revs ]  ♪ ♪    [ Male
Announcer ]    JUST WHEN YOU THOUGHT
YOU HAD EXPERIENCED    PERFORMANCE
A NEW RIDE COMES ALONG    AND CHANGES
EVERYTHING.  ♪ ♪    THE 2013 LEXUS
GS    WITH A DYNAMICALLY TUNED
SUSPENSION    AND ADJUSTABLE DRIVE
MODES.    BECAUSE THE ULTIMATE EXPRESSION
OF POWER IS CONTROL.    THIS IS THE
PURSUIT    OF PERFECTION.
WHERE IS FLO?  ANYBODY KNOW WHERE
FLO IS?  ARE YOU FLO?
YES.  IS THIS THE THING  YOU GAVE
MY HUSBAND?
WELL, YEAH, YES.  THE "NAME YOUR PRICE"
TOOL.
YOU TELL US THE PRICE  YOU WANT TO
PAY,
AND WE GIVE YOU A RANGE  OF OPTIONS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
CAREFUL, THOUGH -- THAT KIND  OF POWER
CAN GO TO YOUR HEAD.
THAT EXPLAINS  A LOT.
YO, BUDDY!
I GOT THIS.
GIMME ONE, GIMME ONE  GIMME ONE!
THE POWER OF    THE "NAME YOUR PRICE"
TOOL.
ONLY FROM PROGRESSIVE.
>> Shepard: AND ON THE
GROUND LOOK NOW OWE
INCREDIBLE CEFINGS OF
MONDAY'S TORNADO HERE IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
POLICE HAVE REJOINT
EXHIBITED MEDIA ACCESS TO
SOME OF THE HARDEST HIT
NEIGHBORHOODS SO GET IN
THERE TO CLEAN UP AND
RESTORING THE POWER.
THEY DID ALLOW OUR OWN
CASEY STEGALL INTO THE
DAMAGE ZONE.
HE HAS BEEN DRIVING AROUND
IN OUR QUICK RESPONSE
VEHICLE.
CASEY?
>> YEAH, SHEPARD GOOD
EVENING TO YOU.
HEATHER ELLAYNA IS WHERE WE
ARE.
NOT FAR FROM YOUR LOCATION
IN OUR QUICK RESPONSE
VEHICLE, A QRV.
WE ARE GOING TO NOW CUT TO
LIVE CAMERAS ON THE VERY
TRUCK THAT I'M RIDING IN.
THEY ARE ON THE RIGHT AND
LEFT.
FRANKLY, YOU CAN SET UP A
TRIPOD AND CAMERA AND YOU
CAN DO LIVE SHOTS BUT TO
REALLY CONVEY TO PEOPLE HOW
WIDESPREAD THE DAMAGE IS,
THIS TELLS THE STORY.
TO THE RIGHT, YOU CAN SEE
THERE ARE BASICALLY TARS ON
TOP OF CARS.
AND YOU SEE THE SPRAY
PAINTED X'S.
THOSE ORANGE X'S.
THOSE WERE THE VERY FIRST
MARKS THAT FAWNDERS MADE
MADE WHEN THEY GOT IN HERE.
THEY LOOKED INSIDE AND
MOVED ON.
M'S STOOD FOR MISSING.
THEY LATER COME BACK AND
UPDATED THAT WE WILL SWITCH
TO THE LEFT SIDE OF THE
VEHICLE.
AND YOU CAN SEE MATTRESSES,
BOARDS, ON TOP OF EACH
OTHER COMING UP ON THE
LEFT-HAND SIDE IS GOING TO
BE AN UPROOTED TREE.
THIS TREE THAT YOU SEE HAS
ALL OF ITS NEEDLES AND
LEAVES STILL ON IT AND AS
YOU HAVE SEEN, SHEPARD THE
WINDS SO POWERFUL IT CAN
STRIP THE BARK RIGHT OFF OF
TREES.
LET'S GO AHEAD NOW AND
SWITCH BACK TO THE RIGHT
JEREMY IF WE CAN AND CAN
YOU SEE THAT THE DAMAGE IS
EXTREMELY RANDOM.
YOU HAVE SOME HOMES THAT
JUST MAY HAVE SOME SHINGLES
MISSING FROM THEM AND RIGHT
NEXT DOOR YOU HAVE TOTAL
DESTRUCTION.
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING
COMING UP ON THE RIGHTS
HERE.
THIS GARAGE COMPLETELY
STANDING BUT YOU CAN SEE
THAT THE HOME AND ALL OF
THE DEBRIS IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE HOME IS JUST ALL STREWN
ABOUT.
LET'S GO AGAIN TO THE LEFT
AND SEE IF WE CAN GET THESE
PEOPLE BECAUSE THESE AREAS
ARE RESTRICTED FOR OBVIOUS
REASONS BECAUSE THEY HAVE
TO LET THE PEOPLE WHO LIVE
HERE COME AND GET TO THEIR
HOMES, GET TO THEIR
BELONGINGS AND TRY TO
SALVAGE WHAT THEY CAN.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAVE SEEN
TODAY.
PEOPLE STANDING ON PILES OF
RUBBLE.
SAT WITH THEIR FAMILIES AND
NOW THEY FIND THEMSELVES
STANDING ON MERE SPLINTERED
BOARDS AND MATTRESSES AND
ELECTRICAL WIRES AND JUST
HEART BREAK IS WHAT IT IS.
AND SHEPARD BACK OUT HERE
LIFE TO US IN THE CAR, YOU
KNOW, THIS IS ONE THING
THAT WE ARE SEEING.
THE RESOLVE OF THESE
PEOPLE.
THEY SAY THAT THEY REBUILT
IN 1999.
YOU CAN TALK TO ME PEOPLE
WHEN THEY ARE ON TOP OF
THEIR-WHAT WAS THEIR HOME
AND THEY ARE IN GOOD
SPIRITS FOR THE MOST PART.
DESPITE EVERYTHING.
IT'S ABSOLUTELY ASTONISHING
THE RESOLVE.
AND THEY SAY WE HAVE
REBUILT BEFORE AND WE'RE
GOING TO DO IT AGAIN.
>> Shepard: CASEY STEGALL
ON THE ROAD NEARBY.
CASEY THANKS.
MUCH MORE TO COME FROM
OKLAHOMA.
JONATHAN HUNT OUR CHIEF
FOX REPORT CORRESPONDENT
WILL TALK TO A TEACHER WHO
RODE OUT THE STORM WITH HER
STUDENTS IN ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
THEIR STORY IS QUITE
SOMETHING.
ALSO DRONING AMERICANS.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT NOW AND
FOR THE FIRST TIME ADMITS
MULTIPLE U.S. CITIZENS HAVE
DIED IN COUNTER TERRORISM
OPERATIONS OVERSEAS.
THEY HAVE BEEN DRONED TO
DEATH.
ONLY ONE OF THOSE AMERICANS
WAS EVEN THE TARGET OF THAT
STRIKE.
THAT'S COMING UP AS FOX
REPORTS LIVE FROM THE
DISASTER ZONE IN OKLAHOMA.
>> Shepard: I'M SHEPARD
SMITH.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR
TIME FOR THE TOP OF THE
NEWS FROM MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
OFFICIALS HAVE JUST
ANNOUNCED THEY HAVE NOW
FOUND SIX PEOPLE WHO WERE
STILL MISSING AFTER
MONDAY'S KILLER TORNADO.
THEY SAY THEY BELIEVE THEY
HAVE NOW FOUND ALL OF THE
SURVIVORS.
THEY ARE GOING TO CONTINUE
THE SEARCH JUST IN CASE
THERE IS SOMEONE NOT ON
THEIR LIST.
AS IT STANDS NOW 24 PEOPLE
HAVE DIED IN THIS DISASTER.
10 OF THEM CHILDREN.
MANY KILLED IN THE
DESTRUCTION OF PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY.
THE SCENE THERE VERY
SIMILAR TO THAT OF ANOTHER
SCHOOL IN TOWN.
BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY WHERE
THE TORNADO HIT LIKE A
BOMB.
THE CHILDREN INSIDE HUDDLED
WITH THEIR TEACHES A THE
STORY GOES AND THE SCHOOL
CRASHED TO THE GROUND
AROUND THEM.
CARS FLEW INTO THE
CLASSROOMS.
YET, EVERY SINGLE TEACHER
AND STUDENT AND
ADMINISTRATOR MANAGED TO
GET OUT OF THEIR ALIVE.
TONIGHT WE ARE HEARING THE
INCREDIBLE STORIES OF
SURVIVE.
CHIEF FOX REPORT
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN HUNT
IS LIVE WITH US ON THAT.
WHAT AN IMPRESSIVE BUNCH.
>> EXTRAORDINARY.
WE HEARD SO MANY
INSPIRATIONAL STORIES OVER
THE PAST COUPLE OF DAYS BUT
FEW TO ME HAVE BEEN AS
INSPIRING AS THAT OF
THERESA MOSIER.
SHE IS A FOURTH GRADE
TEACHER AT BRIAR WOOD
ELEMENTARY.
WHEN THE TORNADO WARNINGS
CAME, IN SEVERAL OF THE
PARENTS OF HER CHILDREN
RUSHED TO THAT SCHOOL, GOT
THEIR KIDS, TOOK THEM AWAY.
BUT WHEN THE TORNADO HIT
SHE STILL HAD 10 CHILDREN
THERE.
THEIR LIVES IN HER HANDS.
HERE IS THERESA MOSIER.
>> YOU TAKE THE CHILDREN UP
AGAINST THE INSIDE WALL.
YOU HAVE THEM GET DOWN ON
THEIR KNEES.
PUT THEIR HANDS OVER THEIR
HEAD AND PUT THEIR HEADS
YOU KNOW, DOWN.
AND THEN AS WE HEARD IT
APPROACHING, BECAUSE YOU
COULD HEAR IT IT WAS LIKE
10 FREIGHT TRAINS.
AND AS IT APPROACHED, YOU
KNOW, I JUST PUT MY ARMS
OVER THE CHILDREN.
I TOLD THEM EVERYTHING IS
GOING TO BE OKAY.
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN, YOU
KNOW BECAUSE YOU ARE SO
CONCERNED ABOUT THEIR
SAFETY.
THERE IS NOT A ONE OF US IN
THAT BUILDING THAT WOULD
NOT HAVE LAID DOWN OUR
LIVES FOR THOSE KIDS.
AND THEY WERE SCARED.
THEY ARE CRYING THEY ARE
UPSET.
BUT THOSE ARE THE BRAVEST
LITTLE CHILDREN IN THE
WORLD.
>> I THINK THEY WOULD SAY
YOU ARE THE BRAVEST TEACHER
IN THE WORLD.
WELL, WHEN IT HAD HAD
PASSED OVER THROUGH THEIR
TEARS, THROUGH EVERYTHING,
THEY GOT UP THEY HELPED
TAKE CINDER BLOCKS OFF
THEIR CLASSMATES' LEGS.
THEY HELPED TO UNWIND WIRES
AND METAL THAT HAD WRAPPED
AROUND ANOTHER STUDENT'S
LEGS.
EVEN IN THAT THEY STILL
KNEW TO HELP THEIR
CO-WORKERS AND SO I'M SO
PROUD OF THEM.
I'M SO PROUD TO BE THEIR
TEACHER BECAUSE THEY ARE
REMARKABLE AND RESILIENT
CHILDREN.
>> THERE IS A LOT OF
FAMILIES THANKING YOU FOR
KEEPING THEIR CHILDREN
ALIVE TODAY.
>> WELL, THERE WASN'T AN
OPTION.
THAT'S NOT AN OPTION NOT TO
KEEP THEM ALIVE.
I HAVE CHILDREN OF MY OWN.
AND I KNOW THAT ANY TEACHER
IN THE DISTRICT WOULD HAVE
DONE THE SAME EXACT THING.
AND I JUST WANTED TO MAKE
SURE THOSE CHILDREN SAW
THEIR PARENTS AGAIN.
AND THEIR PARENTS SAW THEM.
>> SHE CALLED THOSE FOURTH
GRADERS BRAVE AND
REMARKABLE.
SHEP.
I'M NOT SURE I HAVE MET
ANYBODY AS BRAVE OR AS
REMARKABLE AS THERESA
MOSIER HERSELF.
EXTRAORDINARY WOMAN.
>> Shepard: VERY
IMPRESSIVE.
JONATHAN, THANKS FOR HER
STORY.
WELL, FOR THE FIRST TIME
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT IS NOW
CONFIRMING FOUR AMERICAN
CITIZENS HAVE BEEN KILLED
IN WHAT IT CALLS SENSITIVE
COUNTER TERRORISM
OPERATIONS.
WHAT DOES THAT MEAN?
IT MEANS THE GOVERNMENT
DRONED THEM.
THE FEDS ARE ALSO ADMITTING
THAT THEY MEANT TO KILL
ONLY ONE OF THOSE
AMERICANS.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS
PRESIDENT OBAMA WANTED TO
RELEASE THE LIST BEFORE HE
GIVES A SPEECH ON NATIONAL
SECURITY.
THAT'S SET FOR TOMORROW.
JENNIFER GRIFFIN IS AT THE
PENTAGON FOR US TONIGHT.
WHO ARE THESE FOUR
AMERICANS WHOM OUR
GOVERNMENT KILLED?
>> WELL, IT'S INTERESTING
SHEPARD.
IN HIS LETTER TO CONGRESS
ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC
HOLDER DID NOT ACTUALLY USE
THE WORD DRONE OR UNMANNED
AERIAL VEHICLE AS SOME NEWS
REPORTS HAVE SUGGESTED.
BUT INSTEAD, AS YOU
MENTIONED, HE USED THE
PHRASE SENSITIVE COUNTER
TERRORISM OPERATIONS TO
DESCRIBE HOW THESE FOUR
AMERICANS WERE KILLED.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS ADMITTED
THAT IT WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR
KILLING THESE AMERICANS.
WHO WERE THEY?
WHO WERE THESE AMERICANS?
ANWAR AL-AWLAKI WAS ONE OF
THEM.
HE INTENDED TO BRING DOWN A
U.S. PLANE WITH THE
UNDERWEAR BOMBER.
YOU'LL REMEMBER THAT AL
AWLAKI'S 16-YEAR-OLD SON
WAS ALSO KILLED.
IRAQMAN.
THEN THERE WAS SAMIR KHAN.
THE EDITOR OF INSPIRE
MAGAZINE AND -- NORTH
KOREAN WHO LEFT FOR
PAKISTAN IN 2008 AND
INDICTED FOR A PLOT TO BLOW
UP BRIDGES AND TUNNELS IN
THE UNITED STATES.
HOLDER SAYS ONLY AL AWLAKI,
ANWAR AL-AWLAKI WAS
TARGETED DIRECTLY, SHEPARD.
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S MY
UNDERSTANDING JENNIFER
THAT THE PRESIDENT IS
EXPECTED TO MAKE SOME VERY
BIG NEWS ON GUANTANAMO BAY
HIS SPEECH TOMORROW.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IN FACT THE PRESIDENT
DURING HIS SPEECH TOMORROW
PLANS TO ANNOUNCE WE KNOW
ACCORDING TO SOURCES, PLANS
TO ANNOUNCE THAT HE IS
LIFTING RESTRICTIONS ON THE
TRANSFER OF DETAINEES FROM
GUANTANAMO BAY TO YEMEN.
THAT PROCESS HAD BEEN
FROZEN.
THE TRANSFER OF THOSE
DETAI YEMEN HAD BEEN
FROZEN FOR SOME TIME.
THE RENEWED COOPERATION
WITH YEMEN IS LIKELY TO
DECREASE THE GITMO DETAINEE
POPULATION WE'RE TOLD WHICH
CURRENTLY STANDS AT 166
PRISONERS.
103 OF THOSE PRISONERS ARE
CURRENTLY ON HUNGER STRIKE.
THEY ARE BEING FORCE FED
FOR THE PAST 100 DAYS.
THE PRESIDENT, AS YOU WILL
REMEMBER, PROMISED TO CLOSE
GITMO WHEN HE TOOK OFFICE.
BUT HE HAS BEEN STYMIED IN
DOING SO SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: JENNIFER
GRIFFIN REPORTING FROM THE
PENTAGON TONIGHT WITH A
LITTLE DRAMA OVER ON
CAPITOL HILL TODAY WHEN A
TOP IRS OFFICIAL SHOWED UP
AT THE HEARING AND TOOK THE
FIFTH.
ONE REPUBLICAN THOUGH SAID
NOT SO FAST.
LOIS LERNER IS THE HEAD OF
THE AGENCY'S TAX EXEMPT
DIVISION.
SHE HAS APOLOGIZED FOR
STAFFERS TARGETING
CONSERVATIVE GROUPS THAT
APPLIED FOR TAX EXEMPT
STATUS.
TODAY SHE REFUSED TO ANSWER
ANY QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
SCANDAL.
BUT ONE REPUBLICAN SAYS
LERNER TRIED TO HAVE IT
BOTH WAYS.
BY ALSO PLEADING HER CASE
IN AN OPENING STATEMENT.
>> I HAVE NOT DONE ANYTHING
WRONG.
I HAVE NOT BROKEN ANY LAWS.
I HAVE DECIDED TO FOLLOW MY
COUNSEL'S ADVICE AND NOT
TESTIFY OR ANSWER ANY OF
THE QUESTIONS TODAY.
>> SHE JUST TESTIFIED.
SHE JUST WAIVED HER FIFTH
AMENDMENT RIGHT TO
PRIVILEGE.
YOU DON'T GET TO TELL YOUR
SIDE OF THE STORY AND THEN
NOT BE SUBJECTED TO
CROSS-EXAMINATION.
>> THE GENTLE LADY WHO HAS
DEPARTED WAS ENTITLED TO
ASSERT HER FIFTH AMENDMENT
ALTHOUGH THERE ARE SOME
QUESTIONS HOW IT WAS DONE
IT THERE COULD BE NO
QUESTION THAT WE HAVE TO
RESPECT IT.
>> WELL, THAT'S CHAIRMAN
DARRELL ISSA.
HE SAYS THE COMMITTEE WILL
CALL LERNER BACK TO TESTIFY
IF THE LAWYERS DECIDE SHE
DID BREAK ANY RULES.
DOUG McKELWAY IS ON THIS
FROM WASHINGTON TONIGHT.
DOUG?
>> SHEP, WHEN SOMEBODY
CLAIMS THE FIFTH THEY
USUALLY DO SOUGHT WITHOUT
EQUIVOCATION.
THEY STATE IT, AND THEN
THEY SHUT UP.
NOT SO LOIS LERNER.
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN TREY
GOWDY HIMSELF A FORMER
PROSECUTOR JUMPED ON IT AS
YOU JUST SAW.
IT WASN'T JUST REPUBLICANS
TODAY FIRING SHOTS AT THE
IRS.
THE COMMITTEE'S TOP
DEMOCRAT WENT AFTER FORMER
IRS COMMISSIONER DOUGLAS
SHULMAN FOR SAYING BACK IN
MARCH OF 2012 THAT THERE
WAS ABSOLUTELY NO TARGETING
TAKING PLACE.
AND THEN NOT CORRECTING THE
RECORD.
>> AT THE TIME I LEARNED
ABOUT THIS LIST I FELT I
WAS TAKING THE APPROPRIATE
ACTIONS AND THAT MY COURSE
WAS THE PROPER ONE AND I
STILL FEEL THAT WAY TODAY.
>> I'M SORRY THAT'S SIMPLY
NOT GOOD ENOUGH.
YOU PERSONALLY KNEW THERE
WAS A TARGET LIST.
>> THE COMMITTEE WANTS TO
KNOW HOW HIGH KNOWLEDGE OF
THE TARGETING WENT AND WHO
ORDERED IT.
SHULMAN ACKNOWLEDGED TO THE
COMMITTEE THAT HE VISITED
THE WHITE HOUSE 118 TIMES
DURING HIS TENURE AS
COMMISSIONER.
>> YOU ARE VERY AWARE OF
THE FACT THAT YOU ARE UNDER
OATH TODAY.
>> VERY AWARE OF THAT.
>> AND YOUR TESTIMONY TO
BE VERY CLEAR, IN RESPONSE
TO THIS MR. JORDAN'S
QUESTION IS THAT YOU HAVE
NEVER HAD ANY CONVERSATION
WITH RESPECT TO THIS
SUBJECT THE SUBJECT OF
THIS HEARING WITH ANYBODY
AT THE WHITE HOUSE THOUGH
YOU WERE AT THE WHITE HOUSE
118 TIMES?
>> YEAH, I MEAN JUST SO I'M
CLEAR I HAVE NO MEMORY,
WOULD HAVE BEEN
APPROPRIATE.
>> AFTER 118 VISITS.
CHAIRMAN ISSA PRODUCED A
STRING OF EMAILS TODAY
SHOWING BEFORE A
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION.
THE IG REREPEATEDLY FAILED
TO ALERT THE COMMITTEE TO
ITS ONGOING INVESTIGATION
AS REQUIRED BY LAW.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: DOUG McKELWAY
IN WASHINGTON.
DOUG, THANKS.
FOX NEWS HAS CONFIRMED
TONIGHT THAT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT HAS SEIZED
RECORDS ASSOCIATED WITH THE
CELL PHONE OF THE CHIEF
WASHINGTON CORRESPONDENT
FOR FOX NEWS JAMES ROSEN
AND HIS PARENTS' HOME PHONE
LINE ON STATEN ISLAND, NEW
YORK.
FOX NEWS ALSO CONFIRMS
THOSE RECORDS INCLUDED AREA
CODES AND EXCHANGES FOR
OTHER NUMBERS THAT MATCHED
THE PHONE LINES FOR FOX
NEWS WORK SPACES AT THE
WHITE HOUSE, THE STATE
DEPARTMENT AND AT THE
PENTAGON.
THE FINAL FOUR NUMBERS OF
MANY OF THOSE PHONE LINES
WERE REDACTED MAKING IT
IMPOSSIBLE TO KNOW EXACTLY
HOT JUSTICE DEPARTMENT WAS
TRACKING IN EACH OF THOSE
CASES.
NOW, REMEMBER THE
GOVERNMENT ORIGINALLY
OBTAINED A SEARCH WARRANT
GIVING INVESTIGATORS ACCESS
TO JAMES ROSEN'S PERSONAL
EMAIL G MAIL ACCOUNT AFTER
AN FBI AGENT JAMES ROSEN
MAY HAVE COMMITTED A CRIME.
THE CHIEF JUDGE OF THE
FEDERAL DISTRICT COURT IN
WASHINGTON TODAY
ACKNOWLEDGED THE DOCUMENTS
IN THE JAMES ROSEN CASE
WERE KEPT UNDER SEAL FOR 18
MONTHS LONGER THAN THEY
SHOULD HAVE BEEN.
THAT JUDGE APOLOGIZED.
AND NOW SAYS A REVIEW IS
UNDERWAY.
THE BOSTON BOMBING
INVESTIGATION TOOK A
SURPRISING TURN TODAY WHEN
A MAN WHO APPARENTLY KNEW
ONE OF THE TERRORIST
SUSPECTS WAS ABOUT TO
CONFESS TO A DIFFERENT
MURDER.
UNTIL THINGS GOT VIOLENT.
NOW THAT MAN IS DEAD.
AND THAT STORY IS COMING UP
FROM THE JOURNALISTS OF FOX
NEWS LIVE FROM MOORE.
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE TO SEVERE  RHEUMATOID
ARTHRITIS, LIKE ME,  AND YOU'RE TALKING
TO  YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST
ABOUT TRYING OR  ADDING A BIOLOGIC.
THIS IS HUMIRA, ADALIMUMAB.
THIS IS HUMIRA WORKING  TO HELP RELIEVE
MY PAIN.
THIS IS HUMIRA HELPING ME  THROUGH
THE TWISTS AND TURNS.
THIS IS HUMIRA HELPING  TO PROTECT
MY JOINTS
FROM FURTHER DAMAGE.
DOCTORS HAVE BEEN PRESCRIBING  HUMIRA
FOR OVER TEN YEARS.
HUMIRA WORKS BY TARGETING  AND HELPING
TO BLOCK
A SPECIFIC SOURCE  OF INFLAMMATION
THAT CONTRIBUTES TO RA SYMPTOMS.
FOR MANY ADULTS, HUMIRA IS  PROVEN
TO HELP RELIEVE PAIN
AND STOP FURTHER JOINT DAMAGE.
HUMIRA CAN LOWER YOUR ABILITY  TO
FIGHT INFECTIONS,
INCLUDING TUBERCULOSIS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS,
SUCH AS INFECTIONS, LYMPHOMA  OR OTHER
TYPES OF CANCER
HAVE HAPPENED.
BLOOD, LIVER AND  NERVOUS SYSTEM PROBLEMS,
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
AND NEW OR WORSENING  HEART FAILURE
HAVE OCCURD.
BEFORE STARTING HUMIRA , YOUR  DOCTOR
SHOULD TEST YOU FOR TB.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU LIVE  IN OR
HAVE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL  INFECTIONS ARE
COMMON.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU  HAVE HAD
TB, HEPATITIS B
ARE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,  OR HAVE
SYMPTOMS SUCH AS FEVER
FATIGUE, COUGH, OR SORES.
YOU SHOULD NOT START HUMIRA IF  YOU
HAVE ANY KIND OF INFECTION.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF  HUMIRA CAN WORK
FOR YOU.
THIS IS HUMIRA AT WORK.
You thought this beach couldn't  get
any more tempting...
... you thought  wrong.
Get up to 50% off  Memorial Day hotels.
Final Days.
Book now with Travelocity.
WITH THE Spark Cash Card  FROM Capital
One...  BORIS EARNS UNLIMITED REWARDS
FOR HIS SMALL BUSINESS.  CAN I GET
THE SMITH CONTRACT  EASE?  THANK YOU.
THAT'S  THREE NEW PAPER SHREDDERS.
[ Boris ]  PUT 'EM ON MY Spark Card.
[ Garth ] BORIS' SMALL BUSINESS  EARNS
2% CASH BACK  ON EVERY PCHASE EVERY
DAY.  GREAT BUSINESSES  DESERVE UNLIMITED
REWARDS.  READ BACK THE CHICKEN'S
TESTIMONY, PLEASE.  "BUK, BUK, BUKKA!"
[ Male Announcer ]    GET THE Spark
Business Card    FROM Capital One
AND EARN UNLIMITED REWARDS.    CHOOSE
2% CASH BACK    OR DOUBLE MILES
ON EVERY PURCHASE EVERY DAY.  TOLD
YOU I'D GET HALF.  WHAT'S IN  YOUR
WALLE
>> Shepard: MYSTERIOUS
DEVELOPMENTS INTO THE
BOSTON MARATHON TERROR
ATTACK.
THE FBI NOW REPORTS A YOUNG
MAN WITH POSSIBLE TIES TO
THE BOMB SOMETHING NOW
DEAD.
AND OUR STATION IN BOSTON
FOX 25 IS REPORTING THAT
THE YOUNG MAN WAS ABOUT TO
CONFESS TO A DIFFERENT
STRING OF MURDERS.
HERE IS WHAT WE KNOW.
BE A FBI SPOKESMAN SAYS
THAT ONE SPECIAL AGENT, TWO
MASSACHUSETTS STATE POLICE
TROOPERS AND OTHER LAW
ENFORCEMENT WERE
QUESTIONING THIS MAN IN
ORLANDO EARLY THIS MORNING
IN CONNECTION WITH THE
BOSTON ATTACK.
THE SPOKESMAN SAYS THAT
YOUNG MAN GOT INTO A
VIOLENT CONFRONTATION WITH
THOSE AUTHORITIES AND THAT
IT ESCALATED INTO A
SHOOTOUT THAT KILLED THE
YOUNG MAN AND WOUNDED THE
SPECIAL AGENT.
NOW A FRIEND SAYS THAT
ORLANDO MAN KNEW THE NOW
DEAD BOSTON SUSPECT
TAMERLAN TSARNAEV YOU MAY
HAVE HEARD ABOUT THIS
BECAUSE BOTH OF THEM WERE
MIXED MARSHALL ARTS
FIGHTERS FROM THE CHECHNYA.
THE ATTACK IN BOSTON OF
COURSE KILLED 10 PEOPLE AND
INJURED 250 OTHERS.
HE HAD A VIOLENT HISTORY,
PHIL.
>> SHEP, HE CERTAINLY LIKED
TO USE HIS FISTS ARRESTED
IN BOTH BOSTON AND ORLANDO
FOR VICIOUS ASSAULTS FOR
BEATING UP STRANGERS.
A FLORIDA FRIEND OF THE
SUSPECT SHOT OVERNIGHT SAYS
THE FBI CAME DOWN TO
ORLANDO TO INTERVIEW
EASTBOUND EBRA HAM.
THE RUSSIAN NATIONAL HAD
BECOME VERY AFRAID.
>> WHEN THE BOMBING
HAPPENED, HE ACTUALLY CAME
TO ME THE NEXT DAY AND SAY
I CAN'T BELIEVE IT.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THEY DID IT
YOU KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
THE FBI STARTED FOLLOWING
HIM.
STARTED ASKING HIM
QUESTIONS WHY YOU GUYS WHAT
KIND OF CONNECTION DO YOU
HAVE WITH THEM, DO YOU KNOW
WHAT I MEAN?
TRYING TO MAKE A CONNECTION
BETWEEN THEM YOU KNOW WHAT
I MEAN?
THERE IS NO CONNECTION.
>> ACCORDING TO FOX'S
BOSTON STATION LAST NIGHT'S
INTERROGATION FOCUSED ON
UNSOLVED GRIZZLY TRIPLE
MURDER IN MASSACHUSETTS.
ALL THREE VICTIMS THERE HAD
THEIR THROATS SLASHED.
POLICE SAY ONE OF THOSE
VICTIMS IS A FRIEND OF
TAMERLAN TSARNAEV.
ACCORDING TO FOX 25 BOSTON
HE HAD BASICALLY CONFESSED
TO THOSE MURDERS LAST
NIGHT.
WAS ABOUT TO SIGN A
STATEMENT BUT THEN SUDDENLY
LUNGED OUT WITH A KNIFE AND
WAS SHOT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: PHIL KEATING IN
FLORIDA TONIGHT.
FINALLY GETTING TO THE
POINT OF THIS ONE.
THANK YOU.
THERE IS YET ANOTHER CASE
OF SOMEONE IN THE MILITARY
FACING CHARGES OF
MISTREATING WOMEN.
THIS TIME A SERGEANT FIRST
CLASS AT WEST POINT,
AMERICA'S OLDEST AND MOST
PRESTIGIOUS MILITARY
ACADEMY.
HE STANDS ACCUSED OF MAKING
SECRET VIDEO RECORDINGS OF
CADETS WHILE THEY SHOWERED.
ALERTING A DOZEN WOMEN THAT
THE SERGEANT MAY HAVE
VIOLATED THEIR PRIVACY.
THIS AS LAWMAKERS AND THE
'PRESIDENT DEMAND THE
MILITARY DO MORE TO STOP
SEXUAL ASSAULTS AND
HARASSMENT AFTER A SERIES
OF RECENT CASES.
DOCUMENTS SHOW THE WEST
POINT SERGEANT WAS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THE HEALTH,
WELFARE AND DISCIPLINE OF A
COMPANY OF 125 CADETS.
THERE IS A NEW FRÑ.
FOR IT.
BUT CONSUMER PRIVACY
ADVOCATES ARE WARNING ABOUT
THE DOWN SIDES HERE.
THE FOX BUSINESS NETWORK
GERRI WILLIS LIVE IN NEW
YORK.
WHAT ARE THE PROS AND CONS
HERE GERRI I'M A BIT
CONFUSED.
>> PROS ARE OBVIOUS.
GET DISCOUNTS FOR SERVICES
AND GOODS YOU MIGHT REALLY
WANT TO BUY.
THE DOWNSIDE IS YOU HAVE NO
CONTROL OVER THIS
INFORMATION.
YOU DON'T KNOW WHERE IT IS
GOING.
AND IT'S VERY PRIVATE.
BE THE RESULTS OF YOUR
MEDICAL EXAMS.
YOUR PRESCRIPTION HISTORY.
SOME ARE EVEN COLLECTING IF
YOU HAVE A DANGEROUS HOBBY.
THAT INFORMATION COULD GO
TO YOUR INSURER.
COULD GO TO YOUR EMPLOYER
OR WHAT IF YOU'RE
UNEMPLOYED LOOKING FOR A
JOB A POTENTIAL EMPLOYER.
THE IMPACT FOR CONSUMERS
ARE BIG, SHEP RECOVERING
IT ON OUR SHOW ON FOX NEWS
SISTER NETWORK FOX BUSINESS
ALL THIS WEEK.
TOMORROW WE ARE GOING TO BE
TALKING ABOUT YOUR PRIVACY
ON THE CLOUD.
WHAT HAPPENS THERE.
WE'LL BE COVERING TALL.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: PRIVACY ON THE
CLOUD.
I HAVE ALWAYS WONDERED
ABOUT THAT GERRI WILLIS
EACH NIGHT 6 CENTRAL 5
EASTERN ON FOX BUSINESS
NETWORK.
MORE DEVASTATION MOORE
OKLAHOMA.
ONE WOMAN INSIDE A MEDICAL
FACILITY WITH NEARLY A
DOZEN PATIENTS WHEN THE
WALLS CAME CRASHING DOWN
AROUND THEM.
HOW THEY ESCAPED NEXT.
Why are twice as many people  choosing
Verizon  over any other carrier?
Many choose us because we have  the
largest 4GLTE network.
Others, because of our  reputation
for reliability.
Or maybe it's because  we've received
JD Power
and Associates' customer service
award 4X in a row.
In the end  there are countless reasons.
But one choi.
>> BACK LIFE IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA TONIGHT LEARNING
MORE ABOUT THE 24 PEOPLE
THE MASSIVE TORNADO KILLED
MONDAY IN THIS COMMUNITY
AND NEXT DOOR IN THE TOWN
OF NEW CASTLE.
THE OKLAHOMA STATE MEDICAL
EXAMINER SAYS 10 OF THE
VICTIMS WERE CHILDREN.
TWO OF THEM INFANTS.
MANY MORE PEOPLE SURVIVED A
TWISTER BUT SUFFERED MANY
INJURIES.
NO PRECISE COUNTY DATE.
HOSPITALS REPORT THEY ARE
200 PEOPLE.
DOZEN BEES OF THEM
CHILDREN.
MANY PATIENTS ARE STILL IN
SEVERAL AREA HOSPITALS.
PEOPLE SURVIVED THE
TORNADO, TURNS OUT A
MEDICAL FACILITY TURNING A
MEDICAL FACILITY INTO
ABSOLUTE RUBBLE TRAPPING 14
PEOPLE INSIDE.
JOHN ROBERTS WITH THIS HERE
LIVE TONIGHT IN MOORE,
JOHN?
>> YOU KNOW, WE HAVE HEARD
MANY TIMES OVER THE PAST
COUPLE OF DAYS SHEP, POWER
OF MANY ATOMIC BOMBS AND
BEHIND ME IS A CLEAR
EXAMPLE OF THIS.
THIS WAS THE OKLAHOMA HEART
INSTITUTE.
YOU CAN SEE CONCRETE
GERDERS ON TOP OF THIS
BUILDING.
THEY WEREN'T PART OF THAT
STRUCTURE.
THOSE WERE BLOWN FROM THE
TORNADO 300 YARDS FROM THE
TOP OF THAT HOSPITAL.
TAKE A LOOK AT THESE
PICTURES OF THE RUBBLE.
THERE ARE ABOUT 10 ELDERLY
PATIENTS INSIDE AT THE
TIME.
WHEN THEY HEARD THE
WARNINGS THAT THE TORNADO
WAS COMING AND THEY STARTED
TO FEEL THE VIBRATION.
THEY DUCKED DOWN UNDER
DESKS.
WHEN THE WINDS BLEW OUT THE
WALLS AND THOSE GERDERS
CAME DOWN AND COLLAPSED THE
ROOF.
THE WHOLE HEART INSTITUTE
COLLAPSED LIKE IT WAS A PAN
PANCAKE.
ALMOST LIKE HIT BY
EARTHQUAKE.
SANDY JONES IS THE CLINIC
DIRECTOR THERE.
>> I HAD THIS MUCH ROOM.
THEY CRAWLED OUT.
THEY WERE FURTHER DOWN THAN
I WAS.
PINNED UP AGAINST THE WALL
WITH ONE OF THOSE BRING
PILLARS.
THEY CRAWLED OUT FROM UNDER
THE TABLE I COUNTED THEM AS
THEY CAME OUT.
EVERYBODY HAD TO GET OUT.
>> SANDY TOLD US SHE
ACTUALLY HAD TO BE DRAGGED
OUT BY HER FEET BY
PARAMEDICS.
REMARKABLY, SHEP, ALL OF
THE INJURIES FROM THIS WERE
MINOR.
IT'S ALMOST DIFFICULT TO
BELIEVE.
SANDY HERSELF, THE ONLY
INJURY SHE HAD WAS A BRUISE
TO THE INSIDE OF HER ARM.
IT'S AMAZING, SHEM, THAT
ANYBODY COULD HAVE SURVIVED
THAT LET ALONE COME OUT
LITERALLY WITHOUT A
SCRATCH.
>> IT REALLY IS JOHN
ROBERTS LIVE WITH US
TONIGHT.
JOHN THANKS.
MONDAY'S TWIST ERR NOT ONLY
WIPED AWAY HOMES AND
SCHOOLS BUT MANY
BUSINESSES.
TWO DAYS LATER ONE OWNER OF
ONE OF THOSE BUSINESSES
SAYS IS HE ALREADY GETTING
READY TO REOPEN.
HIS STORY AHEAD AS FOX
REPORTS LIVE IN THE
HEARTLAND.
[ Woman ] FOR DAVID AND KELLY  A PLAYFUL
THOUGHT...  HOW LONG BEFORE HE GOES
TO COLLEGE?  [ Woman ]  ...BECAME
A REAL QUESTION.  ARE WE READY  TO
PAY FOR COLLEGE?  [ Woman ]  SO THEY
CAME TO SEE ME  AND WE TALKED ABOUT
WAYS TO MANAGE THEIR MONEY  AND SAVE
FOR COLLEGE  THAT FIT THEIR SITUATION.
SO WHEN LITTLE DAVID --  WELL, NOT-SO-LITTLE
DAVID  WAS READY TO GO TO COLLEGE,
HIS PARENTS WERE READY, TOO.  WE DID
IT.    [ Female Announcer ]    LET'S
TALK ABOUT SMARTER WAYS    TO MANAGE
AND SAVE YOUR MONEY.    WHEN PEOPLE
TALK,    GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.    WELLS
FARGO.    TOGETHER WE'LL GO FAR.
♪ BONJOUR ♪  ♪ JE T'ADORE ♪  ♪ C'EST
AUJOURD'HUI ♪  ♪ ♪  ♪ ET TOUJOURS
♪  ♪ ME AMOUR ♪  ♪ HOW ABOUT ME? ♪
[ Male Announcer ]    HERE'S TO A
LIFE LESS ROUTINE.  ♪ AND IT'S UN,
DEUX  TROIS, QUATRE ♪  ♪ GIVE ME SOME
MORE OF THAT ♪    [ Male Announcer
]    THE MORE CONNECTED, ATHLETIC
SEDUCTIVE LEXUS RX.  ♪ JE T'ADORE,
JE T'ADORE,  JE T'ADORE ♪  ♪ ♪  ♪
S'IL VOUS PLAIT ♪    [ Male Announcer
] THIS IS    THE PURSUIT OF PERFECTION.
ALL STATIONS COME OVER TO  MISSION
A FOR A FINAL GO.  THIS IS FOR REAL
THIS TIME.
STEP SEVEN POINT  TWO ONE TWO.
RIFY AND LOCK.
COMMAND IS LOCKED.
FIVE SECONDS.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
STANDING BY FOR CAPTURE.
THE MOST INNOVATIVE  SOFTWARE ON THE
PLANET...
DRAGON IS CAPTURED.
IS CONNECTING TODAY'S LEADING  COMPANIES
TO PLACES BEYOND IT.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
MINE WAS EARNED        IN DJIBOUTI
AFRICA. 2004.  VIETNAM IN 1972.
[ All ]            FORT BENNING, GEORGIA
IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]      USAA AUTO
INSURANCE     IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN
FROM GENERATION TO GENERATION.
BECAUSE IT OFFERS           A SUPERIOR
LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE MILITARY MEMBERS,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY,         GET AN
AUTO INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA. WE KNOW         WHAT IT MEANS
TO SERVE.
>> Shepard: FOX REPORT LIVE
TONIGHT.
MOORE, OKLAHOMA O, WHERE
ONE LOCAL BUSINESS THAT
COULD HELP PEOPLE GET AWAY
FROM ALL OF THIS
DEVASTATION WILL REOPEN
THIS WEEK.
THAT'S THE WORD TONIGHT
FROM THE OWNER OF THE LOCAL
WARREN MULTI-PLEX MOVIE
THEATER.
A LIVE LOOK AT THAT THEATER
WITH THE BILLBOARD UP "GOD
BLESS MOORE."
YOU CAN SEE THE SIGN THERE.
WE WATCHED YESTERDAY AS
THEY PUT IT UP.
AS CREWS WORKED ON THAT
THEATER EARLIER THIS WEEK
THERE WAS A MESSAGE ON THE
MARQUEE THAT READ PLEASE
PRAY.
THE BUILDING SUSTAINED UP
TO $1 MILLION IN DAMAGE BUT
THAT AS MANY AS 200 PEOPLE
WERE INSIDE DURING THAT
TORNADO AND NOT ONE SINGLE
ONE OF THEM GOT HURT.
FOR A WHILE, THE THEATER
REPORTEDLY SERVED AS A HUB
FOR VOLUNTEERS.
THE MOORE THEATER RIGHT
HERE IN THE HEART OF ALL OF
THE DESTRUCTION A PLACE
MAYBE WHERE FOLKS COULD GET
AWAY AND TAKE THEIR MINDS
OFF ALL OF THIS MESS EVEN
FOR JUST A FEW MINUTES.
SET TO REOPEN THIS WEEK.
UPDATING SOME OF FOX TOP
STORIES TONIGHT.
THE AFTERMATH OF THE
APPARENT TERROR ATTACK IN
LONDON.
WITNESSES SAY TWO MEN WITH
A BUTCHER KNIFE OR MULTIPLE
KNIVES KILLED A MAN, HACKED
HIM TO DEATH.
VIDEO CAPTURED ONE EVER THE
TERRORISTS RANTING HOLDING
ONE OF THE BLOODY KNIVES
BEFORE HE POLICE SHOT HIM.
THERE ARE NO SPECIFIC
THREATS THERE.
HERE IN MOORE OKLAHOMA,
OFFICIALS NOW SAY MONDAY'S
TORNADO MAY HAVE DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED AS MANY AS 13,000
HOMES.
24 PEOPLE NOW CONFIRMED
DEAD.
HUNDREDS MORE ARE HURT.
CREWS SAY THEY BELIEVE THEY
HAVE NOW ACCOUNTED FOR
EVERYBODY WHO IS MISSING
AFTER THAT TWISTER HIT.
AND PRESIDENT OBAMA SET TO
VISIT HERE THIS SUNDAY TO
MEET WITH SURVIVORS AND
FIRST RESPONDERS OR THAT'S
THE PLAN AS THE PRESIDENT
COMES TO THE HEARTLAND THIS
SUNDAY.
>> ON THIS DAY IN 1999, THE
PEOPLE OF MOORE, OKLAHOMA
HAD BEEN CLEANING UP FOR 19
DAYS.
FROM THE WORST TORNADO THAT
HAD EVER STRUCK THIS AREA.
19 DAYS LATER IT WAS AS IF
IT MIGHT NEVER END.
LOOK BELOW.
THERE WAS SO MUCH DEBRIS ON
THAT DAY THERE WAS SO MUCH
WORK TO BE DONE.
THEN IT SEEMED LIKE THEY
MIGHT NOT EVER BE ABLE TO
GET IT ACCOMPLISHED.
THEY HAD BEEN LOADING TRUCK
LOAD AFTER TRUCK LOAD BY
THE HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS
DAY AFTER DAY AFTER DAY.
AND THE PILES WERE STILL
OVERWHELMING.
IT WAS LIKE YOU GO TO THAT
RESTAURANT WHERE THE
PORTIONS ARE SO LARGE THAT
YOU EAT FOR 30 MINUTES AND
IT FEELS LIKE I HAVE
ACCOMPLISHED NOTHING.
IT'S MUCH THE SAME WAY
HERE.
1 DAYS INTO THIS.
THE CAMERAS WON'T BE AS
PREVALENT.
THE NOTICE WON'T BE AS
GREAT AND FRANKLY THEY WILL
JUST BE LEFT WITH A
HERCULEAN TASK OF FIGURING
OUT HOW TO GET THEIR LIVES
BACK TOGETHER.
THAT'S WHEN THEY WILL NEED
ALL OF US THE MOST IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
WHEN THEY WILL NEED OUR
MONEY AND OUR SUPPORT, OUR
PRAYERS AND OUR HELPING
HAND.
JUST AS JOPLIN, MISSOURI
DID, AS SOUTH MISSISSIPPI
DID, AND AS THE NORTHEAST
DID AFTER SUPER STORM
SANDY, THEY WILL NEED US
AND AS AMERICANS, WE WILL
BE THERE FOR THEM BECAUSE
THAT'S HOW WE ROLL.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
WE ARE ALL BACK TOMORROW
FOR "THE FOX REPORT" AND
"STUDIO B."
THE O'REILLY FACTOR BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>> Bill: THE O'REILLY
FACTOR IS ON.
TONIGHT:
>> I HAVE DECIDED TO FOLLOW
MY COUNSEL'S ADVICE AND NOT
TESTIFY OR ANSWER ANY OF
THE QUESTIONS TODAY.
>> Bill: THE IRS SCANDAL
GETTING BIGGER.
NOW SOME EXECUTIVES THERE
THINK THEY MAY BE IN
CRIMINAL TERRITORY.
ALSO, THE LINK BETWEEN THE
IRS AND THE WHITE HOUSE
GETTING STRONGER.
>> HOW MANY TIMES DID YOU
GO TO THE WHITE HOUSE?
>> Bill: WE'LL HAVE A FULL
REPORT ON EVERYTHING THAT
HAPPENED TODAY.
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID HE
WAS OUTRAGED LAST WEEK BY
THE IRS SCANDAL.
IS HE OUTRAGED THEN THAT
LOIS LERNER IS TAKING THE
FIFTH?
>> Bill: WHITE HOUSE
POUNDED OVER THE IRS
SCANDAL.
WE WILL SHOW YOU WHAT
HAPPENED TO JAY CARNEY.
>> I DON'T THINK OBAMA HAD
ANYTHING TO DO WITH IT YOU
KNOW, MAYBE HE DIDN'T.
SOMETIMES THINGS GO WRONG.
>>