JUST BACK FROM A YEAR OF
SERVICE AT GUANTANAMO BAY AND
SURPRISED HIS DAUGHTER.
100 MILITARY OFFICERS WERE
SENT HOME RECENTLY.
THAT'S ALL FOR TONIGHT.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP DOUBLING
DOWN AFTER A NEW WAVE OF NFL
PROTEST, CRITICIZING PLAYERS
WHO REFUSED TO STAND FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
I'M RICK LEVENTHAL.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
MORE THAN 130 PLAYERS AND
COUNTING, SITTING, KNEELING OR
RAISING THEIR FIST DURING THE
STAR-SPANGLED BANNER.
ONE TEAM, THE PITTSBURGH
STEELERS STAYED IN THERE
LOCKER ROOM.
SOME LOCKED ARMS IN SOLIDARITY
BUT SOME TEAM OWNERS WERE
JOINING THEM.
MANY ARE CONDEMNING THE
PRESIDENT FOR COMMENTS THEY
SAY ARE DIVISIVE.
THE PRESIDENT ISN'T BACKING
DOWN.
A SHORT TIME AGO HE SAID
SPORTS FAN SHOULD NEVER
CONDONE PLAYERS THAT DO NOT
STAND PROUD FOR THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM WEATHER COUNTRY.
NFL SHOULD CHANGE POLICY.
KRISTIN FISHER IS REPORTING
FROM SOMERSET NEW JERSEY NEAR
THE PRESIDENTS PRIVATE GOLF
CLUB.
THE PRESIDENT SPOKE WITH
REPORTERS LAST HOUR.
WHAT IS HE SAYING NOW.
>> IN SOME WAYS HE IS DIGGING
IN AND IN SOME WAYS HE'S
TAKING A STEP BACK.
THIS MORNING ON TWITTER, HE
ENCOURAGE SOME FANS TO GO TO
GAMES AND HE RETWEETED SOMEONE
WHO SAID THEY SHOULD BOYCOTT
THE NFL.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ASKED
DIRECTLY, ARE YOU CALLING ON
YOUR SUPPORTERS TO BOYCOTT THE
NFL.
HE SAID NO.
HE IS DIGGING IN HIS CRITICISM
OF THE NFL PLAYERS WHO
CONTINUE TO TAKE ANY DURING
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
HE SAYS THIS IS ABOUT RESPECT
FOR OUR FLAG AND RESPECT FOR
OUR COUNTRY AND NOTHING ELSE.
>> THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
RACE.
I NEVER SAID ANYTHING ABOUT
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
RACE OR ANYTHING ELSE.
THIS HAS TO DO WITH RESPECT
FOR OUR COUNTRY AND RESPECT
FOR OUR PLAYERS.
>> THIS MORNING THE TREASURY
SECRETARY STEVE HIT THE SUNDAY
SHOWS TO TALK ABOUT TAX REFORM
EMMA BUT HE WAS ALSO ASKED
ABOUT PRESIDENT TRUMP TAKING
THIS SITE WITH THESE POPULAR
PLAYERS NOW.
HERE'S WHAT HE SAID.
>> THE NFL HAS ALL DIFFERENT
TYPES OF ROLES.
YOU CAN HAVE STICKERS ON YOUR
HELMET, YOU HAVE TO HAVE YOUR
JERSEYS TUCKED IN, I THINK
WHAT THE PRESIDENT IS SAYING
IS THAT THE OWNER SHOULD HAVE
A ROLE THAT PLAYERS SHOULD
HAVE TO STAND AND RESPECT FOR
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
THIS ISN'T ABOUT DEMOCRATS OR
REPUBLICANS, IT'S NOT ABOUT
RACE, IT'S NOT ABOUT FREE
SPEECH.
THEY CAN DO FREE SPEECH ON
THEIR OWN TIME.
THIS IS ABOUT RESPECT FOR THE
MILITARY AND THE FIRST
RESPONDERS IN THE CONCRETE.
>> I KNOW THERE'S A LOT OF
PEOPLE OUT THERE TONIGHT WHO
SAY THIS IS ONE BIG
DISTRACTION TO TAKE AWAY FROM
THE IMPORTANT ISSUES OF THE
DAY.
RICK, IF THIS IS A
DISTRACTION, IT CERTAINLY IS
WORKING.
>> NO DOUBT.
IT'S NOT JUST PROFESSIONAL
FOOTBALL.
HE ALSO HAS SOME A PROBLEM
WITH SOME OF THE PLAYERS IN
THE NBA.
THERE IS AN INVITATION TO THE
WHITE HOUSE BEING RESCINDED.
WHERE DOES THAT CONTROVERSY
STAND.
>> WE ARE SEEING THE SPREAD TO
OTHER TEAMS IN OTHER SPORTS.
JUST BRING US UP TO SPEED, HE
SAID HE WAS HESITANT TO GO TO
THE WHITE HOUSE AFTER WINNING
THE NBA CHAMPIONSHIP ARE THE
PRESIDENT CALLED YESTERDAY AND
SAID FINE, I'M RESCINDING MY
INVITATION AND NOW THE ENTIRE
TEAM ISN'T GOING.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TODAY, HE
PRAISED THE DIFFERENT TEAM IN
A DIFFERENT SPEED AND
TRANSPORT.
THE PITTSBURGH PENGUINS JUST
ONE THE CUP.
IT WAS VERY DIFFERENT
STATEMENT.
THE PITTSBURGH PENGUINS
RESPECT THE OFFICE OF THE
PRESIDENT AND THE LONG
TRADITION OF CHAMPIONSHIP
TEAMS VISITING THE WHITE
HOUSE.
ANY AGREEMENT OR DISAGREEMENT
WITH THE POLITICS, POLICY OR
AGENDA CAN BE EXPRESSED IN
OTHER WAYS.
WE ARE CERTAINLY SEEING
PLAYERS ACROSS THE COUNTRY,
ACROSS THE NFL, OWNERS
INCLUDING PRESIDENT TRUMP OWN
FRIEND AND DONOR, THE OWNER OF
THE NEW ENGLAND PATRIOTS
COMING OUT THINK THEY ARE
DISAPPOINTED IN THE
PRESIDENTIAL REMARKS THIS
WEEKEND.
>> KRISTIN FISHER, THANK YOU
SO MUCH.
FOR MORE LET'S GO TO JIM
GRAY.
THE FORECASTER AT FOX NEWS
SPORTS.
THEY MUST BE CRINGING OVER
THIS AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> YES, ABSOLUTELY.
THIS IS NOTHING THEY WANTED,
AND NOW THEY ARE IN RESPONSE
MODE AND THEY KNOW THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
HAS A TREMENDOUS FOLLOWING AND
CAN BE VERY DAMAGING TO THEIR
GAME.
THEY HAVE GALVANIZED.
THEY HAVE UNIFIED UNDER THESE
DIVISIVE COMMENTS AND I THINK
WHAT STRUCK THE MOST IS WHEN
THE PRESIDENT SAID THEY SHOULD
BE FIRED.
THE NFL PLAYERS BELIEVE THIS
IS SOCIAL JUSTICE THAT THEY
ARE TRYING TO CHANGE AND NOT
TRYING TO BE DISRESPECTFUL TO
THOSE WHO WENT BEFORE THEM IN
THE MILITARY.
THEY SEND A VERY MIXED MESSAGE
, AND MANY OF THE FANS, 70% OF
THE FANS ARE AGAINST THE
KNEELING.
THEY LOOK AT IT AS VERY
DISRESPECTFUL AND THAT'S WHAT
THE PRESIDENT IS COMMENTING
ON.
THEY SEE THAT SOCIAL JUSTICE
AND THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
STOP.
THIS HAS BROUGHT THE ENTIRE
NATIONAL FOOTBALL LEAGUE
TOGETHER.
>> WE SAW THAT EARLIER TODAY
WHEN A LARGE GROUP OF PATRIOTS
WERE AMONG THE PLAYERS TAKING
A KNEE IN FOXBORO.
SOME PEOPLE WERE YELLING STAND
UP AT THEIR OWN TEAM.
>> BOTH TEAMS WERE ALSO BOOED
IN TENNESSEE.
THE SEAHAWKS AND THE TITANS
DID NOT COME OUT.
THE PITTSBURGH STEELERS DID
NOT COME OUT BECAUSE THEIR
HEAD COACH THAT OUR PLAYERS
SHOULDN'T HAVE TO DECIDE.
THEY SHOULDN'T HAVE TO PICK
SIDES SO I'M GOING TO KEEP ALL
OF THEM INSIDE THE LOCKER
ROOM.
THERE WAS ONE PLAYER WHO DID
COME OUT FOR THE NATIONAL
ANTHE ANTHEM.
OF COURSE HE WAS AN ARMY
RANGER AND HAD THREE TOURS IN
AFGHANISTAN SO HE WAS THE LONE
STEELER, BUT MIKE JUST SAID
THIS IS NOT ABOUT FOOTBALL AND
I'M NOT PUTTING MY GUYS IN THE
CENTER OF THIS DIVISIVE
POLITICS.
>> THAT WAS PROBABLY THE MOST
POWERFUL IMAGE OF THE DAY.
HE'S ONE OF MAYBE ONLY THREE
MEMBERS ARE PLAYERS IN THE NFL
WHO SERVED IN THE MILITARY
PRIOR TO PLAYING FOOTBALL, AND
THERE HE IS, NOT STANDING WITH
HIS TEAM BUT COMING OUT TO
SHOW RESPECT FOR THE FLAG
DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> YES, IT WAS A VERY POWERFUL
MOMENT.
>> THE FANS DON'T LIKE THIS AT
ALL.
LOOK, THIS IS ONE OF THE
PLACES WHERE FANS GO TO ESCAPE
ALL THIS, WHERE PEOPLE CAN SIT
DOWN ON A SUNDAY AFTERNOON OR
SATURDAY NIGHT AND WATCH
FOOTBALL GAMES AND REALLY GET
AWAY FROM ALL THIS, AND NOW,
THIS IS FRAYING THE VERY
FABRIC OF THIS WEB THAT WE
HAVE AND THE SOCIETY IS NOW
SHREDDED, BUT ONE OF THE LAST
REFUGE, ONE OF THE LAST PLACES
WE CAN GO.
WE CAN'T TALK POLITICS OR RACE
OR RELIGION AND NOW IT'S GOING
TO GET TO THE POINT WHERE WE
CAN'T TALK SPORT.
>> THE TRUTH OF IT IS, EVEN
THOUGH THE PRESIDENT SUGGESTED
THAT THE TEAM OWNER SHOULD
FIRE THE PLAYERS, IN MOST
CASES THEY CAN'T FIRE THEM
BECAUSE OF THE UNION RULES IN
THE CONTRACT THEY SIGNED.
>> FORGET ABOUT THAT, THEY
COULDN'T WITHSTAND THE
BACKLASH IN THE COMMUNITY.
PEOPLE ARE NOT AGAIN SOCIAL
JUSTICE.
SO WHILE IT MAY BE THE WRONG
TIME TO BE SENDING THIS
MESSAGE, THEY ARE USING THE
PLATFORM.
THEY ARE USING A PLACE WHERE
THEY CAN GET THE ATTENTION
THEY FEEL IS NECESSARY AND
WARRANTED, WHERE THEY CAN
BRING ATTENTION TO WHAT THEY
SEE AS WRONGS OF SOCIETY.
A LOT OF THIS HAD DIED DOWN.
A LOT OF IT WAS ON THE BACK
BURNER.
THERE IS A HANDFUL OF GUYS WHO
ARE PARTICIPATING IN THIS AND
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN HIS SPEECH
ALABAMA BROUGHT THIS ISSUE
BACK TO THE FOREFRONT.
HERE HAS BEEN THE RESULT.
WHAT YOU SEE NOW IS UNLIKE ANY
OTHER TIME IN OUR COUNTRY.
WE'VE HAD GUYS GOING FOR
SOCIAL CHANGE.
TOMMY SMITH AND JOHN CARLOS,
THE 1968 OLYMPICS WHEN THEY
ROSE THEIR FISTS UP IN THE AIR
ON THE VICTORY PLATFORM,
MUHAMMAD ALI THROUGHOUT HIS
CAREER IN THE 60s AND 70s
AND 80s, BUT NEVER HAVE WE
EVER SEEN AN ENTIRE LEAGUE
VIRTUALLY IN UNISON SPEAK OUT
IN THE WAY THEY SPOKE TODAY.
>> AND CLEARLY THIS IS NOT
OVER YET.
WE APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
>> THE FBI IS INVESTIGATING
AFTER A SHOOTING IN A CHURCH
IN TENNESSEE, SOUTHEAST OF
NASHVILLE.
A WOMAN IS DEAD.
AS MANY AS SIX OTHERS ARE
INJURED.
AUTHORITIES SAY A MASKED
GUNMAN OPENED FIRE JUST AFTER
SERVICES LET OUT.
AND USHER AT THE CHURCH TRIED
TO INTERVENE.
>> HE CONFRONTED THE GUY, WAS
PISTOL WHIPPED AND HE WENT
AFTER HIS CAR.
WE SEIZED THE WEAPON, CAME
BACK INSIDE AND THEN THE
GUNMEN SHOT HIMSELF.
>> THE VICTIMS WERE ADULTS,
MANY OVER THE AGE OF 60.
JONATHAN IS REPORTING LIVE
FROM TENNESSEE.
FBI INVESTIGATING WHETHER RACE
MAY HAVE BEEN A MOTIVE.
>> YES, AS FAR AS LOCAL
POLICE, THEY ARE PURSUING
SEVERAL LEADS.
THEY WON'T SPECULATE PUBLICLY
ON ANY MOTIVE.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS HAVE
CONFIRMED THAT THE FBI WILL BE
LAUNCHING A CIVIL RIGHTS
INVESTIGATION WITH THE
SHOOTING.
AUTHORITIES HAVE IDENTIFIED
THEM AS EMMANUEL SAMPSON.
HE IS A 25-YEAR-OLD
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MALE.
HE HAS BEEN RELEASED FROM
HOSPITAL AND WILL BE CHARGED
WITH MURDER AND ATTEMPTED
MURDER IN CONNECTION WITH THE
SHOOTING SPREE.
THE GUNMAN FATALLY SHOT
39-YEAR-OLD MELANIE SMITH IN
THE CHURCH PARKING LOT AND
WENT INSIDE THE CHURCH
BUILDING, OPENING FIRE,
INJURING SIX OTHERS.
THE MAYOR
ISSUED A STATEMENT
SAYING THIS IS A TERRIBLE
TRAGEDY FOR OUR CITY.
MY HEART ACHES FOR THE FRIENDS
AND FAMILY AS WELL AS THE
WOUNDED VICTIMS AND THEIR
LOVED ONES.
SHE WENT ON TO PLEDGE HER
ADMINISTRATION SUPPORT FOR
CRIME-FIGHTING EFFORTS IN THE
COMMUNITY, PREVENTING VIOLENCE
AND PROMOTING PEACEFUL
RESOLUTION TO CONFLICTS.
REMEMBER, THIS IS A RULE
SUBURB JUST OUTSIDE THE CITY
OF NASHVILLE.
A QUIET COUNTRY CHURCH.
IT'S TERRIBLE IF THIS HAPPENS
ANYWHERE, BUT HERE IS ONE OF
THE LAST PLACES YOU WOULD
EXPECT IT.
>> IT COULD'VE BEEN A LOT
WORSE HAD IT NOT BEEN FOR THAT
CHURCH USHER WHO STEPPED IN.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THAT CHURCH USHER IS ONLY 22
YEARS OLD.
HIS NAME IS ROBERT INGLE.
HE ACTUALLY CONFRONTED THE
GUNMEN ACCORDING TO WITNESSES
DURING THE SCUFFLE.
HIS GUN WENT OFF INJURING THE
GUNMEN.
WHAT'S UNCLEAR, AUTHORITIES
AREN'T SURE WHETHER THE
SUSPECT WANTED TO SHOOT
HIMSELF OR WHETHER THE GUN
ACCIDENTALLY WENT OFF INJURING
THE GUNMEN.
EITHER WAY, IT STOP THE
SHOOTING SPREE IN ITS TRACKS
AND POLICE ARE CALLING THIS
YOUNG MAN A HERO.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION IS
WEIGHING ITS OPTIONS ON A NEW
VERSION OF THE TRAVEL BAN.
WHAT THAT NEW ORDER MIGHT LOOK
LIKE.
PLUS, THE GRAND CASSIDY HEALTH
CARE BILL COULD BE ON LIFE
SUPPORT WITH TO MORE GOP
SENATORS SAYING THEY ARE ON
THE FENCE.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAID IT IS NOT
READY TO PULL THE PLUG.
>> WHAT WE ARE ACTUALLY DOING
AS WE ARE TAKING DOLLARS OUT
OF WASHINGTON D.C. AND SENDING
IT TO THE STATE.
HOW EACH STATE GETS THOSE
RESOURCES IS BEING CONTINUED
TO TRY TO PROTECT PERFECT THAT
Cigna. Together, all the way.
3 toddlers won't stop him..
And neither will lower
back pain.
Because at a Dr. Scholl's Kiosk
he got a recommendation for
our Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve his foot,
knee, or lower back pain,
from being on his feet.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
I have age-related maculare
degeneration, AMD,
he told me to look at this
grid every day.
And we came up with a plan
to help reduce
my risk
of progression,
including PreserVision
AREDS 2.
My doctor said
PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
the National Eye
Institute recommends
to help reduce
the risk of progression of
moderate to advanced AMD
after 15 years
of clinical studies.
PreserVision
AREDS 2.
Because my eyes
are everything.
the toothpaste that helps
prevent bleeding gums.
If you spit blood
when you brush or floss
you may have gum problems
and could be on the journey
to much worse.
Help stop the journey
of gum disease.
Try parodontax
toothpaste.
♪
When food is good
and clean and real,
it's ok to crave.
And with Panera catering,
there's more to go around.
Panera.
Food as it should be.
Unlike ordinary diapers with
two layers, Pampers have three
Pampers.
absorbent layers to stay
up to three times drier,
so babies can sleep
soundly all night.
Wishing you love, sleep
and play. Pampers.
Whentrust the brand doctors
trust for themselves.
Nexium 24HR is the number one
choice of doctors
and pharmacists for their
own frequent heartburn.
And all day
all night protection.
When it comes to frequent
heartburn, trust Nexium 24HR.
[Grandma] You misplaced your
You have Wells Fargo, right?
[Grandson] Yeah.
[Grandma] Open up the app.
[Grandson] Okay.
[Grandma] And turn off your
card.
[Grandson] Grandma, how are you
better at this than me?
[Grandma] You know, you can use
that phone to call me.
RICK: PRESIDENT TRUMP'S TRAVEL
BAN IS EXPIRING TODAY.
WE COULD LEARN DETAILS OF THE
NEW PLAN AS EARLY AS
TOMORROW.
IT BANNED SIX COUNTRIES FROM
ENTERING THE U.S. UNLESS THEY
HAD A RELATIONSHIP WITH
SOMEONE IN THE U.S.
THEY BEEN WORKING ON NEW RULES
TO AVOID THE CHAOS AND PROTEST
THAT FOLLOWED THE FIRST BAND.
COUNTRIES THAT REFUSE TO
COMPLY COULD FACE TRAVEL
RESTRICTIONS AND TOUGHER
SCREENING MEASURES.
THE REPUBLICAN-LED EFFORT TO
DISMANTLE OBAMACARE.
ANOTHER SENATOR EXPRESSED
RESERVATIONS AND THE CLOCK IS
TICKING TO REACH A DEAL ON
HEALTHCARE BEFORE THE END OF
THE MONTH.
ALLISON BARBER HAS MORE FROM
WASHINGTON.
>> GOOD EVENING.
TWO POSSIBLE BLOWS TO THE
GRAND CASSIDY HEALTH CARE BILL
COMING FROM SENATOR TED CRUZ
IN TEXAS AND SENATOR SUSAN
COLLINS.
SHE SHE IS A KEY SENATOR IN
ALL OF THIS.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS SPEND A LOT
OF TIME TRYING TO CONVINCE HER
TO SUPPORT THE GRAND CASSIDY
BILL.
STAY SHE SAID SHE IS MOST
LIKELY NOT GOING TO SUPPORT
IT.
>> IT IS VERY DIFFICULT FOR ME
TO ENVISION A SCENARIO WHERE I
WOULD END UP VOTING FOR THIS
BILL.
>> REPUBLICANS LOSE THREE OF
THEIR OWN.
>> THERE IS NO DEMOCRAT
SUPPORT.
ALL 48 DEMOCRATS OPPOSE PAY WE
NEED TO MAKE SURE THAT THE
LAST REPUBLICANS WE WENT OVER,
THOSE ARE JOHN MCCAIN, THAT'S
OUR PATH TO VICTORY.
>> THEY ADDED HIS NAME TO THAT
LIST OF PEOPLE NEEDING
CONVINCING.
>> SO LOOK, RIGHT NOW, THEY
DON'T HAVE MY VOTE, AND I
DON'T THINK THEY HAVE MIKE
LEE'S EITHER.
>> SENATOR JOHN MCCAIN SAID HE
WILL NOT VOTE FOR THIS
LEGISLATION.
SENATOR RAND PAUL HAS SAID THE
SAME.
>> MIKE SHORT TOLD FOX NEWS
SUNDAY, THERE WILL NOT BE
MAJOR CHANGES.
>> I DON'T THINK THERE ARE
SIGNIFICANT CHANGES.
WE HAVE BEEN CONTINUING TO
TALK TO VARIOUS SENATORS ON
WAYS TO REFINE THE FORMULA.
WHAT WE ARE ACTUALLY DOING IS
TAKING DOLLARS OUT OF
WASHINGTON D.C. AND SENDING IT
OUT TO THE STATE.
>> THE DEADLINE IS
SEPTEMBER 30.
REPUBLICANS ONLY NEED 50 YES
VOTES, A SIMPLE MAJORITY TO
PASS LEGISLATION.
, OCTOBER THEY NEED 60.
IN WASHINGTON, I'M ALLISON
BARBER, FOX NEWS.
RICK: RESCUE TEAMS DIGGING FOR
THE FIFTH DAY AFTER A STRONG
EARTHQUAKE CAUSED BUILDINGS TO
COLLAPSE IN MEXICO.
HOW THE COURTS ARE GETTING
INVOLVED IN THOSE SEARCH
EFFORTS.
PLUS, ANOTHER NATURAL DISASTER
ESTATES PUERTO RICO.
PEOPLE JUST TRYING TO USE
THEIR PHONES AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA SLAMMED THE ISLAND.
>> HAVE TRYING FOR DAYS TO GET
THE TOUCH WITH MY FAMILIES IN
THE UNITED STATES.
You totaNobody's hurt, new car.
but there will still be pain.
It comes when your insurance
company says they'll only pay
three-quarters of what
it takes to replace it.
What are you supposed to do?
Drive three-quarters of a car?
Now if you had Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
you'd get your whole car back.
I guess they don't want you
driving around on three wheels.
Smart.
With Liberty Mutual
New Car Replacement™,
we'll replace the full
value of your car.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
and life's beautiful moments.ns
get between you
Flonase outperforms the #1
non-drowsy allergy pill.
It helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause symptoms.
Pills block one
and 6 is greater than 1.
Flonase changes
everything.
for tech advice.
Dell Small Business Advisor
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪
I even accept I have a
higher risk of stroke
as far as I used to.
due to AFib,
a type of
irregular heartbeat
not caused by a
heart valve problem.
But no matter
where I ride,
I go for my best.
So if there's something
better than warfarin,
I'll go for that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS reduced
the risk of stroke
better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor
tells you to,
as stopping increases your
risk of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
...and it may take
longer than usual
for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate
medical care
for sudden signs
of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about
all planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor
about ELIQUIS.
♪
THEY STAY.
RICK: RESCUE TEAMS ARE SIFTING
THROUGH RUBBLE HOPING TO FIND
MORE SURVIVORS FIVE DAYS AFTER
A DEADLY EARTHQUAKE.
MEXICAN AUTHORITIES SAY THE
NUMBER DEAD STAND THAT MORE
THAN 300.
CREWS ARE SEARCHING COLLAPSE
BUILDING.
THEY ARE FRANTICALLY SEARCHING
FOR ANY SIGNS OF LIFE.
NEIGHBORS OF A COLLAPSED
APARTMENT BUILDING WERE
GRANTED AN INJUNCTION FROM A
JUDGE THAT SAYS RESCUE EFFORTS
MUST CONTINUE FOR FIVE MORE
DAYS.
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE ARE NOW
HOMELESS AS A RESULT OF THIS
EARTHQUAKE AND THE MORE
POWERFUL ONE EARLIER THIS
MONTH.
>> HURRICANE MARIA CAUSED
HEAVY DAMAGE IN PUERTO RICO
WHERE THE POWER AND PHONE
SERVICE IS STILL OUT FOR MOST
OF THE ISLAND.
NOW A THREAT OF A DAM COLLAPSE
IS FORCING THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
FROM THEIR HOME.
GARRETT IS IN SAN JUAN.
>> SOME OF THE BEST NEWS I CAN
REPORT IS THAT COMMUNICATIONS
ARE SLOWLY RETURNING IN SAN
ONE.
AT&T DISPATCHED SOME OF THE
CREWS TO REBUILD AND REPAIR
THE CELL TOWERS HERE IN PUERTO
RICO.
THIS LAST HOUR WE STARTED
GETTING A LITTLE BIT OF SIGNAL
ON OUR CELL PHONE WHICH HAD
PREVIOUSLY BEEN NONEXISTENT.
THAT HAS BEEN ONE OF THE
TOUGHEST, MOST CHALLENGING
PART FOR PEOPLE IN PUERTO RICO
AS WELL IS BACK IN THE
STATES.
THAT DISCONNECT, NOT BEING
ABLE TO SPEAK WITH YOUR LOVED
ONES AND LET THEM KNOW HOW
YOU'RE DOING.
IN FACT, FOLKS HAVE DRIVEN AS
FAR AS 40 OR 50 MILES TO TRY
TO FIND CELL PHONE SIGNAL TO
BE ABLE TO PLACE A CALL OR
MAKE A TEXT OR JUST SEND THAT
MESSAGE OUT.
ALONG THE HIGHWAY IS ONE OF
THE FEW PLACES THAT HAS
SIGNAL.
YOU CAN SEE LONG LINES OF CARS
STOPPING TO TRY TO CONNECT
WITH THEIR LOVED ONE.
THEY HAVE SLOWLY STARTED TO
COME INTO THE COUNTRY.
FOR A LOT OF FOLKS, AFTER
LOSING THEIR HOME, THE LONG
LINES FOR FUEL, FOOD AND
WATER, ALONG WITH THE PROSPECT
OF GOING MONTHS WITHOUT POWER
IS JUST TOO MUCH AND HUNDREDS
OF THEM ARE NOW TRYING TO FIND
A WAY.
>> IT'S TERRIBLE.
EVERYONE IS FIGHTING FOR
GASOLINE.
MY HUSBAND GOES OUT AT FOUR IN
THE MORNING EVERY DAY TO GET
GASOLINE FOR THE GENERATOR.
GETS BACK AT TWO OR
3:00 O'CLOCK IN THE AFTERNOON
WITH TEN DOLLARS AT THE MOST.
WE ARE TRYING TO LEAVE.
WE CAN SURVIVE THAT WE HAVE A
LITTLE GIRL AND IT'S
COMPLICATED.
THIS IS CRAZY.
>> IN WESTERN PUERTO RICO, THE
THREAT OF A COLLAPSING DAM HAS
FORCED 8000 PEOPLE TO
EVACUATE.
OFFICIALS SAY THAT DAM COULD
STILL BREAK AT ANY MOMENT.
AFTER RECEIVING MORE RAIN
TODAY, THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE EXTENDED A FLASH FLOOD
WARNING UNTIL 815 TONIGHT.
OFFICIALS ACROSS THE TERRITORY
ARE STILL TRYING TO ASSESS
JUST WHAT HOW WIDESPREAD THE
DAMAGES AND HOW BAD IT IS IN
SOME AREAS, PARTICULARLY THOSE
SMALL TOWNS ALONG THE WESTERN
AND SOUTHERN AND EASTERN PARTS
OF THE TERRITORY WHERE THE
STORM REALLY DAMAGED
SEVERELY.
THEY ARE TRYING TO REESTABLISH
COMMUNICATION THERE.
TODAY THE GOVERNOR SAID THE
DEATH TOLL REMAINED AT TEN.
THAT NUMBER COULD STILL RISE
AS THE INDICATIONS ARE
REESTABLISHED.
THIS WEEKEND PUERTO RICO
CONGRESSWOMAN SAID FEMA
ADMINISTRATOR AS WELL AS
FLORIDA SENATOR MARCO RUBIO
WILL BE MAKING THEIR WAY TO
THE ISLAND TOMORROW TO SURVEY
THE DAMAGE FOR THEMSELVES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ALSO SAID HE
PLANS TO VISIT THE ISLAND.
NO DATE OR TIME HAS BEEN
SCHEDULED FOR THAT VISIT.
>> A SHOW SOLIDARITY ACROSS
THE NFL.
PLAYERS AND OWNERS STAND UP
FOR FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
THIS AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CALL FOR PLAYERS AND PROTEST
TO BE FIRED.
WHAT DO THE FANS THINK?
WE WILL HEAR FROM THEM.
AN INFAMOUS FIGURE IN POLITICS
NOW EYEING A POLITICAL COME
BACK AFTER A REMARKABLE FALL
FROM GRACE.
>> HAD I BEEN GIVEN A CIVIL
FINE WITH THEY STILL FEEL I
SHOULDN'T REPRESENT THEM IS
MARK I HEAR OVERWHELMING
MAJORITY OF PEOPLE WOULD SAY
YES.
Upeace of mind.s
We had a power outage
for five days total.
We lost a lot of food.
We actually filed
a claim with USAA
to replace that spoiled food.
And we really appreciated that
We're the Webber family and
we are USAA members for life.
I AM TOTALLY BLIND.
AND NON-24 CAN THROW MY
DAYS AND NIGHTS OUT OF SYNC,
KEEPING ME FROM THE
THINGS I LOVE TO DO.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-214-2424.
Endless Shrimp is back
at Red Lobster.
And we went all out
to bring you even more
incredible shrimp
and new flavors.
Like new
Nashville Hot Shrimp,
drizzled with
sweet amber honey,
and new grilled
Mediterranean Shrimp
finished with a savory blend
of green onions,
tomatoes, and herbs.
Feeling hungry yet?
Good, 'cause there's plenty
more where these came from.
Like Garlic Shrimp Scampi,
and other classics you love.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
But hurry, Endless Shrimp
won't be here long.
If you have moderate to severe
plaque psoriasis,...t them.
...isn't it time to let the real
you shine through?
Maybe it's time for Otezla
(apremilast).
Otezla is not an injection or a
cream.
It's a pill that treats plaque
psoriasis differently.
With Otezla, 75% clearer skin
is achievable after just 4
months,...
...with reduced redness,...
...thickness, and scaliness of
plaques.
And the Otezla prescribing
information has...
...no requirement for routine
lab monitoring.
Don't use if you're allergic to
Otezla.
Otezla may cause severe
diarrhea, nausea, or vomiting.
Tell your doctor if these occur.
Otezla is associated with an
increased...
...risk of depression. Tell your
doctor if you have...
...a history of depression...
...or suicidal thoughts,...
...or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla...
...reported weight loss.
Your doctor should monitor your
weight and may stop treatment.
Other side effects include
upper...
...respiratory tract infection
and headache.
Tell your doctor about all the
medicines you take...
...and if you're pregnant or
planning to be.
Ask your dermatologist
about Otezla today.
Otezla. Show more of you.
This iNot this John Smith.Smith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
I'M RICK LEVENTHAL.
THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ARRIVED BACK
AT THE WHITE HOUSE AFTER A
WEEKEND OF CONTROVERSY.
THE PRESIDENT WENT ON THE
ATTACK AGAINST NFL PLAYERS WHO
REFUSE TO STAND FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
HE CALLED THEM AS OB AND SAID
TEAM OWNER SHOULD FIRE THEM.
THAT IGNITED A WAVE OF PROTEST
ACROSS THE LEAGUE.
MORE THAN 130 PLAYERS AND
COUNTING SITTING, KNEELING OR
RAISING THEIR FIST DURING THE
STAR-SPANGLED BANNER.
THE PITTSBURGH PLAYERS STAYED
IN THE LOCKER ROOM WHILE THE
ANTHEM WAS PLAYED.
BRIAN, HOW ARE FANS REACTING
TO TODAY'S PROTEST.
>> WE ARE AT RED'S RESTAURANT
AND BAR WHERE THE JETS BEAT
THE DOLPHINS.
THE PEOPLE HERE LOVE TO WIN.
IN TERMS OF EVERYTHING ELSE,
LOOK, SOME PEOPLE SAY
GENERALLY THEY DO NOT LIKE THE
FACT THAT PEOPLE ARE USING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM TO PROTEST.
IN FACT MOST PEOPLE DON'T LIKE
THAT.
WHEN IT COMES TO WHETHER OR
NOT THEY'RE GOING TO BOYCOTT
THE SPORT OR HOW FAR THEY'RE
WILLING TO GO TO SUPPORT THAT
OR GO AGAINST IT, THEY ARE NOT
WILLING TO BOYCOTT.
HERE IS SOME OF WHAT THE FOLKS
SAID TO US.
>> I THINK OUR YOUNG MEN AND
WOMEN FOUGHT FOR US TO HAVE
THE RIGHT TO EITHER STAND UP
OR TAKE THAT KNEE.
IT'S JUST WHAT WE BELIEVE IN.
IF IT'S A WAY TO GET THE
MESSAGE ACROSS IN TERMS OF
WHAT THEY'RE FIGHTING FOR.
WHY NOT.
YOU JUST HAVE TO SUPPORT THEM
NO MATTER WHAT.
>> CAN WE JUST HAVE OUR
SUNDAYS WITH FOOTBALL.
LOOK.
I'M TRYING TO ENJOY SUNDAY
WITH MY WIFE.
WERE TALKING ABOUT POLITICS
NOW.
IT'S JUST TOO MUCH.
>> LISTEN, I'M A VETERAN.
THOSE GUYS ARE GETTING PAID
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS AND I
USED
TO GET A PAYCHECK OF $750 IN
THE MILITARY.
IF YOU CAN'T STAND FOR THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM, THEN GET OFF
THE FIELD.
>> I THINK IT TURNED THE WHOLE
THING FROM AWFUL.
IT WAS A GREAT MOVE ON
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO DO IT.
>> THAT WAS JUST SOME OF THE
OPINIONS WE GOT HERE TODAY.
MOST PEOPLE ARE JUST TELLING
US THEY ARE NOT HAPPY WITH THE
FACT THAT POLITICS ARE GETTING
INVOLVED WITH THEIR NFL
SUNDAY.
IN FACT, A LOT OF
CONVERSATIONS WERE
UNCOMFORTABLE.
PEOPLE DIDN'T REALLY WANT TO
TALK ABOUT IT.
IT TOOK A WHILE TO GET PEOPLE
WHO WANTED TO SPEAK BECAUSE
IT'S NOT A GOOD MIX FOR THESE
FOLKS.
THEY JUST WANT TO SEE THE
GAME.
>> SOME FANS SAY THEY ARE
GOING TO STOP WATCHING BECAUSE
OF HIS PROTEST?
>> WE SPOKE TO A COUPLE FANS
WHO SAY THEY KNOW OF PEOPLE
WHO WILL STOP WATCHING BECAUSE
OF THIS.
OR WHO HAVE STOPPED WATCHING.
IN FACT THERE WAS A SURVEY
DONE FROM JD POWER IN JULY AND
IT SHOWED THAT THE NUMBER ONE
REASON THAT PEOPLE STOPPED
WATCHING FOOTBALL RECENTLY IS
BECAUSE OF THESE NATIONAL
ANTHEM PROTEST.
BEHIND THAT WERE THE
COMMERCIALS ARE GAME DELAYS
AND EVEN THE PRESIDENTIAL
ELECTION.
BUT THAT'S AN INTERESTING POLL
BECAUSE IT DOES SHOW WITH THE
PRESIDENT WAS SAYING IN TERMS
OF FANS NOT NECESSARILY LIKING
THE WAY THE GAME IS OR NOT
LIKING THE ANTHEM, I GUESS
THAT WOULD SORT OF SUPPORT
THAT.
IN TERMS OF THE NUMBER OF FANS
WE SPOKE TO TODAY THAT WERE
WILLING TO BOYCOTT, WE DID NOT
FIND THAT TODAY.
WE WILL SEE HOW THEY FEEL.
THIS IS THE FIRST WEEK IN
WHICH WE'VE SEEN THIS AT THIS
LEVEL IN TERMS OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP GETTING INVOLVED.
I GUESS THE QUESTION IS HOW
WILL THIS AFFECT THE SPORT.
>> YOU MIGHT REMEMBER THE NAME
AND YOU PROBABLY REMEMBER THAT
INTERVIEW THAT ONE OFF THE
RAIL.
MICHAEL GRAHAM WENT TO THE BIG
HOUSE BUT NOW HE'S BACK AND HE
TALKS TO US ABOUT HIS PLANS
FOR THE FUTURE.
MICHAEL GRAHAM WAS THE RIGHT
RISING STAR IN THE REPUBLICAN
PARTY.
HE WAS THE ONLY ELECTED
REPUBLICAN IN CONGRESS
REPRESENTING NEW YORK CITY
FROM 2011 UNTIL 2015.
A FEDERAL INVESTIGATION INTO A
RESTAURANT HE ONCE OWNED LED
THE CHARGES OF FRAUD AND TAX
EVASION AND THEN THIS
HAPPENS.
>> OF PEOPLE SAID WHAT ARE
YOUR BIGGEST REGRETS, IT'S NOT
HAVING CHILDREN IS PROBABLY
NUMBER ONE BUT WITHIN THE TOP
THREE IS THAT INTERVIEW.
>> THE REPORTER AND LOCAL
NETWORK HAD AGREED TO STAY ON
TOPIC BUT DIDN'T.
HE LOST HIS COOL AND THEN WENT
HOME.
>> I WALK IN AND I SAID MOM, I
KNOW.
DON'T SAY IT.
SHE SAID NO, YOU DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW WE LOOK LIKE?
I SAID NO, WHO DO I LOOK
LIKE.
SHE SAID YOU LOOK LIKE YOUR
FATHER.
I SAID WHY MY FATHER SON.
SHE SAID BUT YOUR FATHER COULD
GET A WE AWAY WITH IT.
YOUR CONGRESSMAN, YOU CAN'T.
IT HIT ME LIKE A TON OF
BRICKS.
>> HE PLED GUILTY TO A SINGLE
COUNT OF TAX FRAUD FOR PAYING
ILLEGAL WORKERS OFF THE
BOOKS.
HE RESIGNED FROM CONGRESS AND
SERVED SEVEN MONTHS IN PRISON.
>> WHAT WAS THAT LIKE FOR
YOU.
>> HORRIBLE.
ONE OF THE WORST EXPENSES OF
MY LIFE.
I WOULDN'T WISH IT ON MY
ENEMY.
HE SAID HIS CASE WAS POLITICAL
HE MOTIVATED AND HIS CRIME
DESERVE NO TIME.
>> IN THE ENTIRE HISTORY OF
NEW YORK CITY, THERE HAVE BEEN
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF CIVIL
FINES BY THE DEPARTMENT OF
LABOR TO RESTAURANT OWNERS FOR
THIS EXACT SAME CONDUCT.
I'M THE FIRST TO BE CRIMINALLY
CHARGED.
MICHAEL GRAHAM SAYS HE IS
READY TO WORK FOR THE PEOPLE
AGAIN.
>> SHOULD I RUN?
>> IF YOU DO, YOU'VE GOT MY
VOTE.
>> I APPRECIATE THAT.
I DON'T RUN UNLESS I KNOW I
CAN WIN.
WHEN I GO OUT AND I SHAKE
THESE HANDS AND PEOPLE HUG ME
AND THEY TELL ME YOU HAVE NO
IDEA HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE
BEHIND YOU, I JUST KNOW IT.
I FEEL IN MY HEART.
RICK: JOINING ME NOW, MICHAEL
GRAHAM.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE.
LET'S GET IT OUT OF THE WAY,
MAKE IT FO OFFICIAL.
ARE YOU RUNNING FOR CONGRESS.
>> I THINK IT'S A DECISION
THAT THE PEOPLE ARE GOING TO
DECIDE.
I HAVE A BIG RALLY COMING UP
SUNDAY OCTOBER 1 AND IF THE
PEOPLE REALLY WANT ME TO RUN
THEN YES I'M GOING TO RUN.
>> BASED ON THE PEOPLE WHO WE
SAW IN THE DINER THAT DAY,
THEY WANT YOU TO RUN.
>> PRETTY MUCH EVERYWHERE I'VE
BEEN, WHAT I'M GETTING
CONSISTENC CONSISTENTLY IS
WE'VE BEEN WAITING FOR YOU,
WE'VE MISSED YOU.
THE DIFFERENCE IS WHEN I WAS
THE CONGRESSMAN, WHEN I WAS
REPRESENTING THESE PEOPLE, I
GAVE MY HEART MY SOUL.
I WAS EVERYWHERE.
I WAS WITH THEM.
THERE WERE DAYS WHERE
LITERALLY I WOULD SHOW UP AT
SOMEONE'S HOUSE BECAUSE I KNOW
THEY HAD BEEN THROUGH REALLY
DIFFICULT TIMES.
I WOULD HUG THEM AND THERE WAS
A TIME WHERE WE ACTUALLY CRIED
TOGETHER.
I REALLY KNEW MY
CONSTITUENTS.
THEY GOT TO KNOW ME AND IT WAS
VERY PERSONAL.
>> YOU HAVE A COUPLE HURDLES
HERE.
I KNOW YOU WANT TO FOCUS NOT
TO BE ON THAT ONE INTERVIEW OR
THAT ONE REPORT, OR THE TIME
THAT YOU SPENT IN A FEDERAL
LOCKUP.
YOU WANTED TO BE ON YOUR
NEARLY 20 YEARS OF PUBLIC
SERVICE.
>> YOUR TIME IN THE GULF WAR,
YOUR TIME IS AN UNDER
UNDERCOVER AGENT.
>> FIRST OF ALL YES.
DO I HAVE THREE DELIVERY BOYS
AND A KITCHEN WORKER OFF THE
BOOKS FOR A COUPLE YEARS,
MYSELF AND TWO OTHER PARTNERS,
YES I DID AND I OWN THAT.
I'M NOT RUNNING AWAY FROM THAT
OR HIDING.
THAT'S A CIVIL MATTER.
AT THE DEPARTMENT OF LABOR.
EVERYONE BUT ME.
I FOUND OUT 14 MONTHS BEFORE
THE INDICTMENT THAT A DEAL WAS
MADE WITH LORETTA LYNCH.
I KNEW SHE WAS CORRUPT.
I WAS TOLD IF SHE TOOK ME DOWN
SHE WOULD BE THE NEXT ATTORNEY
GENERAL OF THE UNITED STATES
FOR TWO MONTHS AFTER WHAT I
WOULD CALL A SHAM INDICTMENT,
SHE WAS THE ATTORNEY GENERAL
OF THE UNITED STATES.
>> YOU'RE SAYING SHE TARGETED
YOU TO ADVANCE HER OWN
CAREER.
>> THERE IS NO QUESTION.
>> WILDS WHAT I WOULD BE THE
FIRST AND ONLY PERSON IN THE
HISTORY OF NEW YORK CITY TO
NOT GET A CIVIL FINE.
>> YOU MADE THAT POINT IN THE
CASE THAT SOME PEOPLE DO
THIS.
YOUR POINT WAS THAT YOU
WEREN'T TAKING MONEY AND PUT
IT IN YOUR POCKET.
YOU ARE TAKING MONEY TO PAY
THE PEOPLE WHO COULDN'T PAY ON
THE BOOKS.
>> AND I NEVER TOOK THE RIGHT
AFTER THE REALITY IS, ANY
ACCOUNT WOULD TELL YOU, I
WASN'T DOING IT TO MAKE MONEY,
YOU CAN'T GET IT DISHWASHER
UNDER THE BOOKS.
SO MOST IMPOSSIBLE TO GET A
KIT ON THE BICYCLE TO
DELIVER.
IT'S NOT RIGHT.
I WAS WRONG PRODUCTION OF DONE
IT.
I SHOULD'VE HAD THE COURAGE TO
FAIL, CLOSE THE RESTAURANT AND
POSSIBLY EVEN LOSE MY HOUSE.
THAT'S WHAT I SHOULD'VE DONE
AND I REGRET THAT FOR THE REST
OF MY LIFE.
>> I KNOW YOU BELIEVE YOUR
FOREIGN-POLICY EXPENSE CAN
HELP ON CAPITOL HILL,
INCLUDING YOUR EXPERIENCE WITH
NORTH KOREA.
TELL ME ABOUT IT.
>> THERE'S NO QUESTION.
I THINK MY FOREIGN-POLICY
EXPERIENCE BUT ALSO MY
LOYALTY.
I'M A MARINE THROUGH AND
THROUGH.
I ALMOST GOT KILLED IN THE
GULF WAR.
MY HUMMER HIT A TANK AND BY
THE GRACE OF GOD I SURVIVED.
AND THEN I WALKED THAT VERY
NIGHT DOWN THAT MINEFIELD TO
BRING PRISONERS BACK TO
SAFETY.
SO, I HAVE A SPINE.
THERE'S A LOT OF MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS WITH A VERY WEAK
SPINE THAT HAVE TURNED THEIR
BACK ON OUR PRESIDENT AND HAS
UNDERMINED THE AGENDA THAT
EVERYONE VOTED FOR.
FIRST AND FOREMOST, I WOULD BE
THERE TO HAVE OUR PRESIDENT'S
BACKPACK THAT'S NUMBER ONE.
NUMBER TWO, YES, WE HAVE A
VERY PRECARIOUS, VERY
DIFFICULT SITUATION WITH NORTH
KOREA AND IT'S GETTING WORSE.
WE HAD THE CLINTON
ADMINISTRATION THAT TRIED TO
BRIBE THEM.
THAT DIDN'T WORK.
FAST-FORWARD AND YOU HAVE
EIGHT YEARS OF AN APPEASEMENT
POLICY BY PRESIDENT OBAMA.
NOW WHAT WE HAVE?
NOW HAVE A LUNATIC WITH THE
CAPABILITY, VERY SOON, ICBMS
WITH NUCLEAR WEAPONS THAT CAN
POSSIBLY STRIKE NOT ONLY THE
UNITED STATES BUT OUR ALLIES.
I THINK THE PRESIDENT HAS
TAKEN SUCH A HARSH STANCE, BUT
THAT'S BECAUSE NOT ONLY DO WE
NEED TO SEND A MESSAGE TO
NORTH KOREA, AND MAYBE HE'S
NOT MENTALLY STABLE TO HEAR
IT, BUT ALLIES NEED TO KNOW
THAT OUR RESOLVING COMMITMENT
IS UNWAVERING.
THAT MEANS JAPAN, WE REALLY
HAVE TO MAKE SURE ARE UNDE
ALLIES UNDERSTAND THAT WE ARE
HERE FOR THEM.
THIS IS A VERY DIFFICULT
SITUATION.
>> NOT TO SWITCH TOPICS BUT
THE PRESIDENT ALSO TOOK A
HARSH STANCE AGAINST NFL
PLAYERS.
AS A VETERAN, HOW DO YOU FEEL
ABOUT PLAYERS KNEELING DURING
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> I THINK THERE ARE TWO
ISSUES.
NUMBER ONE, AS SOMEONE WHO
WATCHES THE FOOTBALL GAMES,
THIS IS MY ESCAPE.
I DON'T WANT TO HEAR ABOUT
POLITICS.
I WANT TO WATCH A GAME AND GET
AWAY FROM THAT.
THAT'S THE FIRST THING.
THE SECOND THING, NOT ONLY AS
A VETERAN BUT AS SOMEONE WHO
HAS SHARED THE BLOOD SWEAT AND
TEARS WITH THOSE THAT HAVE
GIVEN THEIR LIVES AND THEIR
LIMBS, ABOUT THE FAMILIES OF
SOMEONE WHO LOST A SON OR
DAUGHTER OR LOVED ONE IN
COMBAT AND THEY HAVE TO SEE,
PEOPLE WHO WE SHOULD BE
LOOKING UP TO, SPORTS FIGURES,
PEOPLE THAT OUR CHILDREN LOOK
UP TO, THEY MAKE MILLIONS OF
DOLLARS IN A VERY TALENTED.
TO TURN YOUR BACK ON THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM, AND OUR FLAG,
IT SENDS A MESSAGE THAT I
THINK STRIKES AT THE HEART OF
WHO WE ARE AS AMERICANS.
AS A VETERAN, IT'S OFFENSIVE.
>> MICHAEL GRAHAM, TELL US,
YOU'RE RUNNING.
JUST TELL US LIVE ON TV.
>> I WILL SAY THIS.
THE RESPONSE HAS BEEN
OVERWHELMING, I'M ENERGIZED,
I'M VERY EXCITED, EVERYONE
I'VE SPOKEN TO IS EXTREMELY
ENTHUSIASTIC AND I THINK THAT
ON SUNDAY, IF WE HAVE A HUGE
TURNOUT YOU WILL GET THE
ANSWER YOU WANT.
>> THAT'S WHEN IT'S OFFICIAL.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US
TONIGHT.
THE U.S. DRONE BOMBED AND ISIS
CAMP IN LIBYA.
U.S. MILITARY OFFICIALS SAY
THEY WERE TO CARRY OUT SIX
AIRSTRIKES ON FRIDAY NIGHT ARE
STOCKPILE WEAPONS AND PLANNED
ATTACKS.
THE PENTAGON ESTIMATES THERE
ARE HUNDREDS OF ISIS FIGHTERS
IN LIBYA AND IS COMMITTED TO
WORKING WITH LIBYA TO KEEP THE
TERRORIST FROM FINDING SAFE
HAVEN THERE.
TWO CANDIDATES IN ALABAMA ARE
BUYING FOR THE SEAT VACATED BY
JEFF SESSIONS.
A LOOK AHEAD TO THAT ELECTION
HAPPENING THIS WEEK PLUS A NEW
FOX SERIES TAKES AN IN-DEPTH
LOOK INTO THE LIVES OF
CELEBRITY.
THEY JOIN US TO TALK ABOUT THE
LATEST EPISODE FEATURING HULK
HOGAN.
It could save your life.
Cigna. Together, all the way.
's List
for free.
It could save your life.
Which means everyone has access
to our real reviews
that we actually verify.
And we can also verify
that what goes down,
[ Splash, toilet flush ]
doesn't always come back up.
Find a great plumber
at Angie's List.
Join today for free.
I NEEDED SOMETHING MORE TO HELP
CONTROL MY TYPE 2 DIABETES.
MY A1C WASN'T WERE
IT NEEDED TO BE.
SO I LIKED WHEN
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
THAT I MAY REACH MY BLOOD
SUGAR AND A1C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE MY BODY TO
DO WHAT IT'S SUPPOSE TO DO,
RELEASE ITS OWN INSULIN.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE A LUMP OR
SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
SEVERE PAIN IN
YOUR STOMACH,
OR SYMPTOMS SUCH AS ITCHING,
RASH, OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS,
WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN,
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS WORSE.
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY MAY HELP
ME REACH MY BLOOD SUGAR GOALS.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING
YOUR A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR,
ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
>> WHAT WENT THROUGH YOUR MIND
WHEN THIS TAPE CAME OUT?
>> WHEN I DO THAT WAS COMING
OUT, ALL THE LAWYERS SAID IF
YOU WANT TO STOP, STOP.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO FORWARD.
THERE'S A HUGE AMOUNT OF MONEY
BEING OFFERED.
THIS WILL NEVER SEE THE LIGHT
OF DAY.
I SAID I CAN'T DO THAT.
>> OF THIS TAPE WASN'T LEAKED,
SUPPOSE THERE IS NO.
[INAUDIBLE]
>> THAT'S A PREVIEW OF
TONIGHT'S EPISODE OF OBJECTIVE
FIGHT.
HARVEY LEVIN SITTING DOWN WITH
HULK HOGAN FOR THAT WIDE
RAISING INTERVIEW.
HIS USE OF A RACIAL SLUR, AND
ALSO THE LOW POINT IN HIS LIFE
WHEN HE CONSIDERED SUICIDE.
JOINING ME NOW TO TALK MORE
ABOUT IT IS THE EXECUTIVE
PRODUCER.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US
EVERY.
>> AS SOMEONE WHO COVERS
CELEBRITIES AND PROFESSIONAL
ATHLETES, I HAVE TO ASK YOU
FIRST ABOUT WHAT'S GOING ON IN
THE NFL.
YOUR REACTION TO THE PROTEST.
>> LOOK.
I AM REALLY UPSET WITH WHAT
THE PRESIDENT HAS DONE HERE.
I THINK IT'S REALLY WRONG FOR
SOMEONE IN HIS POSITION TO GET
PERSONAL LIKE THAT AND TO CALL
THEM SOP.
WHAT HE HAS DONE IS HE HAS NOW
MADE THIS PARTISAN, POLITICAL,
AND THERE ARE PROBABLY PEOPLE
WHO WOULD'VE NEVER TAKEN ANY
WHO ARE GOING TO TAKE A KNEE.
NOW IT DOESN'T JUST HAVE TO DO
WITH BLACK LIVES MATTER, IT
HAS TO DO WITH DONALD TRUMP.
IN A WAY DIDN'T DO HIMSELF A
FAVOR.
I'M PRETTY UPSET BY IT.
>> YOU SAT DOWN WITH HIM.
YOUR FIRST SHOW WAS ABOUT THE
PRESIDENT.
WERE YOU SURPRISED?
OR DOES THIS FIT INTO THE
PRESIDENT THAT YOU KNOW?
>> THERE IS A BIGGER
DISCUSSION HERE, BUT I'M NOT
SURE I KNOW THE MAN THAT I'M
SEEING NOW BECAUSE IT'S
DIFFERENT FROM THE PERSON I
KNEW BEFORE.
>> TELL US ABOUT THE SHOW,
THERE'S A PRETTY UNIQUE
CONCEPT BEHIND IT.
>> THE IDEA RICK, IS THAT WE
TAKE OBJECTS THAT PEOPLE
CHOOSE TO KEEP OVER A
LIFETIME, FROM CHILDHOOD ON,
AND WE USE THOSE OBJECTS AS
KIND OF A JUMPING OFF POINT.
THE PEOPLE I TALKED TO CHOOSE
THE OBJECT.
THEY ARE INVESTED IN IT AND
THEY HAVE CONTROL AT THE
BEGINNING.
I THINK IT OPENS THEM UP MORE
THAN IF YOU ARE JUST SITTING
ON A SOFA TALKING TO THEM.
WE'VE DONE THIS NOW WITH A
BUNCH OF PEOPLE, FROM BUSINESS
AND SPORTS PEOPLE AND WORLD
LEADERS.
IT JUST OPENS PEOPLE UP AND
THEY TALK ABOUT THINGS MORE
CANDIDLY THAN THEY GENERALLY
DO.
>> THE STUFF THAT THEY HAVE
SAVED, THEY TALK ABOUT THAT
AND RELATE TO THAT AND THAT
LEADS THEM INTO MORE PERSONAL
STUFF.
>> YES, AND I WILL SAY, THIS
IS NOT JUST EXPENSIVE STUFF
THAT THEY KEEP.
THERE IS ONE ITEM, IT'S IRAQ.
IT HAS REAL MEANING TO HIM.
WAS PASSED ON TO HIS SON AND
BACK TO HIM AND THERE IS
MEANING IN THINGS.
TYLER HAS A PAIR OF WALMART
PAJAMAS THAT REALLY MEAN
SOMETHING TO HIM.
THIS IS A VERY RICH MAN.
THESE PAJAMAS MEAN SOMETHING
TO HIM.
IT'S NOT JUST THE EXPENSIVE
STUFF.
>> WHAT IS HIS THING THAT HE
IDENTIFIES WITH THE MOST.
CAN YOU TELL US?
>> I WANT TO SAY WHIP CREAM,
BUT THERE'S A STORY BEHIND
THAT.
I WILL SAY THIS, THE THING
ABOUT MARK, WHO IS JUST A
FANTASTIC GUY, MARK, I TALKED
TO HIM ABOUT POLITICS AND
ABOUT RUNNING AND I CALLED BS
ON HIM BECAUSE I DIDN'T
BELIEVE WHAT HE WAS SAYING,
AND HE OPENED UP SOME.
I WOULD NOT BE SURPRISED IF
MARK MAKES A RUN FOR
PRESIDENT.
>> ON THE GUIDE BE SURPRISED
EITHER.
THAT WOULD BE SOME SHOWDOWN.
>> HE TALKS ABOUT IT AND HE
GETS VERY SPECIFIC.
I THINK YOU MIGHT BE
SURPRISED.
>> IF SOMEONE WAS DOING IN A
AND OBJECTIFY ABOUT YOU, WHAT
WOULD BE THAT ONE OBJECT YOU
WOULD TALK ABOUT.
>> HE PROBABLY INNOCENTLY
WALKED INTO SOMETHING THAT IS
SO SUPER EMBARRASSING FOR ME,
BUT I WILL TELL YOU RICK.
WHEN I PITCHED THE SHOW, WHEN
I WAS TRYING TO SELL IT, I
THOUGHT I HAVE TO HAVE AN
OBJECT THAT I CAN BRING IN SO
I CAN EXPLAIN IT.
WHEN IN TO MY OFFICE IN MY
HOME AND THERE WAS A GLOBE
THAT I KEPT SINCE I WAS SIX
YEARS OLD.
IT MEANS A LOT TO ME.
SO I PULLED THE GLOBE OFF THE
SHELF AND I TOOK IT INTO THE
ROOM AND AS I WAS TRYING TO
FILM THE SHOW, I LOOK AT THE
GLOBE.
THE UNITED STATES ONLY HAD 48
STATES.
>> WOW.
YOU REALLY DATING YOURSELF.
>> WE APPRECIATE YOUR TIME
TONIGHT.
GOOD LUCK WITH THE SHOW.
BE SURE TO WATCH OBJECTIVE
FIGHT.
IT AIRS TONIGHT RIGHT AFTER
FOX REPORT AT 8:00 P.M.
EASTERN.
A REPUBLICAN RUNOFF FOR AN
ALABAMA SENATE SEAT IS
CAPTURING THE NATION'S
ATTENTION.
THE INCUMBENT CANDIDATE HAS
THE SUPPORT OF PRESIDENT TRUMP
BUT HIS COMPETITION IS PUTTING
UP A FIGHT.
THIS RACE COULD COME DOWN TO
THE WIRE.
put under a microscope,
we could see all the
bacteria that still exists.
Polident's unique
micro clean formula
works in just 3 minutes,
killing 99.99% of
odor causing bacteria.
For a cleaner,
fresher,
brighter denture
every day.
For a cleaner,
fresher,
3 toddlers won't stop him..
And neither will lower
back pain.
Because at a Dr. Scholl's Kiosk
he got a recommendation for
our Custom Fit Orthotic
to relieve his foot,
knee, or lower back pain,
from being on his feet.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
When food is good
and clean and real,
it's ok to crave.
And with Panera catering,
there's more to go around.
Panera.
Food as it should be.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS SIGNED A
PROCLAMATION IMPLEMENTING
TRAVEL RESTRICTIONS ON EIGHT
COUNTRIES.
THIS REPLACES THE EMBATTLED
TRAVEL PLAN WHICH JUST EXPIRED
TODAY.
SOME OF THE AFFECTED COUNTRIES
INCLUDE NORTH KOREA AND
VENEZUELA AS WELL AS SIX
OTHERS ACROSS THE MIDDLE EAST
AND AFRICA.
SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON SANG WITH THIS
PROCLAMATION, THE PRESIDENT IS
CARRYING OUT HIS DUTY TO
PROTECT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT WILL
COORDINATE WITH OTHER FEDERAL
AGENCIES TO IMPLEMENT THESE IN
AN ORDERLY MATTER.
WE CONTINUE TO WORK CLOSELY.
THE STATE OF ALABAMA ON THE
EVE OF ELECTION, INCUMBENT
SENATOR LUTHER STRANGE AGAINST
ROY MOORE IN A RACE WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS LOOMING
LARGER THAN OTHER.
PETER'S REPORTING FROM
BIRMINGHAM.
DOES HE THINK THE NFL
CRITICISM AT HIS EVENT WILL
CHANGE THIS RACE AT ALL?
>> YES HE DOES.
HE ACTUALLY THANKS IT WILL
HELP HIM.
HE THANKS BEING ASSOCIATED
WITH THAT KIND OF CONDEMNATION
OF KNEELING NFL PLAYERS ONLY
HOPE HELPS HIS CHANCES.
HE DOES NOT MIND THAT THE BIG
HEADLINE FROM HIS OWN CAMPAIGN
EVENT WITH SOMETHING OTHER
THAN THE PRESIDENT'S
ENDORSEMENT.
>> I LOVE THAT HEADLINE.
HE WAS ONE OF THE MOST
PATRIOTIC CITIES IN THE
COUNTRY, HUNTSVILLE AND A
PATRIOTIC STATE.
WE RESPECT THE FLAG.
EVERYBODY HAS GOT THE RIGHT TO
DO WHAT THEY WANT THE COUNTRY
BUT THEY OUGHT TO RESPECT THE
FLAG AND I THINK IT WAS WELL
RECEIVED.
I COULDN'T AGREE WITH THE
PRESIDENT MORE.
>> SENATOR STRANGE SAYS IN
ALABAMA, THE PRESIDENT'S VISIT
IS REALLY RESONATING BECAUSE
IN ALABAMA, VOTERS REALLY WANT
THE PRESIDENT TO SUCCEED AND
HE IS OUT OF THIS RUNOFF.
>> HOW IS THE CHALLENGER THIS
WEEKEND.
>> BY CONTINUING TO TRY TO CAP
TWO QUOTES, THE GOP LEADER
INCLUDING SENATOR MCCONNELL.
EVEN THOUGH THESE ARE FROM THE
SAME PARTY, THEY ARE TOTALLY
DIFFERENT.
>> WE ARE WAITING TO SEE IF
THE PEOPLE OF ALABAMA WILL
GIVE UP THEIR VOTE TO AN
ESTABLISHMENT IN WASHINGTON
THAT DOES NOT WANT TO MOVE
THIS COUNTRY FORWARD.
THEY DO NOT WANT TO MAKE
PROGRESS OR STOP ILLEGAL
ALIENS OR STOP SOCIALIZED
MEDICINE, AND WANTS TO KEEP
THINGS JUST LIKE IT IS SO
PEOPLE IN WASHINGTON CAN HOLD
ONTO THEIR POWER, THEIR
PRESTIGE AND THEIR POSITION.
>> SENATOR STRANGE INSISTED
THAT HE IS PART OF AN OUTSIDER
MOVEMENT AND WAS JUST AS
FRUSTRATED WITH MITCH
MCCONNELL OVER THE LACK OF
PROGRESS DURING THE LAST
COUPLE MONTHS.
>> ARE THEY EXPECTING A BIG
TURNOUT TOMORROW.
>> TOMORROW AT A PAIR OF
RALLIE RALLIES, STATEWIDE,
SMALL TURNOUT BUT WHICHEVER
SIDE IS MOST EXCITED BY THEN
WILL OBVIOUSLY BE THERE.
>> WE APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK
to ridiculous
plot twists.
(Gasping)
Son?
Dad!
We also know
you can avoid drama
by getting
an annual check-up.
So we're partnering
with Cigna
to remind you to go
see a real doctor.
Go, know, and take
control of your health.
It could save
your life.
Doctor Poses!
Dad!
Cigna. Together, all the way.
the toothpaste that helps
prevent bleeding gums.
If you spit blood
when you brush or floss
you may have gum problems
and could be on the journey
to much worse.
Help stop the journey
of gum disease.
Try parodontax
toothpaste.
♪
for tech advice.
Dell Small Business Advisor
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪
Endless Shrimp is back
at Red Lobster.
And we went all out
to bring you even more
incredible shrimp
and new flavors.
Like new
Nashville Hot Shrimp,
drizzled with
sweet amber honey,
and new grilled
Mediterranean Shrimp
finished with a savory blend
of green onions,
tomatoes, and herbs.
Feeling hungry yet?
Good, 'cause there's plenty
more where these came from.
Like Garlic Shrimp Scampi,
and other classics you love.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
But hurry, Endless Shrimp
won't be here long.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
But on the inside, I feel
chronic, widespread pain.like
most people.
Fibromyalgia may be invisible to
others, but my pain is real.
Fibromyalgia is thought to be
caused by overactive nerves.
LYRICA is believed to calm these
nerves.
I'm glad my doctor prescribed
LYRICA.
For some, LYRICA delivers
effective relief
for moderate to even severe
Fibromyalgia pain.
And improves function.
LYRICA may cause serious
allergic reactions,
suicidal thoughts or actions.
Tell your doctor right away if
you have these,
new or worse depression,
unusual changes in mood or
behavior,
swelling, trouble breathing,
rash, hives,
blisters, muscle pain with
fever,
tired feeling, or blurry vision.
Common side effects: dizziness,
sleepiness, weight gain,
swelling of hands, legs and
feet.
Don't drink alcohol while taking
LYRICA.
Don't drive or use machinery
until you know how LYRICA
affects you.
Those who've had a drug or
alcohol problem
may be more likely to misuse
LYRICA.
With less pain, I can do more
with my family.
Talk to your doctor today.
See if LYRICA can help.
G NEW CARS.
YOU'RE SMART.
YOU ALREADY KNEW THAT.
BUT IT'S ALSO GREAT FOR FINDING
THE PERFECT USED CAR.
YOU'LL SEE WHAT
A FAIR PRICE IS,
AND YOU CAN CONNECT WITH
A TRUECAR CERTIFIED DEALER.
NOW YOU'RE EVEN SMARTER.
THIS IS TRUECAR.
[Grandma] You misplaced your
You have Wells Fargo, right?
[Grandson] Yeah.
[Grandma] Open up the app.
[Grandson] Okay.
[Grandma] And turn off your
card.
[Grandson] Grandma, how are you
better at this than me?
[Grandma] You know, you can use
that phone to call me.
>> AFTER FOX REPORT THIS
SUNDAY SEPTEMBER 24, 2017.
IS WATCHING.
HAVE YOURSELF A FANTASTIC
WEEK.
to keep in their home
define who they are.
This is...
>> THE OBJECTS PEOPLE CHOOSE
TO KEEP IN THEIR HOME TO FIND
WHO THEY ARE.
THIS   IS OBJECTIFY HULK HOGAN.
THIS IS A STORY ABOUT THE BABE
RUTH OF PROFESSIONAL
WRESTLING.e
HULK HOGAN PUT AN ENTIRE
INDUSTRY ON THE MAP, BUT NOT
WITHOUT PAYING A HEAVY PRICE.
>> THE NEEDS ARE FAKE, THE
HIPS ARE FAKE, THE BACK IS
FULL METAL.
>> HE BECAME ONE OF THE MOST
RECOGNIZABLE AND BELOVED
FIGURES IN THE WORLD.
BEHIND THE SCENES, HIS LIFE
WAS CRUMBLING.
>> YOU LITERALLY HAD A GUN TOu
YOUR