TONIGHT.
WHY -- WENF
WATERTOWN AND POLICE ARE
RESPONDING.
BREAKING NEWS.
WE HAVE A SPECIAL EDITION
OF "SPECIAL REPORT'"
TOMORROW NIGHT.
CONTINUING COVERAGE HERE ON
FOX.
FAIR, BALANCED AND STILL
UNAFRAID.
>> Shepard: THERE IS
BREAKING NEWS NOW ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
AND IT APPEARS THAT
SOMETHING IS HAPPENING AT
THIS MOMENT IN WATERTOWN.
>> Shepard: CAN I TELL YOU
HERE WHERE WE ARE STANDING
IN BOSTON A FEW BLOCKS FROM
WHERE THE ORIGINAL
TERRORIST ATTACK HAPPENED,
POLICE AND SWAT VEHICLES
HAVE BEEN STREAMING TOWARD
WATER TOWN FOR THE LAST TWO
MINUTES.
THE FIRST SWAT VEHICLE
LIGHTS AND SIRENS FOR THE
FIRST TIME WE HAVE HEARD
HERE ALL DAY ACCORDING TO
THE CREWS WHO HAVE BEEN
HERE.
NOW THIS WORD FROM WATER
TOWN WHICH IS THE SPOT
WHERE WE HAVE BEEN FOCUSING
ALL DAY LONG.
SHOTS HAVE BEEN FIRED
ACCORDING TO LOCAL REPORTS
THERE THRORTS STREAMING IN
FOX 25 FROM BOSTON IS LIVE
ON SCENE THERE NOW.
LET'S LISTEN TO THEIR
COVERAGE.
>> IF I'M CORRECT HERE AND
I'M TOLD THIS IS THE SAME
AREA WHERE THE SUSPECTS
WERE SPOTTED LAST NIGHT AS
WELL W WAS
A REPORT THAT.
PHONE SHE IS ON FRANKLIN
STREET ANDEPORT
OF SHOTS FIRED.
WE HAD SEVERAL CALLS INTO
THE NEWSROOM.
THEN WE HAD REPORTS THAT
POLICE CARS WERE LEAVING
CRYSTAL HAINES IS ON THE
PHONE.
I HOPE YOU ARE SAFE.
THEY HEARD THE GUNSHOTS AND
ACTUALLY PULLED OVER.
CRYSTAL, CAN YOU SPEAK.
[DIAL TONE.
[OFFER THE LINE.
TRY TO REESTABLISH.
>> LIVE PICTURE OF THIS
AMBULANCE RIGHT ON FRANKLIN
STREET.
WE SEE A NUMBER OF
AUTHORITIES RIGHT HERE THEY
ARE BACKING IN A RESCUE
TRUCK.
HEAVY, HEAVY POLICE
PRESENCE RIGHT HERE.
SWAT TEAM AS WELL.
STATE POLICE ON HAND.
LOCAL AUTHORITIES.
SHOTS FIRED IN THIS
VICINITY IS WHAT WE ARE
GETTING CALLS OF.
>> OUR REPORTER CRYSTAL
HAINES JUST CALLED US.
UNFORTUNATELY WE JUST LOST
HER.
SHE SAID SHE AND
PHOTOGRAPHER MAT TOMLIN
WERE RIGHT IN THE AREA AND
ACTUALLY HEARD THOSE SHOTS
FIRED AND MOMENTS LATER A
RUSH OF LAW ENFORCEMENT
THE SCENE ON FRANKLIN
STREET WHICH IS ON WATER
TOWN.
IT IS A RESIDENTIAL AREA.
AND YOU CAN SEE THERE ARE A
BUNCH OF HOMES RIGHT THERE
THAT ARE VERY CLOSE
TOGETHER.
VERY ACTIVE SCENE.
>> Shepard: RIGHT NOW IN
DOWNTOWN BOSTON THERE ARE
POLICE AND SWAT VEHICLES AS
YOU CAN SEE STREAMING IN
THAT DIRECTION.
I SEE TWO MEN IN THE FRONT
OF THAT.
AND THEY ARE FLYING PAST A
LARGE SWAT HEADQUARTERS HAS
BEEN DOWN HERE AND THEY ARE
ALL HEADED RIGHT THIS
MINUTE TOWARD WATERTOWN
GETTING STRAIGHT ON TO THE HIGHWAY
AND IN THAT
DIRECTION.
WE CAN'T KNOW YET WHAT THE
REPORTS OF GUNFIRE ARE.
YOU CAN SEE FROM FOX 25 IN
BOSTON, THIS IS THE SAME
AREA THAT HAS BEEN CORDONED
OFF ALL DAY WHERE 20 BLOCKS
OF TOWN WERE SHUT DOWN FOR
THE DAY.
IT'S IT THE SPOT THAT BEGAN
THE LOCKDOWN OF BOSTON
FIRST WE KNOW IN THE
HISTORY OF THIS CITY WHERE
PEOPLE HAVE SHELTERED IN
THE DRIVE IN FROM THE
AIRPORT ALL DAY.
AS IF THERE WAS A HOLIDAY
FOR ALL RELIGIONS AND NO
ONE WAS MOVING ON ANY
STREET.
THE DRIVE FROM THE AIRPORT
TO DOWNTOWN BOSTON WAS LESS
THAN 10 MINUTES AND ANYBODY
WHO KNOWS ANYTHING ABOUT
THIS CITY KNOWS THAT MEANS
BOSTON WAS AT HOME.
NOW BACK TO WATERTOWN WHERE
THE POLICE ACTIVITY
CONTINUES.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
FOX 25 FROM BOSTON.
>> THE IDENTITY, THEY TOLD
US TO GET OUT OF THE AREA.
>> YOU HEARD MULTIPLE
SHOTS.
>> MULTIPLE SHOTS.
AT LEAST 20 SHOTS.
IT WAS ALL LIKE IT WAS
ALL -- IT WAS STATE POLICE
ON ONE SIDE.
THEY STARTED TO MOVE TO SEE
WHERE IT WAS COMING FROM
AND THEN ALL HELL BROKE
LOOSE.
>> THAT'S PAUL SUTHERLAND
HE ACTUALLY HEARD THE
SHOTS, TELLING US SEVERAL
SHOTS.
AT LEAST MORE THAN A DOZEN
POLICE CARS.
THEY ARE BLOCKING OFF THE
AREA AND AMBULANCES GOING
DOWN THE ROAD.
THERE IS AN ARMORED VEHICLE
JUST PULLING UP TO THE
SCENE RIGHT NOW.
WE HEARD POLICE TALKING
ABOUT HE IS IN A BOAT.
HE IS IN A BOAT.
>> HEATHER OUTSIDE OF
WATERTOWN MALL.
>> AND MARK, I JUST HEARD
FROM A VERY TRUSTWORTHY
STATE SHOTS FIRED AND A
SUSPECT IS DOWN.
AGAIN, THIS IS ACCORDING TO
A STATE POLICE SOURCE THAT
I HAVE DEVELOPED THROUGH MY
TIME HERE IS TELLING ME
THAT THE SUSPECT IS DOWN.
HERE IS ANOTHER TEAM OF
MILITARY PERSONNEL GOING
DOWN THE ROAD.
STILL A VERY ACTIVE SCENE.
CAN SEE THEY ARE NOT
SPEEDING ANYMORE AND THE
SIRENS ARE NOT BLARING.
IT MIGHT BE THAT THIS
SUSPECT IS INDEED DOWN AS
MY STATE POLICE SOURCE IS
TELLING ME.
>> LIVE PICTURES OF
FRANKLIN STREET AS WELL
WHERE WE CAN SEE THE STATE
POLICE AND SQUAD TEAM
MEMBERS AND ALSO MEMBERS OF
THE LAW ENFORCEMENT
COMMUNITY OF WATERTOWN ARE
THERE AS WELL.
THEY SEEM TO BE WALKING.
YES, THEY HAVE GUNS DRAWN
BUT THEY ARE WALKING AROUND
AND MILLING ABOUT MORE THAN
RUNNING TO AND FRO
ANYWHERE.
AND WE ALSO HAD A FIRE
RESCUE TRUCK BACK INTO THE
AREA AS WELL.
AN AMBULANCE TYPE VEHICLE
OBVIOUSLY.
SHOULD SOMEONE SUFFER ANY
TYPE OF WOUNDS OR INJURIES
AT THIS POINT.
SO, RIGHT NOW IT SEEMS
FAIRLY PEACEFUL WHEN WE
HEAR WHAT PAUL SUTHERLAND,
AN EYEWITNESS JUST TOLD
JARED HOLBROOK ON THE
PHONE.
TOLD HIM IN PERSON AND US
ON THE PHONE THE FACT THAT
HE THOUGHT HE HEARD AS MANY
AS 20 SHOTS.
JARED HOLBROOK, AGAIN
COULD YOU GIVE US THE EXACT
LOCATION OF THE HOUSE WHERE
AUTHORITIES ARE RIGHT NOW? WE WERE
QUITE
CLOSE AND THEN THEY JUST
STARTED PUSHING US BACK.
ALL OF THESE CARS STARTED
COMING RIGHT AT US.
WE HAD TO JUMP OUT OF THE
WAY.
POLICE WANT TO RUSH TO THE
SCENE AND STATE POLICE
WERE, YOU KNOW, MAKING SURE
EVERYBODY WAS BACK.
THEY WERE PUSHING US BACK
SEVERAL BLOCKS AND WE
DIDN'T REALIZE HOW CLOSE WE
WERE.
RIGHT NOW I'
HIDING BEHIND A TREE RIGHT
NOW AND LOOKING AT THE
SCENE AND SEEING THE
ARMORED VEHICLE AND THE
HELICOPTERS ABOVE US RIGHT
NOW.
SEVERAL POLICE OFFICERS AND
YOU HEARD PAUL SUTHERLAND
SAYING MULTIPLE SHOTS
FIRED.
HE THOUGHT HE HEARD AS MANY
AS 20.   CAN HEAR THE
SOUND.
GOT MORE POLICE ACTIVITY
COMING IN UNMARKED CARS
RIGHT NOW.
AND A LOT OF COMMOTION.
WE HEARD OFFICERS TALKING
ABOUT WE GOT HIM.
HE IS IN A BOAT WITH A
CANVAS COVER AND SOMEBODY
WAS POKING HOLES IN THE
CANVAS COVER IN THE BOAT.
AND THEN THAT'S WHEN PAUL
SUTHERLAND HEARD THE SHOTS
SHORTLY AFTER THAT.
>> HE WOULD WANTED TO BRING
BACK WHAT HEATHER SAID.
POLICE SOURCE TELLING HER
THAT THE SECOND SUSPECT IS
DOWN ON FRANKLIN STREET
THAT WOULD BE SUSPECT
NUMBER 2 WE BELIEVE.
AT LEAST THE SUSPECT THEY
ARE GOING AFTER RIGHT NOW.
IF WE CAN THROW UP A GOOGLE
MAP, AGAIN, THERE WAS A
BOAT TRAILER IN THE YARD OF
THE HOME IN THE BACKYARD.
NOW, JARED IS TELLING US
OBVIOUSLY THAT THERE WAS A
BOAT ON THAT
AND THAT THE INDIVIDUAL MAY
HAVE BEEN IN THERE TRY TO
POKE HOLES TO SEE WHO WAS
OUTSIDE.
HE MAY HAVE BEEN HIDING IN
THAT BOAT WITH THAT COVER
OVER IT.
>> AGAIN HEAVY POLICE
PRESENCE ON FRANKLIN STREET
IN WATER TOWN.
THIS COMES ABOUT 40 MINUTES
AFTER A PRESS CONFERENCE
WHERE THEY SAID THEY DID
NOT HAVE A SUSPECT.
SUDDENLY NOW FIVE
MINUTES TO GO WE GET A
NUMBER OF CALLS FROM PEOPLE
SAYING SHOTS FIRED.
SOME 20 SHOTS FIRED IN THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD IN WATER TOWN
AS ONE OF THE NEIGHBORS
SAID ALL HELL BROKE LOOSE.
YOU CAN IMAGINE A FRANTIC
SCENE.
HEATHER SAID FROM HER
SOURCE FROM THE STATE
POLICE SUSPECT IS DOWN.
>> LIVE LOOK AT FRANKLIN
STREET IN WATERTOWN WHERE
MOMENTS AGO THERE WAS SOME
TYPE OF POLICE ACTIVITY OFF
THE CHARTS TO ACCORDING TO
ONE OF THE PEOPLE THERE WHO
SAID ALL HELL BROKE LOOSE
AS YOU MENTIONED.
AND THEY APPEARED TO HAVE
POSSIBLY HAVE THE SECOND
SUSPECT IN THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBING THAT TOOK
PLACE ON MONDAY.
A SOURCE TELLING OUR OWN
HEATHER THAT THE SUSPECT IS
DOWN.
>> LET'S GO TO BOB WARD WHO
IS STANDING BY NOW.
WHAT DO YOU MAKE OF THIS,
BOB?
>> WELL, I HEARD THE
GUNSHOT.
IT HAD TO BE ABOUT 30
SHOTS.
THERE WAS A RAPID FIRE
BARRAGE.
JUST LIKE A ROLL OF FIRE
CRACKERS GETTING SHOT OFF.
AND WE WERE -- IT'S JUST
ABOUT A BLOCK AWAY FROM
WHERE WE WERE DOING OUR
LIVE SHOT.
WE ARE STILL ARSENAL
STREET.
OVER NEAR FRANKLINEET
RIGHT NOW.
AND WHEN WE PULLED UP, WEAT RIGHT
ALL
KINDS OF POLICE TO THE AREA
RUNNING TO THE SCENE.
HAD THEIR HANDS ON THEIR
HIPS WHERE THEY WOULD HAVE
THEIR GUNS OVERHEAD.
THERE IS A STATE POLICE
HOSPITAL OVERHEAD
MONITORING THE SITUATION.
SO, HEAVY POLICE PRESENCE
HERE.
PEOPLE HERE ON THE STREET
JUST NEIGHBORS HERE ARE
REACTING TO THIS.
THEY THINK THAT SUSPECT
NUMBER TWO HAS BEEN FOUND.
IT'S VERY TENSE.
I'M 50 TO 100 YARDS AWAY.
I'M WATCHING WHAT'S GOING
ON.
A LOT OF MOVEMENT DOWN
HERE.
A LOT OF THE STATE
TROOPERS, ALL THE POLICE
OFFICERS THAT WERE ON SCENE
ALL DAY LONG INSIDE THE
PERIMETER WERE BEING
RELIEVED AND MANY OF THEM
WERE RE-ROUTED RIGHT HERE A
FEW BLOCKS AWAY INTO THIS
AREA.
WHERE THE SHOTS WERE FIRED.
>> BOB, I JUST WANT TO TELL
YOU WHAT WE ARE SEEING
HERE.
WE ARE SEEING FAMILIES
BEING EVACUATED.
ESCORTED BY POLICE DOWN THE
STREET IN A VERY CALM
MANNER BUT MOVING ALONG AT
A VERY GOOD CLIP AS WELL.
OBVIOUSLY IN THE VICINITY
OF THE SHOTS WHERE THE
SHOTS WERE FIRED AND WHAT
YOU HEARD.
WE HAD AN EYEWITNESS JUST
TELL JARED HOLBROOK 20
THOUGHTS YOU SAY 30 SHOTS.
QUITE A BIT.
>> IT WAS A LOT.
I WASN'T COUNTING THEM.
IT WAS A LOT.
IT WAS A LOT OF SHOTS.
JUST AS IF FIRE CRACKERS
GETTING LIT OFF.
A WHOLE ROLL OF FIRE
CRACKERS.
THAT'S WHAT IT SOUNDED
LIKE.
IT WAS A LOT.
WHEN I SAY 30 DON'T TAKE IT
LITERALLY BUT IT WAS A LOT
OF SHOTS BEING FIRED.
A BARRAGE OF GUNFIRE.
>> WE WERE JUST WATCHING A
FAMILY WALK BY.
A WOMEN WITH HER CHILDREN
AND THE PANIC ON THEIR
FACES AFTER LISTENING TO
WHETHER IT WAS 20 OR 30
SHOTS FIRED YOU CAN'T
IMAGINE WHAT THESE PEOPLE
IN WATERTOWN.
>> SHEPARD SMITH IN BOSTON
MONITORING FROM DOWNTOWN
THE POLICE DEPARTMENT IN
BOSTON HAS JUST ISSUED AN
ALERT FOR ALL BOSTONIANS TO
SHELTER IN PLACE NOW THOUGH
IT SOUNDS AS IF THE NEWS
MAY BE GOOD OUT OF
WATERTOWN.
WE JUST GOT THIS.
A WOMAN CALLED POLICE IN
WATER TOWN AND SAID THAT
THE COPS HAD EARLIER SWEPT
THIS BOAT ABOUT WHICH THE
LOCAL ANCHORS ARE SPEAKING
BUT NOW SHE SEES THE SHED
DOOR IS OPEN.
SHE SEES BLOODY CLOTHES AND
BLOOD ON THE BOAT.
AND AS A RESULT, SHE CALLS
UP AND SAYS PLEASE COME
CHECK THIS OUT.
THEY DID AND IT WAS AFTER
THAT, WE'RE LED TO BELIEVE
THAT SHE'S SHOTS BEGAN
RAPID FIRE, 20 TO 30 SHOTS
ACCORDING TO THE LOCALS.
OUR LOCAL STATION IS NOW
REPORTING THAT THE SECOND
SUSPECT IN THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBING IS NOW
DOWN ON FRANKLIN STREET IN
WATERTOWN.
LET'S GET RIGHT BACK TO
LOCAL COVERAGE.
WE HAVE REPORTERS AND
PRODUCERS ON SCENE AND
WE'LL TAKE YOU BACK THERE
THIS IS BREAKING NEWS
COVERAGE ON FOX NEWS
CHANNEL WITH WFXT IN
BOSTON.
>> YEAH, YOU ARE RIGHT.
AS THE SUN GOES DOWN.
>> FOX 25 BOB ON THE SCENE
AND JARED HOLBROOK FOX 25
OUT THERE AS WELL.
AGAIN TO REPORT AND REPEAT
OUR HEATHER IS SAYING THAT
A SOURCE TELLS HER THAT
SHOTS WERE FIRED AND WE
CLEARLY KNOW THAT NOW AND
THAT THE SUSPECT IS DOWN.
THAT IS THE WORD.
FROM POLICE, WHETHER OR NOT
THAT SUSPECT IS DECEASED AT
THIS POINT, WE DO NOT KNOW.
IF IT IS, IN FACT,
POTENTIALLY SUSPECT NUMBER
2.
BEAR IN MIND THAT HIS
BROTHER WAS SAID TO
POSSIBLY HAVE HAD ANOSIVE DEVICE LAST
NIGHT.
ON HIS PERSON.
IT WOULD TAKE A WHILE TO
GET CLOSE TO SUSPECT NUMBER
2.
>> JUST ABOUT 40 MINUTES
AGO THE GOVERNOR SAYING WE
ARE BACK TO MONDAY, MEANING
THEY DID NOT APPREHEND THE
SUSPECT TODAY THAT THEY HAD
TO FOLLOW NEW LEADS.
NOW BELOOK AT THIS AND GET
NEW INFORMATION THAT SHOTS
HAVE BEEN FIRED SOME 20 TO
30 SHOTS FIRED IN WATERTOWN  STREET.
NOT FAR FROM WHERE WE HAVE
BEEN SITUATED ALL DAY LONG.
STATE POLICE ARE FLOODING
THIS AREA.
THEY ARE EVACUATING THE
AREA WE HAVE SEEN FAMILIES
RUNNING OUT WITH TERROR ON
THEIR FACE.
BUT, AGAIN SHOTS FIRED AT
LEAST 20 SHOTS.
HEATHER HEARD FROM A SOURCE   A SUSPECT
IS DOWN.
A SUSPECT IS DOWN.
AND THERE IS IS HOPE THAT
THIS IS SUSPECT NUMBER 2.
>> LOOKING AT FRANKLIN
STREET HEAVY POLICE
ACTIVITY.
FAMILIES BEING ESCORTED.
20 MINUTES AGO REPORTS OF
SHOTS FIRED THEY CAME INTO
OUR NEWSROOM FROM NEIGHBORS
AND WE WENT FROM HAVING
VERY LITTLE GOING ON
OBVIOUSLY FOLLOWING THAT
PRESS CONFERENCE VERY
MELLOW IN THE STREETS OF
WATERTOWN.
THOUGH PEOPLE ARE ON EDGE.
THEN SUDDENLY WE HAD A NUMBER OF POLICE
VEHICLES
ALL START TO MAKE THEIR WAY
DOWN THE STREETS OF
WATERTOWN.
AND OUR HEATHER AGAIN FROM
THE SOURCE SAYING THAT,
INDEED, SHOTS WERE FIRED
AND THE SUSPECT IS DOWN.
JARED HOLBROOK IF HE IS ON
THE LINE LIKE TO BRING HIM
BACK MORE ABOUT THIS
POTENTIAL HIDING SPOT FOR
THE INDIVIDUAL AND NOW WE
SEE IF YOU LOOK FURTHER ON
DOWN, SOME MORE WELL-ARMED
OFFICIALS.
BOB, DO YOU HAVE AN
ADVANTAGE POINT DOWN TO THE
EDGE OF THIS STREET?
WE SAW PEOPLE WITH WEAPONS
RUSHING HURRIED AROUND THE
EDGE OF THE HOME AT THE END
OF THE STREET.
>> NO, I'M ON [INAUDIBLE]
[AUDIO CUTTING OUT]
>> EXACT AREA.
>> HERE IS WHAT WE KNOW
NOW.
I'M GETTING UPDATE RIGHT
HOLD ON ONE SECOND, PLEASE.
I UNDERSTAND WE ARE NOW
GETTING INFORMATION THAT
THEY ARE INDEED AND WE
TALKED ABOUT THE
POSSIBILITY OF EXPLOSIVES
GOING TO GET A ROBOT TO GO
IN TOWARDS WHAT JARED
HOLBROOK DESCRIBED EARLIER
AS A BEAT ON A TRAILER IN A
BACKYARD.
THEY WANT TO BRING THIS IN
TO TRY AND INVESTIGATE AND
THERE IT IS RIGHT THERE.
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE TALKINGOUT RIGHT
THERE.
THEY ARE GOING TO BRING IN
A DEVICE THAT CAN GO UP.
A ROBOTIC DEVICE THAT WILL
BE ABLE TO SEARCH THE BOAT
AND THAT AREA AND IN THE
BACKYARD WHERE IT IS BEEN
TOLD TO US AND JARED
HOLBROOK REPORTED EARLIER
THAT POTENTIALLY THE
SUSPECT WAS HIDING IN THAT
BOAT UNDER ONE OF THOSE
CANOPIES YOU PUT ON TO
WINTERIZE YOUR BOAT.
AND PERHAPS HE WAS HIDING
IN THERE.
SO THEY ARE GOING TO TAKE
THIS VERY CAREFULLY ONE
STEP AT A TIME.
>> Shepard: SHEPARD SMITH
IN BOSTON NOW.
THIS IS WHAT WE BELIEVE HAS
HAPPENED FROM THE BEST OF
THE REPORTING AT THIS
MOMENT.
15, 20 MINUTES AGO AS IT
HAS BEEN DESCRIBED TO US.
A WOMAN CALLS THE POLICE
THERE AND SAYS THEY CHECKED
MY BOAT, BUT NOW THE DOOR
IS OPEN AND THERE IS BLOOD
THERE.
THE POLICE GO OUT, FIND IT,
AT SOME POINT SHOTS BEGIN
TO FIRE.
ACCORDING TO WITNESSES SOME
30 SHOTS FIRED.
IN FACT, HEARING IT ALL ON
SCENE IS OUR PRODUCER CHRIS
LIABLE WHO IS LIVE ON THE
LIVE LINE WITH US NOW.
CHRIS, I GUESS THIS WAS
WHAT, 10, 15 MINUTES AGO?
TELL US HOW IT STARTED.
>> IT WAS 15 MINUTES AGO
RIGHT AFTER THE PRESS
CONFERENCE ENDED.
ALLOWING PEOPLE TO GET
OUTDOORS AGAIN.
THE BAN WAS LIFTED ON
PEOPLE HAVING TO STAY
INDOORS.
TALKING TO A FEW NEIGHBORS.
I WAS JUST ACTUALLY DOING
AN INTERVIEW ABOUT ONE OF
THEM WHAT IT WAS LIKE BEING
INDOORS FOR THE LAST 24
HOURS OR SO WHEN WE HEARD
PROBABLY ABOUT 10 TO 20 IF
NOT MORE GUNSHOTS GO OFF.
WE STOPPED, WE RAN OVER
HERE, WE SAW POLICE
FLOODING THE SCENE.
A LOT OF MOVEMENT.
WE SEEN A CONSTANT STREAM
OF POLICE CARS WITH THEIR
SIRENS ON, RUSHING TOWARDS
WHAT WOULD APPEAR TO BE THE
SITE, ABOUT A MILE WEST OF
US.
WE'RE KIND OF BEING HELD IN
PLACE RIGHT NOW.
WE CAN'T GO ANYWHERE.
WE ARE ON LOCKDOWN.
YEAH, IT WAS PRETTY INTENSE
THERE.
>> Shepard: CHRIS, BOSTON
HAS NOW RETURNED TO A STATE
OF ALERT AS WELL.
THE CITY POLICE DEPARTMENT
HERE IN BOSTON PROPER HAS
SENT OUT A TWEET ASKING ALL
BOSTON RESIDENTS TO SHELTER
IN PLACE AS THEY ASK THEM
TO DO ALL DAY.
AND, FRANKLY THEY
RESPECTED THAT REQUEST AND
DID SO.
CAN YOU TELL BY WANDERING
ABOUT THIS CITY.
AND NOW AUTHORITIES SENDING
IN A ROBOT TO MAKE SURE
THERE ARE NO EXPLOSIVES.
IT'S THE BELIEF AT THIS
MOMENT THAT SUSPECT NUMBER
2 IN THE BOSTON MARATHON
BOMBING IS DOWN ON FRANKLIN
STREET IN WATERTOWN
MASSACHUSETTS.
THAT IS NOT YET CONFIRMED
BY POLICE.
BUT WE KNOW THERE IS
SOMEONE DOWN.
AND WE HAVE GIVEN YOU THE
SCENARIOS.
WE KNOW IT TO THIS MOMENT.
WE ARE WAITING TO HEAR FROM
POLICE AS THEY MOVE IN WITH
THAT ROBOT.
GO BACK TO WATERTOWN AND
LIVE COVERAGE FROM WFXT FOX
NEWS IN BOSTON.
>> GAVE HER THE INFORMATION
THAT SHOTS HAD BEEN FIRED.
SUSPECT WAS DOWN.
HERE AGAIN WE SEE MORE
PEOPLE RUNNING DOWN THE
STREET.
FAMILIES WERE EVACUATING
EARLIER RUNNING AT A GOOD
CLIP.
HE THEY DIDN'T WANT TO SEE
TO MOVE THEM TOO FAST.
THEY WEREN'T RUNNING.
NOW YOU ARE SEEING MEMBERS
OF LAW ENFORCEMENT THAT ARE
PICKING UP THE PACE A BIT.
THE SCENE IS BECOMING A
LITTLE BIT MORE ACTIVE DOWN
THERE TOWARDS THE END.
WE DID SEE HEAVILY ARMED
OFFICERS WITH GUNS DRAWN.
GOING AROUND THE BASE --
YOU SEE THE WINDOWS DOWN
THERE WITH THE WHITE
SHUTTERS, THEY WERE WALKING
AROUND THE FRONT OF THAT
HOME.
BUT NOW WE SEE SOME PEOPLE
MERELY WALKING UP TO IT AT
THIS POINT.
BUT, AGAIN VERY FLUID
SCENE IN WATER TOWN.
IF YOU ARE JUST JOINING US,
REPORTS THAT ABOUT 20
MINUTES AGO SHOTS FIRED
AFTER THINGS HAD KIND OF
CALMED DOWN A BIT AND THE
PRESS CONFERENCE SAID, YOU
KNOW, IT'S TIME TO LIFT THE
LOCKDOWN ON THE TOWN AND
WILL INCREASE OUR PRESENCE
AS FAR AS SECURITY GOES BUT
TO GO ABOUT YOUR BUSINESS
AND BE VIGILANT, NOW
EVERYBODY WAS AT THAT PRESS
CONFERENCE IS ON FRANKLIN
STREET.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
IT REALLY GOT QUIET AFTER
THAT PRESS CONFERENCE.
THERE WAS THIS THOUGHT OF,
YOU KNOW, WE ARE DONE FOR
THE NIGHT AND YOU KNEW THAT
THEY WERE GOING TO WORK
HARD THROUGH THE NIGHT BUT
WE FELT LIKE THINGS HAD
QUIETED DOWN.
BUT IF YOU LOOK AT THE
SCENE, IT'S A WHOLE ANOTHER
STORY AND IT'S JUST CRAZY
HOW THINGS CAN CHANGE IN A
MATTER OF A SECOND.
LOOK AT THE SCENE.
WE HAVE GOT THE STATE
POLICE AND EVERYONE BACK AT
THE SCENE ON FRANKLIN
STREET IN WATERTOWN WHERE
NOT FAR FROM THE WATERTOWN
MALL.
PROBABLY A MILE OR LESS.
THIS IS IN A POPULATED
AREA.
LOTS OF HOMES AND WE JUST
SAW MOMENTS AGO FAMILIES
RUNNING OUT IN TERROR AFTER
THEY HEARD 20 TO 30 SHOTS
FIRED IN THEIR
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> OKAY.
I WANT TO GO TO THE PHONE
NOW.
WE HAVE MARY SULLIVAN,
RESIDENT OF WATERTOWN AND
MARY, IT'S MARK ALONG WITH
SARAH UNDERWOOD.
I UNDERSTAND YOU WITNESSED
WHAT WENT DOWN ON FRANKLIN
STREET EARLIER.
TELL US ABOUT IT.
>> YES.
WE WERE -- THE GOVERNOR HAD
JUST SAID THERE WAS A LIFT.
AND SO WE KIND OF HOOKED UP
OUR DOG AND MY 20-YEAR-OLD
CHILDREN AND MY SON'S
GIRLFRIEND WAS WITH US AND
WE WERE COMING DOWN RUSSELL
AVE AND WE WERE READY TO
GET TO THE END OF RUSSELL
AVE TALKING TO A STUDENT
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN YOU
HEARD THIS SERIES OF
GUNSHOTS.
AND AS HE WE RAN ACROSS
RUSSELL TO THE CORNER OF
RUSSELL -- ALL THESE CARS
AND POLICE CARS AND HUMVEES
AND POLICE AND EVERYONE
JUST STARTED TO RUN DOWN TO
FRANKLIN STREET, WHICH IS A
VERY RESIDENTIAL AREA AND
SO WE JUST STARTED FILMING
AND THE GUN -- IT WAS JUST
LIKE A VERY QUICK LIKE
ALMOST 30 SECONDS OF
GUNSHOTS.
THEN 2 STOPPED AND THEN
THEY JUST SHUT THE ROADS
DOWN AND THEN EVERYONE IS
HERE.
LIKE THERE IS AMBULANCES
AND NEIGHBORS AND IT WAS
JUST CRAZY BECAUSE THE
WHOLE SERIES HAS BEEN UP IN
THE EAST END AND THIS IS
JUST A FEW BLOCKS AWAY FROM
WHERE WE LIVE.
WE JUST THOUGHT, YOU KNOW,
WE WOULD GO WALK THE DOG.
YOU KNOW, WE FELT SAFE AND
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN WE
HEAR ALL THIS GUNSHOT IN
OUR NEIGHBORHOOD.
SO WE DON'T KNOW IF THEY
HAVE GOTTEN SOMEONE BUT IT
SEEMS THAT SOMETHING BIG
HAPPENED HERE.
>> SURE, WHAT EXACTLY DID
YOU SEE THOUGH IN TERMS OF
LAW ENFORCEMENT AND HOW
THEY WERE CARRYING
THEMSELVES?
>> THE LAW ENFORCEMENT
WERE -- WHEN WE CAME AROUND
THE CORNER, THERE WASN'T A
LOT OF LAW ENFORCEMENT
GOING UP ON AUBURN.
WE WERE TOLD WE COULDN'T
COME UP.
SO WE JUST WENT A BACK WAY
ON RUSSELL AVE.
WE GO DOWN FRANKLIN STREET
AS WE WERE APPROACHING
AUBURN STREET, ALL WE HEARD
WAS GUNFIRE.  OW IF THEY KIND
OF SLIPPED IN BUT WE
DIDN'T SEE A LOT OF
PRESENCE AND THEN WITHIN --
I CAN'T TELL YOU WITHIN
TWO MINUTES THE PLACE WAS
SUR S
COMPLETELY SURROUNDED.
>> HOW FAR AWA
HOME FROM THE CURRENT SCENE
THAT WE ARE LOOKING AT ON
FRANKLIN STREET.
>> I LIVE ON MOUNT AUBURN
STREET.
MY HOME IS THREE BLOCKS
>> SO YOU ARE ALLOWED TO GO
BACK HOME?'M SORRY?
>> YOU ARE ALLOWED TO GO
HOME?
>> WE'RE NOT GOING BACK
HOME.
RIGHT NOW THERE -- THEY ARE
LITERALLY -- THERE ARE JUS
HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS OF   AND POLICE
ARE
HERE AND UNMARKED TRUCKS
AN AMBULANCES AND IT'S --
YOU KNOW EVERYONE IS KIND
OF AT A IT STAND STILL.
SHOOTING, THERE WAS
>> JOINING US ON THE PHONE
IS MARY SULLIVAN A WITNESS
TO THE SHOOTINGS THAT JUST
TOOK PLACE EARLIER AT ABOUT
7:20.
YOU HAVE WALKED YOUR DOG.
THE
STREET.
FRANKL HAVE YOU EVER SEEN A BOAT
IN THE THERE?
>> NO.
SOMEONE HAD ASKED ME THAT
BEFORE.
I CAN'T -- YOU KNOW, I'M
THINKING AND I CAN'T RECALL
EVER NOTICING A BOAT.
IT IS A NEIGHBORHOOD OF
LARGER HOMES.
AND IT'S A VER
VERY
NEIGHBORHOOD.
NO, I HAVE NEVER HAVE
WALK MY DOG THERE EVERY
DAY.
GE ENOUGH
IN THE BACKYARD TO HAVE ONE
ON A TRAIL PERHAPS?
>> I HAVEN'T
IT LOOKS LIKE FROM WHAT I'M
LOOKING AT, IT LOOKS LIKE.
>> Shepard: GOOD EVENING
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
WE INTERRUPT REGULAR
STATIONS
AND FOX STATIONS TO BRING
YOU BREAKING NEWS FROM
WATER TOWN, MASSACHUSETTS.
BELIEF NOW THAT
THE SECOND SUSPECT IN THE
BOSTON MARATHON SHOOTING IS
DOWN ON THE STREET IN WATER
TOWN MASS.  SECOND SUSPECT
MAY  BEENINCAPACITATED.
THIS WENT DOWN ABOUT 20
MINUOMAN IN
WATER TOWN IN AENTIAL
NEIGHBORHOOD CALLED POLICE
IT'S OUR STANDING TONFORM
THEM THAT POLICE HAD SWEPT
HER BOAT AND HER BOAT HOUSE
EARLIER IN THE DAY AND
FOUND THAT THERE WAS
NOTHING THERE.
YET, SHE LOO
WINDOW AND SAW THAT THE
DOOR OF THE SHED DOOR WAS
OPEN.
AND SHE NOTICED WHAT LOOKED
BOAT.
THE -- AND SHE SAID THAT
THERE WERE BLOODY CLOTHES
THERE AS WELL.
SUGGESTING POSSIBLY THAT
SOMEBODY MAY HAVE CHANGED
THERE FAST FORWARD JUST A
FEW MINUTES.
THE POLICE ARRIVE AND  OUR STANDING
FROM THE
REPORTING OF WFXT
IN BOSTON AND A REPORTER
THERE THAT WHEN POLICE
ARRIVED THERE WAS A BARRAGE
OF GUNFIRE.
MULTIPLE WITNESSES HAVE
ALREADY REPORTED SOME 20 TO THERE
IN WATERTOWN.
NOW, POLIC
A ROBOT TO MAKE SURE THAT
THERE ARE NOLOSIVE
DEVICES THERE.
AS YOU MAY KNOW, WHEN THEKEDOWN HAPPENED,
SUSPECT NUMBER 1 IN THE
OVERNIGHT HOURS IN THE
EARLY MORNING HOURS OF
TODAY, THERE WERE MULTIPLE
EXPLOSIVES, ONE OF THESE
PRESSURE COOKER BOMBS WAS
THROWN OUT A WINDOW.
THANKFULN'T
EXPLODE IN THE WAY THEY HAD
HELPED.
MAKESHIFT GRENADES.
NOW THEY ARE MAKING SURE
THERE ARE NO MORE
EXPLOSIVES THAT MIGHT WELL,
HARM ANYONE ELSE.
IN THE MOMENTS AFTER THIS
HAPPENED WE ARE
DOWNTOWN BOSTON AND SWATTED
VEHICLES
BEGAN STREAMING TO THE
TO HEAD TO
WATERTOWN WHICH IS JUST A
SHORT DISTANCE AWAY FROM
HERE.
AND AT THE SAME TIME, WFXT
IN BOSTON OUR LOCAL STATION
NUMBER OF REPORTERS THERE
ON SCENE HAD EYEWITNESS
REPORTS FROM THEIR OWN
REPORTERS AND FROM A LOCAL
RESIDENT WHO SAW THIS AND
SAID THAT THEIR ENTIRE
NEIGHBORHOOD IS NOW ON
LOCKDOWN.
IN ADDITION, THE BOSTON
POLICE DEPARTMENT HAS SENT
OUT AN URGENT TWEET OVER
TWITTER SAYING THAT BOSTON
IS BACK TO A -- SHELTER IN
PLACE ORDER FOR THE
CITIZENS OF THIS CIT
IN THE WAKE OF THIS
BREAKING NEWS, THE HOPE IS
THAT THE SECOND SUSPECT IS
DOWN, THAT THERE A
OTHERS INVOLVED IN THIS AND
THAT BOSTON CAN REST A
LITTLE BIT MORE EASILY
TONIGHT.
BUT IT'S WAY TOO EARLY TO
GO THERE WE HEARD FROM
AUTHORITIES EARLIER TODAY
THEY CAN'T BE SURE THAT
THERE IS NO ONE ELSE
INVOLVED BESIDES THESE TWO
SUSPECTS.
THEY CAN'T BE SURE THAT
THERE IS NO LARGER
ORGANIZATION THAT MAY HAVE
PLAYED A PART IN THIS.
THE FACT I
KNOW AND WE CAN'T KNOW.'S GET
RIGHT TO WATER TOWN WHERE
OUR PRODUCER CHRIS LAIBLE
IS STANDING BY.
HE WAS THERE WHEN THE
GUNSHOTS BEGAN TO BE FIRED.
F THEM
IS MY STANDING.
>> YEAH, SHEP, THERE WERE.
THERE WAS A FEW DOZEN OF
THEM THAT WE HEARD.
WE WERE JUST ON THE SIDE
STREETS RIGHT THERE WHERE
THE MEDIA HAS BEEN STAGING
HERE FOR THE LAST 24 HOURS
ABOUT, MAYBE 16 HOURS.
TALKING TO RESIDENTS THAT
WERE JUST COMING OUT OF
THEIR HOMES AFTER THE ORDER
WAS LIFTED TALKING ABOUT
WHAT THEIR EXPERIENCES WERE
LIKE OVER THE LAST 16
HOURS, HOW NERVOUS THEY
WERE GOING THROUGH ANOTHER
NIGHT NOT KNOWING IF THE
SUSPECT WAS CAUGHT OR
KNOWING THAT HE WASN'T
CAUGHT.
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN WE
HEARD GUNSHOTS.
WE CAME BACK OVER TO OUR
CAMERA POSITION, COP
STARTED SCREAMING DOWN THE
STREET TOWARDS THE SOUND OF
THE GUNSHOTS.
THERE IS A LOT OF ACTIVITY.
WE'RE STUCK HERE RIGHT NOW.
POLICE HAVE LOCKED DOWN THE
AREA.
IT SEEMS LIKE RESIDENTS ARE
CURIOSITY IS GETTING THE
BETTER OFTHEY ARE COMING OUT OF
THEIR HOMES TO TAKE A LOOK
I CAN SEE A COUPLE BLOCKS THERE IS
A GROUP OF
THEM FORMING.
POLICE ARE KEEPING THEM OFF
TO THE SIDE ON THE SIDE OF
THE ROAD.
BUT IT IS A FLUID SITUATION
HERE TO SAY THE LEAST.
WITHOUT DOUBT, CHRIS.
LOOKING AT THE VIDEO I CAN TELL FROM
WATCHING THROUGHOUT THE DAY
THE MEANING OF ALL THOSE ON
SCENE IN WATER TOWN IS
COMPLETELY DIFFERENT THAN
WE HAVE SEEN SINCE THE
EARLY MORNING HOURS TOY
WHEN ALL OF THIS BEGAN.
ONCE THE SUN C
WAS A VERY TENSE PLACE.
IT LOOKED LIKE AN ARMED
CITY AT WAR.
THERE WERE MILITARY
VEHICLES AND SWAT IN FULL
BODY ARMOR.
AND REALLY THE CITY HAD
BEEN LOCKED DOWN TO A
DEGREE THAT BOSTON HAS
NEVER EXPERIENCED IN ITS
LONG AND STORIC HISTORY.
BECAUSETONIANS RESPONDED
WELL ESPECIALLY THERE IN
WATER TOWN.
WE ARE GETTING BACKGROUND
INFORMATION OF GREAT
INTEREST TO ME.
WE HAVE JUST GOTTEN THIS
FROM A SOURCE AT THE FBI.
THIS IS FROM OUR JUSTICE
PRODUCER MICHAEL LAVIGNE.
I'M JUST GOING TO QUOTE
THIS FOR YOU.
TWO YEARS AGO AN UNNAMED
FOREIGN GOVERNMENT ASKED
THE FBI TO CHECK OUT THE
OLDER OF THESE TWO
BROTHERS.
THE BROTHER WHO DIED LAST
NIGHT IN A SHOOTOUT WITH
POLICE BECAUSE THAT FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT, NOT THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT, IT NOTES HERE,
HAD CONCERNS ABOUT POSSIBLE
EXTREMIST TIES.
TWO YEARS AGO WITH A MAN
WHO DIED OVERNIGHT.
THE FBI FULLY SCRUBBED THIS
INDIVIDUAL SCRUBBED
MEANING THEY CHECKED OUT
EVERYTHING ABOUT HIM AND
THEN EVENTUALLY WENT --
ENDED UP TALKING TO HIM
QUOTING NOW:  WE DID NOT
FIND ANYTHING, THE OFFICIAL
SAYS.
THE FBI REPORTED BACK TO
THE FOREIGN GOVERNMENT THAT
IT FOUND NOTHING BUT TOLD
THE FOREIGN GOVERNMENT TO
FOLLOW UP IF THEY HAD ANY
MORE CONCERNS.
AND THAT FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT, WHATEVER
GOVERNMENT IT IS, AND MOST
LIKELY WE WILL LEARN THAT
WITHIN THE HOURS OR DAYS
AHEAD, THE FOREIGN
GOVERNMENT NEVER FOLLOWED
UP, QUOTE, IN ANY WAY
SHAPE, OR FORM.
AGAIN, THAT'S FROM A SOURCE
CLOSE TO THE FBI.
FAST FORWARD NOW TO JUST A
FEW MINUTES BEFORE 7:00
TONIGHT IN WATERTOWN
MASSACHUSETTS WHERE SHOTS
RANG OUT.
NOW THERE IS A ROBOT GOING
IN IT'S OUR STANDING TO
CHECK TO SEE IF THERE ARE
ANY BOMBS THERE.
A ROBOT WITH CAMERA SO
AUTHORITIES ON SCENE CAN
LOOK AND SEE FOR THEMSELVES
WHETHER THIS MAN WHO IS
DOWN IN THE STREET IN THE
CITY THERE IN A RESIDENTIAL
NEIGHBORHOOD MAY HAVE LEFT
ANY EXPLOSIVE DEVICES
BEHIND.
AND AT SOME POINT, IN THE
NEAR TERM, WE EXPECT TO
HEAR FROM POLICE ABOUT WHAT
HAS JUST HAPPENED AND
WHETHER IT'S POSSIBLE THAT
BOSTON AND THE UNITED
STATES' NIGHTMARE IS AT
LEAST DRAWING TO A CLOSE
AT LEASE -- LEAST THIS
STAGE OF IT.
WFXT FOR BOSTON HAS BEEN
COVERING THIS 24 HOURS A
DAY AND IS LIVE ON SCENE
NOW WITH THE FIRST
REPORTER, TO MY KNOWLEDGE
WHO WAS ABLE TO CONFIRM
THAT INDEED A SUSPECT WAS
DOWN AND SHE CITED LOCAL
POLICE SOURCES FOR THAT.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
>> WE NEED TO BE A NORMAL
CITY AGAIN.
EVERYBODY STARTED COMING
OUT.
YOU COULD SEE EVERYBODY
HANGING OUT ON THE PORCH.
>> HANG ON ONE SECOND.
>> IT'S LIKE THE FIRST
BREATH OF FRESH AIR THEY
HAVE HAD IN A WHILE.
WE JUST GOT RIGHT DOWN THE
STREET AS WE WERE STARTING
TO HEAD BACK.
WE SAW LAW ENFORCEMENT
STARTING TO LEAVE AND THEN
ALL OF THIS JUST UNFOLDED
SO QUICK SO FAST.
>> ALL RIGHT, JARED, HANG
ON ONE SECOND, JARED.
WE WANT TO REASSESS THE
SCENE HERE AND STAND BY ON
THE PHONE.
WE WANT TO SHOW THIS IS
WHAT WE BELIEVE TO BE 67
FRANKLIN STREET AND THERE
WAS TALK OF SUSPECT
POTENTIALLY HIDING IN A
BOAT AND WE GET A BETTER
LOOK AT IT NOW AS WE PULL
THIS IMAGE IN CLOSER.
CAN YOU SEE THAT TRAILER IN
THE BACKYARD.
AGAIN, THERE WAS TALK THAT
POTENTIALLY THE SUSPECT WAS
FOUND IN THAT TRAILER.
GUNFIRE, 20 TO 30 SHOTS WE
HAVE HEARD.
WE BELIEVE AGAIN THIS IS 67
FRANKLIN STREET IN WATER
TOWN.
AND THE SUSPECT IS DOWN.
>> AND WE DON'T KNOW WHAT
HIS CONNECTION IS TO THIS
HOUSE.
>> HOLD ON ONE SECOND.
WE ARE GETTING WORD IN
RIGHT NOW FROM SOURCES AS
WELLING.
-- WELL.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT THE
SUSPECT IS ALIVE SURROUNDED
AND STILL MOVING.
SO THE SUSPECT IS ALIVE
SURROUNDED BY LAW
ENFORCEMENT, BUT STILL
MOVING.
SO THAT'S WHERE WE ARE
RIGHT NOW AT 7:28 IN THE
EVENING AS POLICE HAVE THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD SURROUNDED AS
WELL.
THIS IS FRANKLIN STREET IN
WATERTOWN.
WE HEARD 20 TO 30 SHOTS
FIRED BY EYEWITNESS
ESTIMATES.
AND WE BELIEVE THEY ARE AT
67 FRANKLIN STREET.
SOURCES TELL US THE SUSPECT
IS ALIVE AND SURROUNDED.
STILL MOVING.
>> IT WAS JUST ABOUT 30
MINUTES AGO THAT THE
GOVERNOR LIFTED THE ORDER
TO STAY AT HOME.
SO SO MANY PEOPLE CAME OUT
TO GET A BREATH OF FRESH
AIR AND AS SOON AS THEY
WALKED OUTSIDE THEY HEARD
SOME 20 TO 30 GUNSHOTS
FIRED IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
A RESIDENTIAL NEIGHBORHOOD.
LOTS OF HOMES HERE AND IF
YOU LOOK AT THIS ARROW
BOAT IS THAT THEY BELIEVE A
SUSPECT WAS HIDING.
LET'S GET TO BOB WARD RIGHT
NOW.
>> HI SARAH AND MARK, AN
AMAZING TURN OF EVENTS
MOMENTS AFTER THE STATE
POLICE MAKE THE
ANNOUNCEMENT THAT THEY ARE
GOING TO RESUME THE SEARCH
IN ANOTHER WAY.
I HEARD SHOTS FIRED.
AS MANY AS 30 SHOTS FIRED
JUST DOWN THE STREET JUST A
FEW BLOCKS AWAY FROM WHERE
OUR POLICE HAVE BEEN
SEARCHING FOR THIS SUSPECT
NUMBER 2 FOR HOURS.
MY SOURCES ARE TELLING ME
THAT THEY DO NOT HAVE THIS
PERSON YET.
BUT THAT HE IS STILL ALIVE.
SUSPECT NUMBER 2.
I HAVE ANOTHER SOURCE
SAYING THAT HE IS
SURROUNDED.
THEY HAVE GOT HIM CORNERED.
WE HAVE GOT ANOTHER
STANDOFF HERE.
ARSENAL STREET IN
WATERTOWN.
I'M A GOOD DISTANCE AWAY
FROM WHERE THE EVENTS ARE
TAKING PLACE BUT THE POLICE
HAVE MOVED THE PRESS BACK
SUBSTANTIALLY.
AND WE'RE KEEPING AN EYE ON
IT.
THERE IS A VERY FLUID
SITUATION AIR WING OF THE
MASSACHUSETTS STATE POLICE
IS UP OVER THE SCENE.
THERE IS DOZENS OF POLICE
ON THE SCENE.
THERE IS AN AMBULANCE RIGHT
NEXT TO ME.
BOSTON E.M.S. NOT TOO FAR
AWAY.
WE ARE ALL JUST NOW WAITING
FOR THIS TO BE OVER.
IT APPEARS THIS MAY BE
RESOLVING ITSELF FINALLY
AFTER THE HORRIBLE BOMBINGS
ON MONDAY.
IT SEEMS THAT FRIDAY
EVENING THAT THINGS MAY
FINALLY BE COMING TO A
CLOSE.
>> BOB AGAIN --
>> -- WE'RE ANXIOUSLY
AWAITING WORD.
>> BOB AGAIN YOUR SOURCES
AGAIN FOR THOSE WHO MAYBE
ARE JOINING US RIGHT NOW.
AGAIN, TELL US WHAT YOUR
SOURCES ARE SAYING.
>> SOURCES ARE TELLING ME
THAT THE SUSPECT NUMBER 2
IS NOT APPREHENDED BUT HE
IS SURROUNDED.
HE IS STILL ALIVE.
AND WE ARE LOOKING AT AN
AREA OF BIRCH AND WALNUT IN
WATER TOWN WHICH RUNS SORT
OF OFF OF ARSENAL STREET IN
WATERTOWN.
THE HOUSE LOOKS LIKE IT IS
ON BIRCH STREET IN THE AREA
OF WALNUT STREET OF
WATERTOWN.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BOB, JUST TO RECAP.
20 TO 30 SHOTS FIRED.
ONE MOMENT.
>> HOLD ON ONE SECOND,
GUYS.
BECAUSE WE ARE GETTING MORE
INFORMATION AS THIS COMES
IN.
BOB, I WANT YOU TO HEAR
THIS AS WELL.
67 FRANKLIN STREET IS WHAT
WE BELIEVE TO BE THE
ADDRESS.
WE BELIEVE THE SUSPECT IS
SURROUNDED AND IN A BOAT.
POTENTIALLY IN THE BACKYARD
OF 67 FRANKLIN STREET.
AS WE ARE SEEING HERE THERE
IS A TRAILER TO PULL THE
BOAT AND POTENTIALLY HE WAS
UP UNDER THE CANOPY THAT
CAME IN FROM JARED
HOLBROOK.
>> Shepard: CONTINUE
COVERAGE.
WE ARE LISTENING TO QFXT
FOX 25 OUR LOCALLY OWNED
STATION IN BOSTON.
REPORTS THAT THE SUSPECT IS
SURROUNDED, POSSIBLY IN THE
BOAT IN WATER TOWN.
SHOTS WERE FIRED.
IF HE IS SHOT WE DON'T YET
KNOW BUT WE KNOW HE IS
ALIVE ACCORDING TO THE
REPORTING OF WFXT.
IT'S THEIR REPORTERS WHO
ARE ON THE SCENE AT THIS
MOMENT.
WE HAVE A NUMBER OF THEM
STATIONED ALL OVER THE
AREA.
AS IT SO HAPPENS THEY ARE
THE ONES RIGHT BY THE SPOT
WHERE THIS WENT DOWN JUST
ABOUT 35 MINUTES AGO.
SUSPECT IS ALIVE AND
SURROUNDED AND BELIEVED TO
BE THE SECOND OF TWO KNOWN
SUSPECTS IN THE BOMBING AT
THE MARATHON HERE IN BOSTON
ON MONDAY.
OUR CORRESPONDENT MIKE
TOBIN IS NEARBY AND ON
SCENE IN WATERTOWN.
MIKE, IT'S MY STANDING THAT
THE SCENE JUST WAS OVERRUN
IN A MATTER OF JUST A
COUPLE OF MINUTES.
>> IT HAPPENED VERY
RAPIDLY.
AND THE SCENE WE ARE
TALKING ABOUT GROUND ZERO
IS JUST ABOUT TWO BLOCKS IN
THAT DIRECTION SHEP.
THE WAY IT ALL WENT DOWN IS
THAT SHELTER IN PLACE ORDER
WAS LIFTED.
AND AS QUICKLY AS IT WAS
LIFTED, YOU COULD HE SEE
THE PEOPLE RETURNING TO THE
STREET.
THE CABIN FEVER HAD GOTTEN
THE BEST OF THEM.
A LOT OF THEM DIDN'T SEEM
TO HAVE ANYWHERE TO GO.
THEY WILL WANTED TO GET OUT
OF HOUSE AND WALK AROUND.
SHORTLY AFTER THAT, WE
STARTED SEEING SOME OF THE
POLICE VEHICLES ZOOMING UP
IN THIS DIRECTION.
THAT WASN'T UNCOMMON
THROUGH THIS PROCESS.
YOU WOULD OFTEN TIMES SEE
THE POLICE VEHICLES ZOOM   ING
IN ONE DIRECTION AND THEN
ANOTHER.
ONE COP CAR AND ANOTHER
THREE, FOUR, THEY WERE ALL
GOING IN THE SAME
DIRECTION.
PRETTY SOON YOU HAD THE
POLICE HELICOPTER OVERHEAD
IT BECAME APPARENT THAT
SOMETHING WAS GOING ON.
SO, AND THAT IS HOW IT ALL
CAME DOWN.
THAT'S HOW IT TRANSPIRED.
NOW YOU HAVE THE
INFORMATION THAT, AGAIN,
ABOUT TWO BLOCKS IN THAT
DIRECTION YOU HAVE SOMEONE
WHO IS SURROUNDED RIGHT
NOW, ACCORDING TO THE
INFORMATION WE ARE GETTING
FROM OUR AFFILIATE SHEP.
>> Shepard: ALL RIGHT.
MIKE TOBIN ON SCENE.
STAND BY IF YOU WOULD.
THIS IS THE EXACT SAME AREA
THAT WAS CORDONED OFF AND
LOCKED DOWN FOR THE
ENTIRETY OF THE DAY.
A 20 BLOCK AREA WHERE
SWATTED TEAMS AND ARMORED
PERSONNEL -- ARMORED --
BODY ARMORED PEOPLE,
AUTHORITIES FROM THE FBI
THE LOCAL POLICE, THE STATE
POLICE ALL WENT IN AND NOW
THAT'S WHERE THEY FOUND
HIM.
WFXT FOX 25 IN BOSTON WITH
LIVE LOCAL COVERAGE TO YOU.
>> 35 MINUTES AGO ON THE
STREETS OF WATERTOWN.
GUNFIRE LAST NIGHT RESULTED
IN THE DEATH OF ONE OF THE
SUSPECTS.
TONIGHT WE'RE TOLD THAT A
SUSPECT IS DOWN BUT THAT
SUSPECT IS STILL ALIVE AND
SURROUNDED AT THIS HOUR.
WE BELIEVE IT TO BE 67
FRANKLIN STREET IN
WATERTOWN.
THEY HAVE THE BOMB SQUAD ON
HAND AS WELL.
VERY FLUID SITUATION AS YOU
CAN IMAGINE.
IT APPEARS PROGRESS
SOMETHING MADE WE'RE TOLD
FROM THE SCENE.
PROGRESS BEING MADE TO
APPREHEND THE SUSPECT.
AGAIN, WE ARE VERY
INTERESTED TO KNOW WHO THIS
SUSPECT IS.
IS IT, IN FACT, SUSPECT
NUMBER 2 FROM THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBINGS?
>> A LOT OF RESIDENTS
COMING OUT OF THEIR HOUSE
TO GET A BREATH OF FRESH
AIR AFTER THE GOVERNOR
LIFTED THAT STAY-AT-HOME
BAN.
THEY CAME OUT TO HEAR THE
GUNSHOTS FIRED.
SOME 20 TO 30 GUNSHOTS.
THE SOUNDS REMINISCENT WHEN
WE HEARD EARLIER THIS
MORNING GUN BATTLE WITH 200
GUNSHOTS FIRED AND THE
DEATH OF SUSPECT NUMBER 1.
RIGHT NOW WE KNOW SUSPECT
NUMBER 2 IS ALIVE.
HE IS SURROUNDED.
HE IS STILL MOVING.
WE KNOW HE WAS POSSIBLY
HIDING IN A BOAT AT 67
FRANKLIN STREET AND WE KNOW
THERE IS A BIG POLICE
PRESENCE.
EVERYONE HAS MOVED FROM
THEIR OTHER SCENES TO THIS
SCENE AND WHAT A SCENE FOR
THE NEIGHBORS OF FRANK LIB
STREET HERE IN WATERTOWN.
>> CERTAIN SOLID A MAJOR
SCENE AS THE DEVELOPMENTS
DEVELOPING RAPIDLY HERE
RIGHT NOW AS WE HAVE LAW
ENFORCEMENT FROM ALL OVER
DESCENDING ON THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD IN WATER TOWN.
WE TALKED WITH WITH MARY
SULLIVAN AN EYEWITNESS WHO
SAID SHE WAS GETTING OUT
BECAUSE THE LOCKDOWN HAD
BEEN LIFTED AND SHE WENT
OUT AND WAS GOING TO TAKE
THING TO FOR A WALK AS THEY
OFTEN DO AND SUDDENLY HEARD
THE GUNFIRE AND KNEW THINGS
WERE NOT NORMAL.
AND TOAD IT WHEN SHE SAW
THE LAW ENFORCEMENT RACING
THROUGH THE NEIGHBORHOOD
AND EVENTUALLY DOWN TO THIS
LOCATION RIGHT HERE WHERE
WE ARE TOLD THROUGH SOURCES
AT 67 FRANKLIN STREET THAT
THEY DO NOT HAVE THIS
PERSON IN CUSTODY YET.
THEY DO HAVE HIM CORNERED.
AND RIGHT NOW BASICALLY
WHAT YOU HAVE IS A
STANDOFF.
DON'T FORGET THERE IS THE
AMBULANCE BEING BACKED UP
RIGHT HERE.
WE SAW THAT EARLY ON WHICH
GAVE US A THOUGHT THAT
POTENTIALLY SOMEONE HAD
BEEN WOUNDED.
RIGHT NOW THOUGH WE DON'T
HAVE THAT VERIFIED BUT
CERTAINLY HAVE IT ON HAND
AND HAVE IT AT THE READY
RIGHT NOW THEY WILL STAY
IT'S A STANDOFF BETWEEN
AUTHORITIES AND THE SUSPECT
THAT COULD POTENTIALLY BE
HIDING IN A BOAT.
>> WE KNOW WHAT THE SUSPECT
IS CAPABLE OF IN TERMS OF A
BOMBS.
WEAVE KNOW THEY HAVE A
ROBOT GOING INTO THIS BOAT
ON THE TRAILER TO CHECK IT
OUT IN THE BACKYARD TO MAKE
SURE THERE ARE NO
EXPLOSIVES.
WE KNOW TODAY THEY FOUND A
PRESSURE COOK ERM BOMB AS
WELL AS OTHER PIPE BOMBS IN
THE STREET NEAR THEIR HOME
OF CAMBRIDGE:  SO THEY ARE
BEING AS CAUTIOUS AND
CAREFUL AS THEY POSSIBLY
CAN TO KEEP THE NEIGHBORS
IN THIS RESIDENTIAL AREA
SAFE.
>> IT'S BEEN A LONG WAIT
OBVIOUSLY FOR A LOT OF
PEOPLE ON N. WASHINGTON.
BEEN ON EDGE FOR A WHILE.
GET MORE FROM THE SCENE FOX
25 JARED HOLBROOK.
JARED?
>> WE ARE STILL HERE ON
SCENE.
HELICOPTERS ARE FLYING
OVERHEAD.
A LOT OF ACTIVITY OUT
THERE.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN THE
AMBULANCE MOVE YET.
IT HAS BEEN STATIONARY
SINCE IT GOT THERE.
A VERY QUIET CROWD RIGHT
NOW.
EVERYBODY IS WONDERING
WHAT'S GOING ON.
I'M BACK WITH OUR FRIEND
PAUL SUTHERLAND WHO CAME
HERE ON SCENE AND HE WAS
RIGHT THERE RUNNING RIGHT
AHEAD OF US TOWARD THE
ACTIVITY.
AND, PAUL, WHAT DID YOU
HEAR?
>> I HEARD THE GUNSHOTS.
I FIRST WHAT I HEARD OR SAW
WAS I PULLED OVER AND THE
SWAT TEAM HAD GONE BY ME.
THREE TRUCKS WENT BY AND I
SAID SOMETHING IS GOING ON
TO JANEL.
I SAID RAPID GUNFIRE OVER
AND OVER BOOM BOOM BOOM
BOOM BOOM.
I WAS TALKING WITH FRED I
SAID THIS IS GOING DOWN
RIGHT NOW.
THIS IS HAPPENING RIGHT
NOW.
I WAS PRETTY SURE OF IT.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS
GOING ON.
SOMEBODY IS BEING SHOT AT
IT AND WE KEPT FOLLOWING
THE.
WE COULDN'T GO ON FRANKLY.
WE SLOWED DOWN.
SWAT TEAM PEOPLE GET OUT
AND THEY ALL DISPERSE RIGHT
OUT IN FRONT OF THE HOUSE.
LAY DOWN IN -- I DIDN'T SEE
ANYBODY GOING BACK.
MY STANDING WAS THAT IT WAS
IN A BOAT.
AND I DON'T KNOW HOW ELSE
TO DEFINE IT BUT YOU COULD
JUST TELL SOMETHING BIG WAS
HAPPENING.
SOMETHING REALLY BIG.
ALL OF A SUDDEN CARS CAME
FROM EVERYWHERE.
>> THEY ARE SAYING THAT ONE
OF THE SUSPECTS IS LIKELY
ONE OF THE SUSPECTS HERE IN
THIS WHOLE THING IS DOWN.
SO WHAT IS YOUR THOUGHT ON
ALL OF THIS AS IT IS
STARTING TO SINK IN.
>> IT'S THE FEELING OF
RELIEF BECAUSE I'M
WATERTOWN RESIDENT AND MOST
OF THE DAY I WAS COOKED UP
AND I LEFT THE HOUSE.
I WENT UP AND ALL THE ALL
OF A SUDDEN THEY WAYMAN
BACK.
WE WILL TAKE A RIDE TO SEE
IF WE CAN GET CLOSE TO
DECKS E. AVENUE THAT WASN'T
POSSIBLE.
WE TOOK A RIGHT.
WHATEVER IT IS WE WERE
REACHING WHEN ALL THE
GUN --
>> JARED, CAN YOU HOLD ON
ONE SECOND PLEASE?
JARED?
>> WHAT THEY HAD TO DO.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> JARED, THANK YOU.
JARED, I'M JUST GOING TO
TELL TO YOU STAY ON HOLD.
WE HAVE, UNDERSTAND THAT
THE SUSPECT IS IN THE BOAT.
HE IS INDEED IN THE BOAT.
AGAIN, LOOK AT THE TRAILER
BACK HERE AT 67 FRANKLIN
STREET.
APPARENTLY HE IS IN THE
BOAT AND REFUSING TO COME
OUT.
HE IS SURROUNDED BY LAW
ENFORCEMENT IN THE
BACKYARD.
IT'S 67 FRANKLIN STREET IN
WATER TOWN.
HE IS IN THERE.
HE IS ALIVE BUT IS HE
REFUSING TO COME OUT.
SO THERE IS A NEGOTIATION
PERIOD GOING ON RIGHT NOW
THIS A STANDOFF, THIS WOULD
OBVIOUSLY BE SUSPECT NUMBER
2.
WE CAN'T CONFIRM THAT AS OF
YET.
THE FACT IS THAT HE IS HOLD
UP IN A BOAT IN A BACKYARD
IS ALIVE AND IS REFUSING TO
COME OUT LET'S HEAR THE
AUDIO OF THE GUNSHOTS AGAIN
FOR THOSE WHO MAY HAVE
MISSED IT AND JOINING US
RIGHT NOW.
[GUNFIRE]
>> HOLY, HOLY.
HOLY, HOLY HOLY.
[HELICOPTER]
[GUNFIRE]
>> HOLY, HOLY.
HOLY, HOLY HOLY.
>> AND THAT YOU HEARD WAS
THE SOUND OF 20 TO 30
GUNSHOTS FIRED JUST MOMENTS
AGO.
WE ARE TOLD SUSPECT NUMBER
2 MAY BE HOLD UP.
>> Shepard: LISTENING TO
LIVE COVERAGE FROM WFXT FOX
FOR BOSTON AND THE
SURROUNDING.
WE HAVE A RESIDENT FROM
WATERTOWN WHO LIVES A FEW
BLOCKS AWAY FROM THE SPOT
WHERE THIS ACTIVITY IS
GOING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: YOU WERE
OUTSIDE AND YOU HEARD ALL
OF THIS, RIGHT?
>> YES.
YES.
WE HAD LISTENED TO THE
GOVERNOR AND THE BAN WAS
LIFTED SO FOUR OF US WENT
OUT.
WE WERE WALKING THE DOG.
WE WERE COMING DOWN RUSSELL
AVE.
AND WE WERE JUST ON THE
CORNER ACROSS FROM FRAN
LYNN STREET AND WE JUST
HEARD THIS RAPID GUNFIRE
THAT STAND SOUNDED LIKE
FIREWORKS.
AND WE HID BEHIND THE CAR
AND WE STAYED THERE.
AND JUST ALL THE POLICE
CAME IN AND THAT SOMETHING
WAS HAPPENING.
AND IT IS JUST ABOUT THREE
BLOCKS AWAY FROM MY HOME.
>> Shepard: THOSE JUST
JOINING US MY STATIONS
ACROSS THE STATION.
THERE HAD BEEN A NEWS
CONFERENCE THAT HAPPENED
HERE IN BOSTON IN THE 6:30
HALF HOUR EASTERN TIME.
>> WE ARE MAKING PROGRESS
BUT WE DON'T HAVE A SECOND
SUSPECT.
THEY LISTED THE ORDER WHICH
REQUIRED PEOPLE TO SHELTER
IN PLACE.
AND I GUESS YOU HAVE BEEN
SHELTERING IN PLACE ALL
DAY, RIGHT?
>> YES.
YES.
WE STAYED IN ALL DAY.
YEAH.
>> Shepard: THEY LIFTED THE
BAN.
FINALLY THE DOG CAN GO OUT
FOR A WALK AND YOU HEARD
ALL OF THIS.
>> YEAH.
WE WALKED UP.
AND IT'S A STREET THAT --
THE CIRCLE OF STREETS THAT
I TAKE MY DOG WITH AND WE
WERE JUST READY TO COME TO
THE END OF RUSSELL AND
CROSS OVER AND WE JUST
HEARD LIKE THIS POP, POP
POPPING KIND OF LIKE
FIREWORK POPCORN FIRE.
AND THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN IT
WAS JUST, YOU KNOW,
INUNDATED WITH POLICE AND
THESE SHELTERED TRUCKS.
BLACK TRUCKS AND THE DEA
AND EVERYTHING.
I MEAN, AND THEN JUST
LITERALLY THERE ARE JUST
HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS AND
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE HERE
RIGHT NOW.
SUSPECT IS IN THAT BOAT IN
THE BACKYARD AT 57 FRANKLIN
STREET IN WATERTOWN.
>> RIGHT.
RIGHT.
>> Shepard: THEY TOOK THE
TARP OFF THE BOAT THAT THE
MAN IS STILL INSIDE THE
BOAT AND REFUSING TO COME
OUT.
>> RIGHT.
>> WAS HE SHOT IN THIS
BARRAGE OF GUNFIRE?
WE DON'T KNOW.
DOES HE STILL HAVE A
WEAPON?
DOES HE STILL HAVE
AMMUNITION?
AGAIN, WE HAVE NO WAY OF
KNOWING.
POLICE WERE TOLD HAVE
SURROUNDED THIS BOAT IT IS
THE BELIEF OF ALL INVOLVED
THAT THIS IS THE SUSPECT.
THE SECOND SUSPECT IN THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBING
THAT HAPPENED MONDAY
AFTERNOON BEFORE 3:00.
NOW ANOTHER STANDOFF AFTER
ABSOLUTELY INCREDIBLE NIGHT
IN WATER TOWN WHEN THESE
TWO SUSPECTS REPORTEDLY IN
A STOLEN OR CAR JACKED CAR
AS POLICE ARE CHASING THEM
AND A GUN FIGHT IS ONGOING.
THE OLDER OF THESE TWO
BROTHERS, IT'S OUR STANDING
IS SAID TO HAVE THROWN ONE
OF THESE PRESSURE COOKER
BOMBS OUTS AND TOWARD
POLICE.
INSTEAD OF THE LID LOCK
SOLID, THAT LID CAME OFF
BEFORE IT WAS ABLE TO
EXPLODE.
IT DID LESS DAMAGE THAN IT
OTHERWISE WOULD HAVE.
IT'S FURTHER OUR STANDING
THAT THERE WAS LARGE NUMBER
OF POLICE OFFICERS AROUND
THIS AREA.
AND HAD THAT BOMB WORKED
PROPERLY, THIS STORY WOULD
HAVE TAKEN ITSELF TO AN
ENTIRELY NEW LEVEL.
THANKFULLY, IN THIS CASE,
THAT DIDN'T WORK.
WE'RE TOLD THEY HAD
IMPROVISED GRENADES AS WELL
AND HURLED THOSE TOWARDS
THE VEHICLE.
STANDOFF ENDED AND THE CAR
CAME TO A STOP.
THE NUMBER ONE SUSPECT THE
OLDER OF THE PRO BROTHERS
DIED IN WHAT WE ARE LED TO
BELIEVE WAS A SHOOTOUT WITH
POLICE.
AND THIS YOUNGER SUSPECT
TOOK OFF ON FOOT.
IT'S THE DARK OF NIGHT.
THE WATER TOWN POLICE WILL
TELL YOU AND THEY DID TO
THE WORLD TODAY.
WE JUST DIDN'T HAVE ENOUGH
MANPOWER TO LOCKDOWN THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD.
OR THEY DIDN'T THINK THEY
DID.
BECAUSE THEY WENT
DOOR-TO-DOOR, THEY TELL US
EVERY HOUSE IN WATER TOWN
FOR A 20 SQUARE BLOCK
RADIUS SEARCHED THE ATTIC.
EVERY FRONT PORCH HAS AN
AREA UNDERNEATH IT AND
THERE IS A -- PLENTY OF
PLACES WHO HIDE THE WAY
CONSTRUCTION IS DONE IN
WATER TOWN BUT THEY
SEARCHED IT ALL AND
COULDN'T FIND ANYTHING.
THEY SEARCHED THIS BOAT IN
THE BACK OF THIS HOME AT 57
FRANKLIN STREET AS WELL.
AND FOUND THAT THERE WAS
NOTHING THERE.
BUT, THE WOMAN WHO LIVES IN
THAT HOUSE ACCORDING TO THE
MOST RECENT REPORTS CALLED
UP THE POLICE AND GOES,
HEY, YOU SEARCHED HERE BUT
IT LOOKS DIFFERENT NOW.
THERE IS A DOOR TO THE SHED
OPEN.
SHE WENT OUT AND LOOKED,
THERE WERE BLOODY CLOTHES
INSIDE THE SHED SHE
REPORTED TO POLICE.
AND THERE WAS BLOOD ON THE
FLOOR.
SO POLICE CAME BACK.
AND IT'S OUR STANDING THAT
THEY SEARCHED THE AREA.
THERE IS SOME REPORTS NOW
THAT THEY MAY HAVE ACTUALLY
FOUND THE GUY INSIDE THIS
BOAT WITH THE TARP OVER IT
BY USING IMAGES FROM A
HELICOPTER.
BUT WE DON'T KNOW THAT.
OUR LOCAL RADIO STATION IS
REPORTING THAT AT ANY RATE,
WE ARE PRETTY COMFORTABLE
AT THIS POINT WITH THE
REPORTING OF WFXT FOX 25 IN
BOSTON.
THE BOAT IS SURROUNDED,
THIS GUY IS INSIDE IT IS HE
BLEEDING?
WE DON'T KNOW.
HE IS NOT COMING OUT AT
THIS MOMENT.
WE HAVE CORRESPONDENTS AND
CREWS ON SCENE FOX 25 LIVE
TO YOU ACROSS THE NATION.
>> BOTTOM LINE IS THEY WANT
TO GET HIM AS YOU SAID,
THEY WANT TO TAKE HIM
ALIVE.
>> IT IS A VERY TENSE
SITUATION RIGHT NOW OUTSIDE
67 FRANKLIN STREET WHERE
THERE IS A STANDOFF WITH
THE SUSPECT NUMBER 2 HIDING
IN THAT BOAT.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW LONG HE
HAS BEEN IN THAT BOAT IF
IT'S BEEN ALL DAY SINCE
THIS MORNING WHEN HE
ESCAPED THE GUN FIGHT.
WE DON'T KNOW IF HE IS
INJURED IN THAT BOAT BUT WE
DO KNOW HE IS ALIVE.
IS HE SURROUNDED BY A
NUMBER OF AUTHORITIES, BUT
HE DOES NOT WANT TO COME
OUT.
>> BOB WARD, GO AHEAD.
>>
>> WE'RE IN A PARKING LOT.
>> BOB, I'M SORRY WE CAN'T
HEAR YOU AND WE DO WANT TO
UPDATE PEOPLE ON THE
LATEST.
I UNDERSTAND NOW SOURCES
TELLING US THAT THE ROBOT
IS INDEED HEADED INTO THAT
AREA WHERE THE BOAT IS
RIGHT NOW.
SWAT TEAM PULLED BACK.
THE INDIVIDUAL KNOWS THEY
ARE SURROUNDED.
SENDING IN A BOMB ROBOT AND
SEE THE IMAGES.
I UNDERSTAND THEY HAVE A
CAMERA ON THERE.
TAKE A LOOK AROUND.
OBVIOUSLY WITHOUT PUTTING A
HUMAN LIFE IN HARM'S WAY.
>> THIS IS SO IMPORTANT
MARK, BECAUSE WE KNOW THAT
THIS SUSPECT LIKED BOMBS.
WE KNOW THE PRESSURE COOKER
BOMBS THAT WERE USED IN THE
BOSTON MARATHON.
PRESSURE COOKER BOMB WAS
FOUND TODAY IN CAMBRIDGE.
WE KNOW PIPE BOMBS WERE
AND WE KNOW THAT PIPE BOMBS
WERE FOUND ON COMMONWEALTH
AVENUE IN BOSTON AS WELL SO
THIS IS A VERY SERIOUS AND
DELICATE SITUATION.
THEY WANT TO BRING THIS
ROBOT IN TO THE BOAT TO
MAKE SURE THERE ARE NO
EXPLOSIVES.
HE THEY WANT TO KEEP THIS
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 ALIVE.
HE HAS IMPORTANT
INFORMATION THAT
AUTHORITIES NEED AS THEY
CONTINUE THIS
INVESTIGATION.
THEY DON'T WANT TO DO
ANYTHING THAT WOULD
NECESSITATE HIM POTENTIALLY
TAKING HIS OWN LIFE IN THIS
SITUATION.
HE IS FROM A DIRE SITUATION
AT THIS POINT.
IS HE TOTALLY SURROUNDED.
AS BOB WARD SAID HIS
SOURCES TELL HIM THIS GUY
HAS ABSOLUTELY NO PLACE TO
GO AT THIS POINT.
YOU THINK ABOUT THE DRAGNET
THEY CAST SO WIDE ALL THE
COMMUNITIES AROUND BOSTON,
BOSTON IN LOCKDOWN, SEVERAL
OTHER COMMUNITIES AROUND
THE WATER TOWN AREAS.
CITIES AND TOWNS LOCKED
DOWN ALL DAY.
NOW IT COMES DOWN TO THIS.
A BACKYARD, 67 FRANKLIN
STREET IN WATER TOWN.
A BOAT, INSIDE THE BOAT THE
SUSPECT.
>> IT IS POSSIBLE, MARK,
THAT THIS SUSPECT --
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 IS INJURED
FROM THIS MORNING'S GUN
BATTLE, DURING THAT GUN
BATTLE THERE WERE SOME 200
SHOTS FIRED.
HIS BROTHER DIED DURING
THAT GUN BATTLE.
IT'S VERY POSSIBLE THAT HE
TOO HAS AN INJURY AGAIN
THIS WAS 67 FRANKLIN STREET
IF YOU ARE JUST JOINING US
IN WATER TOWN WHERE SUSPECT
NUMBER 2 FROM THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBING IS
APPARENTLY IN THAT BOAT
THAT YOU SEE RIGHT THERE
WITH THE TARP UNDER HIM.
HE HAS BEEN HIDING THERE.
WE DON'T KNOW HOW LONG HE
HAS BEEN HIDING THERE FOR.
BUT HE IS SURROUNDED.
THIS IS STANDOFF AND YOU
CAN IMAGINE THAT NEIGHBORS
THERE IN THAT AREA ARE ON
EDGE.
>> YOU CAN SEE IN FRONT OF
THE HOUSE RIGHT THERE ON
THE LEFT AS NIGHT FALL
FALLS HERE, YOU CAN SEE THE
BOMB SNIFFING DOGS ARE IN
THE AREA AS WELL.
THEY STARTED TO TAKE SOME
OF THE CANINE UNITS OUT.
I'M NOT SURE IF THEY'RE
WALKING THIS WAY OR OTHER
WAY.
THEY ARE OUT OF THEIR
VEHICLES AND ON THE STREETS
OF WATERTOWN RIGHT NOW.
7:49 IN THE EVENING.
THE SUSPECT CONSIDERED
INSIDE THIS BOAT ACCORDING
TO SOURCES.
ALSO THOSE SOURCES SAY THE
SWAT TEAM THAT HAD THAT
BOAT SURROUNDED.
THE SUSPECT IS STILL ALIVE.
THEY HAVE BEEN TOLD TO PULL
BACK TO ALLOW A ROBOT TO GO
IN THERE AND TAKE A LOOK
AROUND AND SEE THE SUSPECT
FIRSTHAND AND TRY TO
DETERMINE WHETHER OR NOT
THERE ANY EXPLOSIVES MAY BE
THERE AS WELL.
AROUND HIM IN HIS HANDS OR
POTENTIALLY ON HIS PERSON.
COULD BE ON HIS BODY
ANYWHERE.
HIS BROTHER WAS FOUND TO
HAVE AN IED ON HIMSELF THIS
MORNING WHEN THEY
IDENTIFIED HIM LATER AFTER
HE PASSED AWAY AT BRIGHAM
WOMEN'S -- BETH -- HOSPITAL
I SHOULD SAY.
THIS HAS BEEN A LONG
SEVERAL DAYS HERE IN
BOSTON.
ALTHOUGH THERE VICE
PRESIDENT BEEN MANY OF THEM
BUT THERE HAVE BEEN LONG
DAYS WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
THE MENTAL DURESS PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN GOING THROUGH IN
THIS COMMUNITY AND AROUND.
GO TO VIEWER VIDEO COMING
IN AND WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
THIS -- THIS IS VIEWER
VIDEO FROM THE SCENE.
HERE YOU GO.
>> OH MY GOD.
OH [BLEEP]
[GUNFIRE]
>> LET'S GO STRAIGHT OUT TO
BOB WARD.
WHAT DO YOU HAVE.
>> A SITUATION MOMENTS AGO
WE HAD A SERIES OF --
[INAUDIBLE] SUSPECT NUMBER
2 IS HOLD UP.
WE JUST HEARD TWO OR THREE
BLASTS, THEN A PAUSE AND
THEN TWO OR THREE MORE.
LOOKING AT POLICE, THEY
DON'T SEEM TO BE MOVING
VERY QUICKLY.
THERE IS ANOTHER ONE.
AND THEN ANOTHER ONE.
ANOTHER ONE.
I WILL HOLD THE PHONE UP.
>> WHAT'S BOB SAYING?
>> ARE YOU SAYING YOU ARE
HEARING TWO OR THREE BASS
BLAS?
>> Shepard: AGAIN, NEW
SHOOTING HAPPENING NOW.
THE REPORTER BOB WARD FROM
WFXT REPORTING LIVE.
LISTEN.
>> I DIDN'T COUNT THEM BUT
THAT SOUNDED ABOUT RIGHT.
THREE -- THERE WERE THREE
SERIES OF EXPLOSIONS WITH
PAUSES IN BETWEEN.
AND THERE IS TWO MORE JUST
NOW.
TWO MORE, A TOTAL OF 8
EXPLOSIONS.
>> TENSE SITUATION IN
WATERTOWN WHERE WE BELIEVE
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 IS HOLD
UP.
JUST TRYING TO WATCH AS
CLOSELY I CAN.
IT'S GETTING DARK.
THERE IS NO LIGHT ON THE
AREA.
VERY DARK IN THE AREA WHERE
THE SHOTS ARE COMING FROM.
>> WE HAVE HEARD I WOULD
SAY 8 TO 10 EXPLOSIONS IN
TOTAL.
>> JUST FOR THE VIEWERS AT
HOME, BOB, TO KNOW WHAT WE
ARE EXPERIENCING HERE.
WE ARE WATCHING THIS HERE
UNFOLD 67 FRANKLIN STREET.
HE WE ARE TRYING TO LISTEN
AS WELL.
IF YOU HEAR US DROP OFF WE
ARE TRYING TO LISTEN IN AS
WELL.
YOU HAVE HEARD THE BLASTS
AS MANY AS 8 YOU ARE
SAYING?
>> YEAH.
TWO MORE JUST NOW.
>> WE CAN SEE THE FLASH AS
WELL.
>> I WOULD SAY 10
EXPLOSIONS RIGHT NOW MARK.
I WOULD SAY AS MANY AS 10.
>> BOB, IS THERE A
HELICOPTER OVERHEAD AT THIS
POINT?
>> SAY IT AGAIN?
>> IS THERE A HELICOPTER
OVERHEAD AT THIS POINT?
>> YES.
STATE POLICE HELICOPTER IS
ALMOST DIRECTLY ABOVE THE
LOCATION WHERE THESE
EXPLOSIONS ARE ARE
HAPPENING.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT THE SWAT
TEAM WAS SENDING IN SOME
KIND OF A ROBOTIC DEVICE TO
THAT AREA.
THERE IS NO WARNING THAT
THEY WERE GOING TO TRY
TO -- THERE IS IS NO
WARNING THAT THEY WERE
GOING -- WE KNOW THAT WE
HAVE HEARD ABOUT 10
EXPLOSIONS OUT HERE IN THE
AREA WHERE SUSPECT NUMBER 2
TRAPPED.
>> THEY SEEM TO BE COMING
IN THE BACKYARD OF THAT
HOME AT 67 FRANKLIN STREET?
>> SARAH, I CAN'T TELL.
[AUDIO BREAKING UP]
SUSPECT NUMBER 2 IS
SURROUNDED.
>> AGAIN, THE SUSPECT
COMPLETELY SURROUNDED AND
NOW LATE WORD THAT ARE AS
MANY AS 8 TO 10 BLASTS AND
JUST HEARD TWO MORE.
WE ARE SEEING FLASHES IN
LIGHT IN ADDITION TO THE
STROBE LIGHTS COMING FROM
THE VEHICLE.
EVERY SO OFTEN WE HAVE SEEN
A COUPLE OF BRIGHT WHITE
FLASHES.
NOT SURE IF THOSE ARE
RELATED.
BOB SAID THERE HAS BEEN 8
TO 10 EXPLOSIONS THAT HE
HAS HEARD.
AND THIS ALL HAPPENING IN
THE BACKYARD AT 67 FRANKLIN
STREET WHERE WE BELIEVE
SUSPECT 2 IS HOLD UP IN
THIS BOAT THAT YOU SEE ON
THE RIGHT PICTURE HERE IN
THE ARROW WITH THE TARP ON
IT THAT HE HID IN THERE.
SWAT TEAM SURROUNDED HIM.
HAD HIM SURROUNDED.
BASH TAKE A LOOK AROUND
BECAUSE THEY ARE VERY
CONCERNED ABOUT THE FACT
THAT THERE COULD BE
EXPLOSIVES THERE AS WELL.
ONCE THAT ROBOTIC DEVICE
WENT IN, WE UNDERSTAND THAT
POTENTIALLY THAT IS WHEN WE
STARTED TO HEAR SOME OF THE
EXPLOSIONS.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
BOB WARD SAID HE HEARD SOME
8 TO 10 EXPLOSIONS IN THAT
AREA POSSIBLY COMING FROM
THE BACKYARD WHERE THAT
SUSPECT IS HOLD UP IN A
BOAT THAT YOU SEE RIGHT
THERE.
IT IS NIGHT FALL RIGHT NOW.
AND IT'S AMAZING HOW THIS
STORY HAS CHANGED IN A
MATTER OF SECONDS MARK.
>> IT CERTAINLY IS.
THIS WAS ALL DAY PRESENCE.
>> THE POLICE IN WATERTOWN
OUGHT NIGHT.
THEY HAVE BEEN THERE FROM
THE TIME THAT THE CAR CHASE
ENDED UP IN WATERTOWN.
WE HAD SHOOTOUT, A FIRE
FIGHT LAST NIGHT WITH
POLICE RESULTING IN SUSPECT
NUMBER 1' DEMISE AS IT
TURNED OUT AS HE WAS GUNNED
DOWN.
THEN WE ALSO HAD THE FOOT
CHASE THAT ENSUED FOR THIS
INDIVIDUAL HERE IT APPEARS.
THIS WOULD BE SUSPECT
NUMBER 2.
THROUGHOUT THE DAY
WATERTOWN WAS IN LOCKDOWN
AS WERE ALL THE COMMUNITIES
AROUND IT AS WAS THE CITY
OF BOSTON.
AS NIGHT.
>> Shepard: WE ARE
LISTENING TO WFXT IN BOSTON
LIVE COVERAGE OF DEVELOPING
STORY IN WATERTOWN.
IT'S OUR BELIEF THAT THE
SUSPECT THERE IN THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBING WAS
UNDERNEATH THIS BOAT TARP
AND NOW THERE ARE REPORTS
OF ALL OF THESE EXPLOSIONS
AND THE EXPLOSIONS, THOUGH
THEY ARE BEING REPORTED BY
THE LOCAL REPORTER AS A
SERIES OF EXPLOSIONS, IT'S
POSSIBLE THAT WHEN THEY
SENT THIS ROBOT IN TO DO
THE EXPLORATION OF THE
AREA, TAKE A LOOK AT VIDEOS
AND THE REST, THEY COULD
HAVE SET OFF A FLASH BANG
IN THERE.
IF YOU REMEMBER THE
SHOOTING THAT HAPPENED IN
CALIFORNIA WHEN THE MAN WAS
GOING TO -- HE WAS SHOOTING
A BUNCH OF COPS OUT THERE.
AND AUTHORITIES SET OFF
FLASH BANGS INSIDE THE
BUILDING TO TRY AND RESCUE
THE HOSTAGE SHOWS FLASH
BANGS ENDED UP SETTING THE
HOUSE ON FIRE, REMEMBER?
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT THAT'S
THE SAME THING THAT'S GOING
ON NOW.
IT'S POSSIBLE THAT THIS IS
ISN'T AN ESCALATION BUT
PART OF THE ONGOING
PROCESS.
WE HAVE NOTHING TO INDICATE
ANY FURTHER HAVE BEEN
INJURED THERE AT LEAST AT
THIS MOMENT.
SO WE DON'T GET AHEAD OF
OURSELVES IN THE REPORTING
WHAT WE DO KNOW THAT IS
THAT THE SUSPECT IS NOW
SURROUNDED IN THE BACKYARD
OF A STREET IN FRANKLIN
STREET IN WATERTOWN.
AUTHORITIES HAVE COME FROM
BOSTON AND DID IMMEDIATELY
FROM OUR POSITION IN
DOWNTOWN BOSTON WE WATCHED
THEM HEADING IN THAT
DIRECTION.
WE BELIEVE THERE ARE
SOMEWHERE AROUND HUNDREDS
OF OFFICERS ON SCENE AND
THAT THE SECOND SUSPECT IS
SURROUNDED.
WHAT THESE NEW EXPLOSIONS
ARE, WE DON'T YET KNOW.
THEY WERE WORKING TO MAKE
CONTACT WITH A NEIGHBOR AND
WE WILL LET YOU KNOW WHEN
WE DO.
NOW BACK TO LOCAL COVERAGE
FROM FOX 25 WFXT FOR NEW
ENGLAND.
>> THIS WHOLE CROWD HERE,
DOZENS OF PEOPLE.
YOU COULDN'T HEAR A PIN
DROP IT'S SO QUIET OUT HERE
RIGHT NOW.
WE HEARD A SERIES -- MANY
HERE BELIEVE INCLUDING
MYSELF THAT THERE WERE
GUNSHOTS FIRED.
WE HEARD TWO FAINT POPS.
ONE OF THOSE TWO DEFINITELY
SOUNDED LIKE A GUNSHOT.
THEN WE HAD A LULL OF ABOUT
30 SECONDS.
AND THEN WE HEARD A LOUD
BOOM.
AND I'M NOT SURE WHAT THAT
WAS.
COULD HAVE BEEN EXPLOSIVE
OR COULD HAVE BEEN A
GUNSHOT.
AFTER ABOUT A MINUTE WE
HEARD TWO MORE POPS WHICH
SOUNDED LIKE GUNSHOTS.
EVERYONE HERE IS LISTENING
TO FIGURE OUT WHAT THAT WAS
EXACTLY.
EVERYBODY YELLED GUNSHOTS
WHEN THEY HEARD THE NOISE.
I'M STANDING HERE WITH DAWN
WHO ACTUALLY HEARD THE
SOUNDS AS WELL.
WHAT DID IT SOUND LIKE TO
YOU?
>> WELL, FIRST I HEARD
ABOUT -- TWO POPS, YOU
KNOW LOUD DISTINCT POPS,
GUNSHOTS.
ABOUT 10 SECOND INTERVAL
AND THEN WE HEARD A THIRD
SHOT.
AND THEN A COUPLE MINUTES
WENT BY.
TIME IS KIND OF FUZZY RIGHT
NOW AND THEN WE HEARD
THAT'S THE LAST WE HAVE
HEARD.
>> AND IT'S REALLY QUIET ON
SCENE RIGHT NOW.
EVERYONE -- EVERYBODY IS
TRYING TO LISTEN IN AND GET
A GRASP FOR WHAT EXACTLY
THOSE SOUNDS WERE.
>> JARED I'M GOING TO STOP
YOU FOR JUST A MOMENT TO
SAY WE ARE GETTING FROM BOB
WARD.
HE BELIEVES THEY MAY HAVE
BEEN FLASH BANKS.
I KNOW YOU HAVE SOME
EXPERIENCE IN THE MILITARY
AS YOU ARE A MARINE WHO
ALSO WORKED WITH
EXPLOSIVES, SO TELL US A
LITTLE BIT ABOUT THAT AND
WHAT YOU MAY HAVE HEARD OR
DIDN'T HEAR.
>> RIGHT, ONE OF THOSE WAS
VERY LOUD.
IT DIDN'T SOUND LIKE A
GUNSHOT TO ME.
IT DID SOUND LIKE A FLASH
BANG.
I CAN'T SEE IT.
IT DID SOUND MORE OF LIKE
AN EXPLOSIVE.
I FIGURED IT WAS EITHER A
FLASH BANG OR PIPE BOMB.
NOT KNOWING EXACTLY WHAT'S
ON SCENE.
IT DID SOUND MORE THAN
GUNSHOT ONE OF THOSE
SOUNDS, A LITTLE MORE
FAINT.
>> JARED, I JUST WANT TO
PASS ALONG TO THE AUDIENCE
BECAUSE WE ARE GETTING NEW
INFORMATION.
SOURCES TELLING US NOW THAT
THE SUSPECT IS INJURED FROM
LAST NIGHT FROM LAST
NIGHT'S CAR CHASE.
THE FIRE FIGHT THAT ENSUED
AND THEN HIS SUBSEQUENT
FLEEING ON FOOT.
SO WE'RE TOLD AGAIN THAT
THE SUSPECT WAS INJURED IN
LAST NIGHT'S SHOOTOUT.
AND SO NOW WE KNOW HE IS
INJURED, HE IS IN THAT
BOAT.
HE DOESN'T WANT TO COME
OUT.
SOME TYPE OF ROBOTIC DEVICE
HAS GONE IN TO SEE WHAT IT
LOOKS LIKE IN THAT AREA,
POTENTIALLY WHETHER OR NOT
HE IS THE SUSPECT THEY HAVE
BEEN LOOKING FOR ALTHOUGH
WE HAVE EVERY REASON TO
BELIEVE IT MAY BE.
OBVIOUSLY THEY ARE GOING TO
TRY TO TAKE HIM OUT ALIVE.
THERE IS A QUESTION HERE.
DOES HE WANT TO COME OUT
AND HE SIMPLY CAN'T BECAUSE
HE IS INJURED?
>> THAT'S EXACTLY RIGHT.
WE DON'T