IN THIS CLIMATE WHERE WE SEEM
MORE DIVIDED BUT WE'RE NOT AS
DIVIDED AS YOU THINK.
I'M DANA PERINO.
THANKS FOR JOINING "THE DAILY
BRIEFING."
SHEPARD SMITH IS NEXT.
>> Shepard: HE RECORDED THE
CARNAGE.
REPORTS THAT THE GUNMAN VIDEOED
HIMSELF AS HE MURDERED PEOPLE.
IT'S NOON IN LAS VEGAS WHERE
VICTIMS RELATIVES TRY TO PROCESS
THEIR LOSS AND THEIR FEELINGS
FOR THE KILLER.
>> YOU HAVE PROBLEMS WITH
SOMEONE, DON'T TAKE IT OUT ON
EVERYBODY.
THIS IS WHAT HAPPENS.
>> AHEAD, WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT THE
VICTIMS ALONG WITH THE BRAVE
BYSTANDERS THAT RISKED AND IN
SOME CASES GAVE THEIR LIVES TO
HELP SAVE OTHERS.
FROM AN IRAQ WAR VETERANS TO
CIVILIAN PARAMEDICS THAT FOUND
THEMSELVES UNDER FIRE, WE'LL
MEET THE HEROS OF LAS VEGAS.
WE'RE ALSO WATCHING THE RECOVERY
EFFORT IN PUERTO RICO WHERE
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS MEETING WITH
LEADERS AND FIRST RESPONDERS.
WE EXPECT TO HEAR FROM THE
PRESIDENT IN THIS HOUR.
LET'S GET TO IT.
>> Shepard: FIRST FROM THE FOX
NEWS DECK, THERE'S VIDEO OF THE
MASSACRE SHOT FROM THE SNIPER'S
ROOST IN HIS 32nd FLOOR SUITE AT
MANDALAY BAY.
THAT'S THE REPORT NOW FROM THE
DAILY MAIL NEWSPAPER BASED IN
THE UNITED KINGDOM.
THE PAPER IS REPORTING THAT
ALONG WITH 23 GUNS THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK BROUGHT INTO THE ROOM,
HE ALSO BROUGHT MULTIPLE CAMERAS
WITH HIM.
THE PAPER INDICATES HE SET UP
ONE BY A WINDOW WHICH HE BROKE
TO RECORD THE KILLING SPREE AND
ANOTHER IN THE HALL OUTSIDE THE
HOTEL ROOM DOOR SO HE WOULD KNOW
WHEN THE COPS APPROACHED.
AUTHORITIES HAVE NOT CONFIRMED
THAT REPORT.
WE ARE GETTING A LOOK INTO THE
HOTEL ROOM ITSELF FROM WHICH THE
GUNMAN CARRIED OUT THE DEADLIEST
SHOOTING IN MODERN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
THE "NEW YORK POST" OBTAINED
THIS VIDEO FROM THE CRIME SCENE
IN TEXAS -- FROM THE CRIME SCENE
IN LAS VEGAS, I SHOULD SAY.
FOX NEWS CHANNEL AND THE PAPER
SHARE COMMON OWNERSHIP.
THE VIDEO SHOWS AN ASSAULT RIFLE
RESTING ON A BIPOD ON THE FLOOR.
YOU CAN SEE WHAT APPEARED TO BE
A USED ROOM SERVICE TRAY.
YOU CAN SEE THE BREACHED DOOR
ITSELF THERE COVERED WITH THE
YELLOW POLICE TAPE.
THE SWAT TEAM BROKE DOWN THE
DOOR WITH EXPLOSIVES TO GET TO
THE GUNMAN ALREADY TO FIND OUT
HE ALREADY KILLED HIMSELF.
INVESTIGATORS LOOKING INTO THE
SUSPECTS SAY THEY'RE STRUGGLING
TO FIGURE OUT WHY HE CARRIED OUT
THIS MASSACRE.
FEDERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIALS TELL FOX NEWS, STEPHEN
PADDOCK SENT ABOUT $100,000
OVERSEAS.
THE MONEY MAY HAVE GONE TO HIS
GIRLFRIEND AND THEY'RE STILL
LOOKING INTO IT AND HAVE NOT
CONFIRMED THAT.
WE HAVE NEW IMAGES OF THE GUNS
THE SHOOTER USED DURING THE
MASSACRE.
FROM BOSTON 25 NEWS, WE OBTAINED
THESE PHOTOS.
AT THE END OF EACH GUN APPEARED
TO BE A BUMP STOCK WHICH
MODIFIES WEAPONS TO MAKE THEM
FULLY AUTOMATIC.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE SHOOTER
BROUGHT TEN SUITCASES FILLED
WITH GUNS INTO THE HOTEL ROOM.
POLICE OFFICERS SAY 23 FIREARMS
WERE FOUND THERE.
WE'RE LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
PEOPLE THAT RISKED THEIR LIVES
TO SAVE OTHERS.
FIRE OFFICIALS SAY OFF DUTY
FIREFIGHTERS WERE SHOT WHILE
TAKING ACTION.
>> AFTER ALL HELL BROKE LOOSE,
12 OF THE MEMBERS WERE SHOT AS
THEY WENT TO WORK HELPING OTHER
MEMBERS IN THE AUDIENCE.
TWO OF THESE MEMBERS WERE SHOT
WHILE PERFORMING CPR.
THIS IS A TRUE FEAT OF HEROISM
ON THEIR PART.
>> Shepard: MORE AHEAD ON THE
ACTS OF HEROISM.
INVESTIGATOR SAY THE GUNMAN
SMASHED OUT TWO WINDOWS TO FIRE
GUNS ON BIPODS AT CROWDS A
QUARTER MILE AWAY.
INJURING MORE THAN 500 AND
KILLING 59.
DURING THE MASSACRE,
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE SHOOTER
SHOT AT SECURITY GUARDS THROUGH
HIS HOTEL DOOR HITTING ONE IN
THE LEG.
THE GUARD WE'RE TOLD SURVIVED.
STEPHEN PADDOCK LIVED IN A
RETIREMENT COMMUNITY IN
MESQUITE, NEVADA.
HE WAS A 64-YEAR-OLD FORMER
ACCOUNTANT.
PEOPLE THAT KNEW HIM SAID HE WAS
A MILLIONAIRE, HAD A HIGH STAKES
VIDEO POKER HABIT.
INVESTIGATORS SAY POD DOCK HAD
NO CRIMINAL RECORD AS FAR AS
THEY KNOW.
HE WAS THE SON OF A BANK ROBBER
THAT DECADES AGO WAS ON THE
FBI'S MOST WANTED LIST.
FAMILY MEMBERS SAY THEY ALSO
CANNOT EXPLAIN WHAT WOULD
MOTIVATE PADDOCK TO CARRY OUT
THE MASSACRE.
ACCORDING TO HIS BROTHER,
STEPHEN PADDOCK WAS A
MULTIMILLIONAIRE.
HE MADE MUCH OF THE MONEY FROM
REAL ESTATE AND LIVED A
COMFORTABLE LIFE.
THE BROTHER SAYS THE GUNMAN
DIDN'T CARE ABOUT RELIGION OR
POLITICS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY PADDOCK WAS
THE ONLY SHOOTER.
JASON ALDEAN WAS PERFORMING AT
THE END OF THE THREE-DAY
FESTIVAL WHEN THE GUN FIRE
BEGAN.
HE POSTED A STATEMENT SAYING HE
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND WHY THIS
HAPPENED.
HE SAID I'M SORRY FOR THE HURT
AND PAIN EVERYONE IS FEELING
RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S WORDS I CAN SAY TO TAKE
THAT PAIN AWAY.
JASON ALDEAN ADDED, TIME TO COME
TOGETHER AND STOP THE HATE.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON ALL OF THE
DEVELOPMENTS IN LAS VEGAS,
INCLUDING VIDEO IN JUST A
MOMENT.
BUT FIRST, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
SPEAKING.
THIS IS HAPPENING IN PUERTO
RICO.
YOU'LL REMEMBER, THAT HE'S
HELPING HAND OUT SUPPLIES AT A
CHURCH THERE ABOUT TEN MILES
NORTH OF -- SOUTH OF SAN JUAN.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
>> I SEE AN INCREDIBLE JOB DONE
BY FEMA, THE COAST GUARD, THE
ARMY, THE NAVY, THE AIR FORCE,
THE MARINES.
THE JOB OF THE FIRST RESPONDERS
HAS BEEN SOMETHING LIKE I HAVE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
WHAT FEMA HAS DONE, WHAT THE
PEOPLE THAT GOT HERE BEFORE THE
HURRICANE HAVE DONE -- AND THE
GOVERNOR IS WITH US.
YOUR MAYOR IS WITH US ALSO, THE
GOVERNOR.
WHAT HAS HAPPENED IN TERMS OF
RECOVERY IN TERMS OF SAVING
LIVES, 16 LIVES.
THAT'S A LOT.
BUT YOU COMPARE THAT TO THE
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE THAT DIED IN
OTHER HURRICANES AND FRANKLY
WE'RE NOT NEARLY AS SEVERE.
I JUST HAVE SUCH RESPECT FOR
FEMA AND ALL OF THE PEOPLE THAT
GOT HERE EARLY.
GOVERNOR, YOU MAY WANT TO SAY
SOMETHING.
>> WE'RE GRATEFUL FOR THE
PRESIDENT, GRATEFUL FOR THE
EFFORTS THAT THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT HAS EMBARKED.
THIS IS A TEAM EFFORT.
WE HAVE ALL THE WAY FROM MAYORS
TO FEMA, THE DODs, GENERAL
BUCHANAN IS HERE AS WELL.
WE COULDN'T HAVE DONE THIS IF WE
DIDN'T HAVE THOSE SUPPORT.
OF COURSE, WE RECOGNIZE AND THE
PRESIDENT RECOGNIZES WE STILL
NEED TO DO MORE.
WE KNOW WE'LL DO IT TOGETHER,
THIS IS A COMMITMENT BY THE
PRESIDENT, THE FIRST LADY BEING
HERE SHOWS A COMMITMENT TO BEING
HERE FOR THE LONG HAUL, HELPING
US GET THE EMERGENCY HELP,
HELPING US GET STABILITY AND
BUILDING PUERTO RICO STRONGER
THAN BEFORE.
>> FIRST OF ALL, THANK YOU.
ONE OF THE THINGS YOU MAY HEARD
ON THE MAINLAND THAT IS NOT
HAPPENING HERE.
PEOPLE WERE ON THE ISLAND BEFORE
THE HURRICANE, BEFORE, DURING
AND AFTER MARIA.
SO WE'VE BEEN HIT BY A HURRICANE
CAT 5 IN LESS THAN TEN DAYS, ONE
AFTER THE OTHER.
SO IT'S NOT BY THE NAVY AND THE
COAST GUARD.
THEY ARE RESCUING MORE THAN 800
PEOPLE AND STILL ONGOING IN
RESCUE MISSIONS.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN HISTORY,
THE PUERTO RICAN HAS WORKED WITH
THE GOVERNOR, TO DEAL WITH THIS
ISSUE.
WE NEVER HAVE BEFORE.
WE'RE USED TO HAVING A HURRICANE
BUT NEVER LIKE THIS ONE.
THIS IS A MAJOR ONE.
DEVASTATION.
THANKS FOR ALL OF THE HELP AND
ALL THE RESOURCES.
ALL FEDERAL AGENCIES ARE ON THE
ISLAND BECAUSE OF YOU.
>> THANK YOU.
>> THE POWER GRID WAS DEVASTATED
BEFORE THE HURRICANES EVEN HIT.
THEN THE HURRICANES HIT.
THEY WIPED THEM OUT.
WE'RE GETTING A LOT OF
GENERATORS THAT HAVE BEEN
BROUGHT TO THE ISLAND.
MOST OF THE HOSPITALS ARE OPEN.
AT LEAST PARTIALLY OPEN.
MOST OF THEM NOW ARE OPEN.
AGAIN, THE JOB DONE HERE IS
NOTHING SHORT OF A MIRACLE.
IT'S BEEN INCREDIBLE.
I APPRECIATE VIRTUALLY -- THIS
IS THE MAYOR FROM THIS VERY
IMPORTANT AREA.
MR. MAYOR, I APPRECIATES YOUR
EFFORTS.
>> THANK YOU.
ON BEHALF OF MY PEOPLE, ON
BEHALF OF THE 3.5 MILLION U.S.
CITIZENS.
IS A TEAM.
YOUR PEOPLE ARE DOING THE RIGHT
STUFF FOR US.
WE AS THE MAYOR -- THIS IS A
TEAM.
THAT IS MY EXPERIENCE AND THE
HELPING OF THOUSANDS AND
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
THANK YOU, MR. PRESIDENT.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH,
EVERYBODY.
>> WHAT DID YOU MEAN EARLIER
THAT THEY COULD DO MORE?
>> Shepard: NOW THE PRESIDENT
WILL WALK IN THE BUILDING AND
BEGIN THIS EFFORT OF
DISTRIBUTING SUPPLIES TO PEOPLE
WHO WERE THERE.
SO LET'S LISTEN TO THIS.
[APPLAUSE]
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: THERE YOU HAVE IT.
LOTS OF PHOTOGRAPHS WITH THE
PRESIDENT.
SOME WELL-WISHES, SOME CHEERS
AND APPLAUSE AND SOME SUPPLIES
TO BE HANDED OUT THERE.
OF COURSE, THE REAL PROBLEM IN
PUERTO RICO HAS BEEN WITH
DISTRIBUTION.
SO MANY OF THE DRIVERS OF THE
TRUCKS THAT WOULD NORMALLY TAKE
THE PRODUCTS, THAT ARE NECESSARY
FOR SURVIVAL AROUND THE ISLAND,
THOSE DRIVERS HAVE LOST IN MANY
CASES THEIR HOMES OR THEIR
ABILITY TO GET WHEREVER THEY
NEED TO GO TO DRIVE THE
VEHICLES.
SO THEY'RE HAVING A LOT OF
PROBLEMS WITH DISTRIBUTION.
HURTING A LOT OF PEOPLE IN SMALL
TOWNS AND OUTSIDE OF SAN JUAN.
TO HEAR IT FROM THE WHITE HOUSE,
THEY'RE WORKING AS HARD AS THEY
CAN TO GET THE DISTRIBUTION
CHANNELS IN LINE SO THAT NO ONE
ELSE LOSES THEIR LIVES IN THE
HORROR THAT HAS BEEN PUERTO
RICO.
IN JUST A MOMENT, WE'LL RETURN
TO TRACE GALLAGHER WHO IS IN
LAS VEGAS.
AGAIN, THE HEADLINE FROM THIS
HOUR, WE NOW HAVE REPORTS FROM
THE DAILY MAIL THE UNITED
KINGDOM THAT THE GUNMAN BROUGHT
ALONG WITH ALL THE WEAPONS TO
CREATE HIS CARNAGE, CAMERAS TO
RECORD IT SET UP AT THE WINDOW
WHERE HE WAS SHOOTING AT LEAST
ONE OF THEM AND IN A HALL SO HE
WOULD KNOW WHEN POLICE WERE
COMING.
NEW DETAILS ON THE SUSPECT AND
THE VICTIMS STRAIGHTAWAY ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
Patrick woke up
with a sore back.
But he's got work to do.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Check this Sunday's paper
for extra savings on
products from Aleve.
>> Shepard: WE KNOW FROM THE
REPORTING OF THE DAILYMAIL.COM
FROM THE UNITED KINGDOM THAT THE
GUNMAN HAD CAMERAS REPORTING HIS
CARNAGE.
IN ADDITION, WE LEARNED MORE
ABOUT THE WEAPONS THAT HE HAD IN
THE ROOM.
23 IN THE ROOM TOTAL.
MORE THAN 40 IN HIS POSSESSION
AT HIS HOMES AND THERE.
INSIDE THE ROOM, 4  DDM-4
RIFLES.
SOME HAD BEEN AUGMENTED, AFTER
MARKET, SO THEY COULD BECOME
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS AND MANY MORE.
TRACE GALLAGHER IS LIVE IN
VEGAS.
WHAT ARE INVESTIGATORS DOING AT
THE SCENE TODAY.
>> SHEP, THERE'S A COUPLE OF
CRIME SCENES AS YOU KNOW.
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE GOING BACK TO
THE CRIME SCENE IN MESQUITE.
THAT'S WHERE THEY FOUND 17
WEAPONS AND EXPLOSIVES.
THEY PULLED HARD DRIVES AS WELL.
WE'LL HAVE MORE IN A NEWS
CONFERENCE.
AT THE HOTEL, THEY WERE STILL ON
SCENE PROCESSING THE WEAPONS AND
THE AMMUNITION.
THAT WILL TAKE THEM A COUPLE
MORE DAYS.
THEY WITH BACK HERE EARLY THIS
MORNING.
THE MANDALAY BAY IS FULLY OPEN
EXCEPT FOR THE 32nd FLOOR, WHICH
IS COMPLETELY SHUT DOWN.
THIS VIDEO WHERE THE CONCERT
TOOK PLACE, STILL SHUT DOWN TO
THE MEDIA AND THERE'S STILL
INVESTIGATORS CRAWLING ALL OVER
THIS PLACE TRYING NOT TO DISTURB
THE EVIDENCE BY WEARING BOOTIES.
YOU CAN TELL THE CARS TELL THE
STORY HERE.
STILL HUNDREDS OF CARS AROUND
THIS AREA.
WE HAD SOME PEOPLE COME OUT LAST
NIGHT ASKING US IF THEY COULD
GET THEIR CAR, ASKING POLICE.
THEY'RE BEING TOLD NO.
WE'RE BEING TOLD THAT EVERY CAR
HAS TO MATCH UP TO A CERTAIN
PERSON.
AS WE ALL KNOW, SOME OF THESE
CARS WILL NOT BE PICKED UP BY
THEIR OWNERS.
THE FBI IS ON SCENE.
THEY'RE MAPPING CARS OVER HERE.
THERE'S A SPECIFIC PURPOSE.
SOME OF THESE CARS TRIED TO GET
OUT WHEN THE SHOOTING STARTED
AND RAN INTO A DEAD END.
THE GREEN JEEP HAS BLOOD-STAINED
HAND PRINTS ON THE HOOD.
IF YOU LEAVE THE CAR, LOOK
AROUND THE GROUND AND THERE'S
BLOOD PRINTS ALL THE WAY OUT
HERE.
THIS DOESN'T GIVE US MOTIVE BUT
GIVES US AN IDEA HOW THE
INVESTIGATORS ARE TRYING TO MAP
THIS INVESTIGATION, WHICH COULD
GO ON FOR WEEKS AND WEEKS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER ON
SCENE.
EACH ONE OF THE VICTIMS IN
LAS VEGAS HAS HIS OR OWN STORY.
ALL OF THEM HAVE PEOPLE THAT
CARE ABOUT THEM, WHO MISS THEM,
WHO MOURN THEM.
WE'LL REMEMBER THE ONES ABOUT
WHICH WE HAVE KNOWLEDGE AND TELL
YOU ABOUT THEIR LIVES NEXT.
FIRST, TWO YEARS AGO, THE
REPLICA EIFFEL TOWER AT THE
PARIS CASINO IN LAS VEGAS WENT
DARK IN MEMORY OF ALL THAT WENT
DIED IN A TERROR ATTACK IN THE
FRENCH CAPITOL.
LAST NIGHT, THE ORIGINAL
RETURNED THE RESPECT.
DARKENING THOSE THAT WERE KILLED
IN LAS VEGAS AND A WEEKEND
TERROR ATTACK IN MARSEILLE.
THE NEWS CONTINUES NEXT.
al stooe
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night,
so he got home safe.
Yeah, my dad says our
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
>> Shepard: MUCH OF THE FOCUS IN
LAS VEGAS HAS BEEN ON THE
SHOOTER FOLLOWING THE MASSACRE.
BUT STORIES AFTER HEROISM
CONTINUE TO EMERGE.
FOR INSTANCE, 30-YEAR-OLD COPY
MACHINE REPAIR MAN JONATHAN
SMITH.
ACCORDING TO "THE WASHINGTON
POST," THE FATHER OF THREE WAS
SEPARATED FROM HIS FAMILY BUT
STAYED BEHIND TO DIRECT DOZENS
OF PEOPLE TO SAFETY.
A BULLET STRUCK HIM IN THE NECK
LEAVING HIM WITH A CRACKED RIB
AND BRUISED LINK.
THEN THERE'S 29-YEAR-OLD MARINE
VETERAN TAYLOR WINSTON WHO SAID
HE STOLE A TRUCK TO DRIVE PEOPLE
TO THE HOSPITAL.
HE TRANSPORTED BETWEEN 20 AND 30
PEOPLE AND LATER RETURNED THE
KEYS TO THE TRUCK'S OWNER AND
THEN THERE'S TRAVIS PHIPPEN AN
EMT.
HE STAYED BEHIND TO REVIVE HIS
FATHER THAT WAS SHOT.
ONE OF THE GUNMAN'S BULLETS HIT
TRAVIS WHO IS EXPECTED TO
SURVIVE.
HIS FATHER DID NOT MAKE IT OUT
ALIVE.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE WENT TO
HOSPITALS AFTER THE SHOOTING AND
SOME DOCTORS HAVE SAID IT WAS
VERY TOUGH TO KEEP UP AS THE
PATIENTS KEPT COMING.
OUR CHIEF CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN
HUNT IS LIVE AT UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL CENTER IN LAS VEGAS.
JONATHAN, HOW MANY PATIENTS ARE
STILL LISTED AS CRITICAL?
>> WELL, THERE'S TWO HOSPITALS
WITH CRITICAL PATIENTS NOW.
OVER AT SUNRISE MEDICAL, THEY
HAVE 33 IN CRITICAL CONDITION.
HERE AT UNIVERSITY MEDICAL
CENTER, 20 REMAIN AT THIS POINT
IN THE ICU.
I SPOKE TO ONE OF THE SURGEONS
WHO HAS BEEN WORKING DAY AND
NIGHT HERE.
HE SAID MANY OF THE GUNSHOT
WOUNDS WERE SO HORRIFIC, A LOT
OF THE STAFF WILL LIKELY NEED
PSYCHOLOGICAL HELP.
LISTEN HERE.
>> THERE WAS A LOT OF ANXIETY
AND LOSS OF FOCUS.
THAT CAN BE EASILY CORRECTED.
THE UNCONSCIOUS FORMS OF STRESS
ARE THINGS THAT AFFECT PEOPLE IN
THE SECOND AND THIRD DAY.
WE HAVE DEBRIEFING TEAMS
OFFERING SERVICE TO THE STAFF.
>> A REMINDER, SHEP, AS WELL AS
SO MANY PHYSICAL SCARS, THERE
WILL BE MANY MENTAL SCARS THAT
WILL TAKE A LONG TIME TO HEAL.
>> TELL US HOW THE MURDERER
MODIFIED THE WEAPONS TO SHOOT
MORE BULLETS QUICKLY.
>> YEAH,  WE TALKED TO AN ATF
SERVICE THAT SAID SOME OF THE
WEAPONS WERE MODIFIED AS WHAT IS
CALLED A SLIDE-FIRE MECHANISM.
THE INFORMATION APPARENTLY AND
THE COMPONENTS TO DO THAT EASILY
AVAILABLE ON THE INTERNET.
THIS VIDEO IS FROM ONE SUCH
SITE.
WE DON'T KNOW THAT MR. PADDOCK
USED THIS PARTICULAR SITE, OF
COURSE, BUT IT'S AN EXAMPLE OF
WHAT IS OUT THERE.
WHAT IT DOES, ACCORDING TO OUR
SOURCE, IS CHANGED THE SHOULDER
REST AND EFFECTIVELY MAKE THE
TRIGGER MIMIC FULLY AUTOMATIC
OPERATION.
OUR SOURCE SAYS THAT IT
BASICALLY TURNS A SEMIAUTOMATIC
RIFLE INTO A MACHINE GUN AND
REMEMBER, PADDOCK WAS ARMED WITH
MORE THAN ONE MACHINE GUN.
THAT'S THE KIND OF FIREPOWER
THAT RAINED DOWN ON THOSE
INNOCENT CONCERT GOERS.
>> THANKS, JONATHAN.
FIRST A LOOK AT MORE OF THE
VICTIMS.
MEN AND WOMEN MURDERED AT A WARM
WEEKEND NIGHT IN LAS VEGAS.
People would stare.
Psoriasis does that.
It was tough getting out there
on stage.
I wanted to be clear.
I wanted it to last.
So I kept on fighting.
I found something that worked.
And keeps on working.
Now?
They SEE ME.
SEE ME.
See if COSENTYX could make a
difference for you-
COSENTYX is proven to help
people with moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis...
...find clear skin that
can last.
Don't use if you're allergic
to COSENTYX.
Before starting COSENTYX,
you should be checked
for tuberculosis.
An increased risk of infections
and lowered ability
to fight them may occur.
Tell your doctor if you have
an infection or symptoms.
Or if you have received a
vaccine or plan to.
If you have inflammatory
bowel disease,
tell your doctor if symptoms
develop or worsen.
Serious allergic reactions
may occur.
Never give up.
SEE ME.
Clear skin can last.
Don't hold back...
...ask your dermatologist
if COSENTYX can help you
find clear skin that lasts.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
THE U.S. BOOTING MORE THAN HALF
OF CUBA'S DIPLOMATS FROM
WASHINGTON.
THIS COMES AFTER A MYSTERIOUS
SONIC ATTACK AGAINST AT LEAST 22
AMERICANS IN HAVANA.
THE SYMPTOMS ARE BRAIN DAMAGE
AND HEARING LOSS.
THE CUBAN GOVERNMENT HAS DENIED
ANY INVOLVEMENT.
THE STATE DEPARTMENT IS ALSO
PULLING MOST OF ITS STAFF OUT OF
CUBA AND WARNING AMERICANS
AGAINST TRAVELING THERE.
NEARLY TWO WEEKS AFTER A MASSIVE
EARTHQUAKE ROCKED MEXICO, SEARCH
TEAMS ARE STILL PULLING OUT
BODIES.
THE QUICK KILLED MORE THAN 300
AND DAMAGED THOUSANDS OF HOMES.
MUSIC FANS REMEMBERING TOM PETTY
LEAVING CANDLES AND FLOWERS ON
HIS HOLLYWOOD STAR.
HIS MANAGER SAID HE WENT INTO
CARDIAC ARREST AND DIED AT THE
HOSPITAL.
HE WAS 66.
THE NEWS CONTINUES WITH SHEP
AFTER THIS.
eed in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP
VISITING PUERTO RICO AFTER TWO
WEEKS AFTER HURRICANE MARIA TORE
THROUGH THE U.S. TERRITORY.
THE PRESIDENT AND THE FIRST LADY
ALSO MEETING THIS HOUR WITH THE
GOVERNOR OF THE U.S. VIRGIN
ISLANDS WHICH ARE STILL
RECOVERING FROM HURRICANES IRMA
AND MARIA.
WE'LL HAVE THAT FOR YOU WHEN WE
GET IT.
TODAY PRESIDENT TRUMP MET WITH
STORM VICTIMS IN PUERTO RICO.
OFFICIALS SAY ABOUT 95% OF THAT
ISLAND STILL HAS NO ELECTRICITY.
THAT INCLUDES SOME HOSPITALS.
LOTS OF PEOPLE ARE STILL
DESPERATE NEED OF THE BASICS.
FOOD, FRESHWATER, FUEL AND
MONEY.
THE PRESIDENT'S VISIT COMES AS
CRITICS SAY THAT THE FEDS HAVE
BEEN SLOW TO RESPOND.
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR HAS
DEFENDED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S EFFORTS.
THE MAJOR OF SAN JUAN SAID LAST
WEEK THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN
KILLING US WITH INEFFICIENCY.
THAT'S A QUOTE.
SHE ALSO SAID THAT PUERTO RICO
WAS HEADING TOWARDS GENOCIDE
BECAUSE OF THE CRISIS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP OVER THE WEEKEND
PUSHED BACK SAYING THE MAJOR AND
OTHERS HAVE SHOWN POOR
LEADERSHIP.
THE PRESIDENT ALSO TWEETED THAT
THERE'S BEEN TREMENDOUS
PROGRESS.
DESPITE THAT, AS HE PUT IT,
POLITICALLY MOTIVATED INGRATES
WE'RE SAYING.
THAT'S WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP TOLD
JOHN ROBERTS BEFORE LEAVING THE
WHITE HOUSE THIS MORNING.
>> I THINK SHE'S COME BACK A
LONG WAY.
NOW ACKNOWLEDGING WHAT A GREAT
JOB WE'VE DONE.
PEOPLE ARE LOOKING AT THAT.
TEXAS AND FLORIDA, WE GOT AN A
PLUS.
I TELL YOU WHAT, WE'VE DONE JUST
AS GOOD IN PUERTO RICO.
IT'S A MUCH TOUGHER SITUATION.
BUT NOW THE ROADS ARE CLEARED,
COMMUNICATIONS ARE STARTING TO
COME BACK.
WE NEED THEIR TRUCK DRIVERS.
THEIR DRIVERS HAVE TO START
DRIVING TRUCKS.
WE HAVE TO DO THAT.
ON A LOCAL LEVEL, WE NEED MORE
HELP.
THE FIRST RESPONDERS, MILITARY,
FEMA HAVE DONE AN INCREDIBLE JOB
IN PUERTO RICO.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SHOOK HANDS WITH THE SAN JUAN
MAYOR JUST BEFORE A BRIEFING ON
THE RELIEF EFFORTS.
YOU CAN MAKE OUT A LITTLE BIT OF
THAT OR WHAT SHE SAID TO THE
PRESIDENT.
HERE, LOOK.
>> Shepard: DURING THE BRIEFING
WHEN THEY THANKED FEDERAL AND
LOCAL OFFICIALS FOR THEIR
EFFORTS, HE DID NOT MENTION THE
MAYOR.
THE PRESIDENT MENTIONED THE
TRUCKERS.
ACCORDING TO OUR REPORTERS ON
THE GROUND, MANY OF THOSE THAT
WOULD MOVE THE SUPPLIES HAVE
LOST THEIR HOMES AND VEHICLES IN
THE STORM.
SOME OF THE TRUCKERS CAN'T BE
REACHED BECAUSE THERE'S NO
COMMUNICATION WORKING IN SO MANY
AREAS STILL.
REPORTS THAT A UNION TRUCKER'S
STRIKE ADDED TO THE PROBLEMS ARE
NOT TRUE.
THEY ARE IN FACT FAKE NEWS
SPREAD LARGELY BY A WEBSITE
CALLED CONSERVATIVE TREE HOUSE
AND THEN OVER TWITTER AND
FACEBOOK.
AGAIN, THERE'S NO TRUCKER'S
STRIKE.
THAT'S FAKE NEWS.
THE TRUCKERS IN PUERTO RICO ARE
VICTIMS, TOO.
THE CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HAS AN UPDATE.
HI, JOHN.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON, SHEP.
THERE'S SO MANY VICTIMS IN
PUERTO RICO AND THE PRESIDENT
GOT TO MEET A FEW OF THEM.
THE PRESIDENT WITH HIGH PRAISE
FOR THE FEDERAL RESPONSE AND THE
MILITARY.
THE PRESIDENT THANKING VERY MUCH
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR WHO
ALIGNS WITH DEMOCRATS FOR
LEAVING POLITICS OUT OF THIS
THING.
THE DISCUSSION ABOUT STORM
RELIEF.
LISTEN TO WHAT THE PRESIDENT
SAID JUST A LITTLE WHILE AGO.
>> HE WAS TREMENDOUSLY
SUPPORTIVE.
HE KNEW THE LEVEL OF PROBLEM
THAT YOU HAD AT THE BEGINNING
BEFORE AND THE LEVEL OF WHAT
HAPPENED WITH RESPECT TO THE
TREMENDOUS STORMS THAT HAVE HIT
YOUR BEAUTIFUL ISLAND.
TO THE GOVERNOR, I WANT TO TELL
YOU THAT RIGHT FROM THE
BEGINNING, THIS GOVERNOR DID NOT
PLAY POLITICS.
HE DIDN'T PLAY IT AT ALL.
HE WAS SAYING IT LIKE IT WAS.
HE WAS GIVING US THE HIGHEST
GRADES.
ON BEHALF OF OUR COUNTRY, I WANT
TO THANK YOU.
>> THE PRESIDENT SPENDING SOME
TIME WITH RESIDENTS IN A
SAN JUAN NEIGHBORHOOD AND WENT
TO A LOCAL CHURCH, WHICH IS A
DISTRIBUTION POINT FOR RELIEF
SUPPLIES AND HANDING OUT RICE
AND PAPER TOWELS.
THE PRESIDENT HAS TWEETED ABOUT
THE ENORMOUS AMOUNT OF MONEY
IT'S GOING TO TAKE TO REBUILD
PUERTO RICO AND JOKED THIS
MORNING THE DISASTER HAS
STRETCHED THE FEDERAL BUDGET A
LITTLE BIT THIN.
LISTEN HERE.
>> I HATE TO TELL YOU, PUERTO
RICO, BUT YOU'RE THROWING OUR
BUDGET A LITTLE OUT OF WHACK.
WE SPENT A LOT OF MONEY IN
PUERTO RICO.
THAT'S FINE.
WE SAVED A LOT OF LIVES.
>> ON CAPITOL HILL, SENATOR
CHUCK SCHUMER OF NEW YORK SAID
HE DIDN'T APPRECIATE THE JOKE
SAYING IT LOOKS LIKE THE
PRESIDENT WAS BLAMING PUERTO
RICO.
A LOT OF FOLKS WOULD LIKE TO
BLOW THE LINES FOR DISASTER
RELIEF AND THE ENORMOUS DEBT IN
PUERTO RICO.
THE PRESIDENT WANTS TO MAKE SURE
THE FOCUS IS ON DISASTER RELIEF
AND ANY DISCUSSION ABOUT PUERTO
RICO'S DEBT WILL HAVE TO WAIT
UNTIL LATER, UNTIL AFTER THEY
HAVE RECOVERED FROM THE STORM.
>> Shepard: JOHN, THE PRESIDENT
WHILE IN PUERTO RICO TALKED
ABOUT THE HORRIBLE MURDER
RAMPAGE IN LAS VEGAS.
>> YEAH.
HE GETS BACK FROM PUERTO RICO
LATE TONIGHT, TOMORROW MORNING
AND WILL HEAD OUT TO LAS VEGAS.
THE PRESIDENT SAYING A WHILE AGO
IN TERMS OF THE TRIP TO
LAS VEGAS, HE LOOKS FORWARD TO
PAYING HIS PERSONAL RESPECTS AND
CONDOLENCES TO EVERYONE.
SUCH A TRAGEDY, SO UNNECESSARY.
I LOOK FORWARD TO GOING
TOMORROW.
THE FIRST LADY WILL BE COMING
WITH ME AND PAYING OUR RESPECTS.
THE PRESIDENT SAID HIS ANXIOUS
TO GET A FULL UNDERSTANDING WHY
THE GUNMAN DID THIS AND A HIGH
PRAISE FOR POLICE THAT RAN
TOWARDS DANGER AND TRACKED DOWN
WHERE HE WAS FIRING FROM.
LISTEN HERE.
>> WE HAVE A TRAGEDY.
WHAT HAPPENED IN LAS VEGAS IS IN
MANY WAYS A MIRACLE.
THE POLICE DEPARTMENT HAS DONE
SUCH AN INCREDIBLE JOB.
WE'LL BE TALKING ABOUT GUN LAWS.
HIS A SICK MAN, DEMENTED MAN.
WE'RE LOOKING INTO HIM VERY
SERIOUSLY.
BUT WE'RE DEALING WITH A VERY,
VERY SICK INDIVIDUAL.
>> A LOT OF THORNY POLITICAL
ISSUES LIE AHEAD.
DEMOCRATS ARE TALKING ABOUT GUN
CONTROL.
A BILL IN CONGRESS THAT APPEARS
TO HAVE BEEN SHELVED FOR NOW
THAT MAKES SILENCERS ILLEGAL.
I ASKED THE PRESIDENT ABOUT HIS
POSITION.
HE SAID WE'LL TALK ABOUT THAT
LATER.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU, JOHN.
IN PUERTO RICO, SOME BUSINESSES
ARE STARTING TO REOPEN.
AS WE HEARD, MANY AREAS OF THE
ISLAND ARE STILL DEVASTATED AND
IN NEED OF SO MUCH HELP.
SOME FAMOUS PUERTO RICANS ARE
CHIPPING IN.
GERALDO RIVERA REPORTS FROM
SAN JUAN.
>> SHEP, PUERTO RICO IS SLOWLY
GETTING BACK ON ITS FEET.
A LONG ROAD TO RECOVERY.
95% OF THE PEOPLE ARE STILL
WITHOUT ELECTRICAL POWER.
EVEN HERE ON TOURIST STRIP.
HALF THE PEOPLE DON'T HAVE
RUNNING WATER AND A THIRD OF
THEM HAVE ANY KIND OF CELL
SERVICE OR INTERNET.
THAT'S PART OF THE PROBLEM, NO
COMMUNICATIONS.
ONE OF THE THINGS THAT IS
UNDERREPORTED IS HOW THE PUERTO
RICAN FAMILY, THE EXTENDED
FAMILY, NEIGHBORS, RELATIVES AND
SO FORTH ARE COMING TOGETHER TO
HELP PEOPLE.
J-LO DONATING A BUNCH OF MONEY.
RICKY MARTIN CAME YESTERDAY.
LOOK AT THIS CREW FROM QUEENS,
NEW YORK.
NATIONAL GUARDSMEN AND OTHER
VOLUNTEERS BRINGING AID AND
ASSISTANCE TO THEIR PUERTO RICAN
FAMILY.
>> WE CAME.
THESE ARE DONATIONS THAT CAME
FROM NEW YORK CITY.
WE'RE GOING OUT TODAY TO TAKE
CARE OF THEM.
>> SHEP, MANY HERE IN PUERTO
RICO ARE WORRIED THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES WOULD BE
DIVERTED BY THE AWFUL TRAGEDY IN
LAS VEGAS.
THE FOLKS ARE DELIGHTED THAT HE
IS MAKING THE VISIT HERE TO
PUERTO RICO AND WILL GO ON TO
NEVADA ON WEDNESDAY.
THERE HAVE BEEN REPORTS OF
LOOTING HERE IN PUERTO RICO.
I JUST WANT TO SAY THAT
ACCORDING TO THE OFFICIALS, THE
CRIME RATE IS ABOUT THE SAME AS
IT WAS.
THOSE REPORTS ARE EXAGGERATED.
WHAT SHOULD BE EMPHASIZED IS HOW
THE PUERTO RICAN PEOPLE ARE
COMING TOGETHER TO HELP EACH
OTHER.
REPORTING FROM SAN JUAN, SHEP,
BACK TO YOU.
>> Shepard: THANKS, GERALDO.
BETWEEN THE CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO AND THE MASSACRE IN
LAS VEGAS, THE PRESIDENT IS PUT
TO A TEST.
MORE ON HIS ROLE AS CONSOLER IN
CHIEF NEXT.
>> MORE ON THE PRESIDENT'S TRIP
TO PUERTO RICO AFTER OFFICIALS
THERE CRITICIZED THE FEDERAL
RESPONSE TO HURRICANE MARIA.
AT LEAST THE LOCAL MAYOR DID AND
SOME OTHERS.
PUERTO RICO'S GOVERNOR HAS
PRAISED THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S RESPONSE TO
THAT DEADLY STORM.
LET'S BRING IN ALEX FROM
POLITICO.
SAN JUAN IS COMING ALONG WELL.
SOME OTHERS ARE NOT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS A REALLY TROUBLING
SITUATION, WHAT YOU SAW TODAY IS
THE PRESIDENT TRAVELED THERE AND
TRIED TO BEST SPIN FORWARD ON
WHAT HIS ADMINISTRATION'S
EFFORTS HAVE BEEN SO FAR.
EVEN AS HE'S GOTTEN TO THIS
FIGHT WITH LOCAL OFFICIALS
THERE.
A LOT OF THIS SEEMED TO BE ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT TRYING TO DEFEND
HIMSELF AND HIS WHITE HOUSE AND
HOW THEY HAVE DONE SO FAR IN
MANAGING THIS CRISIS.
>> Shepard: IT WAS A BIT OF A
PRESS AVAILABILITY AND PHOTO
OPPORTUNITY THERE UNLIKE ANY
I'VE SEEN WITH PREVIOUS
PRESIDENTS AT DISASTERS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
YOU GOT THE SENSE THAT THE
PRESIDENT WAS TRYING TO PUT ON A
SHOW HERE AND TRYING TO
ADVERTISE HIMSELF AND WHAT HE'S
DONE AND DEFEND HIMSELF AND HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
YOU KNOW, HERE'S THE THING ABOUT
THIS TRIP AND WHAT YOU'LL ALSO
SEE WITH THIS TRIP THAT WILL
COME TOMORROW WITH LAS VEGAS.
THIS SQUEAK SPOTLIGHTS A ROLE
THAT TRUMP HADN'T NECESSARILY
EXPECTED TO PLAY WHEN HE FIRST
RAN FOR PRESIDENT, WHICH IS THAT
OF CONSOLER IN CHIEF.
THAT OF A LEADER THAT IS COMING
TO THE COMFORT --
>> Shepard: I DON'T KNOW WHY HE
WOULDN'T EXPECT TO DO THAT.
EVERY PRESIDENT FOREVER HAS HAD
TO DO THAT.
LOOK HOW GREAT RONALD REAGAN WAS
AT IT ON THE HEELS OF THE
CHALLENGER DISASTER.
EACH PRESIDENT SINCE THEN HAS
HAD A SHINING MOMENT IN TIMES OF
NEED, I WOULD SAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AT ONE TIME OR THE OTHER.
YOU'RE SEEING A PRESIDENT THAT
CAMPAIGNED ON THE IDEA THAT HE
WAS GOING TO BE A STRONG MAN
LIKE FIGURE, A FIGURE OF
STRENGTH.
HE'S DOING SOMETHING THAT HE
DIDN'T REALLY CAMPAIGN ON.
>> Shepard: ALEX, HAVE TO CUT IT
SHORT.
THERE'S NEW INFORMATION COMING
IN TO FOX NEWS ABOUT THE
INVESTIGATION INTO THE LAS VEGAS
MASSACRE, INCLUDING WORD THAT
THE FEDS HAVE TALKED WITH AN
IMMEDIATE RELATIVE OF THE
GUNMAN'S GIRLFRIEND.
WE HAVE BRAND NEW DETAILS.
OUR CHIEF INTELLIGENCE
CORRESPONDENT CATHERINE HERRIDGE
JUST PULLED THEM TOGETHER.
LIVE TO HER NEXT.
KEEPING ME FROM THE
THINGS I LOVE TO DO.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-214-2424.
I just saved thousands
In less than a minute, I found
out how much home I can afford.
I like how you shop for loans
the same way you
shop for flights online.
I didn't realize at LendingTree
you can save money
on almost any sort of loan.
I consolidated my credit card
debt with a personal loan.
I found a new credit card
with 0% interest for 15 months.
You just shop, compare,
and save. And it's all free.
Go to LendingTree right now
and start saving.
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS NOW.
WE HAVE AN UPDATE ON THE
INVESTIGATION OF THE MASSACRE IN
LAS VEGAS.
A U.S. GOVERNMENT SOURCE SAYS
THE FEDS HAVE INTERVIEWED A
RELATIVE OF THE SHOOTER'S
GIRLFRIEND AND WE HAVE JUST
LEARNED THAT IN THE 70s AND 80s,
THE SHOOTER WORKED AS A LETTER
CARRIER AND AN IRS AGENT
SEPARATELY FOR A TOTAL OF A
DECADE.
SO WHAT ABOUT THIS INTERVIEW
WITH THE GIRLFRIEND'S FAMILY?
CATHERINE HERRIDGE HAS THAT LIVE
IN WASHINGTON.
KATHERINE?
>> I'VE BEEN WORKING ON THIS
INFORMATION THROUGHOUT THE DAY
WITH THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
PRODUCER, JAKE GIBSON.
WE CONFIRMED THROUGH A U.S.
GOVERNMENT SOURCE THAT FEDERAL
INVESTIGATORS HAVE INTERVIEWED A
IMMEDIATE RELATIVELY MARILOU
DANLEY.
THIS RELATIVE SAID TO THE FBI
THAT THEY FOUND PADDOCK UNSTABLE
AND HE MADE THEM UNCOMFORTABLE.
FBI OFFICIALS DECLINED TO
COMMENT ON THIS INTERVIEW ONE
WAY OR THE OTHER TO FOX NEWS
EARLIER TODAY.
AND THE FBI RAN PADDOCK THROUGH
THE CRIMINAL SYSTEM.
WE'RE TOLD IT WILL TAKE A DAY OR
TWO TO PROCESS HIS RECORD.
THE FBI INDICATED IN CONNECTION
TO TERROR WAS MADE BEFORE THE
FULL ANALYSIS OF HIS ELECTRONICS
WAS COMPLETE, SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE, WHAT DO
WE KNOW ABOUT THE MONEY THAT
THIS MURDERER SENT OVERSEAS
PRIOR TO THE MASSACRE?
>> INVESTIGATORS HAVE DISCOVERED
THAT PADDOCK SENT TENS OF
THOUSANDS OVERSEAS AND MAY HAVE
BEEN TO THE GIRLFRIEND, MARILOU
DANLEY.
THEY'RE STILL INVESTIGATING.
THEY THINK IT WAS TO THE
PHILIPPINES BUT THERE'S
CONFUSION OVER HER LOCATION AND
WHETHER SHE'S IN JAPAN.
HE SEND A LOT OF MONEY OVERSEAS
BEFORE THE SHOOTING AND
INVESTIGATORS ARE TRYING TO
DETERMINE IF IT WENT TO THIS
GIRLFRIEND OR SOMEONE ASSOCIATED
WITH HER, SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE A LOT OF
GAPS IN THE STORY OF THIS MAN.
AUTHORITIES SAY IT'S SO RARE TO
HAVE A SHOOTING WITHOUT A
MOTIVE.
SOMETHING THEY HAVE NOT FOUND.
>> EVERYONE I SPEAK TO ABOUT
THIS CASE, SHEP, TALKS ABOUT IT
AS BEING AN ANOMALY.
YOU KNOW FROM YOUR EXPERIENCE
COVERING THESE EVENTS, THAT
USUALLY WITHIN 24 HOURS YOU HAVE
A GOOD SENSE OF THE SHOOTER AND
A LIKELY MOTIVATION.
THEY HAVE SOME KIND OF PRESENCE
ON SOCIAL MEDIA OR THEY HAVE
BEEN ON BLOGS WRITING ABOUT
THEIR POINT OF VIEW.
THIS GUY IS REALLY A GHOST WHEN
IT COMES TO SOCIAL MEDIA AND NO
ONE HAS COME FORWARD IN A VERY
PUBLIC WAY TO TALK ABOUT WHAT
HIS MOTIVATION MAY HAVE BEEN ON
THE IDEOLOGY.
BUT WHAT IS CLEAR FROM THE SCOPE
OF THE INVESTIGATION, THE
LOCATIONS, THE FIREPOWER, THE
AMMUNITION, ALL OF THESE THINGS
WE'VE BEEN DISCUSSING THE LAST
24 HOURS IS THAT IT TOOK
SIGNIFICANT PREMEDDATION, RIGHT?
IT'S NOT SOMETHING THAT YOU CAN
THROW TOGETHER ON SHORT NOTICE.
>> Shepard: NOT THIS CLEARLY.
>> YEAH.
>> Shepard: NICE TO TALK WITH
YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> YOU BET.
>> Shepard: WE'LL BE BACK WITH A
LOOK AT TWO OF THE MOST FAMOUS
COURT VERDICTS IN AMERICAN
HISTORY AND BOTH OF THEM
HAPPENED ON THIS DAY.
(AVO)
When you have type 2 diabetes,
you manage your A1C,
but you also have a higher risk
of heart attack or stroke.
Non-insulin Victoza®
lowers A1C,
and now reduces
cardiovascular risk.
Victoza® lowers my
A1C and blood sugar
better than
the leading
branded pill.
(AVO)
And for people with
type 2 diabetes
treating cardiovascular disease,
Victoza® is NOW approved
to lower the risk of major
cardiovascular events
such as heart attack,
stroke, or death.
And while it isn't
for weight loss,
Victoza® may
help you lose some weight.
(AVO)
Victoza® is not for people with
type 1 diabetes
or diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not take Victoza® if you have
a personal or family history
of medullary thyroid cancer,
Multiple Endocrine
Neoplasia syndrome type 2,
or if you are allergic
to Victoza®
or any of its ingredients.
Stop taking Victoza® and get
medical help right away
if you get symptoms of a serious
allergic reaction such as rash,
swelling, difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Serious side effects may happen,
including pancreatitis.
So, stop taking Victoza®
and call your doctor right away
if you have severe pain
in your stomach area.
Tell your doctor
your medical history.
Gallbladder problems have
happened in some people.
Tell your doctor right away
if you get symptoms.
Taking Victoza® with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Common side effects are nausea,
diarrhea, vomiting,
decreased appetite,
indigestion, and constipation.
Side effects
can lead to dehydration,
which may cause kidney problems.
Ask your doctor
about Victoza®.
>> Shepard: ON THIS DAY IN
HISTORY, THE COURT HANDED DOWN
TWO DIFFERENT VERDICTS TO O.J.
SIMPSON.
IN 1995, HE WAS CLEARED OF
MURDERS NICOLE SIMPSON AND RON
GOLDMAN.
O.J. LED POLICE ON A LOW SPEED
CHASE ACROSS L.A.
PROSECUTORS SAID THEY HAD A
MOUNTAIN OF EVIDENCE, A TRAIL OF
BLOCK FROM ROCKINGHAM TO BUNDY.
BUT JOHNNY COCHRAN SAID IF THE
GLOVE DOESN'T FIT, YOU MUST
ACQUIT AND THE JURY DID THIS DAY
22 YEARS AGO TODAY.
AND ON THIS DATE, A.J. WAS
CONVICTED ON CHARGES RELATED TO
AN ARMED ROBBERY IN LAS VEGAS.
INVESTIGATOR SAY HE STOLE SPORTS
MEMORABILIA.
O.J. SAID HE WAS JUST TRYING TO
GET HIS STUFF BACK.
THE JUDGE SENTENCED HIM TO 33
YEARS IN PRISON.
JUST TWO DAYS AGO HE WENT FREE
ON PAROLE AFTER A COURT FOUND
O.J. SIMPSON GUILTY NINE YEARS
AGO TODAY.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
BREAKING NEWS CHANGES EVERYTHING
ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
THE MARKETS ARE UP TODAY AND
NEIL CAVUTO HAS ALL THAT
BEGINNING NOW.
>> Neil: THANK YOU, SHEPARD.
WE'RE ALSO AWAITING A NEWS
CONFERENCE BY LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIALS ON THE LAS VEGAS
SHOOTING.
WHEN IT BEGINS, WE'LL HAVE IT
LIVE.
YOU TOUCHED ON THE WINNING
MARKET DAY.
JUST AN UPDATE.
FIFTH DAY IN THE ROW.
IF THE MARKETS ARE SUPPOSED TO
BE SKIDDISH ABOUT THIS ATTACK
AND CONCERNS ABOUT NORTH KOREA
AND ABOUT TAX POLICY IN
WASHINGTON, THEY HAVE A FUNNY
WAY OF SHOWING IT.
THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS, THAT
IS GOOD ENOUGH FOR A RECORD.
A LOT OF THE HOTEL AND CASINO
STOCKS GOT HIT YESTERDAY, ODDLY
ENOUGH SOME BUT NOT ALL COMING
BACK TODAY.
NOW T