[ LAUGHTER ]
WHO IS YOUR DADDY?
>> Bret: CAPTIVE AUDIENCE.
THANKS FOR INVITING US INTO
YOUR HOME TONIGHT.
THAT'S IT FOR THIS "SPECIAL
REPORT," FAIR, BALANCED AND
UNAFRAID.
BING PULSE TOMORROW NIGHT.
NOT FRIDAY.
>> THE PRESIDENT RETAINS
ALL OPTIONS AVAILABLE TO
HIM.
THE PENTAGON SAYS IT'S
READY TO GO.
WHENEVER PRESIDENT OBAMA
GIVES THE ORDER.
BUT SYRIA WARNS IT WILL
STRIKE BACK WITH EVERYTHING
IT'S GOT.
PLUS,.
>> SHOT MY BABY.
>> Bill: THE MOTHER WHO
SAYS SHE WATCHED THE GUNMAN
SHOOT HER BABY IN THE FACE
TAKES THE STAND.
>> I PUT MY ARMS OVER MY
BABY BUT HE STILL SHOT HIM.
>> Bill: AHEAD, THE
EMOTIONAL DAY IN COURT.
[CHEERS]
>> HER MOTHER CALLS IT A
MIRACLE WELCOME HOME, SARA.
>> THE LITTLE GIRL WHOSE
FAMILY FOUGHT FOR A A LIFE
SAVING LUNG TRANSPLANT
FINALLY GOES HOME.
>> Bill: I'M BILL HEMMER IN
TONIGHT FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
A U.S. MILITARY IS READY TO
GO IF PRESIDENT OBAMA GIVES
THE ORDER FOR A STRIKE
AGAINST SYRIA.
THAT'S WHAT DEFENSE
SECRETARY CHUCK HAGEL SAID
TODAY.
AND UNU.S. OFFICIAL TELLING
FOX NEWS, IT IS NOT A
MATTER OF IF, BUT WHEN.
THE WHITE HOUSE PLANS TO
SHOW SYRIAN GOVERNMENT WAS
BEHIND THE ATTACK.
KILLED INNOCENT CHILDREN.
JOE BIDEN SAID THERE IS NO
DOUBT WHO IS TO BLAME.
>> THE SYRIAN REGIME THE
ONLY ONES WHO HAVE THE
WEAPONS.
HAVE USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS
MULTIPLE TIMES IN THE PAST.
HAVE THE MEANS OF
DELIVERING THOSE WEAPONS.
HAVE BEEN DETERMINED TO
WIPE OUT EXACTLY THE PLACES
THAT WERE ATTACKED
BIOCHEMICAL WEAPONS.
>> Bill: THE WHITE HOUSE
SAYING THERE MUST BE A
RESPONSE TO LAST WEEK'S
ATTACK.
PRESIDENT OBAMA IS STILL
DECIDING WHAT THAT RESPONSE
WILL BE.
WE HAVE TEAM FOX COVERAGE,
JONATHAN HUNT LIVE HERE IN
NEW YORK WITH WITH A LOOK
AT THE OTHER COUNTRIES
CALLING FOR ACTION.
BUT FIRST TO JENNIFER
GRIFFIN LIVE AT THE
PENTAGON WITH US THIS
EVENING.
JENNIFER, GOOD EVENING TO
YOU.
WHAT WOULD A U.S. MILITARY
STRIKE LOOK LIKES A IT
STANDS NOW?
>> BILL, A SENIOR U.S.
OFFICIAL TELLS FOX THAT ANY
STRIKE ON SYRIA IS LIKELY
TO LAST HOURS, NOT DAYS.
ACCORDING TO U.S. MILITARY
SOURCES, THERE ARE NO PLANS
IN THIS INITIAL MISSION SET
TO GO AFTER ASSAD'S
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
IT IS NOT POSSIBLE TO CARRY
OUT A SURGICAL STRIKE ON
CHEMICAL WEAPONS STORAGE
FACILITIES, ASSAD IS
ESTIMATED TO HAVE
1,000 TONS OF THOSE
MATERIALS.
SUCH A STRIKE COULD UNLEASH
THOSE CHEMICALS AND LEAD TO
A LOT OF DEATH AND
DESTRUCTION, SOURCES SAY.
ANY PLANS TO SECURE ASSAD'S
CHEMICAL WEAPONS WOULD
REQUIRE SPECIAL OPERATIONS
AND BOOTS ON THE GROUND.
THAT IS NOT ON THE TABLE
RIGHT NOW.
THE U.S. IS PLANNING A
LIMITED STRIKE.
FOUR NAVY DESTROYERS IN
POSITION AND AT LEAST ONE
NUCLEAR POWERED SUBMARINE.
THE BRITISH COULD PROVIDE
ANOTHER SUBMARINE IF
PARLIAMENT VOTE SLATED LATE
FOR THURSDAY BILL.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE TIME
JENNIFER.
>> NOT BEFORE NATO MEETS
BRUSSELS TOMORROW AND WE'RE
TOLD IT WOULD OCCUR MOST
LIKELY THIS WEEKEND.
CHUCK HAGEL SPOKE TO HIS
BRITISH AND FRENCH COUNTER
PARTS BY PHONE TODAY.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH THE
BBC, HAGEL SAID U.S.
WARSHIPS ARE STANDING BY
AWAITING ORDERS.
>> LET'S GET THE FACTS.
LET'S GET THE INTELLIGENCE.
AND THEN A DECISION WILL BE
MADE ON WHETHER ACTION
SHOULD BE TAKEN, IF ACTION
SHOULD BE TAKEN, WHAT
ACTION.
OR NO ACTION.
BUT IF YOU COME YOU ARE
READY TO GO LIKE THAT.
>> WE ARE READY TO GO LIKE
THAT.
>> AGAIN THE PLAN AT THIS
POINT IS TO DETER ASSAD AND
DEGRADE HIS ABILITIES.
MULTIPLE PENTAGON SOURCES
SUGGEST THE STRIKE WILL BE
LIMITED.
BILL?
>> Bill: THANK YOU
JENNIFER.
JENNIFER GRIFFIN WITH THAT
FOX REPORT TONIGHT FROM THE
PENTAGON.
SECRETARY HAGEL SAYS IF THE
U.S. MILITARY DOES TAKE
ACTION, WE WILL NOT BE
GOING IT ALONE.
OUR TEAM FOX COVERAGE
CONTINUES NOW.
CHIEF CORRESPONDENT
JONATHAN HUNT JOINS US.
IT LOOKS LIKE WE SEE A
COALITION FORMING.
>> FORMING AND IN PLACE.
IMPORTANT PART OF THAT
COALITION EVEN IF
UNOFFICIALLY MAY WELL BE
THE ARAB LEAGUE.
THE ARAB LEAGUE MET TODAY
AND ISSUED A STATEMENT
BACKING U.S. CONCLUSIONS
OVER THE USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS IN SYRIA LAST WEEK
ON THE WESTERN FRONT BOTH
THE FRENCH AND BRITISH
PRIME MINISTERS TALKING
VERY MUCH ABOUT THE NEED
FOR MILITARY ACTION.
BRITISH PRIME MINISTER
DAVID CAMMERON SAYS IT IS
LIKELY TO HAPPEN.
BUT THERE MUST BE A CLEAR
GOAL.
LISTEN.
>> IT WOULD HAVE TO BE
SPECIFICALLY TO DETER AND
DEGRADE THE FUTURE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
LET ME STRESS TO PEOPLE.
THIS IS NOT ABOUT GETTING
INVOLVED IN A MIDDLE
EASTERN WAR OR CHANGING OUR
STAFFS IN SYRIA OR GOING
FURTHER INTO THAT CONFLICT.
IT'S NOTHING TO DO WITH
THAT IT'S ABOUT CHEMICAL
WEAPONS, THEIR USE IS
WRONG.
AND THE WORLD SHUNNED
DISTANT IDOLLY BY.
>> PRESIDENT OBAMA SPOKE TO
PRIME MINISTER DAVID
CAMMERON TODAY.
ALSO WORTH NOTING BILL
THAT THE BRITISH PRIME
MINISTER HAS RECALLED
PARLIAMENT FROM ITS SUMMER
RECESS.
THAT MEETING DUE TO TAKE
PLACE THURSDAY.
IF YOU ARE READING THE TEA
LEAVES ON TIMING, THAT
COULD ALSO BE SIGNIFICANT,
BILL.
>> BUT SYRIA REMAINS
DEFIANT.
>> YEAH, THE FOREIGN
MINISTER SPEAKING OUT TODAY
SAYING THAT ABSOLUTELY
WITHOUT QUESTION SYRIA WILL
DEFEND ITSELF IF ATTACKED.
LISTEN.
>> IF ANY AGGRESSION WERE
TO TAKE PLACE, WE HAVE TWO
OPTIONS.
TO SURRENDER OR TO DEFEND
OURSELVES USING THE OPTIONS
AVAILABLE.
USING ALL MEANS AVAILABLE.
>> IN THE MEANTIME, U.N.
WEAPONS INSPECTORS ARE
STILL ON THE GROUND IN
DAMASCUS, TRYING TO
INVESTIGATE THAT ALLEGED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK.
DESPITE DIFFICULTIES THAT
THEY HAVE FACED, INCLUDING
A SNIPER ATTACK ON THEIR
CONVOY.
YOU CAN SEE THE BULLET
HOLES IN ONE OF THEIR
VEHICLES THERE.
MEANTIME, THE SPOKESMAN FOR
THE U.N. SECRETARY GENERAL
SAYS DIPLOMACY IS STILL BY
FAR THE PREFERRED MEANS OF
ENDING THIS CRISIS.
LISTEN.
>> OUR FOCUS IS AWAY FROM
ANY MILITARY SOLUTION AND
TOWARDS A DIPLOMATIC
SOLUTION AND WE CONTINUE TO
WORK ON AT ALL AVENUES TO
TRY TO GET A DIPLOMATIC
SOLUTION GOING.
WE REMAIN COMBINED THAT
THERE HAS ALREADY BEEN FAR
TOO MUCH BLOOD SHED IN
SYRIA.
>> BUT, WITH THE RUSSIANS
BOUND TO BLOCK ANY UNITED
NATIONS SECURITY COUNCIL
RESOLUTION, IT APPEARS
BILL, THAT THE U.S. HAS
ALREADY MADE THE DECISION
TO GO AHEAD WITH ANY
MILITARY OPTION UNDER THE
AUSPICES OF NATO, RATHER
THAN THE U.N., BILL.
>> Bill: WE WILL LIKELY
FIND OUT VERY SOON.
THANK YOU JONATHAN HUNT
FROM OUR NEW YORK NEWSROOM
TONIGHT.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT'S
CONSULTING WITH CONGRESS
ABOUT HOW TO RESPOND TO
DAMASCUS.
BUT, SOME LAWMAKERS FROM
BOTH PARTIES CLAIM THAT IS
NOT ENOUGH.
THEY SAY CONGRESS HAS TO
APPROVE ANY MILITARY
ACTION.
WE'LL GO LIVE TO THE WHITE
HOUSE IN A MOMENT HERE
INSIDE OUR FOX REPORT
TONIGHT.
IN THE MEANTIME THERE WERE
TEARS AND A LOT OF THEM
TODAY IN A COURTROOM NEAR
ATLANTA.
A MOTHER DESCRIBING THE
MOMENT SHE SAYS A TEENAGER
SHOT HER BABY DEAD.
THAT MOTHER BROKE DOWN
SAYING THE SUSPECT DEMANDED
MONEY WHEN SHE TOLD HIM SHE
DID NOT HAVE ANY MONEY.
SHE SAYS THE TEEN'S
ATTENTION TURNED IT TO HER
BABY, SOUND ASLEEP IN A
STROLLER.
>> HE ASKED ME IF I WANTED
HIM TO SHOOT MY BABY I SAID
PLEASE DON'T SHOOT MY BABY.
HE SHOT A WARNING SHOT TO
THE GROUND.
I ASKED HIM WHY ARE YOU
DOING THIS?
PLEASE DON'T DO THIS.
IT FELT LIKE HE SHOT ME IN
THE EAR.
>> WHAT HAPPENED NEXT?
>> THEN HE SHOT ME IN THE
LEG.
>> WHAT HAPPENED AFTER
THAT?
>> HE WALKED OVER AND SHOT
MY BABY.
>> HE SHOT YOUR BABY?
>> YES.
I TRIED TO STOP HIM I PUT
MY ARMS OVER MY BABY BUT HE
STILL SHOT HIM.
>> PROSECUTORS ALSO SHOWING
A VIDEO OF THE MOTHER
RECREATING THAT SHOOTING.
THIS WAS JUST HOURS AFTER
THE BABY'S MURDER.
THE MOTHER LIMPED AROUND
THE CRIME SCENE, A BULLET
STILL INSIDE OF HER LEG.
STILL TONIGHT, DEFENSE
ATTORNEYS ARE
CROSS-EXAMINING THE MOTHER
AND RIGHT AWAY THEY ARE
TARGETING HER CREDIBILITY.
JOHN ROBERTS IS LIVE AT THE
COURTHOUSE IN MARIETTA,
GEORGIA FOR US THIS
EVENING.
JOHN?
>> BILL, GOOD EVENING TO
YOU.
THE DEFENSE IS TAKING AIM
AT EVERYTHING IT CAN AFTER
WEST'S DRAMATIC TESTIMONY
IN THE COURTROOM EARLIER
TODAY.
TRYING TO, AS IT WERE,
IMPEACH THE WITNESS,
CALLING IN TO QUESTION HER
RECOLLECTION OF THE
SHOOTING, QUESTIONING WHAT
THE DEFENSE CALLS BIZARRE
STATEMENTS SHE MADE TO THE
POLICE IN THE AFTERMATH.
EVEN SUGGESTING THAT SHE OR
THE CHILD'S FATHER, LUIS
SANTIAGO MAY HAVE HAD SOME
INVOLVEMENT IN THE CHILD'S
DEATH.
AT ONE POINT PUBLIC
DEFENDER KEVIN GOFF BROUGHT
UP WEST'S HISTORY OF MENTAL
ILLNESS.
>> ONE THE MENTAL ILLNESSES
FROM WHICH YOU SUFFER IS
WHAT'S KNOWN AS BIPOLAR
DISORDER OR MANIC
DEPRESSION?
>> BIPOLAR ANOTHER IS MOST
TRAUMATIC STRESS DISORDER.
>> YES.
>> ANOTHER IS BORDER LINE
TRAUMATIC DISORDER.
>> YES.
>> ANOTHER IS PARANOIA?
AS THE JURY WATCHED THAT
REENACTMENT.
ALSO QUESTIONED WHETHER SHE
HAD A FINANCIAL INTEREST
THE IN DEFENDANT HER BABY
BECAUSE SHE HAD TAKEN OUT A
$5,000 INSURANCE POLICY IN
HIS LIFE.
MOMENTS AGO IN THE
COURTROOM GUFF SUGGESTED
THAT WEST WAS SUCH A BAD
MOTHER THAT THE MURDER OF
HER CHILD MAY HAVE BEEN
QUOTE MERCIFUL.
THE DEFENSE IS WALKING A
VERY FINE LINE HERE BETWEEN
TOUGH CROSS-EXAMINATION OF
A MOTHER WHO HAD LOST HER
BABY IN A MURDER AND NOT
LOSING THE JURY ALL
TOGETHER.
BILL?
>> Bill: JOHN ROBERTS IN
MARIETTA.
JON, THE SAME JURY WILL
ALSO DECIDE THE GUILT OR
INNOCENCE OF THE TEENAGE
SUSPECT'S MOTHER.
PROSECUTORS SAY SHE HELPED
HER SON GET RID OF THE GUN
IN A NEARBY LAKE IN
GEORGIA.
WHEN THE FORT HOOD SHOOTER
CARRIED OUT HIS MASSACRE,
HE LEFT BODIES BEHIND AND
FAMILIES BROKEN FOREVER.
TODAY, WE HEARD HEART
BREAKING WORDS FROM SOME OF
THOSE WHO LOST LOVED ONES.
PLUS, THE CONVICTED KILLER
REFUSING TO FIGHT FOR HIS
OWN LIFE.
AHEAD, NIDAL HASAN'S
COMMENTS TODAY IN COURT.
ALSO, LATE TONIGHT, THE
WHITE HOUSE SAYS HELP IS ON
THE WAY FOR THIS AMERICAN,
A PRISONER IN NORTH
CAROLINA, ONLY WEEKS AFTER
HIS FAMILY WARNED HIS
FADING HEALTH MADE IT
URGENT TO GET HIM BACK
HOME.
TONIGHT, THE PLAN AIMED AT
SAVING HIS LIFE COMING UP
TONIGHT INSIDE "THE FOX
REPORT."
or more on car insurance.
Yep, everybody knows that.
Well, did you know some owls  AREN'T
that wise?
Don't forget I'm having  brunch with
Meghan tomorrow.
Who?
Meghan, my coworker.
Seriously? You've met her  like three
times.
Who?
(sighs)
GEICO.
Fifteen minutes could save    you...well,
you know.
We've completely  redone the house.
It's hard to find contractors  with
the passion and the skill
and that's why we  use Angie's List.
Online or on the phone, we help  you
hire right the first time
with honest reviews on  over 720 local
services.
I want it done right. I don't  want
to have to worry about it
or have to come back and redo  it.
With Angie's List, I was
able to turn my home into  the home
of my dreams.
For over 18 years, we've  helped people
take
care of the things  that matter most.
Join today.
THE Kyocera Torque  LETS YOU HEAR
AND BE HEARD  EVEN IN STUPID LOUD
PLACES.  TO PROVE IT, WE SET UP  OUR
CALL CENTER RIGHT HERE...  [ chirp
]  ALL GOOD?  [ chirp ]  GETTY UP.
CALL ME.  SERIOUSLY,  THIS IS REALLY
HAPPENING!  [ cellphone rings ]  HELLO?
IT'S A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.
[ Male Announcer ] GET IT DONE  [
chirp ]    WITH THE ULTRA-RUGGED
Kyocera Torque    ONLY FROM Sprint
Direct Connect.  TRBLE HEARING ON
THE PHONE?    BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE
FOR YOUR BUSINESS.  VISIT SPNTCAPTEL.COM
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR HELP  RELIEVING
HEARTBURN,  CAUSED BY ACID REFLUX
DISEASE,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES  24-HOUR
HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE  AVAILABLE  FOR JUST  $18
A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE  AND
LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL  PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH  CONDITIONS
MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF  YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT  HAND FOR JUST  $18 A
MONTH.
TALK TO  YOUR DOCTOR  ABOUT NEXIUM.
>> Bill: LATE WORD TONIGHT
THE UNITED STATES WILL SEND
A REPRESENTATIVE TO NORTH
CAROLINA THIS WEEK ASKING
ASKING -- NORTH KOREA
ASKING FOR RELEASE OF A
FRICHER THERE.
STATE ENVOY WILL REQUEST
RELEASE OF A CHRISTIAN
MISSIONARY SERVING A 15
YEAR SENTENCE OF HARD
LABOR.
HIS FAMILY RECENTLY SAID
THE NORTH KOREANS HAD
TRANSFERRED HIM FROM A
LABOR CAMP TO IT A HOSPITAL
THAT HE HAD LOST 50 POUNDS
AND THAT HIS HEALTH WAS
FAILING.
LAST YEAR NORTH KOREAN
OFFICIALS ACCUSED THE TOUR
GUIDE OF COMMITTING HOSTILE
ACTS AGAINST THAT COUNTRY.
WELL THIS WEEK'S VISIT WILL
BE THE FIRST TIME A SENIOR
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL HAS
TRAVELED TO NORTH KOREA NOW
IN TWO YEARS' TIME.
CLOSER TO HOME NOW, THE
CONVICTED FORT HOOD SHOOTER
IS TREATING HIS SENTENCING
JUST LIKE HIS TRIAL.
NIDAL HASAN BEGINS AND ENDS
HIS CASE WITH THE SAME
THREE WORDS THE DEFENSE
RESTS.
HE OFFERED NO TESTIMONY IN
HIS TRIAL DETERMINING
WHETHER HE LIVES OR DIES
FOR THE CRIME KILLING FROM
HIS POST IN 2009.
JURORS HEARD FROM VICTIMS'
FAMILY MEMBERS TODAY.
ONE WOMAN WHO LOST HER
HUSBAND SAID SHE CANNOT
BRING HERSELF TO MOVE ANY
OF HIS BELONGINGS EVENING
TO THIS DAY.
HIS MOTORCYCLE STILL IN THE
GARAGE.
HIS CLOTHES STILL HANGING
IN THE CLOSET.
ANOTHER WIDOW DESCRIBED HER
RELIEF WHEN AN ARMY
OFFICIAL TOLD HER THAT ALL
THE VICTIMS' FAMILIES HAD
ALREADY BEEN NOTIFIED.
SHE TESTIFIED TODAY IN A
STRANGE SENSE OF IRONY THAT
SHE THOUGHT HER HUSBAND WAS
STILL UNACCOUNTED FOR AND
JOKED TO HERSELF I'M GOING
TO KILL HIM BUT THAT ARMY
OFFICIAL TURNED OUT TO BE
WRONG, HER HUSBAND WAS
ALREADY DEAD.
CASEY STEGALL HAS THE NEWS
LIVE AT FORT HOOD TONIGHT
WITH US.
CASEY?
>> YEAH, BILL.
>> AMONG THOSE WE HEARD
FROM TODAY THREE WIDOWS
AND THREE MOTHERS WHO TRIED
EXPLAINING WHAT LIFE HAS
BEEN LIKE SINCE THEIR
HUSBANDS OR THEIR CHILDREN
WERE KILLED.
EXTREMELY EMOTIONAL, MANY
OF THEM REACHING FOR
TISSUES WHILE ON THE STAND.
IT'S LIKE TINA, HER SON
PRIVATE FIRST CLASS AARON
WAS JUST 19 YEARS OLD WHEN
HASAN GUNNED HIM DOWN.
SHE TEARFULLY RECALLED THE
MOMENT OFFICERS ARRIVED AT
HER HOME TO MAKE THE
NOTIFICATION.
SHE SAID FROM THE STAND AND
I'M QUOTING HERE:  YOU JUST
FREEZE.
YOU CAN'T OPEN THAT DOOR.
YOU DON'T WANT THE NEWS
THAT YOU HAVE LOST YOUR
SON.
IT IS THE WORST NEWS YOU
COULD EVER HEAR.
NOW, FIRST THING TOMORROW
MORNING, THE PANEL WILL
BEGIN SENTENCING
INSTRUCTIONS.
THEN THE PROSECUTION WILL
GIVE CLOSING ARGUMENTS, AND
FINALLY MAJOR HASAN WILL
HAVE ONE MORE CHANCE TO
SPEAK.
THE PROSECUTION HAS A
CHANCE TO GIVE A REBUTTAL
AND THEN THE PANEL GETS
THIS CASE ONCE AGAIN,
DELIBERATIONS BEGIN.
ALL 13 OF THOSE SENIOR ARMY
OFFICERS MUST BE UNANIMOUS
IF THEY WANT' TO GIVE THE
42-YEAR-OLD ARMY
PSYCHIATRIST THE DEATH
PENALTY, BILL.
>> Bill: WHAT A ROAD THIS
HAS BEEN FOR ALL OF THEM.
CASEY, THANK YOU.
CASEY STEGALL THERE.
EVEN IF MAKE HASAN GETS THE
DEATH PENALTY, IT WILL BE
FAR FROM A DONE DEAL IT
WOULD LIKELY MEAN YEARS OF
APPEALS.
IN THE PAST 30 YEARS
MILITARY APPEALS COURTS
HAVE OVERTURNED SOME TWO
THIRDS OF ALL DEATH
SENTENCES.
AND THE MILITARY HAS NOT
EXECUTED ANYONE IN MORE
THAN 50 YEARS.
THREE MILLION DOLLARS' BAIL
FOR A TEENAGER ACCUSED OF
KILLING AN AMERICAN WAR
HERO.
A JUDGE MADE IS THAT RULING
FOR THE 16-YEAR-OLD ACCUSED
KILLER DURING HIS FIRST
COURT APPEARANCE TODAY IN
THE STATE OF WASHINGTON.
ANOTHER 16-YEAR-OLD IS
BEHIND BARS ON $2 MILLION
BAIL.
PROSECUTORS WILL TRY BOTH
TEENS AS ADULTS FOR FIRST
DEGREE MURDER AND ROBBERY.
THEY SAY THE TEENS RANDOMLY
TARGETED THEN KILLED THIS
88-YEAR-OLD VETERAN OF
WORLD WAR II.
THE VICTIM HAD SURVIVED A
SHOT TO THE LEG IN OKINAWA.
ONE OF THE BLOODIEST
BATTLES OF THE SECOND WORLD
WAR.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN LOOKING
FOR HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS
OF DOLLARS FROM THE STATE
OF FLORIDA TONIGHT.
AHEAD WHY THE MAN CLEARED
IN THE DEATH OF TRAYVON
MARTIN COULD BE GETTING A
BIG CHUNK OF CHANGE.
PLUS, THE LITTLE GIRL WHO
TWICE SURVIVED DOUBLE LUNG
TRANSPLANTS FINALLY GOES
HOME FROM THE HOSPITAL.
YOU WILL HEAR FROM YOUNG
SARAH HERSELF COMING UP
TONIGHT INSIDE "THE FOX
REPORT."
[ Male Announcer ]    THESE DAYS,
A SMALL BUSINESS    CAN SAVE BY SHARING.
LIKE CARPOOLS...  POLLY WANTS TO KNOW
IF WE CAN PICK HER UP.  YEAH  WE CAN
MAKE ROOM.  YEAH.    [ Male Announcer
]    ...OFFICE SPACE.  YES, WE'RE
LOVING THIS  COMMUNAL SEATING. IT'S
GREAT.    [ Male Announcer ]    THE
BEST THING TO SHARE?    A DATA PLAN.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
ONE BUCKET OF DATA    FOR EVERYONE
ON THE PLAN    UNLIMITED TALK AND
TEXT    ON SMART PHONES.    NOW, EVERYONE'S
IN THE SPIRIT    OF SHARING.  HEY,
CAN I BORROW YOUR BOAT  THIS WEEKEND?
NO.    [ Male Announcer ]    SHARE
MORE. SAVE MORE.    AT&T MOBILE SHARE
FOR BUSINESS.  ♪ ♪
[ Male Announcer ]    RUNNING OUT
OF STEAM?  ♪ ♪    NOW YOU CAN GIVE
YOURSELF    A KICK IN THE REAR!
V8 V-FUSION PLUS ENERGY.    NATURAL
ENERGY FROM GREEN TEA    PLUS FRUITS
AND VEGGIES.    NEED A LITTLE KICK?
OOH!    COULD'VE HAD A V8.    IN THE
JUICE AISLE.
THE BOYS USED DOUBLE MILES FROM  THEIR
CAPITAL ONE VENTURE CARD  TO FLY HOME
FOR THE BIG FAMILY REUNION.  YOU MUST
BE  GARTH'S FATHER?  HELLO.  MOTHER.
MOTHER!  TRAVELING IS EASY  WITH THE
VENTURE CARD  BECAUSE YOU CAN FLY
ANY AIRLINE ANYTIME.  TWO WORDS.
DOUBLE MILES!  THIS GUY CAN ACT.
WANNA PLAY DODGE ROCK?  OH, YOU GUYS!
AND WITH DOUBLE MILES  YOU CAN ACTUAY
USE,  YOU NEVER MISS THE FUN.  BEARD
GROWING CONTEST AND GO!  ♪ ♪   WIN!
WHAT'S IN YOUR WALLET?
Alert.  The beach on your TV is much
closer than it appears.
Dive into Labor Day with up  to 50%
off hotels
at Travelocity.
>> Bill: QUICK NOTE HERE.
EARLIER WE SHOWED YOU
IMAGES OF AN AMERICAN
MISSIONARY HELD IN NORTH
KOREA, KENNETH BEA.
ONE OF THOSE IMAGES YOU SAW
WAS THE WRONG MAN.
THIS IS A CORRECT PHOTO OF
THE MISSIONARY KENNETH BAE.
NOW THEY ARE HOPEFULLY
COMING HOME SOON.
WE ALL DO.
TAXPAYERS COULD SOON BE ON
THE HOOK FOR A BIG CHUNK OF
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN'S COURT
BILLS.
ACCORDING TO THE OFFICE OF
MARK O'MARA IN FLORIDA THE
CLIENT PLANS TO ASK THE
STATE OF FLORIDA TO COVER
UP TO $300,000 IN LEGAL
BILLS.
THAT WOULD INCLUDE THE COST
OF EXPERT WITNESSES AND
TRAVEL AND A LOT MORE
DURING THAT CASE.
BUT THE ATTORNEY'S OFFICE
REPORTS ZIMMERMAN IS NOT
ASKING THE STATE TO PAY FOR
OWE MAYOR WRAPS SPECIFIC
FEES.
LAST MONTH A JURY CLEARED
ZIMMERMAN IN THE SHOOTING
DEATH OF TRAYVON MARTIN.
FLORIDA LOU ALLOWS A
DEFENDANT TO GET REIMBURSED
FOR CERTAIN LEGAL BILLS IN
THE EVENT OF AN ACQUITTAL
WHICH ZIMMERMAN WAS
GRANTED.
A YOUNG GIRL WHO DOCTORS
SAID WOULD DIE IN A
HOSPITAL IS FINALLY BACK
HOME TONIGHT.
BALLOONS AND BANNERS
GREETING 10-YEAR-OLD SARA
MURNAGHAN HAS SHE ARRIVED
HOME FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
SINGS MONTHS.
SHE SURVIVED NOT ONE BUT
TWO DOUBLE LUNG
TRANSPLANTS.
OPERATIONS THAT SPARKED A
NATIONAL DEBATE ON HOW
TRANSPLANTS ARE
PRIORITIZED.
DOCTORS SAYING THAT SARA
HAD NO CHANCE WITHOUT NEW
LUNGS.
SHE WAS NOT OLD ENOUGH TO
GET ON THE ADULT DONOR
WAITING LIST WHERE THERE
ARE FAR MORE DONATED LUNGS
THAN ON THE PEED AT TRICK
WAITING LIST.
THE PARENTS SUED.
THE FIRST TRANSPLANT
FAILED.
THE SECOND ONE SEEMS TO
HAVE WORKED SO FAR.
TODAY SARAH'S PARENTS
UPDATED REPORTERS OUT OF
THEIR HOME IN PENNSYLVANIA.
>> SARAH IS LOOKING FORWARD
TO BEING A REGULAR LITTLE
KID.
TO GOING OUTSIDE AND
PLAYING WITH HER FRIENDS.
SHE WOULD LIKE TO BE ON THE
SOCCER TEAM.
SHE USED TO HORSEBACK RIDE
AND ICE SKATE.
SHE IS LOOKING FORWARD TO
DOING THOSE THINGS AGAIN.
>> SO DEWE.
SARAH STILL NEEDS A MACHINE
TO HELP HER NEW LUNGS
BREATHE.
SARAH HAS STARTED WALKING
AGAIN WITH THE HELP OF A
WALKER.
AT ONE POINT EVEN VENTURING
OUTSIDE TO FEEL THE WARM
AIR IN AUGUST.
TRACE GALLAGHER IS LIVE
WITH AN UPDATE NOW.
WHAT AN AMAZING COME BACK
STORY THIS HAS BEEN FOR
HER, TRACE.
GOOD EVENING.
>> YOU SAID IT BILL.
GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
CONSIDER THAT HER PARENTS
WERE ACTUALLY GOING TO
COURT FIGHTING TO GET HER
ON THE ADULT TRANSPLANT
LIST, I MEAN SARAH WAS
VERY CLOSE TO DEATH.
SHE WAS ON A BREATHING
TUBE.
SHE WAS HEAVILY SEDATED.
LUNG TRANSPLANT PATIENTS
ARE GRADED BY THIS LUNG
ALLOCATION SCORE GOES FROM
0 TO 100.
ANYTHING ABOVE 50 IS
CONSIDERED DIRE.
AT THE TIME SARAH'S SCORE
91.
AND NOW SHE IS ANSWERING
QUESTIONS.
LISTEN.
>> HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE
HOME?
>> GREAT.
>> YEAH?
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT WAS THE RIDE IN THE
AMBULANCE LIKE?
>> PRETTY FUN.
>> PRETTY FUN?
WERE YOU NERVOUS AT FIRST?
>> YEAH.
>> AND THEN IT GOT KIND OF
COOL?
>> YEAH.
>> YOU CAN SEE SHE IS ON
THE TRACHEOTOMY, STILL VERY
WEAK LUNGS.
THE FIRST THING SHE ASKED
HER SISTER FOR, BILL WAS A
DOLL SO THAT HE SHOOKD
START PLAYING AGAIN.
>> Bill: AMAZE SHE GO
SLEEPING AT HOME TONIGHT.
SHE STILL HAS A LONG WAY TO
GO THOUGH, RIGHT TRACE?
>> YEAH YEARS OF REHAB.
SHE WILL BE IN DOCTORS'
CHECKUP EVERY WEEK FOR THE
FORESEEABLE FUTURE.
SHE WILL BE ON MEDICATION
FOR THE REST OF HER LIFE TO
MAKE SURE HER BODY DOES NOT
REJECT THE LUNGS.
YOU HEARD HER MOM EARLIER
SAY SHE USED TO HORSEBACK
RIDE AND ICE SKATE.
NOW SHE IS USING A WAKE.
SHE CLEAR SOLID A FIGHTER.
NEXT WEEK SHE STARTS HOME
SCHOOL AND HER FAMILY IS NO
LONGER THINKING ABOUT HER
DAY-TO-DAY.
LISTEN.
>> WE'RE LOOKING FORWARD TO
SARAH HAVING A NICE LONG
LIFE GOING TO COLLEGE,
GETTING MARRIED, HAVING A
FAMILY AND DOING EVERYTHING
THAT WE DREAM FOR OUR OTHER
KIDS.
>> AND BY THE WAY THE
PARENTS SAY THEY WILL
CONTINUE TO FIGHT TO GET
OTHER KIDS PLACED ON THAT
ADULT LUNG TRANSPLANT LIST.
>> THEY HAVE A LOT OF CALLS
FOR THAT.
TRACE GALLAGHER, THANK YOU.
TRACE GALLAGHER IN THE WEST
COAST BUREAU THERE AS A
RESULT OF TEMPORARY RULE
CHANGE THAT GAVE SARAH NEW
LUNGS THE FAMILIES OF SIX
OTHER CHILDREN HAVE APPLIED
FOR ADULT LUNG TRANSPLANTS
AS OF NOW.
THE WHITE HOUSE CLAIMS THE
U.S. WILL RESPOND TO THAT
DEADLY CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACK IN SYRIA.
BUT, SOME REPUBLICAN
LEADERS ARE WEIGHING IN ON
WHAT TYPE OF RESPONSE THAT
SHOULD BE.
PLUS THAT ENORMOUS
WILDFIRE BURNING IN AROUND
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK IT
IS STILL GOING AGAIN
TONIGHT.
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR HOW
LONG IT MAY TAKE TO FINALLY
PUT THIS ONE OUT.
IN A DRAMATIC COURTROOM
OUTBURST CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
DID YOU SEE THIS?
WHY A MAN APPARENTLY TRIED
TO GET HIS OWN HANDS ON AN
ACCUSED KILLER.
YOU WILL HEAR HIS STORY
COMING UP.
INSIDE "THE FOX REPORT" AT
THE BOTTOM OF THE HOUR.
D TO DESCRIBE,  BECAUSE YOU HAVE A
NUMBNESS,  BUT YET YOU HAVE THE PAIN
LIKE THOUSANDS OF NEEDLES  STICKING
IN YOUR FOOT.  IT WAS PROGRESSIVELY
GETTING WORSE,  AND AT THAT POINT
I KNEW I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.  ONCE
I STARTED TAKING THE LYRICA  THE PAIN
STARTED SUBSIDING.    [ Male Announcer
] IT'S KNOWN    THAT DIABETES DAMAGES
NERVES.    LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.    LYRICA
IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.    IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS    OR SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS    OR ACTIONS.    TELL YOUR
DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY    IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,    OR
UNUSUAL CHANGES    IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,    CHANGES
IN EYESIGHT    INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,    TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.    COMMON
SIDE EFFECTS ARE    DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN AND SWELLING    OF HANDS,
LEGS AND FEET.    DON'DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.    DON'T DRIVE
OR USE MACHINERY    UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.    THOSE WHO
HAVE HAD A DRUG    OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY    TO MISUSE LYRICA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR    ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT    FOR DIABETIC
NERVE PAIN.
Peace of mind is important when  you're
running a successful  business.  So
we provide IT services you  can rely
on.  With CenturyLink as your trusted
IT partner  you'll experience reliable
uptime for the network and  services
you depend on.  Multi-layered security
solutions  keep your information safe,
and  secure.  And responsive dedicated
support  meets your needs, and eases
your  mind.  CenturyLink.  Your link
to what's next.
♪  (Announcer) Bring the adventure
to their bowl with a
whole world of exciting  flavs.
Friskies. Feed the senses.
HEY, IT'S ME  PROGRESSIVE INSURANCE.
YOU KNOW, FROM OUR 4,000  TELEVISION
COMMERCIALS.
YEP, THERE I AM WITH FLO.
HOO-HOO! WATCH IT!
[Chuckles] ANYHOO, 3 MILLION  PEOPLE
SWITCHED TO ME LAST YEAR,
SAVING AN AVERAGE  OF $475.
[Sigh] IT FEELS GOOD  TO HELP PEOPLE
SAVE...
WITH GREAT DISCOUNTS LIKE  SAFE DRIVER,
MULTICAR,
AND MULTIPOLICY.
SO CALL ME TODAY.  YOU'LL BE GLAD
YOU DID.
CANNONBOX!
[SPLASH!]
A HOT SMELLY CAR VERSUS    A FEBREZE
CAR VENT CLIP.
WHICH COMES OUT ON TOP?    WE BROUGHT
REAL PEOPLE TO    THE TEXAS DESERT
TO FIND OUT.  IT'S JUST NICE.  VERY
CRISP.  COOL AND FRESH.  THAT'S WHAT
I WAS THINKING!  FRESH.  THAT'S EXACTLY
WHAT I WAS THINKING. YEAH.  FRESH.
FRESH.  LIKE I COULD DEFINITELY  WRAP
MYSELF IN IT.    ODORS ARE NO MATCH
FOR THE FEBREZE CAR VENT CLIP.
ANOTHER WAY FEBREZE    HELPS YOU BREATHE
HAPPY.
POLICE ARRESTED THE BROTHER
OF A MURDER VICTIM AFTER HE
TRIED TO BULL RUSSIA
SUSPECTED KILLER INSIDE OF
A COURTROOM.
WATCH HERE.
[SHOUTING]
>> Bill: THAT GUY RAN
TOWARD THE PRISONER BOXES
AS PROSECUTORS READ OUT THE
DETAILS OF THE APPARENT
HOMICIDE NEAR BOSTON.
THE SUSPECT ON SATURDAY
STABBED THE VICTIM ALMOST
70 TIMES AT A TRAILER PARK.
AUTHORITIES FOUND THE
SUSPECT' AT A NEARBY TRAIN
STATION WITH BLOODY CLOTHES
AND A CUT ON HIS HAND.
SOON AFTER THEY DISCOVERED
THE VICTIM INSIDE OF A
BLOOD SPATTERED MOBILE
HOME.
HIS BROTHER FACES CHARGES
OF DISRUPTING COURT
PROCEEDINGS AND RESISTING
ARREST.
I'M BILL HEMMER IN TONIGHT
FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS "THE FOX REPORT."
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT'S
PREPOSTEROUS TO SUGGEST
THAT SYRIA WAS NOT BEHIND
LAST WEEK'S CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK.
THAT REPORTEDLY KILLED
HUNDREDS THERE.
NOW THE ADMINISTRATION SAYS
THERE IS NO DOUBT THE U.S.
WILL RESPOND.
THE ONLY QUESTION IS WHEN
AND HOW THE U.S. HAS
FOUR WARSHIPS OFF THE COAST
OF MILITARY.
THE MILITARY IS READY TO
STRIKE WHENEVER PRESIDENT
OBAMA GIVES THAT ORDER.
BUT DEFENSE SECRETARY CHUCK
HAGEL STRESSING THE U.S.
WILL COORDINATE ANY ACTION
WITH OUR INTERNATIONAL
PARTNERS.
ED HENRY LIVE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE TONIGHT.
ED, GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
WOULD THE THE
ADMINISTRATION GET
CONGRESSIONAL AUTHORITY OR
IS THIS A DECISION THE
PRESIDENT WILL MAKE ON HIS
OWN.
>> GOOD EVENING, BILL.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE PRESIDENT
IS GOING TO OPERATE
UNILATERALLY WITHOUT
CONGRESS.
INTERESTING BECAUSE VICE
PRESIDENT JOE BIDEN TODAY
ADDED HIS NAME TO THE
COURSE OF TOP OFFICIALS
HERE AT THE WHITE HOUSE
SAYING THAT ASSAD AND SYRIA
NEEDS TO BE HELD
ACCOUNTABLE.
THAT HE DID, IN FACT, USE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
BUT SOME DEMOCRATS ON
CAPITOL HILL LIKE
CONGRESSWOMAN BARBARA LEE,
THE ONLY MEMBER OF CONGRESS
TO VOTE AGAINST THE WAR IN
AFGHANISTAN DEMANDING A
DEBATE AND VOTE IN
CONGRESS.
OFFICIALS HERE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE TELLING ME THAT IS
UNLIKELY TO HAPPEN BEFORE
THE PRESIDENT MAKES HIS
DECISION ON WHETHER TO MOVE
FORWARD ON U.S. MILITARY
ACTION.
EVEN THOUGH IN THE 2008
CAMPAIGN, HE SLAMMED THE
BUSH ADMINISTRATION FOR
ACTING UNILATERALLY, TAKE A
LISTEN TO HOW I PRESSED JAY
CARNEY ABOUT THIS AND
LISTEN TO THE VICE
PRESIDENT AS WELL.
>> 2007, CANDIDATE OBAMA
WAS AN ACTUAL OR IMMINENT
THREAT TO THE NATION.
DO YOU BELIEVE THAT EXISTS
RIGHT NOW AN ACTUAL OR
IMMINENT THREAT TO THE
UNITED STATES?
>> I BELIEVE THAT
ABSOLUTELY ALLOWING THE USE
OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON A
SIGNIFICANT STALE TO TAKE
PLACE WITHOUT A RESPONSE
WOULD PRESENT A SIGNIFICANT
THREAT TO UNITED STATES
NATIONAL SECURITY INTEREST.
>> NATIONAL SECURITY IS
STRENGTHENED WHEN WE HOLD
ACCOUNTABLE THOSE WHO
VIOLATE INTERNATIONAL
NORMS.
>> NOW THE WOWS JUST
REVEALED IN THE LAST FEW
MOMENTS AND THE PRESIDENT
JUST GOT OFF THE PHONE WITH
THE BRITISH PRIME MINISTER
DAVID CAMMERON.
WHAT'S SIGNIFICANT ABOUT
THAT SECOND TIMED THEY HAVE
SPOKEN JUST IN THE LAST FEW
DAYS.
CONSULTING WITH ALLIES LIKE
THAT SUGGEST WE ARE EDGING
CLOSER TO U.S. MILITARY
ACTION.
BILL?
>> Bill: WE ARE HEARING
FROM MANY PRODUCTION AT
LEAST SOME OF THEM ANY WAY
SUGGESTING THERE SHOULD NOT
BE SOME SORT OF SYMBOLIC
HIT OR ATTACK, ED?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
REPUBLICANS LIKE JOHN
MCCAIN SAYING TONIGHT LOOK,
IF THERE IS GOING TO BE
MILITARY ACTION, FINE.
BUT THE PRESIDENT NEEDS TO
EXPLAIN THE MISSION TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE AND MCCAIN
SAYING TONIGHT HE CAN'T
JUST BE SOME SYMBOLIC MOVE
TO BACK UP THE PRESIDENT'S
RHETORIC FROM LAST SUMMER
ABOUT A RED LINE ON
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
MCCAIN SAYING IT'S GOT TO
BE A SERIOUS MILITARY
ACTION THAT ACTUALLY
DEGRADES ASSAD'S FORCES.
TAKE LAFN.
>> IF IT'S SIMPLY THAT WE
LAUNCH SOME CREWS MISSILES
AND DO THAT FOR THREE DAYS
AND NOT HAVE SIGNIFICANT
EFFECT ON THE MOMENTUM ON
THE BATTLEFIELD IT WILL
HAVE AN UNHELPFUL EFFECT.
IF WE DO IT RIGHT.
AND WE GET THE MOMENTUM
BACK ON SHIFTED TO OUR
FREEDOM FIGHTERS --
>> NOW, THE NEXT STEP IN
THE CASE FOR MILITARY
ACTION WE'RE EXPECTING THE
WHITE HOUSE AS EARLY AS
TOMORROW TO DECLASSIFY SOME
INTELLIGENCE THAT THEY SAY
WILL SHOW THAT ASSAD DID
USE CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
THAT WILL MOVE THEM ONE
STEP CLOSER TO ACTUAL
MILITARY ACTION,  (A  8GBm&n;<@&E}lK
Z5R$  (PR&L.
>> Bill: A LOT MORE COMING
UP CLEARLY ON THIS
TOMORROW.
ED HENRY THANKS FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE ON THE FRONT
LAWN TONIGHT.
WILDFIRE ALERT NOW.
NEARLY 4,000 FIREFIGHTERS
FROM AROUND THE COUNTRY ARE
FIGHTING A MASSIVE BLAZE IN
CALIFORNIA.
SO FAR THE RIM FIRE HAS
SPREAD TO COVER AN AREA OF
SOME 200 AND 80 SQUARE
MILES.
IT'S THE STATE'S SEVENTH
LARGEST FIRE ON RECORD.
AND IT CONTINUES TO
THREATEN MORE OF THE
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
AS OF THE LAST COUNT, THE
WILDFIRE WAS ABOUT 20%
CONTAINED.
THAT WAS IT.
THIS THING HAS BEEN BURNING
FOR DAYS.
AS WE REPORTED YESTERDAY,
IT'S NOT ONLY THREATENING
POWER AND GAS LINES, BUT
THE WATER SUPPLY FOR
MILLIONS IN THE NEAR SAN
FRANCISCO BAY AREA.
CLAUDIA COWAN IS LIVE NEAR
THE EDGE OF THAT FIRE FOR
US THIS EVENING.
CLAUDIA?
>> BILL, WE ARE UNDER AN
EVACUATION ADVISORY FOR A
SIXTH STRAIGHT DAY.
FIRE CREWS ARE MAKING
PROGRESS BUT SAY STRONG
WIND GUSTS ESPECIALLY IN
THOSE CANYONS ARE MAKING IT
VERY TOUGH GOING.
OUR CAMERAS WERE ON A MEDIA
TOUR THIS AFTERNOON AND
HAPPENED TO SEE THIS GROVE
OF PONDEROSA PINES EXPLODE
INTO FLAMES.
HOT SPOTS LIKE THIS
CONTINUE TO HAMPER
CONTAINMENT EFFORTS AND
STRUCTURE PROTECTION.
31 HOMES AND 80
OUTBUILDINGS LOST SO FAR.
BUT, IRONICALLY, BECAUSE OF
THIS FIRE'S ERRATIC
MOVEMENT, THIS MAY BE THE
BEST TIME TO VISIT
YOSEMITE.
>> YOU GO INTO THE PARK AND
YOSEMITE VALLEY AND IT'S
HARD TO TELL THAT THERE IS
A FIRE JUST 20 MILES AWAY
BECAUSE THE SMOKE IS
FLOWING AWAY FROM THE
VALLEY AND FRASIER POINT.
THE VIEWS ARE ALL STILL AS
BEAUTIFUL AS THEY ALWAYS
ARE.
>> UNFORTUNATELY, A LOT OF
THAT SMOKE IS BLOWING RIGHT
INTO ARENA, NEVADA WHERE
THE AIR QUALITY IS NOW
LISTED AS UNHEALTHY FOR
EVERYONE.
FIRE CREWS HERE SAY THEY
HOPE COOLER TEMPERATURES
AND HIGHER HUMIDITY OVER
THE NEXT COUPLE OF DAY ALSO
HELP THEM GET THE UPPER
HAND.
BILL, THEY SAY IT COULD BE
MONTHS, WELL INTO WINTER
BEFORE THIS MASSIVE
WILDFIRE IS COMPLETELY OUT.
>> WOW THAT'S AMAZING.
STILL DON'T KNOW THE CAUSE
EITHER.
CLAUDIA COWAN NORTHERN
CALIFORNIA FOR US TONIGHT.
THERE IS GOOD NEWS IF YOU
ARE LOOKING TO SELL YOUR
HOME NOW.
A NEW REPORT FINDS THAT
HOME PRICES ACROSS THE
COUNTRY ROSE AN AVERAGE OF
12% IN JUNE COMPARED TO
JUNE OF LAST YEAR.
THAT ACCORDING TO THE S&P
CASE SCHILLER HOME PRICE
INDEX.
IT FOUND THAT MORE
AMERICANS WERE ENCOURAGED
TO BUY HOMES.
THANKS MOSTLY TO STEADY JOB
GAINS AND LOW MORTGAGE
RATES.
BUT ANALYSTS SAY HIGHER
MORTGAGE RATES COULD SOON
WEIGH ON THE HOUSING
RECOVERY.
FROM THE FOX BUSINESS
NETWORK RICH EDISON JOINS
US LIVE TONIGHT WITH THE
NEWS ON THAT TODAY IN
WASHINGTON.
RICH, GOOD EVENING.
>> GOOD EVENING, BILL.
THE HOUSING MARKET
CONTINUES TO IMPROVE.
THOUGH AT A SLOWER PACE.
THERE ARE 20 CITIES IN THIS
SURVEY.
HOME PRICES IN 13 OF THEM
ROSE FASTER IN MAY THAN
THEY DID IN JUNE.
ONE ANALYST SAYS THE
HOUSING MARKET EARLIER THIS
YEAR WAS JUST GETTING TOO
HOT.
>> IT WAS ACCELERATING TOO
QUICKLY AND NOW IT'S
ACCELERATING LESS QUICKLY.
I THINK THAT'S THE RIGHT
WAY TO LOOK AT THE DATA
WHEN YOU BOIL IT ALL DOWN.
>> THIS REPORT SAYS OVER
THE PAST YEAR, THE LARGEST
GAINS IN HOME PRICES ARE IN
CITIES THE HOUSING
RECESSION HIT HARDEST.
HOME VALUES IN LAS VEGAS
IN SAN FRANCISCO ARE UP
NEARLY A QUARTER.
PRICES IN LOS ANGELES,
PHOENIX, AND SAN DIEGO HAVE
INCREASED NEARLY 20% OVER
THE PAST YEAR.
THOUGH THE IMPROVING
HOUSING MARKET HAS
SIGNIFICANT CHALLENGES,
MORTGAGE RATES HAVE SPIKED.
SIX MONTHS AGO A HOME BUYER
COULD LOCK IN A 30 YEARS
FIXED RATE FOR LESS THAN
3.75%.
NOW IT'S MORE THAN 4.5%.
ALSO A RECENT MEASURE OF
NEW HOME SALES RECENTLY
COME IN WELL BELOW
EXPECTATIONS.
BILL?
>> Bill: RICH EDSON ON THAT
STORY FOR US IN WASHINGTON.
SELLING TEA TO REPRESENT
RESCUE GIRLS FROM SEX
TRAFFICKING.
THIS IS AMAZING BUSINESS
WHICH WE FIRST TALKED ABOUT
ABOUT A MONTH AGO.
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR HOW
MUCH BUSINESS IS BOOMING
SINCE OUR REPORT THEN.
PLUS, THERE IS WORD OF A
SAND SHORTAGE AT BEACHES IN
ONE STATE.
OFFICIALS HAVE COME UP WITH
A RATHER STRANGE SOLUTION.
HOW ABOUT BROKEN GLASS?
WE WILL SHOW YOU WHERE AND
HOW THIS MIGHT WORK.
WHEN WE MADE OUR COMMITMENT TO  THE
GULF, BP HAD TWO BIG GOALS:  HELP
THE GULF  RECOVER AND LEARN  FROM
WHAT HAPPENED
SO WE COULD BE  A BETTER, SAFER  ENERGY
COMPANY.
I CAN TELL YOU - SAFETY IS AT  THE
HEART OF EVERYTHING WE DO.
WE'VE ADDED CUTTING-EDGE  TECHNOLOGY
LIKE A NEW DEEPWATER WELL CAP
AND A STATE-OF-THE-ART  MONITORING
CENTER, WHE EXPERTS
WATCH OVER ALL DRILLING  ACTIVITY
TWENTY-FOUR-SEVEN.
AND WE'RE SHARING  WHAT WE'VE LEARNED
SO WE CAN ALL PRODUCE  ENERGY MORE
SAFELY.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS  NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
♪ ♪    [ Male Announcer ] MAY YOUR
LIGHTS ALWAYS BE GREEN.
[ TIRES SCREECH ]
♪ ♪
AND YOUR FAVORITE SONGS    ALWAYS
PLAYING.
[ BEEPING ]
♪ ♪
MAY YOU NEVER BE STUCK    BEHIND A
STINKY TRUCK.
[ BEEPING ]
♪ ♪
MAY THINGS    ALWAYS GO YOUR WAY.
BUT IT'S GOOD TO BE PREPARED...
JUST IN CASE THEY DON'T.
LET'S GO PLACES, SAFELY.
[ HUMAN LEAGUE PLAYS  "I'M ONLY HUMAN"
]
HUMANS.
EVEN WHEN WE CROSS OUR t's    AND
DOT OUR i's,
WE STILL RUN INTO PROBLEMS.
NAMELY, OTHER HUMANS.
WHICH IS WHY    AT LIBERTY MUTUAL
INSURANCE,
TO POLICIES COME    WITH NEW CAR REPLACEMENT
AND ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS    IF YOU
QUALIFY.
SEE WHAT EE COMES STANDARD
AT LIBERTYMUTUAL.COM.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT'S YOUR POLICY?
BILL BUILT A SMALL BUSINESS
OWNER IN ATLANTA HAS BEEN
SELLING TEA TO RESCUE GIRLS
FROM SEX TRAFFICKING IN THE
COUNTRY OF INDIA.
IT'S A STORY WE FIRST
REPORTED BACK IN JULY.
IT GENERATED ENORMOUS
INTEREST.
IN FACT, THE BUSINESS OWNER
SAYS SHE SOLD MORE TEA IN
THE FOUR DAYS AFTER OUR
REPORT THAN SHE DID IN THE
PREVIOUS FOUR YEARS
IMINGETED JONATHAN SERRIE
IS LIVE ON THIS STORY FOR
US TONIGHT.
JONATHAN.
>> IT'S A GREAT ONGOING
STORY.
THE OWNER OF THAT TEA SHOP
HAS RECEIVED OUTPOURING OF
SUPPORT SINCE WE REPORTED
ON HER EFFORTS BACK IN
JULY.
ORDERS ARE UP FOR THE TEA
THAT SHE SELLS FOR SAFE
HOUSING FOR ORGANS A REGION
WHERE POVERTY AND SEX
TRAFFICKING ARE GRIM
REALITIES, LISTEN.
I THINK I RECEIVED AROUND
600 EMAILS BEEN THE FIRST
HOUR THAT TALK PEACE.
I WAS UNPREPARED FOR IT WE
SOLD MORE TEA IN THE FIRST
FOUR FOUR DAYS THAN FOUR
YEARS.
>> CHRISTIE SAYS SHE HAS
BEEN CONTACTED BY OTHERS
WHO WANT TO BUILD CENTERS.
A NEARBY INDIAN RESTAURANT
AS OFFERED TO SELL HER TEA
AND THEN SOME.
LISTEN.
WE WANT TO SPONSOR AN
EMPLOYEE TO GO AND HELP IN
HER ORGANIZATION.
SHE IS LOOKING FOR HANDS ON
HELP THERE.
>> AND FOR MORE ON CAN A
TREMENDOUSLY'S EFFORTS, CAN
YOU VISIT HER WEB SITE AT
THE LEARNING TEA.COM.
BILL?
>> Bill: THAT IS GREAT
NEWS.
NICE TO HEAR.
JONATHAN IN ATLANTA THERE
CAN A TREMENDOUSLY ALSO
TELLING FOX NEWS THAT ONE
OF THE GIRLS SHE HAS BEEN
HELPING OUT JUST GOT
ACCEPTED TO A PRESTIGIOUS
INDIAN UNIVERSITY.
SHE HAS BEEN SUPPORTING 11
GIRLS FOR FOUR YEARS.
EXPECTS THAT NUMBER TO
INCREASE DRAMATICALLY WITH
ALL THE NEW OFFERS OF HELP.
WE WISH HER THE ABSOLUTE
BEST.
AT LEAST SIX ARE DEAD.
19 OTHERS INJURED AFTER A
BUILDING COLLAPSES.
OUR TOP STORY AS WE GO
AROUND THE WORLD TONIGHT IN
80 SECONDS.
BRAZIL, 40S SAY THE
STRUCTURE HAD BEEN UNDER
CONSTRUCTION WHEN IT
TOPPLED TO THE GROUND IN
SOUTH PAL LOW.
RESCUERS COMBED THROUGH THE
RUBBLE AND PULLED OUT
SEVERAL SURVIVORS.
NO WORD ON WHAT MAY HAVE
CAUSED THE BUILDING TO FALL
SPAIN.
CREWS BATTLED A MASSIVE
WILDFIRE THAT'S ALREADY
CHARRED SOME 2400 ACRES IN
THE NORTHWEST.
ABOUT AN HOUR FROM THE
PORTUGAL BORDER.
FIRE OFFICIALS SAY THE
FLAMES BROKE OUT YESTERDAY
AMID HOT WEATHER AND HEAVY
WINDS.
THE GOVERNMENT HAS ISSUED
ITS HIGHEST LEVEL
EVACUATION ALERT SINCE THE
FLAMES COULD SPREAD TO
HEAVILY POPULATED AREA.
RUSSIA.
MEET GEORGE ALEX ANNUAL DER
AND LIEUY.
THE THREE BABY ALBINO HEDGE
HOGS IN A MOSCOW ZOO.
OFFICIALLY NAMED AFTER THE
BRITISH NEWBORN PRINCE.
THEY WERE BORN LAST MONTH
THE SAME DAY THE ROYAL
COUPLE HAD THEIR SONS.
WORKERS NAMED GEORGE
ALEXANDER ENCLOSURE
BUCKINGHAM PALACE.
FINLAND, THE AIR GUITAR
WORLD CHAMPIONSHIPS IN THE
WESTERN CITY OF OLU
COMPETITORS FROM SEVERAL
COUNTRIES INCLUDING THE
U.S. AND JAPAN SHOWCASE
THEIR BEST MOVES FOR THE
JUDGES.
AN AMERICAN WON THE EVENT
AND TOOK HOME THE GRAND
PRIZE, A REAL LICK TRICK
GUITAR.
AND THAT'S A WRAP ON THIS
FOX TRIP AROUND THE WORLD
IN 80 SECONDS.
BEACHES INTERNALLY LITTERED
WITH GLASS COULD BE A
REALITY.
CAME UP WITH THE IDEA AFTER
DISCOVERING A SAND SHORTAGE
AT SEVERAL BEACHES NEAR
MIAMI.
OVER THE YEARS STORMS AND
TIDES HAVE ERODED BIG
CHURCHES OF THE SHORELINE
THERE COMMUNITIES HAVE BEEN
REPLENISHING THE BEACH WITH
SAND THEY HAVE DREDGED UP
FROM THE OCEAN FLOOR.
BUT OFFICIALS SAY THAT
RESOURCE IS RUNNING LOW AND
NOW THEY ARE EYEING EMPTY
GLASS BOTTLES TO HELP
REFILL SOME OF FLORIDA'S
FINEST BEACHES.
PHIL KEATING IS OFTEN THE
BEACH LIVE TONIGHT IN MIAMI
WITH MORE ON THIS NOW.
BILL?
>> BILL SAND HAS MADE
FLORIDA RICH IN TOURIST
KICKING IN 70 BILLION A
YEAR TO THE STATE'S
ECONOMY.
BUT YOU SEE HOW I'M
DROPPING DOWN NOW 4 FEET ON
TO THE BEACH?
THAT IS BEACH EROSION.
AND IN MIAMI, DATED AND
BROWARD COUNTIES ALONE THEY
HAVE RUN OUT OF OFFSHORE
SAND TO DREDGE.
IN BROWARD THEY ARE LOOKING
AT RECYCLING BROKEN BOTTLES
OF GLASS CRUSHING THEM DOWN
TO THE SAME SIZE AND
COARSENESS OF NATIONAL SAND
TO REPLENISH THE BEACH.
>> EVERYTHING SEEMS TO
INDICATE THAT BY ALL
PHYSICAL AND BIOLOGICAL
MEASURES IT'S, YOU KNOW,
PERFORMS AS SAND.
>> THE FINAL GLASS TO STAND
TRIAL IS WATER TO SEE HOW
IT PERFORMS IN THE SURF AND
CONFIDENCE IN S. HIGH.
>> THE IDEA THAT WE COULD
TAKE GLASS THAT WAS BEING
THROWN AWAY, TURN IT INTO
SAND, IN ESSENCE IT'S
BROWARD COUNTY'S GOLD.
>> AND A MAJORITY OF THE
BEACH GOERS WE SPOKE WITH
SUPPORT THIS SHARP IDEA
JUST AS LONG AS THE NEW
SAND IS NOT SHARP.
>> I THINK IT'S A GREAT
IDEA.
AS LONG AS THEY RESEARCH IT
THOROUGHLY.
IT WOULDN'T BOTHER ME AT
ALL.
I'M SURE I WOULDN'T EVEN
NOTICE IT.
>> NOW, OF COURSE, GLASS IS
MADE FROM SAND HEATED UP TO
3700 DEGREES FAHRENHEIT.
SAND IS ALSO NOT VERY
CHEAP.
IT COSTS A MILLION DOLLARS
FOR A HALF MILE OF BEACH.
AND IF YOU HAVE TO SHIP IT
FOR THE BAHAMAS OR DRIVE IT
FROM UP NORTH, THESE
COUNTIES COULD BE LOOKING
AT EXPLODING BUDGETS BILL.
>> Bill: THAT'S HOW YOU
DRESS FOR WORK EVERY DAY
PHIL.
THANK YOU, SIR.
PHIL KEATING ON THE BEACH
IN MIAMI.
A FAREWELL SPEECH TODAY FOR
OUTGOING DIRECTOR OF
HOMELAND SECURITY JANET
NAPOLITANO.
SHE STEPS DOWN IN ABOUT A
WEEK AND SHE SAYS THERE IS
ONE THING HER SUCCESSOR
SHOULD NOT BE WITHOUT.
THAT'S AHEAD INSIDE "THE
FOX REPORT."
Reinforced with scratch-  resistant
glass
and a unibody  Made Kevlar Strong.
Okay Google Now.  Call My Droid.
The new  Droid Ultra by Motorola.
When strength matters,  Droid Does.
[ SCHOOL BELL RINGS ]    [ Male Announcer
]    FROM THE LAST DAY OF SCHOOL,
BACK TO THE FIRST.    THEY'RE GONNA
MAKE EVERYTHING    FROM POSTERS
TO DO IT YOURSELF TATTOOS.    SO MAKE
SURE THEY'VE GOT THE    SHARPIES TO
MAKE THEIR MARK.    THIS WEEK ONLY
GET SHARPIE    FIVE PACKS FOR A DOLLAR.
STAPLES HAS IT.    STAPLES.    THAT
WAS EASY.
[ Male Announcer ]    THIS IS BRAD.
HIS DAY OF COACHING    BEGINS WITH
KNEE PAIN, WHEN...  [ Man ] HEY, BRAD,
WANT TO TRADE THE ALL-DAY RELIEF
OF TWO ALEVE  FOR SIX TYLENOL?  WHAT'S
THE CATCH?  THERE'S NO CATCH.  YOU
WANT ME TO GIVE UP  MY TWO ALEVE FOR
SIX TYLENOL?  NO.  FOR MY KNEE PAIN
NOTHING BEATS MY ALEVE.
>> Bill: SOCIAL NETWORKING
GIANT FACEBOOK SAYS
GOVERNMENTS AROUND THE
WORLD HAVE DEMANDED
INFORMATION ON USERS TENS
OF THOUSANDS OF TIMES SINCE
JANUARY.
IT'S THE FIRST EVER GLOBAL
GOVERNMENT REQUEST REPORT.
FACEBOOK CLAIMS THAT 74
DIFFERENT COUNTRIES HAVE
DEMANDED INFORMATION ON
SOME 38,000 USERS THIS YEAR
ALONE.
COMPANY REPRESENTATIVES SAY
MORE THAN HALF OF THOSE
REQUESTS CAME FROM THE
UNITED STATES.
THEY SAY FACEBOOK PROVIDED
ABOUT DATA IN SOME 79% OF
THOSE CASES.
THE U.S. MEMBERS ARE JUST
RANGES THOUGH.
THE FEDS DON'T ALLOW THEM
TO REVEAL EXACT NUMBERS.
FACEBOOK FLAMES WHEN IT'S
REQUIRED TO GIVE THE
INFORMATION IT OFTEN SHARES
ONLY THE BASICS.
YOU WILL NEED A LARGE BODLE
OF ADVIL.
THAT'S THE ADVICE OUTGOING
HOMELAND SECURITY SECRETARY
JANET NAPOLITANO GAVE TO
HER STILL UNNAMED SUCCESSOR
DURING HER FAREWELL SPEECH
TODAY.
SECRETARY NAPOLITANO GAVE
THAT SPEECH AT THE NATIONAL
PRESS CLUB IN WASHINGTON.
SHE WILL STEP ASIDE NEXT
FRIDAY IN ABOUT A WEEK'S
TIME TO TAKE OVER
UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA
SYSTEM.
HER ACTING DEPUTY SECRETARY
IS SAID TO TAKE OVER UNTIL
THE SENATE CONFIRMS A
PERMANENT REPLACEMENT FOR
THAT JOB.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE KNOWS
THIS STORY ALL TOO WELL.
SHE HAS TRACKED HER EVERY
MOVE.
WHAT ELSE HAS HAD SHE HAD
SAY CATHERINE.
>> WITHOUT TAKING QUESTIONS
TODAY JANET NAPOLITANO
TELLING REPORTERS THE
EXPERIENCE TAUGHT HER ONE
THING.
>> LOOKING BACK OVER THE
PAST FOUR AND A HALF YEARS.
I CAN SAY THAT IF THERE IS
ONE TAKE AWAY, ONE OBJECT
LESSON AND CORE OPERATING
PRINCIPLE THAT I HAVE
LEARNED AND EMBRACED AS
SECRETARY, IT'S THIS:  IN A
WORLD OF EVOLVING THREATS
THE KEY TO OUR SUCCESS IS
THE ABILITY TO BE FLEXIBLE
AND A JILL.
ADD AGILE.
SHE MADE ROLE CENTRAL
FOCUS.
IMMEDIATE RESPONSE TO
HURRICANE SANDY ON THE
GROUND WITHIN HOURS.
WON PRAISE FROM EVEN HER
CRITICS, PHIL.
>> WHAT ABOUT THOSE
CRITICS, WHAT DO THEY SAY.
>> THEY SAY KNAP FOLLOWED
THE ADMINISTRATION'S LEAD
BY TRYING TO MINIMIZE THE
THREAT REFERRING TO
TERRORIST ATTACKS AS MAN
CAUSED DISASTERS WHEN SHE
TOOK THE JOB IN 2009.
ON KNAP'S WATCH TWO MAJOR
TERRORIST STRIKES INCLUDING
THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBING
THREE WERE KILLED AND 260
INJURED AS WELL AS TWO NEAR
MISSES INCLUDING THIS
ATTEMPTED CAR BOMBING OF
TIMES SQUARE WHERE THE
DETONATOR FAILED TO IGNITE.
FORMER CHAIRMAN OF THE
HOUSE HOMELAND SECURITY
COMMITTEE TELLING FOX
RECENTLY THAT KNAP WAS
UNDER USED.
>> UNDER THE BUSH
ADMINISTRATION, WHETHER IT
WAS SECRETARY RIDGE ARE
SECRETARY CHERTOFF THE
BUSH ADMINISTRATION I
THOUGHT HAD MUCH MORE AT
THE CENTER OF COUNTER
TERRORISM ANNOUNCEMENTS AND
ALSO AS FAR AS
INVESTIGATIONS WHILE UNDER
THIS ADMINISTRATION, SEEMED
TO DEFER BECOME ENTIRELY ON
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> AND STILL NO NOMINEE HAS
BEEN PUBLICLY IDENTIFIED BY
THE WHITE HOUSE, BILL.
>> Bill: THE DEBATE SHALL
BEGIN.
CATHERINE THANK YOU.
CATHERINE HERRIDGE IN
WASHINGTON.
ARSON INVESTIGATORS ARE
LOOKING INTO A FIRE THAT
DISPLACED DOZENS OF PEOPLE
FROM THEIR HOMES.
THAT'S OUR TOP STORY IN A
FOX TRIP TONIGHT ACROSS
AMERICA.
NEW JERSEY.
OFFICIALS SAY IT APPEARS
THE FLAMES BROKE OUT IN AN
ABANDONED ROW HOUSE UNIT IN
NEWARK.
THEN QUICKLY SPREAD TO
THREE OCCUPIED HOMES NEXT
DOOR.
SOME 30 PEOPLE HAD TO
EVACUATE.
NOBODY HURT.
THE RED CROSS IS HELPING
THE VICTIMS.
NEW YORK.
RESCUERS SAVED A WORKER
TRAPPED INSIDE A NARROW
TRENCH IN THE SHEEPS HEAD
BAY NEIGHBORHOOD IN
BROOKLYN.
OFFICIALS SAY THE GUY FELL
INTO THE 8-FOOT DEEP HOLE
BEHIND A HOME THAT IS UNDER
CONSTRUCTION.
ACCORDING TO WITNESSES
DEBRIS BURIED THE MAN UP TO
HIS CHEST FOR 20 MINUTES
UNTIL HELP ARRIVED.
CREWS SAY HE WAS CONSCIENCE
THE ENTIRE TIME.
THEY RUSHED HIM TO THE
HOSPITAL.
AT LAST CHECK HE WAS IN
SERIOUS BUT STABLE
CONDITION.
ARIZONA.
A HUGE WALL OF DUST
REPORTEDLY DOWNED POWER
LINES AND TOPPLED TREES AS
IT SWEPT THROUGH THE
PHOENIX METROPOLITAN AREA.
YOU CAN SEE THE DUST STORM
CLOUDED STREETS AND CUT
DOWN VISIBILITY.
NO WORD OF ANYBODY HURT.
OFFICIALS SAY ARIZONA'S
MONSOON SEASON TYPICALLY
BRINGS HEAVY WINDS AND
RAINS WHICH IN RECENT YEARS
HAVE TRIGGERED THESE
MASSIVE DUST STORMS.
KNOWN AS HA BOOBS.
MAN SUNNI SEASON RUNS FROM
MID JUNE TO SEPTEMBER.
THAT'S A FOX WATCH ACROSS
AMERICA.
WELL, THE RESULTS ARE IN
AND WE NOW KNOW WHO IS THIS
YEAR'S HIGHEST PAID
CELEBRITY.
AND IT IS NOT THESE GUYS.
WHO IS IT?
NUMBER ONE IS ON DECK NEXT.
I KNEW TESTOSTERONE  COULD AFFECT
SEX DRIVE  BUT NOT ENERGY  OR EVEN
MY MOOD.  THAT'S WHEN I TALKED  WITH
MY DOCTOR.  HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD
TESTS...  SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.  THAT'S
IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.    [ Male Announcer
]    TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T    HAVE
ANDROGEL    1.62% TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED    TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY    INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.    WOMEN AND CHILDREN
SHOULD AVOID    CONTACT WITH APPLICATION
SITES.    DISCONTINUANDROGEL    AND
CALL YOUR DOCTOR    IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED
SIGNS    OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,    WHICH MAY
INCLUDE    CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE    POSSIBLY
DUE    TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER    OR WHO HAVE
OR MIGHT HAVE    PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.    SERIOUS
SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE    WORSENING
OF AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,    POSSIBLE
INCREASED RIS    OF PROSTATE CANCER
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING    OF
ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY    ENLARGED
OR PAINFUL BREASTS,  PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP    AND BLOOD CLOTS IN
THE LEGS.    TELL YOUR DOCTOR    ABOUT
YOUR MEDICAL CONDITION    AND MEDICATIONS
ESPECIALLY IULIN    CORTICOSTEROIDS,
OR MEDICINES    TO DECREASE BLOOD
CLOTTING.    IN A CLINICAL STUDY,
OVER 80%    OF TREATED MEN HAD THEIR
T LEVELS RESTORED TO NORMAL.    TALK
TO YOUR DOCTOR    ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.    CHANGE YOUR
NUMBER. TURN IT UP.    ANDROGEL 1.62%.
YOU HAVE TIME TO SHOP  FOR CAR INSURANCE
TODAY?  YEAH.
I HEARD ABOUT PROGRESSIVE'S  "NAME
YOUR PRICE" TOOL?
I GUESS YOU CAN TELL THEM  HOW MUCH
YOU WANT TO PAY
AND IT GIVES YOU A RANGE OF  OPTIONS
TO CHOOSE FROM.
HUH? I'M LOOKING  AT IT RIGHT NOW.
OH, YEAH?
YEAH.
WHAT'S THE...  GUEST ROOM SITUATION?
THE "NAME YOUR PRICE" TOOL
MAKING THE WORLD    A LITTLE MORE
PROGRESSIVE.
>> Bill: THAT DONE THAN
RANKING LIST FOR 2013.
LIST OUT TODAY.
HER MOST RECENT TOUR
GROSSED A $335 MILLION.
EARNING HER A TOP TOURING
AWARD AT THIS YEAR'S
BILLBOARD MUSIC AWARDS.
SHE IS 55 AND SHE IS STILL
KILLING IT DIRECTOR STEPHAN
SPIELBERG SECOND ON THE
LIST EARNING $100 MILLION.
TIED FOR THIRD "FIFTY
SHADES OF GREY" AUTHOR
JAMES.
SIMON COWELL AND HOWARD
STERN SETTLED FOR
$55 MILLION THIS YEAR.
ON THIS DAY IN 1883 THE
MOST VOLCANIC IN HISTORY
SPARKED A CHAIN OF NATURAL
DISASTERS AROUND THE WORLD
IT HAPPENED IN WESTERN
INDONESIA.
MONTHS EARLIER PASSENGERS
ON A GERMAN WARSHIP HAD
REPORTED A MASSIVE BLUME OF
ASH COMING FROM THE
VOLCANO'S CREATOR.
THOSE EXPLOSIONS BECAME
ROUTINE IN LATE AUGUST OF
THAT YEAR, A MAJOR BLAST
BLEW MOST OF THE ISLAND
INTO THE SEA TRIGGERS
DEADLY TSUNAMIS.
A SERIES OF EVEN MORE
INTENSE ERUPTIONS FOLLOWED
THE NEXT DAY.
PEOPLE HEARD THE BLAST SOME
3,000 MILES AWAY.
AND FLOWS OF MOLTEN LAVA
BURIED ISLANDS.
THE ASH SHOT 50 MILES INTO
THE AIR IT WAS SO THICK IT
BLOCKED OUT THE SUN AND
LOWERED THE TEMPERATURES
AROUND THE WORLD.
IT REMAINS ACTIVE TO THIS
DAY BUT ITS CRATER LET OUT
A MASSIVE BLAST 130 YEARS
AGO TODAY.
THAT DOES IT FOR THIS FOX
REPORT ON THIS TUESDAY
AUGUST 27TH, 2000 13.
I'M BILL HEMMER IN TONIGHT
FOR SHEPARD SMITH.
SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING ON
AMERICA'S NEWSROOM 9:00
A.M. EASTERN TIME.
HERE NOW THE OTHER BILL.
>> Bill: THE O'REILLY
FACTOR IS ON.
TONIGHT:
>> THERE WOULD BE ENORMOUS
CONSEQUENCES IF WE START
SEEING MOVEMENT ON THE
CHEMICAL SWEPS FRONT.
>> Bill: NOW THE PRESIDENT
MUST ACT ON THAT THREAT.
BUT WHAT SHOULD HE DO?
I WILL ANALYZE WITH RALPH
PETERS, DAVID HUNT AND
CHARLES KRAUTHAMMER.
>> VOTER I.D.
WHY WOULD WE WANT TO GET
OBAMA DO WE NEED SOME
SPECIAL I.D.?
>> Bill: WHY IS IT THE
CIVIL RIGHTS INDUSTRY
TALKING ABOUT
BLACK-ON-BLACK CRIME.
WE WILL TELL YOU YOU
TONIGHT.
I TOO WANT TO TELL EVERYONE
THAT I'M SORRY THAT THIS
HAPPENED.
>> Bill: GEORGE ZIMMERMAN
WANTS THE STATE OF FLORIDA
TO PAY SOME OF HIS LEGAL