CALLED FOR HOME THE LAST SIX
YEARS."
ABC SAYS THE MOVE WAS PURELY
BUSINESS DECISION BY THE NETWORK
TO STOP SCHEDULING COMEDIES ON
FRIDAY NIGHT.
I'M MELISSA FRANCIS.
HERE'S SHEP.
>> Shepard: IT'S NOON ON THECOA.
3:00 AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS FACING THE
MORE SERIOUS ALLEGATION SINCE HE
TOOK OFFICE.
TURNING OVER CLASSIFIED SECRETS
SINCE BECOMING PRESIDENT.
HE SAYS HE DID NOTHING WRONG.
SOME REPUBLICANS AND DEMOCRATS
DEMAND ANSWERS.
NEW CLUES IN THE WORLDWIDE HACK
ATTACK POINTING TO NORTH KOREA.
COULD THE ROGUE NATION HAVE THE
POWER TO CRIPPLE COMPUTERS
AROUND THE GLOBE?
AND PIRATES OF THE CARIBBEAN
HELD HOSTAGE.
CYBER CRIMINALS SAY THEY STOLE A
COPY OF THE BLOCKBUSTER BEFORE
ITS RELEASE AND DEMANDING DISNEY
PAY UP OR ELSE.
LET'S GET TO IT.
FIRST FROM THE FOX NEWS DECK,
THE WHITE HOUSE IS REFUSING TO
CONFIRM WHETHER PRESIDENT TRUMP
SHARED CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
WITH THE RUSSIANS.
THE ADMINISTRATION IS FOCUSING
ON LEAKS RATHER THAN THE
SUBSTANCE.
THIS TIME, THE PRESIDENT IS
ACCUSED OF THE ORIGINAL LEAK.
TAKING INTELLIGENCE, SHARING IT
WITH AN ADVERSARY IN THE OVAL
OFFICE WHILE ONLY THAT COUNTRY'S
MEDIA WERE IN THE ROOM.
NO AMERICANS.
AS CONGRESS AND THE FBI ARE
INVESTIGATING RUSSIAN
INTERFERENCE IN OUR ELECTION AND
POSSIBLE TEAM TRUMP COLLUSION
WITH THE RUSSIANS.
SO FAR NO REPUBLICAN LAWMAKER
HAS COME TO HIS DEFENSE.
SOME ARE SILENT.
SOME ARE EXPRESSING CONCERN.
PAUL RYAN THROUGH A SPOKESMAN IS
ASKING FOR A FULL EXPLANATION.
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS OF MAINE
SAYS SHE HAS NOT BEEN INFORMED
AND THAT "IT'S VERY SERIOUS" AND
SHE WANTS TO "FIND OUT WHAT THE
FACTS ARE."
REPRESENTATIVE BARBARA COMSTOCK
REPUBLICAN OF VERY ISSUED A
STATEMENT SAYING "ONCE AGAIN
WE'RE FACED WITH STORIES COMING
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE THAT ARE
HIGHLY TROUBLING.
WE NEED IMMEDIATE CLASSIFIED
BRIEFINGS SO THAT CONGRESS CAN
KNOW AS MUCH AS RUSSIAN
LEADERS".
MOST STRIKING OF ALL, BOB CORKER
FROM TENNESSEE SAYS THE WHITE
HOUSE IS IN A DOWNWARD SPIRAL
AND THAT IT "HAS GOT TO DO
SOMETHING SOON TO BRING ITSELF
UNDER CONTROL AND IN ORDER."
THEN THERE'S THE PRESIDENT'S
CABINET.
SEVERAL HOURS AGO, H.R. McMASTER
SAID THE INFORMATION PRESIDENT
TRUMP SHARED WITH THE RUSSIANS
WAS WHOLLY APPROPRIATE.
HE WOULDN'T SAY IF THE
INFORMATION WAS CLASSIFIED.
>> WE DON'T SAY WHAT IS
CLASSIFIED AND WHAT IS NOT
CLASSIFIED.
I WILL TELL YOU WHAT HE SHARED
IS WHOLLY APPROPRIATE.
THE STORY COMBINED WHAT WAS
LEAKED WITH OTHER INFORMATION
AND THEN INSINUATED ABOUT
SOURCES AND METHODS.
I WANTED TO MAKE CLEAR TO
EVERYBODY THAT THE PRESIDENT IN
NO WAY COMPROMISED ANY SOURCES
OR METHODS IN THE COURSE OF THIS
CONVERSATION.
>> Shepard: "WHOLLY APPROPRIATE"
USED NINE TIMES.
THIS COMES FROM BUZZ FEED AND
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" AND OTHERS,
REPORTED PRESIDENT TRUMP
REVEALED HIGHLY CLASSIFIED
MATERIAL.
ACCORDING TO THE REPORTS, THE
PRESIDENT REVEALED SENSITIVE
DETAILS THAT MAY HAVE QUOTED
INFORMATION ABOUT THE ISLAMIC
STATES.
OUR COUSINS AT THE "WALL STREET
JOURNAL" ARE REPORTING THAT
INTELLIGENCE SOURCE WAS ISRAEL,
AND THAT ISRAEL WAS NOT INFORMED
THAT THE PRESIDENT WOULD BE
SHARING THAT INFORMATION WITH
ANYONE MUCH LESS THE RUSSIANS.
AS FOR THE PRESIDENT'S MEETING
WITH THE RUSSIANS, "THE
WASHINGTON POST" AND OTHERS
REPORT "HE WENT OFF SCRIPT" AND
GAVE DETAILS OF AN ISIS THREAT
INVOLVING LAPTOP COMPUTERS ON
AIR LANES.
THE "WASHINGTON POST" TOLD THE
RUSSIANS, I GET GREAT
INTELLIGENCE.
I HAVE PEOPLE BRIEF ME ON GREAT
INTEL EVERY DAY.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THIS MORNING
LASHED OUT ON TWITTER POSTING AS
PRESIDENT, I WANTED TO SHARE
WITH RUSSIAN AT AN OPENLY
SCHEDULED WHITE HOUSE MEETING
WHICH I HAVE THE ABSOLUTE RIGHT
TO DO FACTS PERTAINING TO
TERRORISM AND AIRLINE FLIGHT
SAFETY.
HUMANITARIAN REASONS.
PLUS, I WANT RUSSIA TO STEP UP
THEIR FIGHT AGAINST ISIS AND
TERRORISM.
I'VE BEEN ASKING DIRECTOR COMEY
TO FIND MY LEAKERS IN THE
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY.
OF COURSE, PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
MEETING WITH THE RUSSIANS CAME
JUST HOURS AFTER HE FIRED THE
FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY.
THE PRESIDENT HAS NOW ADMITTED
THE RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION WAS AT
LEAST ON HIS MIND WHEN HE MADE
THE DECISION TO FIRE HIM.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WARNED FORMER
DIRECTOR COMEY NOT TO LEAK THEIR
CONVERSATIONS AND SUGGESTED
THERE MIGHT BE TAPES THEREOF.
NOW THE PRESIDENT IS FIGHTING
ACCUSATIONS THAT HE LEAKED SENSE
TY INFORMATION.
CANDIDATE TRUMP BASHED HILLARY
CLINTON FOR LEAKING CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION.
IN THE MONTH OF JULY, HE
TWEETED, "CROOKED HILLARY
CLINTON AND HER TEAM WERE
CARELESS IN SENSITIVE HIGHLY
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
NOT FIT."
LATER THAT MONTH, CANDIDATE
TRUMP TREATED "HILLARY CLINTON
SHOULD NOT BE GIVEN SENSITIVE
BRIEFINGS BECAUSE SHE'S A LOOSE
CANNON AND BAD INSTINCTS."
NOW THE SITTING PRESIDENT IS
ACCUSED OF ACTIONS THAT ARE MORE
DANGEROUS.
ANDREW NAPOLITANO SAYS THESE ARE
THE MOST SERIOUS ACCUSATIONS
LEVELS AGAINST A SITTING
PRESIDENT IN THE MODERN ERA.
WE'LL HEAR FROM HIM SHORTLY.
FIRST, JOHN ROBERTS LIVE FROM
THE NORTH LAWN.
JOHN?
>> GOOD AFTERNOON TO YOU.
I'M BEING TOLD WHILE SINCE OF
THIS INFORMATION MAY HAVE BEEN
DEVELOPED BY ISRAEL, IT WASN'T
IN THE FORM OF A SPECIFIC
DOCUMENT THAT THE PRESIDENT
PULLED OUT AND PRESENTED TO THE
RUSSIANS AND SAID THIS IS WHAT
WE'RE LEARNING.
MORE IT WAS THERE WAS
INFORMATION THAT WAS DEVELOPED
IN ONE REGION AND THE PRESIDENT
HAD A CONVERSATION IN GENERAL
ABOUT THE THREATS THAT SOME OF
THAT INFORMATION DESCRIBED AND
THAT IT'S WRONG TO COMPLETELY
CONNECT THE DOTS BETWEEN THE TWO
THINGS.
WHAT THE PRESIDENT WAS TALKING
TO THE RUSSIANS ABOUT IS THREATS
TO AVIATION.
THAT GOES BEYOND JUST THE LAPTOP
BAN.
A SECURITY OFFICIAL TOLD ME A
SHORT TIME AGO THAT EVERY DAY WE
HEAR NO END OF DIFFERENT WAYS
AND CREATIVE WAYS THAT PEOPLE
WANT TO BLOW UP AIRPLANES
BECAUSE IT SEEMS THAT AL-QUAIDA
AND ISIS ARE STILL CONSUMED WITH
THE IDEA OF BRINGING DOWN
AIRLINERS.
DON'T FORGET THAT RUSSIAN HAD
THAT ATTACK ON OCTOBER 21, 2015
IN WHICH 224 PEOPLE DIED WHEN
ISIS BROUGHT DOWN A RUSSIAN
AIRLINER THAT WAS TAKING OFF IN
THE SINAI PART OF EGYPT.
SO THE PRESIDENT WHEN HE WAS
METING WITH THE PRESIDENT OF
TURKEY SAID THAT HE BELIEVED
THAT IT WAS APPROPRIATE TO SHARE
INFORMATION ANT A COMMON THREAT
WITH A COUNTRY THAT HE WANTS TO
BRING ON AS AN ALLY IN THE FIGHT
OF ISIS.
HERE'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT SAID.
>> WE HAD A VERY SUCCESSFUL
MEETING WITH TRUSSIA.
GENERAL McMASTERS SAID AND I
KNOW HE FEELS WE HAD A GREAT
MEETING WITH THE FOREIGN
MINISTER.
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE GREAT
SUCCESS THE NEXT COMING YEARS
AND WE WANT TO GET AS MANY TO
HELP FIGHT TERRORISM AS
POSSIBLE.
>> WE'RE ALSO TOLD IN AN OFF
CAMERA BRIEFING BY SEAN SPICER
THAT THE PRESIDENT IS VERY UPSET
ABOUT THIS LATEST LEAK,
PARTICULARLY WHEN YOU CONSIDER
IT'S THE LATEST IN A LONG LINE
OF LEAKS.
HERE'S SOME AUDIO WITHOUT
PICTURES BECAUSE THIS IS AN OFF
CAMERA BRIEFING WITH SEAN
SPICER.
>> WHAT HAS OCCURRED TODAY OR
THE LAST LITTLE WHILE IN TERMS
OF THESE LEAKS IS FRANKLY
DANGEROUS.
THE IDEA THAT SOMEONE WHO HAS
BEEN GIVEN ACCESS TO INFORMATION
IS PUSHING THAT INFORMATION OUT
INTO THE MEDIA, UNDERMINES OUR
NATIONAL SECURITY AND I DON'T
THINK THERE'S ANY OTHER WAY TO
SAY IT THAT IT IS FRANKLY
DANGEROUS.
>> WE HEARD THE SAME THING FROM
GENERAL H.R. McMASTER WHEN HE
SAID THAT WHAT REALLY IS A
THREAT TO NATIONAL SECURITY
ISN'T WHAT THE PRESIDENT SHARED
WITH RUSSIANS BUT IT'S IN THE
PUBLIC DOMAIN.
SO I PRESSED THE NATIONAL PUBLIC
SECURITY ADVISER SAID WHAT THE
NSD IS DOING TO CURB SUCH
THINGS.
>> WHAT STEPS ARE YOU TAKING BY
VIRTUAL OF DISCOVERING THIS AS
YOU DID TO TRY TO LIMIT THE
POTENTIAL FOR ANY MORE LEAKS OF
NATIONAL SECURITY INFORMATION?
>> I THINK NATIONAL SECURITY IS
AT RISK BY THIS LEAK AND LEAKS
LIKE THIS.
THERE'S A NUMBER OF INSTANCES
WHERE THIS HAS OCCURRED AND I
THINK IT'S IMPORTANT TO
INVESTIGATE THESE SORT OF THINGS
AND TO MAKE SURE THAT WE HAVE
TRUSTED ORGANIZATIONS ACROSS OUR
GOVERNMENT THAT ALLOWS FOR THE
FREE SHARING OF INFORMATION AND
COLLABORATION.
>> OF COURSE, THE NATIONAL
SECURITY APPARATUS BELIEVES
THESE LEAKS ARE BAD.
OTHERS SAY THEY LIKE THE
INFORMATION ABOUT WHAT THE
PRESIDENT IS DOING IS GETTING
OUT THERE.
I SPOKE WITH ERIC ERICSON, A FOX
NEWS CONTRIBUTOR.
HE SAYS HE KNOWS ONE OF THE
PEOPLE THAT LEAKED THIS
INFORMATION, HAS TALKED TO THAT
PERSON ABOUT IT.
THE REASON IS, THIS PERSON IS A
TRUMP SUPPORTER, DOESN'T LIKE
THE WAY THE PRESIDENT ISN'T
LISTENING TO HIS AIDES.
AND THOUGHT BY GETTING THIS
INFORMATION IN THE PUBLIC
DOMAIN, THE BLOW BACK MAY
INFLUENCE THE PRESIDENT TO
CHANGE HIS WAYS.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: ANYTHING FROM THE
ISRAELIS?
>> THIS FALLS INTO A NARRATIVE
THAT WAS CREATED IN THE INITIAL
STORY BY GIVING THIS INFORMATION
TO THE RUSSIANS DEVELOPED BY A
THIRD PARTNER, THE PRESIDENT MAY
BE JEOPARDIZING THE INFORMATION
SHARING PARTNERSHIPS THAT WE
HAVE AROUND THE WORLD.
BUT LISTENING TO THE ISRAELI
AMBASSADOR TO THE UNITED STATES,
THE RELATIONSHIP WHEN IT COMES
TO INTELLIGENCE SHARING BETWEEN
THE U.S. AND ISRAEL IS ON A FIRM
FOOTING.
THIS IS WHAT WE WERE TOLD.
SO ANY IDEA THAT THIS HAS
DAMAGED ISRAELI-U.S. RELATIONS
IN TERMS OF INTELLIGENCE
SHARING, SHEP, APPEARS TO BE
KNOCKED DOWN BY THIS PARTICULAR
STATEMENT.
BUT THERE'S OTHER ISSUES THAT WE
DON'T HAVE TIME TO TALK ABOUT
THAT DO HAVE ISRAEL WORKED UP IN
TERMS OF WHAT THE U.S. IS
SAYING.
>> Shepard: INDEED.
THANKS, JOHN ROBERTS.
LAWMAKERS FROM BOTH PARTIES ARE
CALLING THE REPORT THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP SHARED
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION WITH
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS DISSERVING.
MIKE EMANUEL IS LIVE ON CAPITOL
HILL.
I GAVE THE REPORT FROM SOME
REPUBLICANS, INCLUDING A BOB
CORKER, THE REPUBLICAN OF
TENNESSEE THAT SAYS -- HAD HARSH
WORDS FOR THE WHITE HOUSE.
WHAT ELSE ARE YOU GETTING?
>> SHEP, SOME REPUBLICANS SOUND
ALARMS SAYING THEY WANT MORE
ANSWERS FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
OTHER REPUBLICANS ARE CONCERNED
ABOUT THE DISTRACTION ASPECT
KEEPING THEM FROM WHAT THEY WANT
TO GET DONE.
A SPOKESMAN FROM PAUL RYAN SAYS
PROTECTING AMERICAN'S SECRETS
ARE PARAMOUNT.
THE SENATE MAJORITY LEADER
WEIGHED IN BRIEFLY A SHORT TIME
AGO.
>> LET ME JUST REPEAT WHAT I
SAID IN AN EARLIER INTERVIEW
THIS MORNING.
IT WOULD BE HELPFUL TO HAVE LESS
DRAMA EMANATING FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> McCONNELL SAID HE WOULD
PREFER TO BE TALKING ABOUT LESS
REGULATION, REPEALING AND
REPLACING OBAMACARE AND TAX
REFORM RATHER THAN THE CRISIS AT
THE MOMENT FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> Shepard: WHAT ARE YOU HEARING
FROM DEMOCRATS?
>> CHUCK SCHUMER SAYS HE WANTS
TO SEE TRANSCRIPTS OF WHAT THE
PRESIDENT SAID TO THE RUSHES.
NANCY PELOSI SAID WE CAN'T HAVE
THE PRESIDENT LOOSE LIP PED TO N
ADVERSARIAL DOMAIN.
>> WITH REGARD TO THE COMPROMISE
OF CODE-WORDED INFORMATION, IT
COMPROMISES OUR INTELLIGENCE
SOURCES, COMPROMISES OUR WAR
AGAINST ISIS, COMPROMISES OUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH OTHER
INTERNATIONAL PARTNERS.
BECAUSE OF WAY IN THIS WAS
REVEALED, IT POTENTIALLY
COMPROMISES OUR YOUNG MEN AND
WOMEN IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
>> OTHER DEMOCRATS ARE CALLING
IT RECKLESS AND DISTURBING.
>> Shepard: MIKE EMANUEL, THANK
YOU.
OUR NEXT GUEST SAYS THE WHITE
HOUSE MAY HAVE TO PUSHING FROM A
AGENDA TO SURVIVING.
SHE'S HEARING FROM ONE
REPUBLICAN THAT IS WORRIED ABOUT
HIS PARTY'S FATE IN THE NEXT
ELECTION.
CONTINUING COVERAGE NEXT ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
♪
Fun in art class.
Come close, come close.
I like that.
[ music stops suddenly ]
Ah.
When your pain reliever
stops working,
your whole day stops.
Awww.
Try this.
For minor arthritis pain,
only Aleve can stop pain
for up to 12 straight hours
with just one pill.
Thank you.
♪
Come on everybody.
You can't quit, neither
should your pain reliever.
Stay all day strong with
12 hour Aleve.
Hansel and Gretel
came upon a houseime
made out of gingerbread.
Being quite hungry,
they started eating the roof.
The homeowner was outraged.
Luckily
the GEICO Insurance Agency
had helped her
with homeowners insurance.
She got all her
shingles replaced.
Hansel and Gretel were last seen
eating their way through
the candy cane forest.
Call GEICO and see how easy
it is to switch and save
on homeowners insurance.
>> Shepard: MORE ON THE FALLOUT
OVER REPORTS THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP REVEALED HIGHLY CLASSIFIED
CODE WORD INFORMATION TO THE
RUSSIANS.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT WAS
WHOLLY APPROPRIATE FOR THE
PRESIDENT TO SHARE THAT
INTELLIGENCE BUT IT WILL NOT SAY
WHETHER THE INFORMATION WAS IN
FACT CLASSIFIED.
LET'S TURN TO ANNA PALMER FROM
POLITICO.
ANNA, GOOD AFTERNOON.
>> GOOD AFTERNOON.
>> Shepard: IS THERE SOME
QUESTION ABOUT WHETHER THIS
INFORMATION WAS CLASSIFIED?
IT DOESN'T APPEAR THAT THERE IS.
>> I THINK THE ISSUE REALLY
IS -- TRUMP CAN DECIDE TO
DECLASSIFY ANYTHING AT ANY TIME.
SO WHETHER OR NOT IT WAS
CLASSIFIED MIGHT NOT BE THE
PROBLEM.
THE PROBLEM IS THE FACT THAT
HE'S GIVING INFORMATION FROM ONE
OF THE U.S.'S MOST GREATEST
ALLIES TO SOMEBODY IN THE
RUSSIAN ADMINISTRATION WHICH IS
CERTAINLY NOT -- HAS NOT BEEN AN
ALLY FOR THE U.S. A LONG TIME.
TRUMP IS CLOSE TO RUSSIAN.
PEOPLE ARE CONCERNED ABOUT WHAT
HAS BEEN HAPPENING THE PAST
COUPLE DAYS.
>> GENERAL McMASTER CAME OUT
NINE TIMES BY MY COUNT AND SAID
WHAT HE SAID WAS WHOLLY
APPROPRIATE.
AT THE END OF THE NEWS
CONFERENCE, HE SAID THE
PRESIDENT DID NOT KNOW THE
SOURCE OF THIS INFORMATION.
IN OTHER WORDS, PLEADING
IGNORANCE TO A MATTER IS BLISS.
THAT'S NOT THE CASE, IS IT?
>> WELL, WHAT WE KNOW NOW IS
THAT OBVIOUSLY ISRAEL, WHICH
BASICALLY HAS BEEN CONFIRMED BY
THEIR GOVERNMENT --
>> Shepard: OR A SOURCE.
>> OR WAS ONE OF THE SOURCES OR
A SOURCE FOR THIS INFORMATION.
THE QUESTION I THINK THAT IS
REALLY TELLING HERE IS YOU HAVE
CERTAINLY McMASTERS COMING OUT
STRONGLY DEFENDING DONALD TRUMP.
YOU DON'T HAVE A SINGLE
REPUBLICAN ON CAPITOL HILL
STEPPING UP TO THE PLATE AND
COMING TO HIS DEFENSE AT ALL.
NOT A SINGLE ONE.
NOT LEADERSHIP, NOT IN THE RANK
AND FILE AND THAT IS STUNNING.
>> Shepard: AND NORMALLY FOR
MANY PEOPLE, OBSERVERS THEREOF,
THIS IS ABOUT TEAM, EMOTION,
IT'S ABOUT VALUES AND MORALS.
BUT FOR THESE POLITICIANS,
LARGELY AND WITH NOTABLE
EXCEPTIONS THAT DON'T COME TO
MINDS, THIS IS ABOUT RE-ELECTION
AND WHAT CHANGES THE WAY PEOPLE
BEHAVE IS THEIR BELIEF ABOUT
THEIR POSSIBILITIES OF GETTING
RE-ELECTED.
WHEN STAYING WITH THE CURRENT
CAUSES YOU PROBLEMS IN THE
FUTURE, YOU ABANDON THE CURRENT
THE HISTORY BOOKS TELL US.
>> ONE OF THE BIGGEST ISSUES
THAT WE'RE TALKING TO EVERY DAY
ARE LOOKING AT 2018.
DONALD TRUMP WILL NOT BE ON THE
BALLOT IN 2018.
A OF MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
WILL BE.
THEY'RE LOOKING TO THE FACT THAT
IS TRUMP UP FROM GOING TO BE A
DRAG, CAN THEY DEFEND THE
ISSUES, WHETHER THE FIRING OF
FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY OR HIS
INFORMATION ON THE CAMPAIGN
TRAVEL.
TRUMP WAS HARSH AND HIS ALLIES
WERE HARSH HOW HILLARY CLINTON
WAS HANDLING CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION.
YOU CAN SEE THE ATTACK ADS HERE.
>> Shepard: THERE'S A LOT COMING
TOGETHER NOW.
THE INVESTIGATIONS, FBI AND
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATIONS,
THE MATTER OF THE RUSSIANS,
HAVING THE RUSSIANS IN THE OVAL
OFFICE THE DAY A AFTER THE
FIRING OF THE FBI DIRECTOR THAT
WAS CONDUCTING THE INVESTIGATION
ON THE RUSSIANS AND THE ALLEGED
TRANSMISSION OF CLASSIFIED
SECRETS GIVEN TO US BY AN ALLY
TO THE RUSSIANS WHO ARE OUR
ADVERSARIES ABOUT SEEING HOW
THIS PUZZLE MIGHT BE COMING
TOGETHER IN THE FUTURE.
IF YOU'RE A REPUBLICAN, BARBARA
COMSTOCK MENTIONED EARLIER,
WHOSE SEAT WILL BE CHALLENGED IN
THE COMING ELECTION, YOU MIGHT
LOOK TO THOSE PEOPLE TO SEE
WHERE THE PARTY WILL GO.
IF IT'S BARBARA COMSTOCK,
THERE'S LOTS OF QUESTIONS.
>> WHAT IS INTERESTING HERE,
IT'S NOT JUST MODERATES AND
PEOPLE THAT WEREN'T WITH TRUMP
IN THE BEGINNING.
YOU'RE NOT HAVING PEOPLE LIKE
SENATE MAJORITY LEADER, MITCH
McCONNELL SAYING HE CAN DEAL
WITH A LOT LESS DRAMA FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THAT IS A CLEAR SIGNAL.
THIS IS NOT EVEN SHADOWBOXING
ANYMORE.
CAPITOL HILL WOULD LIKE TRUMP TO
BE ACTING DIFFERENTLY.
THEY'RE SAYING GET IN LINE,
YOU'RE NOT HELPING US.
AT SOME POINT, WE'RE HEARING
FROM A LOT OF SOURCES THAT
CAPITOL HILL REPUBLICANS ARE
GOING TO GO THEIR OWN WAY, WHICH
WILL BE A MAJOR PROBLEM FOR
DONALD TRUMP AND HIS BIG
PACKAGES LIKE TAX REFORM AND
HEALTH CARE.
>> Shepard: THANKS, ANNA.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Shepard: JUDGE ANDREW
NAPOLITANO SAID IT WAS PERFECTLY
LEGAL FOR THE PRESIDENT TO SHARE
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION WITH THE
RUSSIANS.
BUT STILL, JUDGE ANDREW
NAPOLITANO IS CALLING THE
ACTIONS GRAY AND PROFOUND.
HE'S HERE TO EXPLAIN NEXT.
THIS IS BILL'S YARD.
AND BILL HAS A "NO-WEEDS,
NOT IN MY YARD" POLICY.
BUT WITH SCOTTS TURF
BUILDER WEED & FEED,
BILL HAS NOTHING TO WORRY ABOUT.
IT KILLS WEEDS
AND GREENS GRASS, GUARANTEED.
THIS IS A SCOTTS YARD.
If you have moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis like me,
and you're talking
AND Gto your rheumatologistD.
about a medication...
...this is HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA helping
to relieve my pain...
...and protect my joints
from further damage.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 18 years.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to...
...block a
specific source...
...of inflammation that
contributes to RA symptoms.
It's proven to help
relieve pain and...
...stop further joint
damage in many adults.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas...
...where certain fungal
infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flulike
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Talk to your doctor
and visit HUMIRA.com
This is HUMIRA at work.
REMEMBER HERE AT ALLY,
NOTHING STOPS US FROM DOING
RIGHT BY OUR CUSTOMERS.
WHO'S WITH ME?
WE'RE LIKE A SPORTS
TEAM HERE AT ALLY.
IF A SPORTS TEAM HAD OVER 7...
I'M IN.
7,000 PLAYERS.
OUR PLAYS ARE A
LITTLE UNORTHODOX.
BUT TO BEAT THE BIG BOYS,
YOU NEED SMARTER WAYS
TO SAVE PEOPLE MONEY.
WE KNOW WHAT YOU WANT
FROM A FINANCIAL COMPANY
AND WE'LL STOP AT...
NOTHING TO MAKE SURE YOU GET IT.
ONE, TWO...
AND WE MEAN NOTHING.
♪  ♪
>> Shepard: CONTINUING COVERAGE
OF THE STOP STORY OF THE DAY.
SEAN SPICER CALLING LEAKS ABOUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S SHARING
INTELLIGENCE FRANKLY DANGEROUS
AND THE THREAT TO NATIONAL
SECURITY.
THE WHITE HOUSE CALLING THE
INFORMATION THE PRESIDENT SHARED
WHOLLY A ROPE WHY IT AND
REFUSING TO SAY WHETHER IT WAS
CLASSIFIED.
JUDGE NAPOLITANO IS HERE.
IF YOU COULD ENCAPSULATE AS YOU
DID FOR ME WHAT THE ACCUSATION
HERE AND EXPLAIN TO THE AUDIENCE
THE SERIOUSNESS OF IT.
>> THE PRESIDENT CAN DECLASSIFY
ANYTHING.
HE CAN WHISPER IT INTO YOUR EAR,
IN WHICH CASE IT'S DECLASSIFIED
JUST FOR YOU OR REMOVE IT FROM
THE CATEGORY OF CLASSIFICATION,
IN WHICH CASE IT BECOMES PUBLIC.
IN THIS CASE HE DIDN'T WHISPER
IT IN THEIR EAR BUT SAID IT TO
THOSE IN THE OVAL OFFICE.
AMONG THEM WITH THE FOREIGN
MINISTER TO RUSSIA AND THE
AMBASSADOR TO RUSSIA.
SO ONE WAY TO LOOK AT THIS IS,
BY NAMING THE CITY FROM WHICH
THE INTELLIGENCE INFORMATION IN
SYRIA CAME, THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES TOLD OUR
ADVERSARY, RUSSIA, WHERE OUR
ALLIES, THE ISRAELIS HAVE THEIR
SPIES LOCATED IN SYRIA.
THAT'S VERY DANGEROUS.
BECAUSE IN SYRIA THE RUSSIAN
INTEREST IS ADVERSE TO THE
AMERICAN INTEREST AND THE
ISRAELIS ARE ALIGNED WITH THE
AMERICANS.
>> Shepard: SO WHAT YOU'RE
SAYING THE PRESIDENT TOLD THE
RUSSIAN SPY IN THE OVAL OFFICE,
WE GOT INFORMATION FROM ISRAEL
INSIDE SYRIA AND HERE'S WHERE
THE SPIES ARE INSIDE IN SYRIA.
>> HE APPARENTLY DID THAT
WITHOUT USING THE NAME ISRAEL OR
THE WORD "ISRAELI" BUT THESE
GUYS KNEW OR COULD EASILY
CALCULATE WHAT FOREIGN POWER HAD
ENOUGH RESOURCES LOCATED IN
SYRIA TO PRODUCE THE KIND OF
INFORMATION THAT THE PRESIDENT
WAS TALKING ABOUT.
AGAIN, HE DIDN'T BREAK ANY LAW.
OBVIOUSLY THE ALLEGATION THAT AN
AMERICAN PRESIDENT GAVE TOP
SECRET INFORMATION TO AN
ADVERSARY IS GRAVE AND NEVER
BEEN CHARGED BEFORE IN THE
MODERN ERA.
THE QUESTION IS HOW HARMFUL IS
THIS AND WHAT THE CONCERN ABOUT
IT IN THE FEATURE.
>> Shepard: LEGALLY SPEAKING FOR
THE PRESIDENT.
>> ABSOLUTELY SAFE.
THE STATUTE IS VERY CLEAR.
THE PRESIDENT CAN CLASSIFY
ANYTHING AND HE CAN DECLASSIFY
ANYTHING.
WHEN HE SAID I HAD THE RIGHT TO
DO IT, HE'S ABSOLUTELY CORRECT.
>> Shepard: THE BIGGER PICTURE
QUESTION IS FOR SOMEONE WITH A
DIFFERENT EXPERTISE THAN MINE OR
YOURS AND THIS WOULD BE HOW THAT
WOULD AFFECT OTHERS.
FOR INSTANCE, JORDAN, WHO IS
ALWAYS KNOWN TO BE A VERY GOOD
SOURCE OF INTELLIGENCE FOR NEWS
THE WAR ON TERROR.
WOULD SOME OF OUR ALLIES LIKE
JORDAN BE CONCERNED ABOUT
SHARING INFORMATION WITH US IF
THEY THOUGHT THE INFORMATION
MIGHT FIND ITS WAY TO THE
RUSSIANS?
>> THAT'S THE $64,000 QUESTION.
I'M SURE GENERAL McMASTER AND
HIS TEAM ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
THAT.
BECAUSE THEY RELY ON THE
JORDANIANS AS THE JORDANIANS
RELY ON US.
THEY THINK THE EXCHANGE WOULDN'T
BE GOOD.
THE PRESIDENT CLAIMS WE HAVE A
COMMON ENEMY.
ISIS DESTROYED ONE OF THEIR
FLIGHTS AROUND SEVERAL HUNDRED
RUSSIAN CIVILIANS WERE MURDERED
AND HE WANTED TO HELP THEM FIND
OUT WHAT ISIS WAS UP TO AND
WHERE THEY WERE LOCATED.
I'M SURE IF GENERAL McMASTER
AHEAD OF TIME, HE WOULD HAVE
SUGGESTED THE PRESIDENT USE
DIFFERENT WORDS.
>> Shepard: THANK YOU.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> Shepard: PRESIDENT TRUMP
MEETING FACE TO FACE WITH THE
TURKISH PRESIDENT AFTER ANGERING
THEM WITH ARMING KURDISH
FIGHTERS.
THE KURDS AND THE TURK
GOVERNMENT ARE WILDLY OPPOSED
AND FIGHT ALONG THE BORDER.
DETAILS IN TODAY'S MEETING.
A POSSIBLE LINK BETWEEN NORTH
KOREA AND THE MASSIVE GLOBAL
CYBER ATTACK.
WHAT RESEARCHERS SAY THEY FOUND
AS WE APPROACH THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR AND THE TOP OF THE NEWS.
trust Safelite AutoGlass.
For these parents, driving
around was the only way to get
their baby to sleep.
So when their windshield
got cracked...
CUSTOMER: We can't
drive this car.
TECH: ...they wanted it
fixed right.
So they scheduled with Safelite.
Our exclusive TrueSeal
technology means a strong,
reliable bond,
every time.
At Safelite,
we stand behind our work.
Bye, bye.
Because the ones you love,
sit behind it.
(PARENTS WHISPER JINGLE)
Safelite repair, Safelite
replace.
>> I'M LEA GABRIELLE WITH THE
FOX REPORT.
MORE OF TODAY'S HEADLINES.
IT'S ONLY A MATTER OF TIME
BEFORE U.S. BACKED IRAQI FORCES
RETAKE MOSUL FROM ISIS
TERRORISTS.
COALITION TROOPS HAVE SURROUNDED
ISIS MILITANTS LEAVING THEM IN
CONTROL OF ROUGHLY 10% OF
TERRITORY IN THE WESTERN HALF OF
THE CITY.
IRAQI FORCES DECLARED THE
EASTERN HALF OF MOSUL LIBERATED
IN JANUARY.
CREWS WORKING TO PUT OUT A FIRE
SENDING OUT LARGE PLUMES OF
SMOKE INTO THE AIR AT A
RECYCLING PLANT OUTSIDE OF
BALTIMORE.
NO WORD OF INJURIES.
BILL COSBY SAYS RACISM MIGHT
HAVE PLAYED A ROLE IN THE DOZENS
OF SEXUAL ASSAULT ACCUSATIONS
AGAINST HIM.
HE MADE THE COMMENT TO A SIRIUS
XM RADIO HOST.
HE'S DENIED ALL ACCUSATIONS
ABOUT HIM.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
erby.
♪
Now give up half of 'em.
Do I have to?
This is a tough financial choice
we could face when we retire.
But, if we start saving
even just 1% more
of our annual income...
We could keep doing all
the things we love.
Prudential. Bring Your
Challenges.
♪
I'm Dr. Kelsey McNeely and some
day you might be
calling me an energy farmer.
♪
Energy lives here.
♪ The sun'll come out
For people with Heart Failure,
tomorrow is not a given.
But ENTRESTO is a medicine
that helps make more
tomorrows possible.
♪ Tomorrow, tomorrow...
♪ I love ya, tomorrow
In the largest Heart Failure
study ever,
ENTRESTO helped
more people stay alive
and out of the hospital
than a leading Heart Failure
medicine.
Women who are pregnant
must not take ENTRESTO.
It can cause harm or death
to an unborn baby.
Don't take ENTRESTO
with an ACE inhibitor
or aliskiren.
If you've had angioedema
while taking an ACE
or ARB medicine,
don't take ENTRESTO.
The most serious side effects
are angioedema,
low blood pressure...
...kidney problems,
or high potassium in your blood.
♪ Tomorrow, tomorrow I love
ya, tomorrow ♪
Ask your heart doctor
about ENTRESTO.
And help make tomorrow possible.
♪ You're only a day away.
>> Shepard: RESEARCHERS SAY THE
CYBER ATTACK THAT HIT HUNDREDS
OF THOUSANDS OF COMPUTERS IN 150
COUNTRIES LAST WEEK MAY BE
CONNECTED TO NORTH KOREA.
THE ATTACK AFFECTED A LIMIT
NUMBER OF COUNTRIES.
BRITAIN'S HOSPITAL NETWORK AND
GERMANY'S RAILWAY HIT.
THOSE SAY THE CYBER ATTACK
COMPUTER FILES AND HEAD THEM
RANSOM.
RUSHERS SAY THE WANNA CRY
SOFTWARE CONTAINED CODE USED IN
OTHER HACK ATTACKS LINKED TO THE
NORTH KOREANS.
THAT INCLUDES THE CYBER ATTACK
TO SONY IN 2014.
RESEARCHERS SAY THE DISCOVERY
DOES NOT CONFIRM NORTH KOREA'S
CYBER ATTACK.
IT'S POSSIBLE THE ATTACKERS
COPIED THE CODE.
THIS COMES DAYS AFTER NORTH
KOREA TESTED A MISSILE.
KIM JONG-UN SAYS THE WEAPON IS
ABLE TO HIT THE UNITED STATES
MAINLAND.
GREG PALKOT HAS MORE.
GREG?
>> SHEP, IT'S ALL BEING CALLED
CIRCUMSTANTIAL EVIDENCE.
BUT IT'S LOOKING STRONG.
THIS HAS BEEN GOING ON FOR FOUR
DAYS.
300,000 TARGETS WORLDWIDE.
AND NOW THE ECONOMIC IMPACT OF
THIS HACKING ATTACK SAID TO BE
$4 BILLION.
NOW, SECURITY FIRMS HERE AND IN
EUROPE AS WELL AS THE U.S. AND
TODAY IN SOUTH KOREA ARE MAKING
THIS NORTH KOREAN LINK.
WE'VE KNOWN FOR YEARS THAT KIM
JONG-UN'S REGIME HAD A WHOLE
ARMY OF CROOKS TALKING IN A
VARIETY OF WAYS, A VARIETY OF
TARGETS.
NOW AS YOU HINTED AT, THE
PROGRAM CODE FOUND IN THIS
LATEST MALWARE, RANSOMWARE
ATTACK, IS SOMEWHAT SIMILAR TO
OTHER ATTACKS.
THERE WAS A 2014 ATTACK ON SONY
PICTURES.
BUT THERE'S OTHER ATTACKS MOSTLY
IN ASIA AND SEEM TO THINK THE
RANSOM GAINED IN THE ATTACKS,
$100,000 SO FAR.
BUT THE DISRUPTION IS MAXIMUM.
IN THE U.S., THEY MADE OUT
PRETTY WELL.
EUROPE WAS HIT HARD.
INTERESTINGLY, CHINA HIT VERY
HARD.
30,000 INSTITUTIONS WERE
TARGETED.
EVERYTHING FROM UNIVERSITIES TO
GAS STATIONS.
WE DID HEAR TODAY BEIJING
OFFICIALS SAYING LISTEN, THIS
HAS TO END HINTING THAT NORTH
KOREA HAS TO DO SOMETHING ABOUT
IT.
AGAIN, THE INVESTIGATION NOT
COMPLETELY SURE THAT NORTH KOREA
IS INVOLVED.
THAT'S WHY EUROPOL AND OTHER
INVESTIGATIVE BODIES ARE WORKING
HARD AS WELL AS THE BLAME GAME.
MICROSOFT HAD ITS
VULNERABILITIES IN THE SOFT WAY.
THEY FOUND WAYS TO COUNTER ACT
THAT AND TAKE ADVANTAGE OF THAT.
AND THEN THERE'S THE HACKERS AND
THEN THE USERS LIKE YOU AND ME
THAT SHOULD PUT UP MORE
DEFENSES.
THIS IS NOT THE END OF THIS.
>> Shepard: GREG PALKOT LIVE.
THANK YOU.
AND LET'S GO TO OUR COUNTSER
TERRORISM EXPERT.
WHAT IS YOUR TAKE ON THIS?T'S I
KOREA IS THE CULPRIT, THIS IS A
COUNTRY RUN BY A CRIMINAL
ENTERPRISE THAT ALSO HAS AN
ARMY.
IS THIS A WAY TO GENERATE
REVENUE TO GENERATE BILLIONS IN
RANSOM OR IS IT A SHOT ACROSS
THE BOW?
SHOWS THAT THE NORTH KOREANS OR
WHOEVER IS DOING THIS CAN AFFECT
HUNDREDS OF COUNTRIES AND MAYBE
IN THE EVENT THAT THERE'S A
SHOOTING WAR THAT HAPPENS ON THE
KOREAN PENINSULA, THEY CAN DO
MORE DAMAGE.
IS IT A MONEY-MAKING ENTERPRISE
OR MORE?
IT'S IN THE EARLY DAYS AND CAN'T
WAIT TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
>> Shepard: HELP US UNDERSTAND
THAT SOMEONE MIGHT DRAW THE
CONCLUSION THAT IT WAS THE NORTH
KOREANS?
WE KNOW OUR GOVERNMENT CAN MAKE
WHATEVER THEY DO LOOK LIKE
SOMEBODY ELSE DID IT?
>> WHAT WE'RE TALKING ABOUT IS
ATTRIBUTION.
WE SAW, WE, THE U.S. GOVERNMENT,
BUT COMPANIES LIKE SAMANTAC AND
SOME LABS IN RUSSIA, THEY SAW
BITS AND PIECES OF THIS ATTACK
THAT WAS USED IN PREVIOUS
ATTACKS THAT THE NORTH KOREANS
HAD A HAND IN.
YOU TALKED ABOUT THE SONY
PICTURES DEBACLE.
WE THINK THE NORTH KOREANS WERE
INVOLVED IN THE BANGLADESH
SENTRA BANK ATTACK AND ANOTHER
POLAND BANK ATTACK.
SO IF YOU LOOK AT THE DATA, YOU
SEE THE SAME FINGERPRINT,
USUALLY LEADS YOU TO THE SAME
CONCLUSION.
PEOPLE CAN FAKE DATA AND CHANGE
THINGS AROUND AROUND MAKE THINGS
LOOK LIKE SOMETHING ELSE.
BUT ENOUGH DATA POINTS SUGGEST
THAT THE NORTH KOREANS HAD SOME
HAND IN THIS.
>> Shepard: IF THEY HAD DONE
THIS IN A PHYSICAL WAY, IN OTHER
WORDS, USING HUMANS, GOING TO
THE DIFFERENT COUNTRIES TO DO
WHAT THEY'RE ALLEGED TO HAVE
DONE IN A CYBER WAY, THAT MIGHT
BE CONSIDERED AN ACT OF PRETTY
EXTREME AGGRESSION.
SOME MIGHT TREND TOWARDS AN ACT
OF WAR.
WHY IS THIS NOT?
>> WELL, BECAUSE CYBER IS A
STRANGE THING.
EVEN THOUGH WE'VE HAD THE
INTERNET FOR SEVERAL DECADES
NOW, WE DON'T THINK OF IT IN WAR
CONCEPT.
WE TALK NORTH KOREA AND THEIR
NUCLEAR WEAPONS PROGRAMS, THE
MISSILE CAPABILITIES.
WE DON'T TALK ABOUT THEIR
CHEMICAL AND BIOLOGICAL WEAPONS
ALL AIMED AT SOUTH KOREA.
THE THING ABOUT CYBER IS,
THERE'S NO DISTANT ISSUE HERE.
IF YOU FIRE A MISSILE, YOU HAVE
TO MAKE TO IT JAPAN OR SOUTH
KOREA.
ON CYBER, THEY'RE INSIDE THE
GATE.
DOESN'T MATTER WHETHER HERE IN
THE UNITED STATES OR DOING
THINGS ELSEWHERE.
YOU ARE HERE.
>> Shepard: THANKS, AKI.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Shepard: TURKEY'S PRESIDENT
SAYS HIS COUNTRY IS LOOKING FOR
A NEW BEGINNING TO RELATIONS
WITH THE UNITED STATES.
THE COMMENTS CAME DURING THE
TURKISH PRESIDENT'S MEETING WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP AT THE WHITE
HOUSE AND COMES AFTER THE
PENTAGON WENT AGAINST OBJECTIONS
TO ARM KURDISH FIGHTERS.
TURKEY SAYS THEY HAVE LINKS TO
TERRORISM.
THE TURKS CALLED THE KURDS
TERRORIST.
PENTAGON OFFICIALS SAY THEY NEED
HELP FROM THE KURDS TO TAKE OVER
RAQQA.
IN OTHER WORDS, ONE COUNTRY'S
TERRORISTS IS ANOTHER COUNTRY'S
ALLIES.
SO IT IS WITH THE KURDS AND WITH
THE TURKS.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT HAS REFUSED
TO EXTRA DIET A TURKISH CLERIC
IN PENNSYLVANIA WHO THE TURKISH
PRESIDENT SAID WAS BEHIND A COUP
LAST YEAR.
RICH EDSON HAS MORE.
>> THE PRESIDENT CONGRATULATED
PRESIDENT TRUMP FOR WHAT HE SAID
WAS A LEGENDARY TRIUMPH THAT HE
GARNERED IN THE AFTERER MATH OF
THE ELECTION.
DESPITE THE PRICE, THE
COMPLIMENTS AND THE LONG WORKING
RELATIONSHIP WITH TURKEY AND THE
UNITED STATES, THE ALLIANCE IS
SHOWING STRESS LATELY.
THE U.S.'S REFUSAL TO EXTRADITE
THE CLERIC THAT TURKEY HOLDS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THE COUP ATTEMPT
AND THE U.S.'S COUNTED SUPPORT
OF THE KURDS FIGHTING ISIS.
>>  TURKEY IS ALSO TRYING TO
NEGOTIATE A PEACE IN SYRIA AND
DOING SO WITH IRAN AND RUSSIA.
THE UNITED STATES IS OBSERVING
THE TALKS AND VIEWS THEM WITH
SKEPTICISM.
PRESIDENT TRUMP RECEIVED
CRITICISM FROM HUMAN RIGHTS
GROUPS FROM THE INVITATION OF
PRESIDENT TO HOST HIM AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HE SAID HE'S IMPRISONED HIS
POLITICAL OPPONENTS.
HUMAN RIGHTS HAVE CRITICIZED THE
PRESIDENT FOR A MEETING LAST
MIGHT WITH EGYPTIAN.
SISI AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE PRESIDENT SAID HE WOULD MEET
WITH KIM JONG-UN, THE NORTH
KOREAN DICTATOR AND ALSO INVITED
DUTARTE FROM PHILIPPINES.
>> Shepard: THANKS, RICH.
THE NEXT "PIRATES OF THE
CARIBBEAN" MOVIE IS SUPPOSED TO
COME OUT NEXT WEEK.
BUT PIRATES ARE HOLDING THE
MOVIE HOSTAGE.
THEIR DEMANDS TO DISNEY COMING
UP.
CONTROL MY TYPE 2 DIABETES.
MY A1C WASN'T WERE
IT NEEDED TO BE.
SO I LIKED WHEN
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
THAT I MAY REACH MY BLOOD
SUGAR AND A1C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE MY BODY TO
DO WHAT IT'S SUPPOSE TO DO,
RELEASE ITS OWN INSULIN.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE A LUMP OR
SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
SEVERE PAIN IN
YOUR STOMACH,
OR SYMPTOMS SUCH AS ITCHING,
RASH, OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS,
WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN,
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS WORSE.
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY MAY HELP
ME REACH MY BLOOD SUGAR GOALS.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING
YOUR A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR,
ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
Buttrust Angie's List to help.,
[ Barks ]
Visit angieslist.com today.
♪
To err is human.
To anticipate is Lexus.
Experience the Lexus RX
with Advanced Safety standard.
Experience amazing.
Yeah, 'cause I got ALLSTATE.?
IF YOU TOTAL YOUR NEW BIKE,
THEY REPLACE IT WITH A
BRAND NEW ONE.
So, kinda like your
second husband.
KINDA.
IT'S GOOD TO BE IN
(GOOD HANDS).
>> Shepard: FEDERAL
INVESTIGATORS ARE WANTING TO
FIND OUT WHAT CAUSED A JET TO
CRASH TO THE GROUND OUTSIDE AN
AIRPORT OUTSIDE NEW YORK CITY
YESTERDAY.
POLICE SAY IT WAS A LEER 35.
TWO CREWS ON BOARD.
BOTH DIED.
THIS IMAGE FROM SURVEILLANCE
CAMERA NEAR THE CRASH.
YOU CAN SEE THE PLACE NOSE DIVED
AND ON ITS SIDE.
THE IMPACT SENT A FIREBALL INTO
THE SKY.
FIREFIGHTERS SAY IT TOOK ABOUT
AN HOUR TO PUT OUT THE FLAMES.
THE AIRPORT CLOSED DOWN FOR
HOURS.
MORE PICTURES HERE.
THESE ARE FROM THE SCENE HERE.
CREWS ON THE SCENE.
THE PLANE RUSHED TO AN
INDUSTRIAL AREA IN NEW JERSEY.
IT MISSED THE PUBLIC WORKS
BUILDING AND ALL THE STAFF HAD
GONE HOME FOR THE DAY
THANKFULLY.
THIS IS THE PUBLIC WORKS
BILLING.
YOU CAN SEE THE FIRE HOSE
WASHING DOWN THE BUILDING.
TOWN SUPERVISORS SAID FOLKS
DESCRIBED HEARING POPPING SOUNDS
IN THE FIRE AFTER THE CRASH.
A COUPLE CARS HERE LATE WASTE.
INVESTIGATORS SAY IT DAMAGED 13
VEHICLES IN ALL.
FIREFIGHTERS LOOKING OVER THE
SCENE.
POSSIBLY ONE OF THE ENGINES.
TWO PEOPLE DIED.
EVERYBODY ON THE GROUND OKAY.
HACKERS SAY THEY HAVE STOLEN THE
NEXT INSTALLMENT OF ONE OF
DISNEY'S NEXT FRANCHISES AND
HOLDING IT FOR RANSOM.
HACKERS CLAIM TO HAVE "PIRATES
OF THE CARIBBEAN: DEAD MAN TELL
NO TALES."
IT'S KIND OF A BIG DEAL.
ACCORDING TO REPORTS, THE
HACKERS WILL RELEASE THE MOVIE
IN SEGMENTS IF DISNEY DOESN'T
PAY.
BUT THIS DOESN'T HAVE ANYTHING
TO DO WITH THE CYBER ATTACKS ALL
OVER THE WORLD?
>> NO, SHEP.
IN THE DISNEY CASE, HACKERS MADE
THEIR WAY INTO A COMPUTER THAT
HELD A DIGITAL COPY OF "PIRATES
OF THE CARIBBEAN 5."
IT WAS A DISNEY COMPUTER BUT
COULD HAVE BEEN STOLEN FROM A
THIRD PARTY COMPANY INVOLVED IN
THE PRODUCTION OF THE FILM.
THE AMOUNT OF THE RANSOM IS
UNDISCLOSED BUT SAID TO BE
"ENORMOUS" AND THE HACKERS WANT
IT PAID IN BITCOIN, WHICH IS
HARDER TO TRACE.
THE HACKERS THAT LIFTED THE
PIRATES IS APPARENTLY GETTING
MORE DIFFICULT.
"PIRATES OF THE CARIBBEAN" IS
SUPPOSED TO BE KICKING OFF THE
SUMMER MOVIE SEASON NO LATELY
TARGETING ENTERTAINMENT
COMPANIES IS ALL THE RAGE.
>> YEAH.
A BUNCH OF THEM.
NETFLIX GOT HACKED BY "THE DARK
OVER-LORD."
ALL TEN EPISODES OF "ORANGE OF
THE NEW BLACK" WAS TAKEN.
THE THREAT WAS SIMILAR.
PAY A RANSOM OR ELSE.
THE DARK OVER-LORD CLAIMS TO
UNRELEASE TV SHOWS FROM OTHER
NETWORKS, INCLUDING BIG FOX BUT
NONE OF THOSE NETWORKS ARE
RESPONDING.
A FEW YEARS AGO, "THE
EXPANDIBLES 3" GOT HACKED AND
RELEASED BEFORE THEIR DEBUT AND
BOMBED AT THE BOX OFFICE.
EXPERTS DON'T KNOW IF IT WAS
BOMBED BY MILLIONS ONLINE OR
BECAUSE THE CRITICS SAID IT WAS
AWFUL.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: TRACE GALLAGHER IN
LOS ANGELES.
THANK YOU.
AHEAD, THE LATE NIGHT FUNNY MAN
CONAN O'BRIEN IS HEADED TO COURT
ACCUSED OF STEALING JOKES.
WE'LL TAKE YOU TO TRASH ISLAND.
A LITTLE PLACE IN THE OCEAN WITH
NO PEOPLE AND MILLIONS AND
MILLIONS OF PIECES OF PLASTIC.
THAT'S NEXT.
>> Shepard: A SHERIFF'S DEPUTY
DIED IN A SHOOTOUT DURING A
TRAFFIC STOP IN MONTANA.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO INVESTIGATOR
THERE'S WHO SAY IT HAPPENED NEAR
THREE FORKS ABOUT 50 MILES SOUTH
OF HELENA, THE CAPITOL.
DISPATCHERS SAY THEY LOST
CONTACT WITH THE DEPUTY AS HE
FOLLOWED A VEHICLE.
OFFICERS SAY THEY FOUND HIM DEAD
BY THE SIDE OF THE ROAD.
HIGHWAY PATROL SPOTTED THE
SUSPECT'S VEHICLES AWAY IN
ANACONDA.
OFFICERS PUT DOWN SPIKE STRIPS
BUT KEPT GOING.
WHEN THE VEHICLE FINALLY
STOPPED, THE PASSENGER STARTED
FIRING AND SOMEONE SHOT HIM.
IN NEW YORK, INVESTIGATORS ARE
LOOKING TO THE SHOOTING OF THE
POLICE CHIEF IN THE VILLAGE OF
MAYBROOK, NEW YORK, ABOUT 50
MILES NORTH OF THE BIG CITY.
POLICE SAY THE CHIEF IS EXPECTED
TO SURVIVE.
LOCAL MEDIA REPORT THE SUSPECT
DIED IN A SHOOTOUT WITH PLACE
AFTER BARRICADING HIMSELF IN A
HOME FOR HOURS.
CONAN O'BRIEN SET TO GO ON
TRIAL.
ACCUSATIONS HE STOLE SOMEONE'S
JOKES.
THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY IN AN DIG
A HAS REFUSED TO THROW OUT A
FEDERAL COPYRIGHT INFRINGEMENT
LAWSUIT.
COMEDY WRITER CLAIMS HE POSTED
THE JOKES ONLINE AND O'BRIEN
LATER USED THEM ALMOST WORD FOR
WORD ON HIS LATE NIGHT SHOW.
THE LAWYERS HERE ARE COMPARING
HIT ONLINE POSTS TO TIME STAMPED
E-MAILS WITH WRITERS OF THE SHOW
TO PROVE THE CASE.
O'BRIEN'S COMPANY AND TBS HAVE
DENIED THE ALLEGATION SAYING THE
MATERIAL WAS ORIGINAL.
IF YOU EVER TOSSED TRASH IN THE
OCEAN, A DECENT CHANCE THAT
SCIENTISTS KNOW WHERE IT WENT.
AN ISLAND THAT WOULD BE A
TROPICAL PARADISE IS FULL OF 38
MILLION PIECES OF GARBAGE AND NO
PEOPLE.
>> NO.
IT'S PROBABLY HARD TO FIND A
PLACE MORE REMOTE THAN THIS.
HENDERSON ISLAND, HALFWAY
BETWEEN NEW ZEALAND AND CHILE --
>> Shepard: MIDDLE OF NOWHERE.
>> YEAH, IT IS.
SIX MILES LONG, THREE MILES WIDE
AND COVERED IN TRASH.
38 MILLION PEOPLES IS WHAT
RESEARCHERS ARE ESTIMATING.
THEY SAY MORE WASHES UP
DAY.
>> Shepard: WHY HERE?
>> THE OCEAN CURRENTING CONVERGE
IN THAT AREA.
IT ACTS LIKE A SONG.
THE FLOATING PIECES OF PLASTIC
GET STUCK.
THERE'S A HIGHER DENSITY OF
TRASH HERE MORE THAN ANYWHERE IN
THE WORLD.
THIS HAS HAD A NEGATIVE EFFECT
ON THE WILDLIFE THERE.
THE POOR CRAB HERE.
THAT'S NOT WHAT SHOULD THEY LOOK
LIKE.
>> Shepard: YEAH.
SHOULD LOOK LIKE DINNER.
THAT ABE RIGHT.
>> Shepard: ANYTHING OTHER THAN
PLASTIC TO EAT SAID CRAB DINNER.
SOMEBODY SHOULD CLEAN IT UP.
>> IT'S HARD TO DO.
IT'S SO FAR AWAY.
IT'S ABOUT 3,000 MILES TO THE
NEXT POPULATED CITY.
SO IT'S TOUGH TO GET SUPPLIES
THERE AND THEN TO GET SUPPLIES
OFF OF THERE.
>> Shepard: RISING SEE WILL
PROBABLY WATCH IT AWAY.
>> AND THEN GO TO THE ARCTIC,
WHICH IS ALSO A MESS?
THANKS, LILLY.
WE'LL BE BACK WITH A FIRST LOOK
AT THE WOMAN TO MAKE TO IT THE
TOP OF THE WORLD AND HAPPENED ON
THIS DAY IN HISTORY.
(VO) Gentlemen,
Beggin' Skinny Strips or
Beggin' Black Label?
There's two?!
Now this is a delicious dilemma!
Introducing New Beggin' Strips
Premium Edition.
TWWWOOOOOO?!?!
With real meat as
ingredient one.
Everything to your liking?
Mmm Mmmmm...
New Beggin' Strips Premium.
Becaussssseeee Beggin'!
>> Shepard: BREAKING NEWS.
MEMBERS OF THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE MINUTES
AWAY FROM A CLOSED DOOR MEETING
WITH MIKE POMPEO.
THEY'RE EXPECTED TO ASK ABOUT
THE HIGHLY CLASSIFIED
INTELLIGENCE LAST WEEK DURING A
MEETING WITH THE RUSSIAN FOREIGN
MINISTER AND U.S. AMBASSADOR
COMING UP MOMENTS FROM NOW.
ON THIS DAY IN 1975, THE FIRST
WOMAN CONQUERED MOUNT EVEREST AT
30,000 FEET.
SHE WAS FIVE FEET TALL AND 90
POUNDS.
ABOUT A THIRD OF THE WAY UP THE
MOUNTAIN, AN AVALANCHE KNOCKED
HER OUT FOR A WHILE AND BURIED
THE GROUP'S CAMP.
SHE LEFT THE TEAM AT THE CAMP
AND 12 DAYS LATER REACHED THE
SUMMIT STANDING ON TOP OF THE
WORLD 42 YEARS AGO TODAY.
SHOULD NEWS BREAK OUT, WE'LL
BREAK IN.
BREAKING NEWS CHANGES EVERYTHING
ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
"YOUR WORLD" WITH NEIL CAVUTO IS
COMING UP WITH BREAKING NEW
RIGHT NOW.
>> WHAT THE PRESIDENT DISCUSSED
WITH THE FOREIGN MINISTER WAS
WHOLLY APPROPRIATE.
>> WHAT THE PRESIDENT DID WAS
TOTALLY OUTRAGEOUS.
>> YOU MAY NOT LIKE THIS
PRESIDENT, MAY NOT LIKE WHAT
HE'S DOING.
>> RUSSIA IS NOT OUR FRIEND.
THE PRESIDENT NEEDS TO EXERCISE
DISCIPLINE WHEN TALKING TO
LEADERS.
>> THE PRESIDENT IN NO WAY
COMPROMISED ANY SOURCES OR
METHODS IN THE COURSE OF THIS
CONVERSATION.
>> IT'S EXTREMELY CONCERNING.
A REASON WHY INFORMATION IS
CLASSIFIED.
>> NATIONAL SECURITY IS AT RISK.
BY THIS LEAK AND LEAKS LIKE IT.
>>