LIVE TOMORROW NIGHT
TALKING ABOUT ALL THE
THINGS WE HAVE BEEN TALKING
ABOUT AS OUR PRYING EYES
SERIES AS WELL.
THAT IS IT FOR THIS
"SPECIAL REPORT," FAIR,
BALANCED AND STILL
UNAFRAID.
>> Shepard: THIS IS "THE
FOX REPORT."
TONIGHT SURGERY HAPPENING
NOW FOR THE 10-YEAR-OLD
GIRL AT THE CENTER OF
CONTROVERSY OVER TRANSPLANT
POLICY.
PLUS, NEW FROM THE LEAKER.
ED SNOWDEN SAYS THE U.S. IS
WAGING CYBER WAR ON CHINA,
HAS BEEN FOR YEARS AND HE
CAN PROVE IT.
EDWARD SNOWDEN REPORTEDLY
CLAIMS THE U.S. HAS BEEN
HACKING CHINESE COMPUTERS
FOR YEARS.
NOW HE SAYS HE IS READY TO
FACE JUSTICE IN HONG KONG.
>> I THINK THE U.S.
GOVERNMENT WILL GO AFTER
HIM.
>> Shepard: AND LAWMAKERS
GET A CHANCE TO QUESTION
THE HEAD OF THE NSA.
>> THE NSA OBTAINED PHONE
RECORDS OF MILLIONS OF
INNOCENT AMERICANS WITH NO
CONNECTION TO TERRORISM.
>> IF DOZEN OF TERRORIST
EVENTS THAT THESE ARE
HELPED PREVENT.
>> Shepard: PLUS, THE
LITTLE GIRL WHO WON HER
FIGHT FOR AN ADULT LUNG
TRANSPLANT FINALLY GETS THE
SURGERY THAT COULD SAVE HER
LIFE.
BUT FIRST FROM FOX THIS
WEDNESDAY NIGHT, THE NSA
LEAKER HAS APPARENTLY
RESURFACED.
SOMEWHERE IN HONG KONG ED
SNOWDEN REPORTEDLY SPOKE
WITH THE SOUTH CHINA
MORNING POST NEWSPAPER
TODAY AND CLAIMS THE UNITED
STATES HAS BEEN HACKING
CHINA'S COMPUTERS FOR
YEARS.
HE SAYS THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
HAS TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
SPY OPERATIONS GOING ON
AROUND THE WORLD RIGHT NOW,
61000 TO BE EXACT.
AND JUST HOURS AFTER THE
NEW SNOWDEN INTERVIEW
POPPED UP IN THE PAPER, THE
HEAD OF THE SECRETIVE
NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY
TESTIFIED ON CAPITOL HILL.
GENERAL KEITH ALEXANDER
SAYS GOVERNMENT
SURVEILLANCE PROGRAMS HAVE
HELPED PREVENT DOZENS OF
TERROR ATTACKS.
THE SENATORS DID NOT OBJECT
TO MONITORING SPECIFIC
TERRORIST SUSPECTS.
SOME DID ASK WHY IS THE
GOVERNMENT STOCKPILING THE
PHONE RECORDS OF MILLIONS
OF INNOCENT AMERICANS?
>> IF YOU KNEW THAT A
SUSPECT HAD MADE A CALL
INTO AREA CODE 312, THE
CITY OF CHICAGO, IT
CERTAINLY DEFIES LOGIC THAT
YOU NEED TO COLLECT AWFUL
OF THE TELEPHONE CALLS MADE
IN THE 312 AREA CODE ON THE
CHANCE THAT ONE OF THOSE
PERSONS MIGHT BE ON THE
OTHER END OF THE PHONE.
>> SO WHAT HAPPENS IF YOU
DON'T KNOW HE IS IN 312
YET?
BECAUSE WE HAD STORED THAT
DATA IN A DATABASE WE
COULD TAKE THAT NUMBER AND
GO BACKWARDS IN TIME AND
SEE WHO HE WAS TALKING TO.
>> Shepard: GENERAL
ALEXANDER SAYS HE WANTS TO
DECLASSIFY SOME OF THE
INFORMATION SO HE CAN TELL
ALL THE US ABOUT HOW THE
SURVEILLANCE WORKS.
HE SAYS IF THE GOVERNMENT
RELEASES TOO MANY DETAILS,
QUOTE:  AMERICANS WILL DIE.
LOTS TO COVER ON THIS.
SO TEAM FOX COVERAGE, TRACE
GALLAGHER WITH BRAND NEW
COMMENTS FROM THE NSA
LEAKER.
FIRST LET'S GET TO
CATHERINE HERRIDGE LIVE IN
WASHINGTON.
WHAT ELSE DID WE LEARN AT
THESE HEARINGS TODAY,
CATHERINE.
>> SHEP, WHILE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE LEADERSHIP AND
OFFICIALS CLAIM THE
SWEEPING COLLECTION OF DATA
DISRUPTED A 2009 PLOT
TARGETING THE NEW YORK CITY
SUBWAY SYSTEM BY BULL AZAZI
CONCEDED TO PATRICK LEAHY
THAT WAS SIMPLY NOT THE
CASE.
THE LEAD CAME FROM FOREIGN
SOURCES.
>> WITH A 702 SET OF
INFORMATION, BASED ON
OPERATIVES OVERSEAS WE SAW
CONNECTIONS INTO A PERSON
IN COLORADO.
THAT WAS PASSED TO THE FBI.
>> AND WHILE ALEXANDER SAID
THE DRILLDOWN ON AMERICAN
CITIZENS MUST BE CLEARED BY
A NATIONAL SECURITY COURT,
SENATORS SAYING IT WASN'T
ENOUGH GIVEN THE PERVASIVE
ENVIRONMENT OF MISTRUST.
>> THE AMERICAN PUBLIC IS
FEARFUL THAT IN THIS
MASSIVE AMOUNT OF DATA YOU
GET, THAT THERE IS THE
ABILITY OF THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT TO SYNTHESIZE
THAT DATA AND LEARN
SOMETHING MORE.
>> ON THURSDAY, A RARE
BRIEFING OF THE FULL SENATE
ON THE NSA DATA COLLECTION
PROGRAMS ALEXANDER WILL
TESTIFY AGAIN.
THIS SESSION IS CLASSIFIED
AND CLOSED TO THE PUBLIC
SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE,
TODAY WE LEARNED THE DEPUTY
DIRECTOR OF THE CIA
RESIGNED.
>> WELL, THAT'S RIGHT.
MIKE MORELL AFTER 33 YEARS
WITH THE AGENCY.
IT WAS MADE SOME TIME AGO.
HE WAS CENTER HE OF THE
TALKING POINTS CONTROVERSY.
THE ADMINISTRATION
ULTIMATELY BLAMED THE CIA
FOR PROVIDING BAD
INFORMATION TO THEN
AMBASSADOR SUSAN RICE WHO
BLAMED A DEMONSTRATION THAT
SPUN OUT OF CONTROL FOR THE
TERRORIST ATTACK.
MORE RELATIVE'S MORRELL'S
REPLACEMENT WITH THE
PRESIDENT.
HAINES APPARENTLY HAS NO
EXPERIENCE AT THE CIA BUT
SERVED AS DEPUTY ASSISTANT
TO THE PRESIDENT AND LEGAL
ADVISOR TO THE NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNCIL.
THE TAKE AWAY IS THAT
MORRELL'S RESIGNATION IS
NOT AT ALL CONNECTED TO
THESE NSA SCANDALS, SHEP.
>> Shepard: CATHERINE
HERRIDGE IN WASHINGTON
TONIGHT.
THE NSA DIRECTOR IS ALSO
DEBUNKING ONE OF SNOWDEN'S
PREVIOUS CLAIMS.
HERE, REMEMBER THIS?
>> I SITTING AT MY DESK
CERTAINLY HAVE THE
AUTHORITIES TO WIRETAP
ANYONE FROM YOU OR YOUR
ACCOUNTANT TO IT A FEDERAL
JUDGE TO EVEN THE
PRESIDENT.
>> FALSE.
I KNOW OF NO WAY TO DO
THAT.
>> Shepard: WELL NOW AS I
REPORTED AT THE TOP OF THIS
NEWSCAST ED SNOWDEN IS
APPARENTLY MAKING NEW
CLAIMS ABOUT THE U.S.
ATTACKING CHINESE
COMPUTERS.
QUOTING:  WE HACK NETWORK
BACK BONES LIKE HUGE
INTERNET ROUTERS THAT GIVE
US ACCESS TO HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF COMPUTERS
WITHOUT HAVING TO HACK
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF THEM.
ED SNOWDEN SAYS HUNDREDS OF
THOSE HACKING TARGETS ARE
IN HONG KONG AND CHINA'S
MAINLAND INCLUDING
UNIVERSITY STUDENTS AND
PUBLIC OFFICIALS.
THE SOUTH CHINA MORNING
POST NEWSPAPER REPORTS
SNOWDEN PROVIDED UNVERIFIED
DOCUMENTS TO PROVE HIS
STORY.
LET'S CONTINUE TEAM FOX
COVERAGE WITH TRACE
GALLAGHER IN OUR WEST COAST
NEWS HUB.
DOES HE EXPLAIN WHY HE
ACCUSED THE UNITED STATES
OF TARGETING COMPUTERS ALL
OVER THE WORLD?
>> WELL BECAUSE HE SAYS
THAT AMERICA HAS LONG SAID
THAT IT DOES NOT TARGET
CIVILIAN INFRASTRUCTURE
UNLIKE ITS ADVERSARIES,
SHEP.
HE CALLS THAT BLATANT
HYPOCRISY SAYING AND I'M
QUOTING HERE, NOT ONLY DOES
IT DO SO BUT IT IS SO
AFRAID OF IT BEING KNOWN
THAT IT IS WILLING TO USE
ANY MEANS SUCH AS
DIPLOMATIC INTIMIDATION TO
PREVENT THIS INFORMATION
FROM BECOMING PUBLIC MUCH
THE STATE DEPARTMENT WAS
ASKED TODAY ABOUT TARGETING
FOREIGN COMPUTERS AND
RESPONDED THIS WAY.
LISTEN.
>> THERE IS A DIFFERENCE
BETWEEN, YOU KNOW GOING
AFTER ECONOMIC DATA AND
FINANCIAL INFORMATION, THAT
IS PART OF THE CYBER
ATTACKS.
OR SEEMS TO BE.
AND AN ISSUE WHICH THE
PRESIDENT WELCOMES THE
DEBATE ON AND THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS WELCOMED
THE DEBATE ON WHICH IS
SURVEILLANCE.
AND GOING AFTER PEOPLE WHO
MEAN TO DO HARM.
>>
>> SO HER RESPONSE WASN'T
EXACTLY CRYSTAL CLEAR
SHEP.
EVEN EDWARD SNOWDEN ADMITS
HE HAS NO INFORMATION AT
ALL ABOUT ANY CHINESE
MILITARY TECHNOLOGY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: HE SAYS THAT HE
CAN LEAVE HONG KONG ANY
TIME HE WANTS TO.
>> YEAH, HE SAID HE HAD
MANY OPPORTUNITIES TO FLEE
BUT, INSTEAD, HE DECIDED TO
STAY AND FIGHT.
AND IN THIS INTERVIEW WITH
THE CHINESE NEWSPAPER HE
IS CLEARLY TRYING TO PAINT
HIMSELF AS THE GOOD GUY
HERE.
SAYING TO THE NEWSPAPER,
AND I'M QUOTING AGAIN:
LAST WEEK THE AMERICAN
GOVERNMENT HAPPILY OPERATED
IN THE SHADOWS WITH NO
RESPECT FOR THE CONSENT OF
THE GOVERNED.
BUT NO LONGER.
EVERY LEVEL OF SOCIETY IS
DEMANDINGLITY
AND OVERSIGHT.
FOR NOW, HE IS STILL IN
HIDING BUT FORMER CIA AGENT
MIKE BAKER SAYS NOT FOR
LONG.
>> EVEN FOR SOMEONE WHO IS
TRAINED.
EVEN FOR SOMEONE WHO HAS
BEEN IN OPERATIONS FOR A
LONG TIME, JUST
DISAPPEARING, GOING OFF THE
RADAR SCREEN ENTIRELY IS A
VERY DIFFICULT PROCESS.
IT'S MORE DIFFICULT WHEN
YOU NOW HAVE BEEN IN THE
MEDIA AND EVERYBODY KNOWS
YOUR FACE AND YOUR
BACKGROUND STORY.
MIKE BAKER ALSO BELIEVES AS
SOON AS THE UNITED STATES
WANTS HIM THEY WILL GET
HIM.
SHEP?
>> TRACE THAT NEWSPAPER
THE SOUTH CHINA POST
REPORTS IT CONTACTED THE
U.S. CONSULATE IN HONG KONG
FOR A RESPONSE TO ED
SNOWDEN'S CLAIMS BUT IT WAS
CLOSED FOR A CHINESE
HOLIDAY.
ACCORDING TO A CONSULATE
WEB SITE IT CLOSES FOR
CHINESE AND AMERICAN
HOLIDAYS.
FOX URGENT NOW WE ARE
EXPECTING TO HEAR AT ANY
MOMENT NOW HOW THE SURGERY
WENT FOR THE YOUNG GIRL WHO
IS FINALLY GETTING THE
LUNGS SHE SO DESPERATELY
NEEDS.
DOCTORS BEGAN THE
TRANSPLANT SURGERY ON
10-YEAR-OLD SARAH THIS
AFTERNOON.
WE ARE TOLD A MARATHON
OPERATION SHOULD BE OVER
SOON.
LITTLE SARAH BECAME THE
FACE OF THE DEBATE OVER
RULES FOR TRANSPLANTS IN
CHILDREN.
RULES THAT REQUIRE KIDS TO
BE AT LEAST 12 YEARS OLD TO
RECEIVE ADULT ORGANS OR BE
ON THE LIST.
DOCTORS SAY RULES ARE
OUTDATED MEDICAL ADVANCES
DOCTORS CAN MAKE ADULT
LUNGS TO WORK FOR CHILDREN
LIKE SARAH.
A JUDGE PUT HER THE ADULT
WAITING LIST AND NOT A
MOMENT TOO SOON.
OVER THE WEEKEND SARAH'S
PARENTS SAID HER CONDITION
WAS GETTING WORSE AND FAST.
SHE WENT INTO A COMA.
THE JUDGE'S ORDERS MAY HAVE
COME TOO LATE BUT ALL OF A
SUDDEN THIS HAPPENED.
HER FAMILY POSTING TO
FACEBOOK GOD IS GREAT.
HE MOVED THE MOUNTAIN
SARAH GOT THE CALL.
TODAY IS THE START OF
SARAH'S NEW BEGINNING AND
NEW LIFE.
DOCTORS STARTED THE
OPERATION AND AS THEY DID
SARAH'S MOTHER LEFT THE
HOSPITAL TO UPDATE
REPORTERS.
SHE TALKED ABOUT THE MOMENT
THE SURGEONS WIELD HER
DAUGHTER AWAY.
>> I'M NOT SURE HOW MUCH
SHE IS UNDERSTANDING ME.
I KISSED HER GOOD BY.
IT WAS EASIER WAY TO SAY
GOODBYE TO HER THAN IF SHE
WERE AWAKE AND SCARED.
WE HAD NO OTHER OPTION, NO
OTHER OUT.
WE HAD VERY LIMITED TIME
AND THIS IS JUST LIKE A
BLESSING FROM GOD.
I FEEL LIKE JUST IT CAME AT
JUST THE LAST MINUTE AND WE
WOULDN'T HAVE MADE IT MUCH
LONGER.
>> Shepard: THE SARAH
WOULDN'T HAVE MADE IT AT
ALL WITHOUT THE JUDGE'S
RULING.
THE LUNG CAME FROM AN ADULT
THE VERY TYPE THE RULES
WOULD NOT ALLOW HER TO
HAVE.
MOLLY HAS BEEN FOLLOWING
UPDATES ON THIS ALL DAY.
WHAT ARE YOU LEARNING.
>> SARAH WAS IN A MEDICALLY
INDUCED COMA GOING INTO THE
SURGERY TODAY BECAUSE OF
HER END STAGE SESSION STICK
FIBROSIS.
HER MOTHER SAYS IT MAY BE A
BIT MORE DIFFICULT POST
SURGERY.
THE RECOVERY FOR HER.
THE DOCTORS WILL BE
WATCHING SARAH VERY
CAREFULLY TO SEE IF
HOPEFULLY HER BODY WILL
ACCEPT THE DONOR ADULT
LUNGS.
SO SHE STILL HAS A LONG WAY
TO GO.
AND THE MURAHAN FAMILY SAYS
WHILE THEY CELEBRATE THE
LIFE FOR SARAH THEY ALSO
RECOGNIZE IT WAS THE END OF
ANOTHER LIFE'S, THE
DONOR'S.
>> I'M SO GRATEFUL THAT THE
FAMILY IN THIS TRAGEDY OF
THEIRS MADE THIS DECISION
AND THEY ARE SUCH A
BLESSING TO US AND, YOU
KNOW, SARAH WILL JUST --
SHE WILL TAKE GOOD CARE OF
THESE LUNGS AND BE A LEGACY
OF THESE LOVED ONES.
>> GETTING ON THE ADULT
WAITING LIST AS SARAH WAS
ABLE TO DO BECAUSE OF THAT
FEDERAL JUDGE'S ORDER LAST
WEEK IS SO IMPORTANT TO
YOUNG PATIENTS AWAITING
TRANSPLANTS BECAUSE
HUNDREDS EVEN THOUSAND
MORE ADULT LUNGS BECOME
AVAILABLE EACH YEAR
COMPARED TO PEDIATRIC
LUNGS, SHEP?
>> Shepard: MOLLY AS WE
HAVE BEEN REPORTING HERE
THERE IS ANOTHER SICK CHILD
ON THE ADULT WAITING LIST
THANKS TO THE JAIL-TIME
JUDGE'S ORDER.
HIS NAME IS JAVIER ACCOSTA
HE IS 11 AND LIKE SARAH HE
IS DYING FROM CYSTIC PHI
FIBROSIS.
HIS BROTHER DIED TWO YEARS
AGO WHILE HE WAS WAITING
FOR A LUNG TRANSPLANT.
TONIGHT HE IS STILL
WAITING.
HOW MUCH DO YOU TRUST THE
U.S. GOVERNMENT?
SOME NEW FOX NEWS POLLS
SHOW HE THAT HALF OF
AMERICANS DO NOT HAVE FAITH
IN ELECTED OFFICIALS IN
D.C.
WE WILL BREAK DOWN WHAT
THAT MEANS FOR THE
PRESIDENT AND OTHERS AS THE
PRESIDENT ANSWERS TOUGH
QUESTIONS ABOUT GOVERNMENT
SURVEILLANCE, THE IRS, AND
SO MUCH MORE.
PLUS, AN UNUSUALLY MASSIVE
LINE OF STORMS COULD EFFECT
AS MANY AS ONE IN FIVE
AMERICANS TONIGHT.
FIRST ALERT FORECASTERS ARE
WARNING CHICAGO,
INDIANAPOLIS, CLEVELAND,
AND MANY OTHER CITIES TO
WATCH OUT.
WE WILL GET A LIVE UPDATE
FROM THE EXTREME WEATHER
CENTER AND THE REST OF THE
NEWS FROM THE JOURNALISTS
OF FOX NEWS ON THIS
WEDNESDAY FOX REPORT.
SENDS A CHECK.  SILENCE.  ARE YOU
IN GOOD HANDS?  THE Kyocera Torque
LETS YOU HEAR AND BE HEARD  EVEN IN
STUPID LOUD PLACES.  TO PROVE IT,
WE SET UP  OUR CALL CENTER RIGHT HERE...
[ chirp ]  ALL GOOD?  [ chirp ]  GETTY
UP.
SERIOUSLY,  THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING!
[ cellphone rings ]  HELLO?  IT'S
A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.    [ Male
Announcer ] GET IT DONE  [ chirp ]
WITH THE ULTRAUGGED    ocera Torque
ONLY FROM Sprint   Direct Conct.
BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE    FOR YOUR
BUSINESS.
[ Male Announcer ]    ERICA HAD A
ROUGH DAY.    SHE GOT A PARKING TICKET...
♪ ♪    AND SHE FORGOT TO PAY    HER
CREDIT CARD BILL ON TIME.    GOOD
THING SHE'S GOT    THE CITI SIMPLICITY
CARD.    IT DOESN'T CHARGE LATE FEES
OR A PENALTY RATE. EVER.    AS IN
NEVER EVER.    NOW ABOUT THAT PARKING
TICKET.  [ grunting ]    [ Male Announcer
] TO APPLY    FOR THE CITI SIMPLICITY
CARD    GO TO CITI.COM/SIMPLICITY.
IT'S THE ONLY CARD THAT NEVER    HAS
LATE FEES, A PENALTY RATE,    OR AN
ANNUAL FEE, EVER.    SO APPLY TODAY.
FIRST QUESTION ASKED HOW
FOLKS FEEL ABOUT THE
COUNTRY'S POLITICAL
LEADERS.
71% SAY WE CAN DO BETTER.
MEASLY 71% SAY WE ARE
CONFIDENT AND PROUD.
HOW MUCH TRUST DO YOU HAVE
IN THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
>> 5% SAY THEY HAVE A GREAT
DEAL OF CONFIDENCE.
63% SAY EITHER NOT THAT
MUCH OR NOT AT ALL.
ED HENRY HAS THAT LIVE FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE.
ED?
>> WELL, SHEP OBVIOUSLY
THE BACK DROP FOR ALL OF
THIS IS THE PRESIDENT'S
POLITICAL STANDING AND THE
FACT THAT A LOT OF THESE
CONTROVERSIES LIKE THE IRS
TARGETING CONSERVATIVE
GROUPS HAS HELPED FUEL THIS
ANGER TOWARDS THE
GOVERNMENT.
LOOK AT THE SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAM AT THE NSA AS WELL
AND HOW THAT IS EFFECTING
THINGS.
WHEN WE ASKED WHETHER OR
NOT IT'S ACCEPTABLE
UNACCEPTABLE INVADES
PRIVACY 62%.
ACCEPTABLE, PREVENTS
TERRORISM WHICH IS THE CASE
THE PRESIDENT IS MAKING
ONLY 32% BUYING THAT RIGHT
NOW.
THE OTHER BIG STORY, OF
COURSE, THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT MONITORING
REPORTERS.
FOX NEWS JAMES ROSEN, THE
A.P. AND THEIR PHONE
RECORDS.
LOOK AT WHAT THE PUBLIC
THINKS ABOUT THAT.
WAS THIS DONE FOR POLITICAL
REASONS?
63%.
WAS IT DONOR FUTURE
REASONS ONLY 29%.
THAT IS PUTTING NEW
PRESSURE TONIGHT ON ERIC
HOLDER, THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
HE HAS BEEN IN THE MIDDLE
OF THIS STORM OBVIOUSLY.
WE ASKED IN THIS POLL WHAT
ABOUT ERIC HOLDER'S FUTURE?
ONLY 34% SAYING HE SHOULD
STAY ON THE JOB.
52% SAYING HE SHOULD
RESIGN.
SO A SMALL MAJORITY THERE.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS, WHAT
THESE CONTROVERSIES ADD UP
TO FOR THE PRESIDENT RIGHT
NOW IS A PUBLIC THAT WAS
ALREADY DISTRUSTFUL OF THE
GOVERNMENT MAYBE MORE SO
NOW BECAUSE OF THESE
CONTROVERSIES AND A
PRESIDENT TRYING TO GET THE
NATION'S ATTENTION ON
IMMIGRATION REFORM, A
BUDGET DEAL, OTHER THINGS
BEYOND THESE CONTROVERSIES,
SHEP.
>> Shepard: ED, ONE MORE
BIT OF POLLING, THE POLLS
SHOW THE MAJORITY OF
AMERICANS ARE NOT YET
SATISFIED WITH THE A SENSE
THEY HAVE HEARD REGARDING
THREE MAJOR CONTROVERSIES.
WHEN ASKED MORE THAN 70%
SAY THEY THINK CONGRESS
SHOULD CONTINUE TO
INVESTIGATE THE IRS, THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT AND
BENGHAZI RESPECTIVELY.
WELL, MULTIPLE WILDFIRES
FORCING THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
TO LEAVE THEIR HOMES BEHIND
IN COLORADO.
COMING UP A LIVE UPDATE AS
THE FLAMES RAGE THROUGH THE
ROCKIES.
BUT FIRST, A FOX WEATHER
ALERT.
ENORMOUS LINE OF SEVERE
WEATHER THAT HAS Pá(
THUNDERSTORMS FIRST ALERT
FORECAST FROM IOWA TO
MARYLAND.
THE CONDITIONS COULD EVENLY
SPAWN POTENTIALLY DEADLY
EVENT.
A TYPE OF FIERCE WIND STORM
THAT'S RARER THAN A TORNADO
BUT CAPABLE OF CAUSING
DAMAGE ON A MUCH WIDER
SCALE.
OUR CHIEF METEOROLOGIST
RICK REICHMUTH IN THE
EXTREME WHETHER OR NOT
TONIGHT RICK?
>> WE ONE OF THESE LAST
JUNE IN D.C. IF YOU
REMEMBER THAT BIG EVENT.
MAJOR POWER OUTAGES THAT
LASTED MORE THAN A WEEK.
A DERECHO IS WHAT WE CALL.
THIS WE THINK THAT'S GOING
TO DEVELOP TONIGHT.
RIGHT NOW A PARTICULARLY
DANGEROUS SITUATION,
TORNADO WATCH IN EFFECT
HERE ACROSS PARTS OF IOWA
AND ILLINOIS.
WE THINK POTENTIALLY SOME
VERY LARGE LONG TRACK
TORNADOES WITH THAT THEN A
PARTICULARLY DANGEROUS
SITUATION, SEVERE STORM
WATCH.
THIS IS WHERE WE THINK THAT
DERECHO WILL DEVELOP OVER
THE NEXT COUPLE OF HOURS.
ANOTHER TORNADO WATCH IN
EFFECT UNTIL 10:00 P.M.
OVER PARTS OF OHIO AND
PENNSYLVANIA AS WELL.
THREE WATCHES WE ARE
LOOKING AT.
SOME OF THESE STORMS HAVE
BEEN SEVERE IN OHIO AND
SOME TORNADO WARNINGS STILL
ACROSS AREAS OF IOWA AND IN
TOWARDS ILLINOIS.
WE THINK THIS LITTLE
COMPLEX THAT YOU SEE THESE
STORMS OUTSIDE OF CHICAGO
RIGHT NOW ARE WHAT ARE
GOING TO BE THE BEGINNING
OF THE DEVELOPMENT OF THIS
DERECHO, IT WILL VERY
RAPIDLY OVERNIGHT MOVE
ACROSS AREAS OF MICHIGAN,
INDIANA IN THROUGHOUT OHIO
AND EVENTUALLY BY THE
MORNING STILL BRINGING SOME
STORMS AND WIND ACROSS
PARTS OF THE MID-ATLANTIC.
THEN TOMORROW A
REDEVELOPMENT OF THIS STORM
ACROSS THE MID-ATLANTIC AND
SOME VERY HEAVY RAINFALL.
TONIGHT, WE HAVE A HIGH
RISK OF SEVERE WEATHER FROM
PLACES LIKE DAVENPORT, IOWA
OVER TOWARDS AROUND FORT
WAYNE.
TOMORROW IT MOVES FARTHER
OFF TOWARDS THE EAST AND
THE BULLS EYE WILL BE BIG
CITIES LIKE D.C., BALTIMORE
AND PHILADELPHIA.
A LOT OF RAIN WITH THIS.
VERY SIGNIFICANT FLOODING
ALL THE WAY THROUGH FRIDAY
AS WELL IN TOWARDS MUCH OF
THE NORTHEAST.
WE WILL TRACK THIS AGAIN
LATER ON IN THE HOUR.
RIGHT NOW FOX REPORT WILL
BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Shepard: DANGER NEAR THE
TOM OF A 46-STORY
SKYSCRAPER IN MIDTOWN
MANHATTAN, WHEN A HIGH TECH
SCAFFOLD COLLAPSED AND
TRAPPED NOT ONE BUT TWO
WORKERS FOR NEARLY TWO
HOURS.
YOU WILL BE ABLE TO SEE HOW
HOW THE PLATFORM BUCKLED IN
THE MIDDLE OF IT SORT OF A
V SHAPE LEFT.
FIREFIGHTERS AND OTHERS
RUSHED TO THAT ROOF TO
COMMUNICATE WITH THE TWO
MEN.
ONE CITY OFFICIAL SAID THE
MEN WORKED FOR THE
SCAFFOLDING COMPANY BUT HE
COULD NOT CONFIRM WHETHER
THEY WERE WINDOW WASHERS.
THOUGH WE THINK THEY WERE.
RESCUERS SAID THEY
EVENTUALLY MANAGED TO STRAP
THE TWO GUYS INTO HARNESSES
THEN REMOVED THE 4 BY
4-FOOT PIECE OF GLASS FROM
THE 44TH FLOOR OF THE
BUILDING AND PULLED THEM
SAFELY INSIDE.
EMERGENCY MEDICAL WORKER
SAYS THE TWO MEN ARE CALM
AND ALL SMILES ALL THIS FOR
US?
THAT'S WHAT THEY SAID.
I GUESS FROM WHEN THEY WERE
WATCHING, THEY NOTICED ALL
THE EQUIPMENT AND
EVERYTHING AND EVERYBODY
OUT THERE STANDS IN THE
LOBBY WAITING FOR THEM.
>> YOU COULD SEE ONE OF
THEM TALKING ON THE STAIR
CELL PHONE AND WAVING AT
US.
HELLO.
STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHY THAT COLLAPSED.
SPECIAL SYSTEM DESIGNED TO
FIT THE UNUSUALLY SHAPED
ENVIRONMENTALLY FRIENDLY
HURST TOWER.
THE FIRST SO-CALLED GREEN
BUILDING IN ALL OF
MANHATTAN.
WILDFIRES NOW SERIOUS ONES,
SEVERAL STRETCHING ACROSS
COLORADO AND THEY ARE SO
BAD THAT OFFICIALS SAY THEY
JUST CAN'T TELL HOW MANY
HOMES THEY HAVE DESTROYED.
JUST ONE OF THOSE FIRES HAS
BURNED NEARLY 100 HOMES
THEY TELL US, THOUSANDS OF
FOLKS HAVE HAD TO EVACUATE.
ONE PERSON SAID THE ONLY
THING HE HAD THEY HAD ONLY
HAD MINUTES TO GET OUT AND
GRAB WHAT THEY NEEDED
KNOWING THERE MAY BE
NOTHING LEFT WHEN THEY GET
BACK.
HERE YOU WILL BE ABLE TO
SEE THERE ARE FOUR
DIFFERENT FIRES.
OFFICIALS SAY AT LEAST ONE
OF THEM IS COMPLETELY OUT
OF CONTROL.
ZERO PERCENT CONTAINMENT.
THE FLAMES SAYING ONE
STEP -- STAYING ONE STEP
AHEAD THE CREWS NOW.
THE HIGH WINDS AND HOT
TEMPERATURES ARE NOT
HELPING AT ALL.
ALICIA ACUNA LIVE FOR US IN
MONUMENT, COLORADO THIS
AFTERNOON.
CLOSE TO ONE OF THOSE
FIRES RIGHT?
>> YEAH, TO THE ONE THAT IS
STILL OUT OF CONTROL SHEP,
THE BLACK FOREST FIRE WE
JUST GOT A FOREST UPDATE.
WIND BLOWING IN TWO
DIFFERENT DIRECTIONS.
UNAFFECTED AREA AND
DESTROYING MORE HOMES.
PUSH BACK TO SEE THE FIGHT
GOING ON BEHIND US HERE.
WE ARE WERE BACK IN THAT
AREA EARLIER.
TOLD WE HAD TO EVACUATE.
DROPPING FIRE RETARDANT
TODAY.
THAT GIANT PLANE CAN HOLD
UP TO 11,600 GALLONS OF
STUFF.
SHAWNEE WAS EVACUATED WITH
HER 12 CHILDREN.
WE ALREADY KNOW THAT SOME
FRIENDS HAVE LOST THEIR
HOMES AND WE HAVE HEARD
THAT THE FIRE IS PRETTY
CLOSE TO OUR AREA.
BUT WE DON'T KNOW ANYTHING.
>> WHAT'S BEEN REALLY
FRUSTRATING FOR SOME FOLKS
IS THE MAIN EVACUATION
CENTER WHERE ALL THOSE
DISPLACED FAMILIES WERE
GOING ALSO HAD TO EVACUATE
BECAUSE OF ALL OF THE
SMOKE.
THE GOVERNOR HERE HAS
DECLARED THREE OF THOSE
FOUR FIRES TO BE DISASTER
AREAS.
SHEP?
>> ALICIA, THANKS.
JURY SELECTION IN THE TRIAL
OF GEORGE ZIMMERMAN.
THAT NEIGHBORHOOD WATCH
VOLUNTEER WHO SAYS HE
KILLED THE UNARMED TEENAGER
TRAVON MARTIN IN
SELF-DEFENSE.
TODAY LAWYERS DISMISSED
DOZENS MORE POTENTIAL
JURORS AND WE WILL SHOW YOU
WHY.
PLUS A.A.A. IS WARNING OF
A NEW DISTRACTION BEHIND
THE WHEEL.
OFFICIALS SAY IT COULD BE
MORE DANGEROUS THAN
ACTUALLY TALKING ON A CELL
PHONE.
AND HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO
SEE THIS?
TAKING A BIG BITE OUT OF
YOUR BOAT:  THAT'SAS WE APPROACH THE
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR AND THE
TOP OF THEÑi NEWS.
AT OD, WHATEVER BUSINESS YOU'RE IN,
THAT'S THE BUSINESS WE'RE IN
WITH PREMIUM SERVICE LIKE ONE OF THE
BEST
ON-TIME DELIVERY RECORDS AND A LOW
CLAIMS RATIO
WE DO WHATEVER IT TAKES TO MAKE YOUR
BUSINESS OUR BUSINESS.
OD. HELPING THE WORLD KEEP PROMISES.
VO: I've always thought the best part
about this country
is that we get to create our future.
You get to take ownership of the choices
you make.
The person you become.
I've been around long enough to recognize
the people who are out there owning
it.
The ones getting involved and staying
engaged.
They're not sitting by as their life
unfolds.
And they're not afraid to question
the path they're on.
Because the one question they never
want to ask is
"How did I end up here?"
I started Schwab for those people.
People who want to take ownership
of their investments
like they do in every other aspect
of their lives.
>> Shepard: SO THEY ARE NOT
GOING TO NEED A BIGGER BOAT
JUST MINOR REPAIRS.
FISHERMEN LOOKING FOR MAKE
CO-SHARKS OFF THE COAST OF
NEW JERSEY GOT JUST EXACTLY
WHAT THEY WANTED BUT NOT
THE WAY THEY EXPLAINED IT.
>> ROD, I ACTUALLY MOVED
OUT OF THE WAY.
COURT SIDE BOW.
STARTED CHOMPING RIGHT ON
IN REACH ON THAT BOAT.
AND BROOMS.
SHARK REPORTEDLY 8 FEET
LONG WEIGHED MORE THAN
300 POUNDS.
I'M SHERT THIS IS
REFERENDUM.
A VOTE TO TURN PLANS INTO A
WILL MATCHETT SPARKS TWO
WEEKS OF DEMONSTRATIONS IN
WHICH FOUR PEOPLE HAVE
REPORTEDLY DIED.
HUNDREDS LELAND VITTERT
SPOKE WERE IS PROTESTERS.
GOVERNMENT IS CRACKING DOWN
ON REALITY AND THEY ARE NOT
HAVING IT.
RIOT.
BEFORE THE VIOLENCE STARTED
TWO WEEKS AGO.
>> I'M TERRIBLY ANGRY
BECAUSE THIS IS AGAINST
HUMAN RIGHTS.
>> MANY TOLD STORIES FROM
TUESDAY NIGHT WHEN
DEMONSTRATORS VOLUMES OF
TEAR GAS AND RUBBER BULLETS
ARE BONFIRES.
TURKISH MINISTER MOST OF
THE DEMONSTRATORS ARE.
THEY ARE SINCERE.
THEY HAVE GOOD WELL
INTENTIONS BUT CREATE
PSYCHOLOGY OF FEAR.
THERE.
>> THERE ARE THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE NOW STREAMING HERE
INTO THIS AREA, THEY ARE
PREPARED NOT ONLY FOR THE
RAIN BUT ALSO FOR THE TEAR
GAS.
WE HAVE GOT GUYS WITH
SAFETY GOGGLES ON,
MAKESHIFT GAS MASKS AND
THEN THERE IS THESE YELLOW
HARD HATS THAT THEY HAVE TO
PROTECT AGAINST THE ROCK
AND RUBBER BULLETS THAT
WILL COME LATER.
>> WE ARE NOT MARGINAL.
NOT TERRORISTS, WE ARE JUST
LIVING IN THIS NORMAL
PEOPLE.
JUST DEMOCRATIC RIGHTS.
>> WELL THE UNREST IN
TURKEY COULD HAVE A BIG
IMPACT ON THE CRISIS NEXT
DOOR IN SYRIA.
TURKEY'S PRIME MINISTER IS
A BIG SUPPORTER OF THE
SYRIAN REBEL.
AND ANALYSTS SAY GOVERNMENT
RESPONSE COULD VERY MUCH
COMPLICATE PRESIDENT OBAMA
IN CIVIL WAR.
FOR THAT ANGLE WE TURN TO
THE JONATHAN HUNT LIVE IN
NEW YORK TONIGHT.
JONATHAN DIFFICULT LINE
FOR THE UNITED STATES TO
TREAD HERE.
>> IT IS SHEP, BECAUSE ON
THE ONE HAND THE U.S. HAS
LORDED PRIME MINISTER
ERDOGHAN AS A TRUE DEMOCRAT
AND PARTNER IN THE REGION.
ON THE OTHER HAND, THIS IS
THE SAME PRIME MINISTER ONE
ORDERED HIS SECURITY FORCES
TO CRACKDOWN ON THOSE
PROTESTERS.
USING WHATEVER MEANS IS
NECESSARY.
SO, AGAIN, WE HEAR U.S.
OFFICIALS TODAY USING THE
CAUTIOUS LANGUAGE, CALLING
EFFECTIVELY FOR RESTRAINT
ON ALL SIDES.
LISTEN.
>> PUNISH INDIVIDUALS FOR
EXERCISING THEIR RIGHT TO
FREE SPEECH.
AND WE CONDEMN ATTEMPTS BY
ANY PARTY TO PROVOKE
VIOLENCE.
>> OF COURSE, ONLY LAST
MONTH THAT PRIME MINISTER
ERDOGHAN WELCOMED AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
NEITHER HE OR PRESIDENT
OBAMA APPARENTLY AWARE AT
THE TIME THAT THE
FIGURATIVE STORM CLOUDS
WERE GATHERING, SHEP.
>> SYRIA TIE IN HERE IS
IMPORTANT, JONATHAN.
TURKEY IS IMPORTANT THERE.
>> IT IS.
FOR INSTANCE, IF PRESIDENT
OBAMA WERE TO TAKE THE
DECISION TO START SENDING
WEAPONS TO THE REBELS IN
SYRIA, MANY OF THOSE
WEAPONS WOULD HAVE TO GO
ACROSS TURKEY'S LONG BORDER
WITH SYRIA.
YOU DON'T NECESSARILY WANT
TO SEND THOSE WEAPONS
THROUGH A COUNTRY THAT IS
SHOWING INCREASING SIGNS OF
INSTABILITY.
BUT PRECISELY BECAUSE OF
THAT LONG BORDER WITH
SYRIA, MANY EXPERTS SAY
THAT TURKEY NEEDS THE
UNITED STATES, MORE THAN
THE UNITED STATES NEEDS
TURKEY.
FURYKY WANTS US TO DO MORE
RATHER THAN LEGS.
I WOULDN'T NECESSARILY
WORRY TOO MUCH ABOUT SYRIA
ANGLE IN ALL OF THIS.
I THINK WE CAN HANDLE THE
TURKEY CRISIS LAUNDRY
ROOMILY ON ITS OWN TERMS
FOR WHAT IT IS THERE IN
THAT COUNTRY.
MOST EXPERTS AGREE THAT THE
SNACKET WITHIN TURKEY NOT
YET A SERIOUS THREAT TO THE
GOVERNMENT THERE BUT THE
IMPORTANT WORDS MIGHT BE
NOT YET SHEP?
>> JONATHAN POLICE IN
TURKEY TODAY ARRESTED TWO
REPORTERS
DEMANDING THAT OFFICIALS RELEASE
THEMSELVES.
REGARDING STATISTICS, THEY HAVE
JAILED MORE JOURNALISTS THAN
IRAN OR CHINA.
FOR THE FIRST TIME, A POTENTIAL
JUROR LEFT THE FLORIDA COURTROOM
ROUT FACING QUESTIONS FROM THE
DEFENSE.
IT HAPPENED TODAY.
HE INDICATED THAT HE COULD NOLTT
BE IMPARTIAL.
JURORS FOR BOTH SIDES GR GILLED
ABOUT THE KILLING OF THE
17-YEAR-OLD TRAYVON MARTIN.
HE CLAIMS THAT HE ACTS IN
DEFENSE.
WE ARE LIVE OUTSIDE OF THE
COURTROOM IN CENTRAL FLORIDA,
SANFORD FLORIDA, PHIL?
>>> TEN MORE JURORS MADE IT IN
AND OUT OF THE COURTROOM TODAY.
THIS MORNING BEGAN WITH JUNCTION
DEBRA NELSON ASKING GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN TO STAND UP SO FAR IS
ANDING HIM IF HE IS HAPPY WITH
THE PERFORMANCE OF HIS
ATTORNEYS.
SO FAR 200 WERE SUMMONED.
JUROR R 39 GOT HIMSELF DISMISSED
WITH THIS.
>> MURDER IS MURDER NO MATTER
WHAT.
>> OKAY, SO YOU BELIEVE MURDER
IS MURDER.
>> EVEN IF IT'S SELF DEFENSE IT
STILL DOESN'T MAKE IT RIGHT.
>> AND LATE TODAY ANOTHER JUROR
LIKELY GOT HIMSELF DISMISSED
AFTER THE JUDGE CHALLENGED
HIMSELF ABOUT AN ANTI-ZIMMERMAN
RANT HE POSTED.
IDEALLY, FROM THAT THEY CAN FIND
A FAIR AND IMPARTIAL JUROR.
>> THEY WILL WHITTLE DOWN THAT
POOL TO SIX JURORS AND FOUR
ALTERNATES.
>>> NEW WARNINGS TONIGHT OF A
PUBLIC SAFETY CRISIS IN THE FORM
OF NEW DASHBOARD TECHNOLOGY THAT
LETS DRIVERS TEXT AND E-MAIL
WITH VOICE COMMANDS.
THE SO CALLED INFO-TAIMMENT
SYSTEMS ARE MORE DISTRACTING
THAN YOUR CELL PHONE.
THEY CAN DEVELOP INATTENTION
BLINDNESS.
THEY CAN BE LOOKING STRAIGHT
AHEAD, BUT NOT SEE PEDESTRIANS
OR RED LIGHTS.
AAA REPORTS THERE ARE TEN
MILLION CARS AND TRUCKS ON THE
ROAD NOW WITH INFO-TAINMENT
SYSTEMS.
AT LEAST SEVEN STUDENTS ARE HURT
AS AN EXPLOSION ROCKS A HIGH
SCHOOL CAMPUS AND IT TOPS OUR
NEWS ACROSS AMERICA.
>>> CALIFORNIA SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO CAPTURED THE MOMENT A
BOILER BLUE UP NEAR THE SCHOOL'S
GYM
GYMNASIUM.
OFFICIALS SAY NOBODY WAS IN THE
GYM OR LOCKER ROOMS AT THE TIME
BUT SEVERAL PEOPLE OUTSIDE WENT
TO THE HOSPITAL FOR MINOR
INJURIES.
>>> FLORIDA, A ROAD COLLAPSED
AND TRAPPED SEVERAL CARS IN A
THREE-FOOT DEEP PIT IN ORLANDO.
OFFICIALS SAY THAT RAIN SOFTENED
THE GROUND.
ALL OF THE CARS WERE REPORTEDLY
EMPTY.
SOME WERE SO FILLED WITH WATER
AND MUD THEY ARE A TOTAL LOSS.
>>> OFFICIALS CAPTURED A 12 FOOT
LONG AL IGATOR IN FROM HOME.
THE WOMAN CALLED ANIMAL
TRAPPERS, BUT THE GATOR HAD GONE
BACK INTO THE SWAMP BEFORE THEY
GOT THEM.
THEY NABBED HIM WHEN HE FINALLY
RESURFACED.
>>> FOX ACROSS AMERICA IS
BROUGHT TO YOU BY --
>>> THE EXTREME WEATHER THAT WE
HAVE MENTIONED IS NOW ON THE
MOVE.
MILLIONS IN THE PATH OF SOME
POTENTIALLY VERY DANGEROUS STORM
SYSTEMS.
WE'LL GO BACK TO A RICK FOR A
UPDATE ON THAT.
>>> AND THE KIDNAPPER IN A
CLEVELAND HOUSE OF HORRORS CASE
SAYS I'M NOT GUILTY.
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR WHAT DEFENSE
TEAM WANTS FROM THE PROSECUTORS.
THAT'S NEXT.
WELL, SINCE YOU HAD
PROGRESSIVE'S TOTAL LOSS COVERAGE,
WE WERE ABLE TO REPLACE YOUR TOTALED
BIKE
WITH A BRAND-NEW ONE.
THE TANK THE EXHAUST...
WELL, SHE LOOKS JUST LIKE ROXY!
YOU KNOW, I'LL BET SHE'S IN A BETTER
PLACE NOW.
I'M SURE SHE IS.
[ ETHEREAL MUSIC PLAYS ]
[ MOTORCYCLE REVVING ]
GETTING YOU BACK  ON A BRAND-NEW BIKE.
NOW, THAT'S PROGRESSIVE.
For all those who sleep
too hot or too cool, and struggle
to sleep comfortably together
now there's a solution.
Introducing Sleep Number DualTemp,the
revolutionary
temperature-balancing layer
with Active Air technology that
works on any mattress, including yours.
Whether you sleep hot or cool,
Sleep Number Dual Temp allows each
of you to
select your ideal temperature.
And it's only at one of our over
400 Sleep Number stores nation wide.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
úkúñY]/;o@=Swñofpwgpñ÷?úçwçw7síÑ@#@÷wÑévyñ/TÑnxx7p?úo>fóçOv1Z3ézÑs/n]çwñwíwz9g+5
SñññtsÑwhÑpç oúñçgTótw #@w÷oówñmúñ/Vú9úñnú)>[sñj@j=g÷ñx÷xxsz?Nófñ?VOk=w?ú7ÑloíÑwí<Mñ'?xÑ;ÑPDúmuoú?w÷uó
@>g74/xOpW<0÷?v?pñOç8'$Ñ?k?óçxFóy
óçpnooWvúéñi/xXçp?v@oxsdñ@o,o7÷s%]ñv-6úwñ?@mÑú?oçv?:@óé?óço>÷wñWmúñ@çx?Y?d?ço?Zoq@ñ?7xññójuXo?ñç3púñç?oóókph7[u@]mm?nws>@yñ/wowçúÑáñpóúÑçóÑyo
ñ.=x[úw÷<ú@ñW,ú 7k  WITH THE Spark
Cash Card  FROM Capital One...  BORIS
EARNS UNLIMITED REWARDS  FOR HIS SMALL
BUSINESS.  CAN I GET THE SMITH CONTRACT
EASE?  THANK YOU.  THAT'S  THREE NEW
PAPER SHREDDERS.  [ Boris ]  PUT 'EM
ON MY Spark Card.  [ Garth ] BORIS'
SMALL BUSINESS  EARNS 2% CASH BACK
ON EVERY PCHASE EVERY DAY.  GREAT
BUSINESSES  DESERVE UNLIMITED REWARDS.
READ BACK THE CHICKEN'S  TESTIMONY,
PLEASE.  "BUK, BUK, BUKKA!"    [ Male
Announcer ]    GET THE Spark Business
Card   FROM Capital One    AND EARN
UNLIMITED REWARDS.    CHOOSE 2% CASH
BACK    OR DOUBLE MILES    ON EVERY
PURCHASE EVERY DAY.  TOLD YOU I'D
GET HALF.  WHAT'S IN  YOUR WALLE
>>> FOX WEATHER ALERT,
CONTINUING TO TRACK TOMORROWS
FROM IOWA ALL THE WAY TO THE
EAST COAST.
THIS IS AURORA, ILLINOIS.
IT IS JUST WEST OF CHICAGO.
HERE IS CHICAGO ITSELF, WHERE
OFFICIALS ARE REPORTING HEAVY
RAIN, HAIL AND POSSIBLE
TORNADOES.
RICK IS ALL OVER OF IT.
>> THIS IS THE THREE WATCH BOXES
THAT WE HAVE RIGHT NOW THAT
WE'RE CONCERNED ABOUT.
MOST OF THE TORNADO ACTIVITY
THAT WE'RE CONCERNED ABOUT ARE
ON THIS WESTERN SIDE OF THE
STORM.
YOU SEE THAT ACTIVITY THERE,
THAT WILL PULL OFF TO THE WEST.
THAT BIG WIND EVENT IS WHERE YOU
SEE THIS YELLOW AND MOVING WHERE
YOU SEE THIS RED AREA WHERE WE
HAVE A TORNADO WATCH IN EFFECT
LATER ON.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT A MAJOR
EVENT WITH VERY STRONG STRAIGHT
LINE WINDS.
THAT MEANS BIG POWER OUTAGES
TREES DOWN, AND WIND DAMAGE.
TORNADO WARNINGS IN EFFECT HERE.
WE HAVE SEEN THEM ACROSS MUCH OF
THE CENTRAL AREA TO THE NORTH OF
WATERLOO, IOWA.
WE HAVE SEEN SEVEN TORNADOES
REPORTED THERE TODAY.
YOU SEE ALL OF THIS DIFFICULTACTIVITY,
IT
IS GOING TO COALACE INTO ONE
LEFT FOOT.
SOME ISOLATED AREAS, MAYBE FOUR
TO FIVE INCHES OF RAIN, AND THAT
MEANS MAJOR CONCERNS.
15 STATES.
THERE IS SEVERE WEATHER AND
FLOODING RAINS IN UPSTATE NEW
YORK, CONNECTICUT,
MASSACHUSETTS, AND ALL OF THE
BIG CITIES SHEPHERDED ACROSS THE
COAST.
>>> A LAWYER FOR THE MAN ACCUSED
OF HOLDING THREE WOMAN CAPTIVE
SAY SOME OF HIS CRIMES CANNOT BE
DISPUTED.
HE STILL PLEADED NOT GUILTY
TODAY.
AFTER THE HEARING, HIS DEFENSE
ATTORNEY HINLTED AT -- HINTED AT
A POSSIBLE PLEA DEAL.
THE MURDER CHARGE SAYS THAT HE
STARVED AND BEAT AN ALLEGED
KIDNAPPING VICTIM WHILE SHE WAS
PREGNANT.
HE RAPED EACH OF HIS CAPTIVES
AND ONE HAD TO GIVE BIRTH IN AN
INFLATABLE POOL.
A REPRESENTATIVE FOR THOSE THREE
WOMEN SAYS THEY HOPE FOR A JUST
AND PROMPT LEGAL OUTCOME.
>>> KRESRESCUERS USE THEIR BARE
HANDS TO SAVE A MAN IN A MUDDY
WELL.
>>> CHINA.
THE WELL REPORTEDLY COLLAPSED
BENEATH A CONSTRUCTION WORKER
FOLLOWING DAYS OF RAINS IN THE
SOUTHEAST.
EMERGENCY OFFICIALS SAY THEY
FOUND THE GUY BURIED UP TO HIS
ANDRES.
THEY USED BUDGETS TO DIG THROUGH
THE MUD AND BRING HIM TO SAFETY.
>>> IN BOSNIA AUTHORITIES
DISTROYED DOZENS OF GUNS.
THEY GOT ROCKET LAUNCHERS AND
HANDGUNS IN THE LAST FEW YEARS
TO CURB VIOLENCE.
POLICE SAY THEY WILL MELT DOWN
THE MEDAL FOR RECYCLING.
>>> ISRAEL, A NEW TECHNOLOGY
THAT USES THE SUN TO PRODUCE
CLEAN DRINKING WATER.
THEY USE THE ENERGY TO PURIFY
DIRTY WATER.
THEY MAKE ABOUT 100 GALLONS A
WAY AND IT COULD BE A BIG HELP
IN DEVELOPING NATIONS.
>>> UNITED AIR DD ARAB EMIRATES HAS
THE
HIGHEST TWISTED TOWER.
DEVELOPERS SAY THE LOOK OF A
HUMAN DNA STRAND INSPIRED THE
DESIGN.
THAT IS A WRAP ON THIS FOX TRIP
AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 SECONDS.
>>> AROUND THE WORLD IS
SPONSORED BY VERIZON.
>>> LAWMAKERS SAY FEWER PEOPLE
SHOULD BE ABLE TO GET THEIR
HANDS ON THE GOVERNMENT
SURVEILLANCE DATA AFTER THESE
NEW HIGH PROFILE LEAKS.
BUT WE'RE LEARNING HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF CONTRACTORS ARE
ABLE TO ACCESS TOP SECRET
SECURITY INFORMATION.
GEORGE H.W. BUSH CELEBRATING HIS
80th BIRTHDAY TODAY.
HE HAD SUPERMAN SOCKS AND FOLKS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY CAN CELEBRATE
WITH THE FORMER PRESIDENT,
THAT'S STILL AHEAD.
That means your smartphone her Blackberry
his laptop Mark's smartphone...
But I'm still on vacation...
...stilln the plan. Nice!
So is his tablet, that guy's hotspot,
thentern's tablet.
The intern gets a tablet?
Everyone's devices.
His, hers, oh sorry...
all easier to manage on The Share
Everything Plan
for Small Business.
Connecting more so you can do more.
That's Powerful. Verizon.
Get the Blackberry Q10 for $199.99.
TEST.
>>> MORE THAN HALF A MILLION
GOVERNMENT CONTRACTORS HAVE SOME
KIND OF SECURITY CLEARANCE.
OF COURSE A FORMER NSA
CONTRACTOR JUST BLEW THE LID OFF
TWO GOVERNMENT SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAMS AND ARE THREATENING TO
DO MORE.
NOW SOME SAY IT MAY BE TIME TO
LOOK AT OTHER CLEARANCES.
MICHAEL DANIEL IN THE D.C.
TONIGHT, MIKE?
>> OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
REQUESTED BILLIONS TO SPEND ON
CYBER APP AND TODAY THEY ASK THE
NSA CHIEF, HOW THE HECK DOES
THIS HAPPEN.
>> WHY DOES A CONTRACTOR HAVE
ACCESS TO INFORMATION WE ARE
SPENDING $13 BILLION TO PREVENT
OUTSIDERS FROM GETTING THEIR
HANDS ON.
>> THAT'S ONE OF THE GRAVE
CONCERNS WE HAVE THAT IN OUR
NETWORKS, THE SYSTEM
ADMINISTRATION OF THOSE
NETWORKS, I.T. INFRASTRUCTURE
WAS OUTSOURCED ABOUT 14 YEARS
AGO TO MOVE MORE PUSH MORE OF
OUR WORK OUT TO CONTRACTORS.
>> TODAY DIANNE FEINSTEIN SAID
SHE WAS REDUCING THE NUMBER OF
CONTRACTORS AND THEIR ACCESS TO
HIGHLY CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
BUT AN EXPERT SAYS THE CHALLENGE
FOR THE GOVERNMENT IS THERE'S
SERIOUS COMPETITION WITH WALL
STREET AND SILICON VALLEY FOR
THE BEST TECHNICAL MINDS.
>> THIS IS ELECTRONICS AND
TECHNOLOGY.
THE MORE NEED YOU HAVE FOR
REALLY HIGH END CAPABLE
TECHNOLOGY SKILLS.
AND THAT'S THE PRIVATE SECTOR IS
WHERE THOSE SKILLS ARE.
BUT THIS ISSUE HAS ABSOLUTELY
NOTHING TO DO WITH THAT.
>> AND HE NOTES THE PROCESS OF
GETTING A SECURITY CLEARANCE IS
THE SAME WHETHER YOU'RE A
GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEE OR A
CONTRACTOR.
CHEF?
>> MIKE, FORMER PRESIDENT BUSH
CELEBRATING BIRTHDAY NUMBER 3
THE
THE9,
I SHOULD SAY 89.
HE WISHES 39.
HE HAS BECOME KNOWN FOR THESE.
RED SOCKS WITH SUPERMAN LOGOS ON
THEM.
OTHERS WERE URGED TO WEAR CRAZY
SOCKS AND POST THEM ON-LINE.
HE WORE THIS RED AND BLUE PAIR
LAST YEAR WHEN ARTIST UNVEILED
THE OFFICIAL PORTRAITS OF HIS
SON FORMER PRESIDENT GEORGE W.
BUSH AND FIRST LADY LAURA BUSH.
AND WE SAW THIS BRIGHT PINK AND
BLUE PAIR AT DEDICATION OF THE
GEORGE W. BUSH PRESIDENTIAL
LIBRARY IN APRIL.
THEY ARE VERY MUCH IN STYLE.
OF COURSE PRESIDENT GEORGE H.W.
BUSH CELEBRATED BYSKYDIVING WHEN
HE TURNED 80 85 AND.
THE HOSPITAL RELEASED HIM IN
JANUARY AFTER HE ADD COUGH.
TODAY, THE 89th LESS THAN A
WEEK AFTER HIS WIFE FORMER
FIRST LADY BARBARA BUSH, TURNED
88.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY TO BOTH.
>>> WASHING YOUR HANDS, SO
SIMPLE, RIGHT?
BUT A NEW STUDY INDICATES IT IS
APPARENTLY NOT SO SIMPLE.
>>> COMING UP, WE WILL EXPLAIN
TO YOU JUST HOW MANY PEOPLE ARE
DOING IT ALL WRONG.
AND IT'S A BIG NUMBER.
COPD MAKES IT HARD TO BREATHE...
BUT WITH ADVAIR,  I'M BREATHING BETTER.
SO NOW I CAN HELP MAKE THIS  A GREAT
BLOCK PARTY.  ♪ ♪    [ Male Announce
]   ADVAIR IS CLINICALLY PROVEN
TO HELP SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE    LUNG
FUNCTION.    UNLIKE MOST COPD MEDICATIONS,
ADVAIR CONTAINS    BOTH AN ANTI-INFLAMMATORY
AND A LONG-ACTING    BRONCHODILATOR
WORKING TOGETHER    TO HELP IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION ALL DAY.    ADVAIR
WON'T REPLACE    FAST-ACTING INHALERS
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS    AND SHOULD
NOT BUSED    MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
PEOPLE WITH COPD TAKING ADVAIR
MAY HAVE    A HIGHER CHANCE OF PNEUMONIA.
ADVAIR MAY INCRSE    YOUR RISK OF
OSTEOPOROSIS     SOME EYE PRLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR    IF YOU HAVE A
HEART CONDITION    OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING ADVAIR.  ASK YOUR DOCTOR
IF INCLUDING ADVAIR COULD HELP  IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION.    [ Male Announcer
]    ADVAIR DISKUS    FLUTICASONE
PROPIONATE AND    SALMETEROL INHALATION
POWDER.    GET YOUR FIRST PRESCRIPTION
FREE    AND SAVE ON REFILLS    AT
ADVAIRCOPD.COM.
Save big on great gifts
at Bass Pro Shops' Father's Day Sale.
Like World Wide Sportsman Boca Grande
Shorts for under $25.
And the Bass Pro Aluminum Fish Fryer
for under $30.
Plus check out our free Family Summer
Camp.
I DON'T MAKE ANY DECISIONS ABOUT WHO
TO HIRE WITHOUT GOING TO ANGIE'S LIST
FIRST.
YOU'LL FIND REVIEWS  ON HOME REPAIR
TO HEALTHCARE
WRITTEN BY PEOPLE  JUST LIKE YOU.
WITH ANGIE'S LIST, I KNOW WHO TO CALL
AND I KNOW THE RESULTS WILL BE FANTASTIC.
ANGIE'S LIST --  REVIEWS YOU CAN TRUST.
>>> YOU'RE DOING IT ALL WRONG.
THERE IS A STUDY THAT SUGGESTS 1
IN 20 AMERICANS WASH THEIR HANDS
THE RIGHT WAY.
MICHIGAN UNIVERSITY TRACKED 2700
PEOPLE WASHING THEIR HANDS IN
PUBLIC REST ROOM.
THEY FOUND ONE-THIRD DIDN'T USE
SOAP.
10% SKIPPED WASHING HANDS
ENTIRELY.
GROSS.
AVERAGE GROUP SCRUBBED FOR SIX
SECONDS.
AWFUL.
CDC RECOMMENDS 20 SECONDS IF YOU
WANT IT SKILL THE GERMS.
>>> A HUGE BRAWL BROKE OUT LAST
NIGHT AT A BASEBALL GAME.
AWESOME.
TENSIONS WERE HIGH AFTER
PITCHERS FOR BOTH DODGERS AND
DIAMONDBACKS HIT A FEW BATTERS.
DIDN'T TAKE MUCH FOR BOTH
BENCHES TO CLEAR.
EVEN THE OLDER GUY GOT IN THE
MIX.
LOS ANGELES HITTING COACH MARK
McGUIRE GOING NOSE TO NOSE WITH
KIRK GIBSON.
THEY GOT TOSSED.
AND SO DID FOUR OTHER PLAYERS.
>>> THE U.S. HAS BEEN LAUNCHING
HACK ATTACKS ON CHINA.
THAT THE LATEST FROM ED SNOWDEN.
THAT I GO WHO SAYS HE LEAKED
INFORMATION TO THE SPY PROGRAM.
CONGRESS SAYS THE PROGRAM
PREVENTED DOZENS OF TERROR
ATTACKS.
WE SHOULD GET INFORMATION ON A
YOUNG GIRL'S LUNG TRANSPLANT IN
PHILLY.
10-YEAR-OLD SARAH IS GETTING A
LUNG TRANSPLANT.
>>> WIND COULD REACH 100 MILES
AN HOUR.
>>> ON THIS DAY IN 1987,
PRESIDENT REAGAN MADE AN
UNFORGETTABLE COLD WAR SPEECH IN
A DIVIDED GERMANY.
CHALLENGING THEN SOVIET LEADER
MY KALE GORBACHEV.
THE IDEA WAS TO PREVENT CITIZENS
FROM ESCAPING TO THE DEMOCRATIC
WEST.
PRESIDENT REAGAN VISITED GERMANY
AT A TIME OF HEIGHTENED
EAST/WEST TENSION.
AND WITH THAT WALL AS HIS
BACKDROP, HE DEMANDED AN END TO
THE LONG STANDING SYMBOL OF
REPRESSION SAYING ALL TOGETHER
NOW, MR. GORBACHEV TEAR DOWN
THIS WALL.
IT DID FALL TWO YEARS LATER.
BUT FIRST, THE WORLD HEARD SOME
OF HISTORY'S MOST FAMOUS WORDS.
26 YEARS AGO TODAY.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS.
FOR THIS WEDNESDAY, JUNE 12th
2013, I'M SHEPHERD SMITH.
THANKS FOR CHECKING IN.
HERE ALL BACK TOGETHER FOR
STUDIO B.
BACK HERE FOR THE FOX REPORT
TOMORROW NIGHT.
AND OWE RILEY NORMALLY FOLLOWS.
>>> IF I KNOW EVERY SINGLE PHONE
CALL YOU MAKE, I'M ABLE TO
DETERMINE EVERY SINGLE PERSON
YOU TALK TO.
I CAN GET A PATTERN ABOUT YOUR
LIFE THAT IS VERY, VERY
INTRUSIVE.
>> THAT'S BACK WHEN PRESIDENT
BUSH WAS IN OFFICE.
THEN SENATOR JOE BIDEN SCORCHING
SURVEILLANCE ON TELEPHONE CALLS.
BUT NOW IT'S A DIFFERENT STORY
ISN'T IT?
WE WILL HAVE A FULL REPORT.
>> THIS OPPORTUNITY TO SAY ON
BEHALF OF THE SECRETARY THAT HE
HAS FULL CONFIDENCE.
>> I'M JUST SEEING THROUGH THE
PROCESS.
>> OKAY.
>> STATE DEPARTMENT ONCE AGAIN
ON THE DEFENSIVE OVER
WHISTLE-BLOWER ALLEGATIONS ABOUT
PROSTITUTION AND DRUG USE.
JAMES ROSEN WILL HAVE A
FOLLOW-UP REPORT TONIGHT.