>> THIS IS THE FOX REPORT.
TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT WRAPPING
UP A MEETING WITH THE NATIONAL
SECURITY TEAM ABOUT ALLEGATIONS
ABOUT THE RED LINE CROSSED
AGAIN.
NEW INFORMATION ABOUT THE FLOOD
OF REFUGEES LEAVING THAT COUNTRY
AND ACCUSATIONS.
WABASHAR ASSAD'S REGIME IS USING
WEAPONS OF MASS DESTRUCTION TO
ATTACK OUT ITS OWN CITIZENS.
AND THE PENTAGON SENDING
A MESSAGE.
THE TOP BRASS SUGGESTING THAT
THE U.S. MILITARY IS READY TO
ACT ON A MOMENT'S NOTICE IN
SYRIA.
>> AND REMEMBERING THE DAY WHEN
THE MARTIN LUTHER KING JUNIOR
HAD A DREAM.
IT IS A HALF CENTURY LATER.
AND TONIGHT, FOLLOWING THE TO
THE STEPS OF A CIVIL MOMENT IN
AMERICAN HISTORY.
AND ALSO FORMER VICE-PRESIDENT
CHENEY SPEAKING LOUD AND CLEAR
ON THE NATIONAL ISSUES WHICH ARE
FRONT AND CENTER ON THE MINDS OF
MANY AMERICANS.
>> DON'T PUT THE NSA WITH THE
IRS.
THEY ARE TOTALLY DIFFERENT
PROBLEMS AND ISSUES AND I
BELIEVE THERE IS AMPLE EVIDENCE
THAT THE IRS ABUSED THE PLAYER
AND DAUGHTER LIZ A POLITICAL
CANDIDATE.
WORDS FROM THE FATHER/DAUGHTER
DUOMAKING HEADLINES.
>> I AM HARRIS FAULKNER.
HOW WILL THE UNITED STATES
RESPOND TO THE CRISIS IN SYRIA
THAT HAS MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
POURING OVER THE BORDERS TRYING
TO ESCAPE THE SLAUGHTER HOUSE
THAT THEIR COUNTRY HAS BECOME.
IT COULD CREATE NOW HAVENS FOR
TERRORIST AND AMERICAN NATIONAL
SECURITY TIME TALKED ABOUT THE
NEXT STEP AND TALKED ABOUT WHAT
IS UNFOLDING, PICTURES THAT ARE
SO HARD TO LOOK AT AND
IMPOSSIBLE TO AUNTICATE AND SEEM
TO GO ALONG WITH CHEMICAL
ATTACKS IN SYRIA.
AND MORE ON THE HIGH LEVEL
MEETING FOR YOU.
AND FIRST A DEADLY GAME OF BACK
AND FORTH PLAYED OUT AT THIS
HOURED IN OF SYRIA.
THEY ARE ACCUSING THE ANTI-
GOVERNMENT REBELS OF USING
CHEMICAL WEAPONS AND OTHERS CALL
THAT A THINLY VEILED ATTEMPT
FROM THE NERVE GAS ASSAULT ON
A NEIGHBORHOOD THEY SAY.
DEFENSE SECRETARY CHUCK HAGEL
ASKED THE PENTAGON TO PREPARE
MILITARY OPTIONS FOR SYRIA AND
THAT REQUIRES POSIINGING OUR
FORCES.
WE KNOW A FOURTH WARM SHIP ARMED
WITH BALLISTIC MISSILES HAS BEEN
IS NOT TO THE MEDITERRANEAN SEA.
AND THE CHIEF IS THERE TO URGE
THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT TO ALLOW
UNITED NATION'S EXPERTS TO LOOK
AT CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACKS.
AID GROUPS SAID THROW 55 PEOPLE
WERE KILLED AND SOME HAVE THE
NUMBER MUCH HIGHER AND IF
CONFIRMED IT WOULD BE THE
WOFRSOUS OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS
SINCE SADDAM HUSSEIN GASSED
CURDS.
THE CIVIL WAR AND ESTIMATES PUT
IT AT MORE THAN 100,000.
A YEARING ON PRESIDENT OBAMA
SAID CHEMICAL WEAPON USED IN
SYRIA WOULD BE CROSSING A RED
LINE.
>> PRESIDENT CONFERRED WITH
ANOTHER WORLD LEADER ON SYRIA.
>> HE SPOKE WITH BRITISH PRIME
MINISTER DAVID CAMERON ABOUT THE
POSSIBLE CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACK.
THEY EXPRESSED GRAVE CONCERN AND
AGREED TO WORK TOGETHER AND WITH
THE INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY TO
FIGURE OUT HOW TO RESPOND.
PRESIDENT OBAMA IS GETTING
REPORTS FROM THE U.S.
ENTELEIGENCE COMMUNITY WHICH
ACCORDING TO THE WHITE WHITE
TRYING TO ASCERTAIN WHAT
HAPPENED IN SYRIA AND WAITING TO
HEAR FROM A UNITED NATION'S TEAM
IN SYRIA BEFORE THE PRESIDENT
MAKES A DECISION ON HOW THE U.S.
WILL RESPOND.
IN THE MOAN TIME DEFENSE
SECRETARY CHUCK HAGEL TOLD
REPORTERS THAT THE DEFENSE
DEPARTMENT HAS A RESPONSIBILITY
TO PROVIDE THE PRESIDENT WITH
OPTIONS FOR ALL CONTINGENCY AND
THAT REQUIRES POSITIONING OUR
FORCES AND ASSETS TO BE ABLE FOR
THE PRESIDENT TO CHOOSE.
AND HARRIS, THE U.S. HAS FOUR
WAR SHIPS IN THE REGION, HARRIS.
>> IT IS AWFULLY DIFFICULT WHEN
WE ARE NOT BEGIN INFORMATION OR
NOTES TO KNOW WHETHER AND THIS
IS A QUESTION, DOES THIS MEAN
MILITARY ACTIONS MORE OR LESS
LIKELY AT THIS POINT?
>> IT CERTAINLY GIVES PRESIDENT
OBAMA MORE FLEXIBILITY TO ORDER
AIR STRIKES OR MISSILE ATTACKS
IF HE DECIDES TO DO.
THAT ONE FORMER UN AMBASSADOR
SAID PRESIDENT OBAMA HAS TO
DECIDE THE OBJECTIVES WITH SYRIA
AND ITS GOVERNMENT AND STOCK
POIL OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID HIMSELF
A YEAR AGO THAT THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS WOULD CROSS
A REDLINE AND WHEN THE PRESIDENT
OF THE UNITED STATES MAKES
A STATEMENT LIKE THAT, HE NEEDS
TO BE PREPARED TO DO MANAGE
DRAMATIC IF THE REDLINE IS
CROSSED.
OTHERWISE HIS CREDIBILITY IS
GRAVELY DAMAGED AND THAT'S WHERE
WE ARE AT THE MOMENT.
>> BUT BOLTON BELIEVES THAT THE
ADMINISTRATION WILL TRY TO
INDICT THE SYRIAN REGIME IN THE
INTERNATIONAL CRIMINAL COURT.
>> MOLLY, ON THE STORY ON WHICH
WE HAVE SEEN MOVEMENT SO MUCH.
COMING UP INSIDE OF THE FOX
REPORT RETIRED FOUR STAR GENERAL
AND JACK KING WILL JOIN US.
MY FIRST QUESTION WILL BE WHAT
WE LEARNED FROM MOLLY.
WHAT IS A SERIOUS RESPONSE
LIKELY TO LOOK LIKE?
.
WELL, IT HAS BEEN CALLED ONE OF
THE MOST IMPORTANT DAYS IN
AMERICAN HISTORY.
TODAY IN WASHINGTON, PEOPLE
GAGGERING TO COMMEMORATE 50
YEARS SINCE MARTIN LUTHER KING'S
I HAVE A DREAM SPOECH COMING
A DAY SHY OF HIS SPEECH.
>> THIS IS NOT THE TIME FOR
A NOSTOLLINGIC COMMEMORATION OR
SELF CONGRATULATORY CELEBRATION,
THE TASK IS NOT DONE.
THE JOURNEY IS NOT COMPLETE.
WE CAN AND WE MUST DO MORE.
>> TODAY'S EVENT CONCLUDING WITH
A HALF MILE WALK FROM THE
LINCOLN MEMORIAL TO THE
TWO-YEAR-OLD STAT U THAT HONORS
DR. MARTIN LUTHER KING JUNIOR.
WE CAN SEE DOUG McELWAY FROM THE
NATION'S CAPITOL.
YOUR COMMENTS ON THE ROUTE.
>> IT WAS SPECTACULAR HARRIS.
IT WAS AIDED FROM MOTHER NATURE.
IT IS NOT EVERY DAY IN LATE
AUGUST SHE TURNS OUT A SUN
DRENCHED LOW HUMIDITY AND COOL
COINED OF DAY.
THAT'S WHAT WE HAD TODAY.
THE LATE DR. MARTIN LUTHER KING
WOULD BE PROUD OF THE SPIRIT OF
NONVIOLENCE AND GENERALIZED GOOD
WILL.
FOR ME THE MOST POWERFUL MOMENTS
CAME NOT FROM THE PODIUM BUT
FROM THE PEOPLE IN THE CROWD
SOME OF WHOM WERE HERE TO WATCH
THAT SPEECH IN KNOWN 63, AND
LIVED TO TELL ABOUT IT AND MANY
OTHERS WHO WATCHED IT ON
TELEVISION AND STILL OTHERS WHO
LIVE IN THE SEGGATED SOUTH LIKE
THE BROTHERS WHO GREW UP IN
MOBILE, OBAMA.
>> IT WAS ROUGH.
SEGREGATION WAS ALIVE AND WELL.
AND IT WAS HARD FOR BLACK PEOPLE
TO STICK TOGETHER TO ACHIEVE
THINGS, BECAUSE OF THE
VIOLATION.
THE BOMBING IN BIRMINGHAM AND
MEG AREAS AND ALL OF THE THINGS
WERE GOING ON AND SO YOUR
PARENTS WERE RELUCTANT TO HAVE
YOU PARTICIPATE BECAUSE THEY
KNEW THE CONSEQUENCES.
>> THERE IS A LOT OF WORK IN
PROGRESS AND UP TO US AS THE
BABY BOMERS AND TO PASS ON TO MY
GREAT NEPHEWS AND BEING PART OF
THE MOVEMENT AND ACTION AND TO
VOLUNTEER AND HELP YOUR
FELLOWMAN.
>> WE FOUND ONE MARCHER WHO IS
94 YEARS OLD AND MARCHED IN THE
1963 EVENT.
HE HAD THE SAME SIGN HE CARRIED
IN KNOWN 63 AND HERE HE WAS
IMPARTING ADVICE IN A FEISTY WAY
TO THE YOUNG FOLKS AROUND HIM.
>> THE QUESTION IS NOT WHAT I
THINK, IT IS WHAT YOU PEOPLE
THINK?
WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO DO ABOUT
IT?
ANSWER ME, WHAT ARE YOU GOING TO
DO APPROXIMATE IT?
>> HE TOLD US THAT HE WAS
A TRUCK DRIVER AND HAD A ROUTE
FROM NEW YORK TO WASHINGTON AND
RAN HOME AND TOCK A BATH AND
CAME DOWN TO THE MARCH.
WHAT A MAN.
>> YOU DESCRIBED A FAMILY
ATMOSPHERE, SIMILAR OR
CONTRASTING TO THE ORIGINAL
MARCH?
>> I THINK IT WAS A HUGE
CONTRAST TO THE ORIGINAL MARCH.
WASHINGTON ON THAT PARTICULAR
DAY WAS A TENSE CITY.
I GREW UP HERE AND I WAS NINE
YEARS OLD ON THAT DAY AND
WASHINGTON WAS A SEGREGATED
TOWN.
I CAN REMEMBER TALKING TO MY
FRIENDS WERE THERE GOING TO BE
RIOTS AND PEOPLE COMING TO THE
NEIGHBORHOOD AND THE ADULTS WERE
AFRAID.
IT WAS A REFLECTION OF WHAT THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT WAS DOING.
THE POLICE FORCE WAS ON FULL
ALERT AND ALL HANDS ON DECK AND
NATIONAL GUARD WAS CALLED OUGHT
AND FBI DIRECTOR HOOVER HAD
INFILM TRAITED THE MOVEMENT AND
FOUND COMMUNISM ACTIVITY AND
KENNEDY REFUSED TO MEET WITH
THEM BECAUSE OF A FEAR OF
IMPOSING ON HIM.
AND ONE OUT AND THE REST IS
HISTORY, HARRIS.
>> FOR OUR VOWERS.
YOU HAVE DONE A GREAT JOB
SHOWING YOUR PERSPECTIVE AND
PUTTING THINGS IN CONTEXT IN THE
MEMORIES ON THE CHANNEL TODAY.
>> THANK YOU, HARRIS.
>> RIGHT NOW, A WILDFIRES IS
POSING A THREAT TO SAN
FRANCISCO.
THE WEST IS GETTING EATEN UP.
A CITY ROUGHLY 150 MILE PER HOUR
AND WHY THESE FLAMES COULD
AFFECT HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE NOW.
AND STAY IN CALIFORNIA FOR US.
SAN DIEGO MAYOR BOB FILNER
DENOTICES DOING ANYTHING WRONG.
WE REMEMBER HE SAID HE IS
A HUGGER.
AND ONE PERSON SAID HE COULD
MAKE THE LEGAL TROUBLES FOR
FILNER A LOT WORSE.
STAY CLOSE.
SHE LOVES A LOT OF
THE SAME THINGS YOU DO.
IT'S WHAT YOU LOVE ABOUT HER.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A
QUESTION OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME
THE MOMENT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS
THE ONLY DAILY ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED
AND SYMPTOMS OBPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL YOUR MEDICAL
CONDITIONS AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK  YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN 4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IYOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC
REACTIONS SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
LITTLE THINGS ANYONE CAN DO.
IT STEALS YOUR MEMORIES.
YOUR INDEPENDENCE.
ENSURES SUPPORT,
A BREAKTHROUGH.
AND SOONER THAN YOU'D LIKE.
SOONER THAN YOU'D THINK.
YOU DIE FROM
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
WE CURE ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE.
EVERY LITTLE CLICK, CALL
OR DONATION ADDS UP
TO SOMETHING BIG.
AS YOUR LIFE CHANGES,
FIDELITY IS THERE
R YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY,
HELPING YOU READJUST
ALONG THE WAY,
REFOCUS AS CAREERS CHANGE
AND KIDS HEAD OFF TO COLLEGE,
AND REVISIT YOUR INVESTMENTS
AS RETIREMENT GETS CLOSER.
WHEREVER YOU ARE TODAY,
FIDELITY'S GUIDANCE
CAN HELP YOU
FINE-TUNE
YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY.
START TODAY WITH A FREE
ONE-ON-ONE REVIEW
OF Y
EVERY DAY WE'RE WORKING TO
AND TO KEEP OUR COMMITMENTS.
AND WE'VE MADE A BIG
COMMITMENT TO AMERICA.
BP SUPPORTS NEARLY
250,000 JOBS HERE.
THROUGH ALL OF OUR
ENERGY OPERATIONS,
WE INVEST MORE IN THE U.S. THAN
ANY OTHER PLACE IN THE WORLD.
IN FACT, WE'VE INVESTED
OVER $55 BILLION HERE
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS -
MAKING BP AMERICA'S
LARGEST ENERGY INVESTOR.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS
NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
>> WILDFIRES ALERT.
FLAMES GAINING IN ON ONE OF OUR
COUNTRY'S NATIONAL TREASURES AND
POSING A PROBLEM FOR A MAJOR
CITY 150 MILES AWAY.
WE'LL EXPLAIN HOW THAT COULD
HAPPEN.
WITH THE IMMEDIATE THREAT OF
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
THE ONE OF 50 FOURS.
IT IS THE 16TH LARGEST FOUR IN
CALIFORNIA STATE HISTORY.
AN ARMY OF FIR FOIRT --
FIREFIGHTERS FIGHTING IT.
GOVERNOR JERRY BROWN ISSUED
A EMERGENCY DECLARATION FOR SAN
FRANCISCO.
THE FLAPS ARE A HAZARD FOR THE
UTILITY.
AND RENO, NEVADA.
THAT SMOKE IS A KILLER.
SMOKE WARNINGS LED TO EVENT
CANCELLATIONS.
ANDOM NICK IS LIVE FOR US IN
CALIFORNIA TONIGHT.
SAN FRANCISCO FACING POWER AND
WATER OUT AGES?
>> THAT IS RIGHT.
IT SOUNDS ASTONISHING
CONSIDERING IT IS 150 MILES
AWAY.
YOU HAVE A REZ VORTHAT PROVIDES
SAN FRANCISCO WITH 85 PERCENT OF
ITS WATER.
THE FIRE IS CLOSE TO THAT.
AND THAT IS THREATENING THE
WATER PIPES THAT ARE UP ABOVE
THE GROUND.
IF IT GETS THAT CLOSE IT COULD
DESTRUCT THE WATER SUPPLY.
AND WE HAVE HAD WOODEN POLLS
DOWN.
AND IT WILL CAUSE DISRUPTION IN
THE NOR FUTURE.
THEY ARE NOT SAYING HOW BAD IT
WOULD BE.
IT IS LIKELY AND THE SITUATION
IS OUT OF THE AUTHORITY'S
CONTROL.
>> I WAS READING EARLIER.
YOU GUYS ARE PART OF THE STORY
BECAUSE WHERE YOU ARE IS
PARTICULARLY VULNERABILITY.
WE ARE IN THE CITY OF TOULUMNE
EAST OF WHERE THE FIRE IS
HAPPENING.
2,004 FIRES ARE BROUGHT IN TO
PROTECT HUNDREDS OF HOMES AND
THE TOWN.
IT LOOKS LIKE THE WEATHER IS
GREAT BUT IT IS HEATING UP AND
IT IS MAKING THE FIRE WORST.
THE WINDOWS WILL GO UP TO 45
MILES PER HOUR AND IT WILL
ROCKET IT TO THE FEJ OF THE
TOWN.
WITH THE WINDS THAT STRONG
CONTAINMENT LINES CAN LOPE AND
ANYTHING OVER TEN MILE PER HOUR
IS GOING TO CLEAN BEYOND THE
CONTAINMENT ZONE AND WHY THEY
ARE DEDICATING THOSE ASSETS.
4,004 FIGHTS DEALING WITH THE
RIM FIRE.
>> IT IS SOMETHING YOU SAID.
THAT IS A LOT OF PEOPLE TO MOVE
AND EVACUATE AND CITY OF SAN
FRANCISCO MIGHT NOT HAVE
UTILITIES, WHERE DO YOU PUT
EVERYBODY?
>> EVERYBODY HERE IS UNDER
ADVISORY EVACUATION.
SOME HAVE GONE TO FAMILY
ELSEWHERE IN THE AREA.
BUT WHEN IT COMES TO SAN
FRANCISCO, PEOPLE WILL HAVE TO
SIT OUT THE ROLLING OUTAGES AND
WATER.
IT COULD TAKE DAYS OR WEEKS.
PUTTING THE FIRE OUT ALONE.
FIRE OFFICIALS WILL NOT GET ON
TOP OF IT UNTIL MID WEEK AND
THAT WOULD BE THE TURNING POINT
AND COULD BE MONTHS BEFORE THEY
CAN CHLOR THE AREA.
>> WE HOPE FOR THE BEST.
HE MENTIONED THE FORECAST.
40 MILES PER HOUR WINDOWS.
IT IS GETTING HOTTER.
WE'LL CHECK IN WITH JANA DEAN.
>> THE WHOLE WEST IS ON FIRE AS
WE LOOK AT THE FIRE DANGER MAP.
A LOT OF THOSE FIRES BURNED UP
IN CALIFORNIA AND ID A HO.
THERE IS THE RIM FIRE WHEREDOM
NICK IS.
AND FIVE PERCENT CONTAINMENT.
WINDS WILL PICK UP SOME CASES 20
OR 30 MILES PER HOUR.
AND TEMPERATURES WILL COLOFF AND
THEN ON SUNDAY A WARM DAY ON TAP
AND WINDS GUSTING 25 OR 30 MILES
PER HOUR.
THE FIRES ARE SO LARGE THEY CAN
CREATE THEIR OWN WEATHER SYSTEMS
AND WINDS.
BEEFER CROAK IN SUN VALLEY, 55
DEGREES TONIGHT AND
THUNDERSTORMS IN THE AREA.
IF I CAN SHE YOU WHERE WE ARE
SEEING THE THUNDERSTORM ACTIVITY
AND EAST OF SUN VALLEY A TORNADO
WARNING.
SOME OF THESE THUNDERSTORMS
COULD HAVE LIGHT NIPPING AND
SPARK MORE WILDFIRES DANGER AND
THREAT OF SEVERE WEATHER.
WE ARE WATCHING A TROPICAL STORM
IN THE PACIFIC THAT WILL BRING
MUCH NEEDED MOISTURE IN THE
SOUTHEAST BUT NOT REACHING THE
WILD FIRE AREAS WHERE THEY NEED
THE MOISTURE.
>> JANA, THANK YOU.
I LOVE THIS KIND OF NOWS,
A LITTLE GIRL WHO NEVER GAVE UP
HER WILL TO LIVE.
HERE IS A PROGRESS AND SHE WAS
A CHILD GETTING AN DULT SET OF
LUNGS.
LOOK AT HER NOW.
WE'LL HAVE AN UPDATE ON FORMER
VICE-PRESIDENT CHENEY AND HIS
DAUGHTER LIZ SHARING.
AND TALKING ABOUT A WIDE RANGE
OF TOPICS NOTHING OFF OF THE
TABLE ESPECIALLY TERROR THREATS.
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
AND GOES TO WORK IN SECONDS.
♪ TUM, TUM TUM TUM TUMS!
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
For a strong bag that
grips the can...
♪
get Glad ForceFlex.
Small change,
big difference.
ARE YOU KIDDING ME?
NO, IT'S ONLY 15 CALORIES.
[ Male Announcer ]
WITH REDDI WIP,
FRUIT NEVER SOUNDED
MORE DELICIOUS.
MMM.
[ Male Announcer ]
WITH 15 CALORIES PER SERVING
AND REAL CREAM,
THE SOUND OF REDDI WIP
IS THE SOUND OF JOY.
does your dog food have?
MMM.
[ Male Announcer ]
WITH 15 CALORIES PER SERVING
AND REAL CREAM,
18 percent?
20?
New Purina ONE True Instinct
has 30.
Active dogs crave nutrient-dense
food.
So we made Purina ONE True
Instinct.
Learmore at PurinaONE.com
it's a reality check.
I had my
reality check when
I'd be sitting there
with my friends
who had their Verizon phones
and I'd be sitting there like
"mine's still loading!"
I couldn't get email.
I couldn't stream movies.
I couldn't upload
any of our music.
That's when I decided
to switch.
Now that I'm on Verizon,
everything moves fast.
With Verizon,
I have that reliability.
I'm completely happy
with Verizon.
Verizon's 4G LTE
is the most reliable
and in more places than
any other 4G network.
Period.
That's powerful.
Verizon.
Get the Nokia Lumia 928
for free.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT ALEVE
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HER,
SHE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HER ALL DAY
TO SEE HOW IT GOES.
[ Claira ] AFTER THE DELIVERIES,
I WAS OKAY.
NOW THE CIABATTA IS DONE
AND THE PAIN IS STARTING AGAIN.
MORE PILLS? SERIOUSLY?
SERIOUSLY.
[ GROANS ]
ALL THESE STOPS TO TAKE
MORE PILLS CAN BE A PAIN.
CAN I GET MY ALEVE BACK?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY ALEVE.
[ Male Announcer ] LOOK FOR THE
EASY-OPEN RED ARTHRITIS CAP.
>> ON THE HUNT IN WASHINGTON
STATE FOR THE SECOND SUSPECT
ACCUSED IN THE DEADLY BEATING OF
A WORLD WAR II VETERAN.
82-YEAR-OLD DELL BETTER WAS
BEATEN TO DEATH.
ONE OF THE TONES 16-YEAR-OLD
TURNED HIMSELF IN.
OFFICERS ARE LOOKING FOR THE
ACCOMPLICE AND PLANNING TO
CHARGE THEM BOTH AS ADULTS.
CHARGES FOR MURDER AND ROBBERY.
PEOPLE IN THE COMMUNITY ARE
OUTRAGEDMENT
>> HE DIDN'T DESERVE THIS.
IT IS SO SENSELESS.
AND UNNECESSARY.
NOT FOR 50 BUCKS.
>> WE'LL NOT TOLERATE THAT TYPE
OF BEHAVIOR FROM 60 YEARS OLD OR
ANYONE ELSE IN THE COMMUNITY.
>> LAST NIGHT A FEW THOUSAND
PEOPLE PAID RESPECTS FOR BELTON
AND A AMERICAN FLAG PLACED IN
MEMORIAL TO HIM.
FORMER VICE-PRESIDENT CHENEY
JOINS HIS DAUGHTER ON STAGE.
THEY WERE BLUNT ABOUT A VARIETY
OF TOPICS INCLUDING THE UPCOMING
POLITICAL ELECTION AND PRESIDENT
OBAMA.
THE CHENEY'S SPOKE AN HOUR WITH
EMPHASIS.
>> THIS ADMINISTRATION DOESN'T
GET IT.
THEY JUST DON'T.
AND OBAMA MADE A SPEECH HERE NOT
TO LONG AGO ABOUT THREE
MONTHSING ON IN MAY, BASICALLY
SAID OKAY, NOW WE ARE RETURNING
TO THE PRE9/11 DAYS.
WE ARE NOT AT WAR.  WE ARE GOING
TO PRE9/11 AND IT IS JUST A LAW
ENFORCEMENT PROBLEM AND WE'LL
TRY TO ROUNDUP THE BAD GUY WHEN
THEY BLOW SOMETHING UP.
AND WE ARE NO LONGER ON A WAR
FOOTING IF YOU WILL.
I THINK THAT IS DEAD WRONG.
I THINK IT IS A TOTAL MISREADING
OF WHERE WE FIND OURSELVES
TODAY.
>> AS PRESIDENT GEORGE BUSH'S
SECOND IN COMMAND.
CHENEY HELPED TO DESIGN THE
CONTROVERSIAL NSA AND CONTINUED
SUPPORT IS EVIDENT.
HE SAID AMERICA IS UNDER THREAT
OF A TERRORIST ATTACK.
>> THE BIGGEST THREAT WE FACE IS
TERRORIST ARMED WITH SOMETHING
DEADLIER THAN AIRLINE TICKETS
AND BOX CUTTERS.
WE HAVE TO DEFOOT THAT THREAT.
>> HE DEFENDED THE DIRECTOR OF
THE NSA.
>> LAST THING I WOULD WANT TO
RECOMMEND OBAMA MIGHT ABUSE THE
NSA AUTHORITY AND THEREFORE SHUT
IT DOWN.
LAST POSSIBLE THING WE OUGHT TO
DO.
THEY ARE GOOD FOLKS DOING THE
BEST THEY CAN TO SAFE GUARD THE
NATION.
AND YOU KNOW, O
>> BOTH SAYING WHAT IS NOT
WORKING WITH THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION.
AND WHAT WILL WORK FOR
CONSERVATIVE.
>> IT CAN BE EASY IF YOU LISTEN
TO THE MAINSTREAM MEDIA TO THINK
THAT CONSERVATIVES ARE
A MINORITY AND THAT WE ARE
POWERLESS AND GOSH, WE OUGHT TO
BE DISCOURAGED ABOUT 2012 AND
SIT DOWN AND BE QUIET.
IF YOU START TO LOSE HOPE.
THINK ABOUT THIS.
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES, USED THE IRS, ABUSED THE
POWER OF HIS OFFICE TO GO AFTER
POLITICAL OPPONENTS.
HE WENT AFTER CONSERVATIVES AND
REPUBLICANS AND MEMBERS OF THE
TEA PARTY AND HAS THE IRS TO SAY
WHAT THEY SAY IN THEIR PLAYERS.
THAT IS UNAMERICAN AND TELLS YOU
SOMETHING ABOUT OUR POWER.
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES WOULD NOT BOTHER
TO USE THE IRS TO GO AFTER US IF
HE WAS NOT AFRAID OF EVERY
SINGLE ONE OF US.
AND AGAIN THAT WAS IN STEAM BOAT
SPRINGS, COLORADO.
>> MOMENTUM IS BUILDING FOR THE
WORLD TO TAKE ACTION IN SYRIA IN
THE WAKE OF NEW ACCUSATIONS OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
PRESIDENT OBAMA RECEIVED WHAT
THEY TELL US IS A DETAILED
REVIEW OF A RANGE OF OPTIONS AND
HOW TO RESPOND.
FORMER ARMY VICE CHIEF WILL JOIN
US LIVE SHORTLY.
A LOT TO ASK ABOUT THIS HOUR.
AND MORE SECRETS SPILLING OUT
ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT AGENCY THAT
IS MONITOR THE E-MAIL AND PHONE
CALLS.
YOU HEARD VICE-PRESIDENT CHENEY
TALKING WITH THE NSA.
THEY ARE ACCUSED OF USING
STATE-OF-THE-ART SPY GEAR TO
KEEP TABS ON THEIR LOVERS?
.
[ Male Announcer ]
THESE DAYS, A SMALL BUSINESS
CAN SAVE BY SHARING.
LIKE CARPOOLS...
POLLY WANTS TO KNOW
IF WE CAN PICK HER UP.
YEAH,
WE CAN MAKE ROOM.
YEAH.
[ Male Announcer ]
...OFFICE SPACE.
YES, WE'RE LOVING THIS
COMMUNAL SEATING. IT'S GREAT.
[ Male Announcer ]
THE BEST THING TO SHARE?
A DATA PLAN.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
ONE BUCKET OF DATA
FOR EVERYONE ON THE PLAN,
UNLIMITED TALK AND TEXT
ON SMART PHONES.
NOW, EVERYONE'S IN THE SPIRIT
OF SHARING.
HEY, CAN I BORROW YOUR BOAT
THIS WEEKEND?
NO.
[ Male Announcer ]
SHARE MORE. SAVE MORE.
AT&T MOBILE SHARE FOR BUSINESS.
♪
SEE, I KNEW TESTOSTERONE
COULD AFFECT SEX DRIVE,
BUT NOT ENERGY
OR EVEN MY MOOD.
THAT'S WHEN I TALKED
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD TESTS...
SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.
THAT'S IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.
[ Male Announcer ]
TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T
HAVE ANDROGEL
1.62% TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED
TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY
INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.
WOMEN AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WITH APPLICATION SITES.
DISCONTINUANDROGEL
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED SIGNS
OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,
WHICH MAY INCLUDE
CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE,
POSSIBLY DUE
TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER
OR WHO HAVE OR MIGHT HAVE
PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING,
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
WORSENING
OF AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,
POSSIBLE INCREASED RIS
OF PROSTATE CANCER,
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING
OF ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY,
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS,
PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP,
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICAL CONDITION
AND MEDICATIONS,
ESPECIALLY IULIN,
CORTICOSTEROIDS, OR MEDICINES
TO DECREASE BLOOD CLOTTING.
IN A CLINICAL STUDY, OVER 80%
OF TREATED MEN HAD THEIR
T LEVELS RESTORED TO NORMAL.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.
CHANGE YOUR NUMBER. TURN IT UP.
ANDROGEL 1.62%.
[ Male Announcer ]
STAYING WARM AND DRY
HAS NEVER BEEN OUR PRIORITY.
♪
CATERING TO
THE CONVENIENTLY LATED
HAS NEVER BEEN OUR PRIORITY.
OUR PRIORITY IS, WAS
AND ALWAYS WILL BE
SERVING YOU,
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
WE GET TO SEE EVERYONE
IN AMERICA ALMOST EVERY DAY.
AND WE'VE NOTICED THAT YOU'RE
SENDING AND RECEIVING
MORE PACKAGES THAN EVER.
SO WE WANTED TO GIVE YOU
A MORE RELIABLE WAY
TO SHIP THEM.
WITH IMPROVED PRIORITY MAIL
FLAT RATE.
DON'T JUST TAKE OUR WORD
FOR IT --
NOW WE'LL PROVE IT
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY
WITH TRACKING
UP TO ELEVEN SCANS,
SPECIFIED DELIVERY DATES,
AND FREE INSURANCE UP TO $50
ALL FOR THE SAME LOW RATE.
WE'LL NEVER STOP DELIVERING
FOR EVERY PERSON
IN THIS COUNTRY.
[ Woman ] WE ARE THE
UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.
[ Man ] WE ARE THE
[ Woman #2 ] WE ARE THE
UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.
[ Male Announcer ] WE ARE THE
AND OUR PRIORITY IS YOU.
GO TO USPS.COM®
AND TRY IT TODAY.
>> THIS IS THE FOX REPORT AND
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR AND TIME FOR
THE NEWS.
A DAY OF MARCHING ON OUR
NATION'S CAPITOL TO COMMEMORATE
MARTIN LUTHER KING'S I HAVE
A DREAM SPEEC SEEN BY MANY AS A
OF DR. KING'S EQUALITY FOR ALL
AMERICANS.
>> NOT ONLY MUST WE NOT BE
SATISFIED BUT FIGHT BACK BOLDLY,
TOO MANY OF OUR UNKNOWN HEROES
FOOT AND BLED AND DIED FOR US TO
HAVE THE PRECIOUS RIGHTS TO
VOTE.
>> IF YOU ARE JUST JOINING US.
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT THE
NEXT STEP IN SYRIA LOCKS LIKE.
THAT'S WHAT PRESIDENT OBAMA
TALKED ABOUT A SHORT TIME AGO
WITH THE NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM.
THEIR MEETING AFTER A REPORT
THAT SYRIA'S GOVERNMENT
AGAINOUSED DEADLY CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ON HIS CHILDREN.
WE CAN'T AUTHTENTICATE IT, WE
CAN'T WHETHER THEY ARE CORRECT
OR ROLE.
BUT THEY DO SUPPORT REPORTS THAT
A SUBURB OF DAMASCUS WAS HIT
WITH CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAID THE UNITED
STATES IS TRYING TO CONFIRM THE
REPORT.
ONCE THE FACTS ARE CLEAR
PRESIDENT OBAMA WILL MAKE
A DECISION TO RESPOND.
WE HAVE A FORMER VICE CHIEF OF
STATE AND CHAIRMAN.
I COULDN'T SAY THE WORD BUT I
THINK WE KNOW WHAT WE MEAN.
THE PICTURES ARE HARD TO VIEW,
BUT IF WE CAPTAIN DETERMINE,
GENERAL, WHERE THE TRUTH LIES,
WHETHER IT IS THE GOVERNMENT OR
REBELS BLAMED FOR THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS, WHAT SHOULD OUR
MILITARY MOVE BE?
>> I THINK WE CAN DETERMINE.
IT THE PRESIDENT SPOKE BY THE
EXPERIENCE HIS PREDECESSOR OVER
THE WMD IN IRAQ AND LACK OF
INACCURATE WILL BOW TO THE UN TO
DO WHAT THEY CAN DO.
ASSAD CAN PUSH BACK ON THE UN
THE WAY SADDAM HUSSEIN HUSSEIN
DID.
THE WAY TO GET THE VERIFICATION
IS THE DOCTORS AND OTHERS
TREATING THE PATIENTS KNOW WHAT
IT IS BY NOW AND ANY DOCTOR
LOOKING AT THE VIDEOS ALSO
KNOWS.
WE KNOW IT IS A CHEMICAL ATTACK
TAKING PLACE.
WHO DID IT IS THE ISSUE THEN?
WE HAVE INTELLIGENCE SERVICES ON
THE GROUND.
THEY SHOULD BE GIVEN THE MISSION
TO GO AND DO AN INVESTIGATION TO
GET AT THE ROCKETS THAT WERE
FIRED AND WHERE WERE THEY FIRED
FROM AND WITNESSES TO SEE THAT.
YOU CAN'T FOUR ROCKETS IN
A NEIGHBORHOOD AND NOT HAVE THE
PEOPLE PROVIDE TESTIMONY.
IT IS DISCERNIBLE RATHER
QUICKLY.
>> I WANT TO BE ABLE TO READ
FROM A STATEMENT THAT IS
A FREEDOM FREEDOM IN CANADA AND
ALSO FROM THE PRIME FREEDOM IN
THE UK.
IN THIS MEETING WITH THE
PRESIDENT SHORTLY AFTER PHONE
CALLS WERE MADE AND OTHER
COUNTRIES ARE BEING TALKED TO.
CAN WE PUT WORDS ON THE SCREEN.
SERIOUS RESPONSE ARE BEING
TALKED ABOUT THIS FROM THE
BRITAIN PRIME MINISTER AND
SIGNIFICANT USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS WOULD MERIT A SERIOUS
RESPONSE FROM THE INTERNATIONAL
COMMUNITY AND BOTH HAVE ASKED
OFFICIALS TO EXAMINE ALL OF THE
OPTIONS.
WHAT WOULD THAT LOOK LIKE
EXACTLY?
>> IN TERMS OF OUR OPTIONS,
HARRIS?
>> RIGHT.
>> CERTAINLY.
LET'S GET INSIDE OF ASSAD'S
HEAD.
HE'S USING CHEMICAL WEAPONS
AGAINST A NEIGHBORHOOD IN
EASTERN DAMASCUS BECAUSE THE
REBELS SEIZED THE NEIGHBORHOOD
FOR A NUMBER OF WEEKS AND
DESPITE AIR POWER AND MILITARY
HE IS UNSUCCESSFUL IN DISLODGING
THEM AND HE USED THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS AND HE HAS REASONED
BEGIN HIS INTRODUCTION OF
CHEMICAL WEAPON IN THE PAST AND
NO REACTION TO IT, THAT NUMBER
ONE, THE UNITED STATES WILL
PROBABLY NOT ACT AND NUMBER TWO,
IF THE UNITED STATES DOES ACT, I
BELIEVE THAT ASSAD'S CALCULATION
BELIEVES IT WILL BE A STATEMENT
ATTACK DESIGNED TO RESTORE
PRESIDENTIAL CREDIBILITY THAN AN
ATTACK ON A SIGNIFICANT MILITARY
CAPABILITY THAT IS DESTROYED OR
REDUCED DRAMATICALLY.
THAT IS HIS HEAD AND WHAT HE'S
THINKING ABOUT.
>> GENERAL, WHAT I KNOW YOU SAID
IN THE PAST.
THERE IS A BIG DIFFERENCE TONE
A STATEMENT ATTACK AND WHAT YOU
THINK IS REALLY NECESSARY HERE.
WHAT IS THAT DIFFER?
>> IT IS DRAMATIC.
OPTIONS AVAILABLE TO US IS SEIZE
AND SECOWER CHEMICAL STORAGE.
WE HAVE TO TAKE THE INTEGRATED
AIR DEFENSE TO FLY OUR AIR IN
THERE.
AND WE WOULD NOT DO THAT UNDER
THE CIRCUMSTANCE.
AND SECONDLY WHAT IS AVAILABLE
TO US.
AND MORE LIKELY IS TO STAND OFF
IN THE MED TERRANNIAN AND
SURFACE SHIP SUBMARINE AND USED
PRECISION GUYEDED AMMUNITION IN
SYRIA THAT WILL BE OF VALUE TO
HIM.
I BELIEVE WE SHOULD USE THIS
OPPORTUNITY NOT TO MAKE
A STATEMENT ATTACK BUT ELIMINATE
AND DEGRADE ONE OF HIS MAJOR
CAPABILITIES AND THE FIRST ONE
HE VALUES IS AIR POWER.
THIS IS SIX MAJOR AIR FIELDS AND
TAKE THE INFRASTRUCTURE DOWN AND
AMMUNITION AND AIRPLANE THEM AND
CREATOR THE RUN AWAY.
AND WE HAVE TO DESTROY THE
INFRASTRUCTURE AND COMMAND AND
CONTROL FOR SOMETIME HE WILL NOT
BE ABLE TO USE AIR POWER AND
THAT IS SOMETHING HE IS NOT
EXPECTING TO HELP HIM FRANKLY.
>> WHEN WE HAVE GONE DOWN THE
ROAD BEFORE.
WE SEE MISSION CREEP.
WHERE WE GO IN WITH A MISSION
AND KROEP AWAY AND NEXT THING
YOU KNOW, WE ARE THERE TWO
YEARS.
HOW DO WE GET IN AND OUT AND
WHAT IS THE MISSION?
>> THERE IS NO ENTERTAINING THE
THOUGHT OF BEING ON THE GROUND
WITH OUR TROOPS IS WHERE YOU GET
IN MISSION CREEPS AND MORE
MISSION AND CHALLENGES.
>> YOU DON'T SEE US GOING IN
FROM THE GROUND AT ALL.
JUST FROM THE AIR.
>> WE HAVE INTELLIGENCE SERVICES
ON THE GROUND AND ANY CONFLICT
OF INTEREST AND NO, WE'LL NOT
PUT ANYBODY IN THE GROUND.
IT WOULD BE CRUISE AND TOMAHAWK
AND STAND OFF.
WE WOULD NOT HAVE TO TAKE OUT
THE INTEGRATED AIR SYSTEM.
WE MAY SHOOT AT THE BATTERIES
AND BE VIRTUALLY VULNERABLE TO
THE AIR SYSTEM AND THE SUCCESS
OF WHAT WE ARE DOING WOULD BE
HIGH.
AND LISTEN, HARRIS, THIS IS THE
SWEET SPOT OF THE UNITED STATES
MILITARY CAPABILITY AND WE KNOW
HOW TO DO IT VERY WELL AND WE
HAVE DONE IT IN THE PAST.
WE CAN ABSOLUTELY RENDER
A SIGNIFICANT BLOW TO HIM IF WE
CHOOSE TO DO THAT USING HIS
CHEMICAL WEAPONS AS A REASON FOR
IT.
>> WE SHOULDN'T BE IN THIS
POSITION RIGHT NOW.
IF THEY CROSS THE REDLINE BY
USING CHEMICAL WEAPONS WHICH WE
HAVE REPORTS AND PICTURES
PREVIOUSLY AND WE DIDN'T DO
ANYTHING AFTER THAT THREAT AND
YOU SAY WE DIDN'T HOLD A STRONG
LINE THEN?
>> YOU KNOW, IT IS SO
FRUSTRATING TO WATCH THIS
HAPPEN.
WE HAVE HAD MULTIPLE PRESIDENTS
FROM WORLD WAR II ON DEVELOP THE
HUGE STAT URT OF THE UNITED
STATES IN THE WORLD AND IN TERMS
OF CREDIBILITY AND TRUST AND WE
MAKE A SOMETHING THAT IS GOING
TO HAPPEN BECAUSE THIS IS THE
UNITED STATES AND WE ARE
SQUANDERING IT TO PEOPLE OPENLY
TALK ABOUT THE UNITED STATES
BEING FECKLESS AND THEY HAVE
LOST THEIR WILL ET CETERA.
AND SO CLEARLY WE SHOULD HAVE
ACTED BEFORE IN MY JUDGMENT.
AND I THINK WE PROBABLY WILL ACT
NOW BECAUSE THERE IS CONSENSUS
IN THE INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY
AND THE PRESIDENT AND
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY TO
PARTICIPATE ON THIS.
I JUST HOPE WE DO SOMETHING
MILITARY SIING CAN AND NOT JUST
A STATEMENT ATTACK.
>> BEFORE I LET YOU GO.
THE PENTAGON IS PUTTING THOSE IN
THE REGION AND MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE ARE MOVING ACROSS THE
BORDER THERE.
IN FACT, THE NUMBER OF SYRIAN
REFUGEE CHILDREN IS AT 1
MILLION.
I AM WONDERING WHAT CAN WE DO
ABOUT THE PEOPLE CAUGHT IN THE
MIDDLE?
IS THAT PART OF OUR MISSION,
TOO?
>> ONLYECTIVELY WAY TO DEAL WITH
THE PROBLEM IS TO CHANGE THE
MOMENTUM IN FAVOR OF THE REBELS
SO THE REGIME CAN TOPPLE AND WE
PROVIDE THE ASHES ASSISTANCE
THAT IS NECESSARY.
WE HAVE HUNDRED THOUSAND AND IF
WE LET IT GO ON.
IT WILL GO ON TO 200,000 AND
MULTIMILLIONS OF PEOPLE
DISPLACED FROM THEIR HOMES WHICH
IS 2 MILLION NOW AND IT WILL
TRIPLE AND ALSO MILLIONS THAT
WILL BE REFUGEES IN A HORRIFIC
SITUATION THAT IS.
AND THE PRESSURE ON JORD AN AND
TURKEY IT IS SIGNIFICANT IF WE
CONTINUE TO LET IT UNFOLD THE
WAY ASSAD WANTS IT TO UNFOLD.
I CAN AUTHTENTICATE YOU ARE THE
REAL DEAL.
WE ARE GRATEFUL FOR YOUR
EXPERIENCE.
ALWAYS GOOD TO TALK TO YOU,
HARRIS.
>> A MATTER OF NATIONAL
SECURITY, IT DOES NOT APPEAR
THAT WAY.
EMPLOYEES THAT NATIONAL SECURITY
AGENCY USED THE FEDERAL AGENCIES
ENORMOUS POWER OF SURVEILLANCE
TO SPY ON THEIR LOVERS.
THE AGENCY SAID SUCH ACTIVITY IS
VERY RARE MOSTLY INVOLVING
OVERSEAS COMMUNICATION AND
PARTNER AND SPOUSES THAT THEY
ARE LOOKING OUT FOR AND MOST
INCIDENTS WERE SELF REPORTED AND
THEY GOT CAUGHT AND WENT FORWARD
FIRST.
HAFT WEEK THE NSA CONFESSED TO
VIOLATING PRIVACY RULES THENS OF
TIMES A YEAR.
IN A PRISON RIOT.
THE WRONG PEOPLE ARMED.
LOOK AT WHAT THE INMATES HAD IN
THEIR POSSESSION AND IT WAS
DEADLY.
THIS IS IN SPAIN AND SPANISH
TRADITION MAKING A AMERICAN
DEBUT.
RUNNING OF THE BULLS RIGHT HERE
IN THE UNITED STATES.
WHOO HOO.
CLEARANCE EVENT THE DODGE WAY?
FIRST WAIT TILL SUMMER.
THEN GET THE CARS READY.
NOW ADD THE DODGE PART.
♪
THE DODGE SUMMER
CLEARANCE EVENT.
RIGHT NOW GET 0% FINANCING FOR
TO 72 MONTHS
AND NO PAYMENTS FOR 90 DAYS ON
ALL DODGE VEHICLES.
AND THIS PARK
IS THE INSIDE OF YOUR BODY.
YOU SEE T SPECIAL
PSYLLIUM FIBER IN METAMUCIL
AUALLY GELS TO TRAP
AND REMOVE SOME WASTE.
AND THAT GELLING ALSO HELPS
TO LOWER SOME CHOLESTEROL.
IT EVETRAPS SOME CARBS
TO HP MAINTAIN
HEALTHY BLOOD SUGAR LEVELS
AS PART OF YOUR DIET.
NOW THAT'S ONE
SUPER HARD WORKING FIBER.
METAMUCIL.
3 AMAZING BENEFIT
IN 1 SUPER FIBER.
♪
ACCOMPLISHING EVEN LITTLE THINGS
CAN BECOME MAJOR VICTORIES.
I'M PHIL MICKELSON, PRO GOLFER.
WHEN I WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS,
MY RHEUMATOLOGIST
PRESCRIBED ENBREL
FOR MY PAIN AND STIFFNESS,
AND TO HELP STOP JOINT DAMAGE.
[ Male Announcer ]
ENBREL MAY LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS
INCLUDING INFECTIONS,
TUBERCULOSIS,
LYMPHOMA, OTHER CANCERS,
NERVOUS SYSTEM
AND BLOOD DISORDERS,
AND ALLERGIC REACTIONS
HAVE OCCURRED.
BEFORE STARTING ENBREL,
YOUR DOCTOR SHOULD TEST YOU
FOR TUBERCULOSIS
AND DISCUSS WHETHER
YOU'VE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL INFECTIONS
ARE COMMON.
YOU SHOULD NOT START ENBREL
IF YOU HAVE AN INFECTION
LIKE THE FLU.
TELL YOUR DOCT
IF YOU'RE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,
HAVE CUTS OR SORES,
HAVE HAD HEPATITIS B,
HAVE BEEN TREATED
FOR HEART FAILURE,
OR IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS PERSISTENT FEVER,
BRUISING, BLEEDING,
OR PALENS.
NCE ENBREL HELPED RELIEVE
MY JOINT PAIN,
IT'S THE LITTLE THINGS
THAT MEAN THE MOST.
ASK YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST
IF ENBREL IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
[ Doctor ] ENBREL,
THE NUMBER ONE BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
PRESCRIBED BY RHEUMATOLOGISTS.
HUMANS.
EVEN WHEN WE CROSS OUR t's
AND DOT OUR i's,
WE STILL RUN INTO PROBLEMS.
NAMELY, OTHER HUMANS.
WHICH IS WHY
AT LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE,
TO POLICIES COME
WITH NEW CAR REPLACEMENT
AND ACCIDENT FORGIVENESS
IF YOU QUALIFY.
SEE WHAT EE COMES STANDARD
AT LIBERTYMUTUAL.COM.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT'S YOUR POLICY?
>> THE SITUATION IS GETTING MORE
SERIOUS FOR THE EXMAYOR WHO IS
A HUGGER.
THERE IS A CRIMINAL
INVESTIGATION ON BOB FILNER AND
IN OFFICE NINE MONTHS.
THE CITY COUNCILIL APPROVED
A DEAL TO HELP WITH LEGAL BILLS.
AT LEAST 18 WOMEN A COWED
CENT-YEAR-OLD FILNER OF
HARASSING THEM AND HE DENIES THE
WRONGDOING.
A BABY BREAKS OUT IN A PRISON
AND SOMEHOW A BABY IS CAUGHT UP
IN THE VIOLENCE.
BOLIVIA,
THE COUNTRY'S LARGEST PRISON
BURNING.
INMATES IN ONE CELLBLOCK
ATTACKED INMATES IN
A NEIGHBORING BLOCK WITH
COMBOIFS AND MACHETES.
AND THEY KNOCKED
A HOLE-IN-THE-WALL AND 30 PEOPLE
WERE KILLED INCLUDING A 18 MONTH
OLD BABY.
UNITED NATION COMPLAINED TO
BOLIVIA ABOUT CHILDREN LIVE
NOTHING THE CHILDREN.
>> IN COLOMBIAING RI CULTURE
WORKERS PROTESTING.
>> THE FARMERS WANT SUBSIDIES TO
PAY FOR FERTILIZER.
MEXICO, SCHOOL TEACHERS IN
MEXICO CITY CAUSING TRAFFIC JAMS
AND BLOCKING ACCESS TO THE MAIN
AIRPORT.
THEY ARE ON STRIKE ANGRY OVER
EDUCATION REFORPS LIKE THE
INTRODUCTION OF TEACHER
EVALUATION.
TRAVELLERS HAD TO WALK ALONG THE
HIGHWAY TO CATCH THEIR FLIGHTS.
>> CHINA, HAPPY ONE 16TH
BIRTHDAY TO THE YOUNGEST IN THE
WORLD.
IF YOU WANT TO LIVE A LONG TIME
EAT EVERYTHING AND COPE MOVING
AND NEVER GET ANGRY.
>> PROMISING NEWS TO SHARE WITH
YOU ABOUT DOUBLE LUNG TRANSPLANT
PATIENTS.
LITTLE SARAH.
HER MOM HOSTED ON BOCK BOCK.
TWO AND HALF YEARS ON OXYGEN
SARAH IS OFFICIALLY OFF OXYGEN.
SARAH SUFFERS FROM SIFTIC IF I
BROSIS AND NEEDED A DOUBLE LUNG
TRANSPLANT TO SURVIVE.
HER PARENTS FOUGHT THE COURTS TO
GET HER ON THE TRANSPLANT LIST.
SHE IS RECOVERING AND CELEBRATED
HER 11TH BIRTHDAY EARLIER THIS
MONTH.
AND I TWEETED OUT GO, SARAH.
>> A MUSIC LEGEND'S VOICE
SILENCED BY A DEVASTATING
ILLNESS.
LINDA RONSTADT
♪ I AM GOING BACK COME WHAT MAY
TO BLUE BA YOU.
♪ WHERE THE WORLD IS MINE ON
BLUE BA YOU.
Reinforced with scratch-
resistant glass
and a unibody
Made Kevlar Strong.
Okay Google Now.
Call My Droid.
The new
Droid Ultra by Motorola.
When strength matters,
Droid Does.
>> PARKINSON DISEASE HAS TAKEN
AWAY THE SINGINGITAL EPS OF
LINDA RONSTADT.
SHE IS 67 YEARS OLD AND
DIAGNOSED AND CANNOT SING
A NOTE.
SHE BEGAN SHOWING SYMPTOMS EIGHT
YEARSING ON AND THOUGHT THAT THE
TREMT BLIPPING IN HER HANDS WAS
DOW TO A SHOULDER OPERATION.
SHE WAS A HUGE ARTIST IN THE
$0.19 ASKS SELLING MILLIONS OF
RECORDS WITH HITS LIKE BLUEBA
YOU.
AND YOU ARE NO GOOD AND WHEN
WILL I BE LOVED.
OCEANEC SCIENTIST ARE TRYING TO
UNRAVEL A DEADLY MYSTERY.
250 DOLPHENS HAVE DIED IN THE
NORTHERN SHORES.
THEY HAVE NO IDEA WHAT KILLED
THEM BUT HAVE SUSPICION.
>> IT IS THE WHY THAT IT HAS
SCIENTIST SHAKEN UP.
THEY HAVE WASHED UP AND DOWN THE
OAST COAST.
TEN TIMES THE AVERAGE FOR THIS
TIME OF YEAR AND NOW SCIENTIST
SAY A VIRUS MAY BE TO BLAME.
IT IS THE LARGEST DOLPHEN DO I
OUT SINCE 1987 WHEN 740 ANIMALS
DIED AND SCIENTIST EXPECTS THE
NUMBER OF DEATHS TO RISE.
IT IS ALL TO FAMILIAR SIGHT
SHOCKING BEACH GOERS.
>> ALL OF THE SUDDEN, WE STARTED
SEEING THEM ON THE BECH ALL UP
AND DOWN THE BEACH.
IT IS DOWN ON THE BEACHES LIKE
THAT, THERE IS SOMETHING WRONG.
SOMETHING IS VERY WRONG.
I HOPE WE FIND OUT SOON.
>> IN JULY IN AUGUST.
253 BOTTLE NOSE DOLPHINS WASHED
ASHORE.
AND 64 IN NEW JERSEY AND 25 IN
NEW YORK.
SCIENTIST PERFORMING THE
NEAUTOPSIES BELIEVE THIS A BILLY
VOIRS MAY BE TO BLAME AND
SIMILAR TO MEASLES IN HUMANS.
NDOLPHINS ARE COHESIVE GROUPS OF
ANIMALS AND VERY SOCIAL WITH
EACH OTHER IN THE GROUPS THEY
TRAVEL IN AND SO A LOT OF
DISEASES PROBABLY PASS BETWEEN
EACH OTHER.
THROUGH THAT CLOSE CONTACT.
>> SCIENTIST SAY IF YOU SO AN
ANIMAL ON THE BEACH REMAIN
A SAFE DISTANCE AWAY.
MARINE MAMMALS CARRY A LOT OF
DIFFERENT DISEASES, HARRIS.
>> IT MAY BE AN AMERICAN
TRADITION NOW.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO GO TO SPAIN TO
RUN WITH THE BULLS AND WE TOLD
YOU IT IS GOING TO HAPPEN AND
OUCH, IT'S HERE.
This day calls you.
To fight chronic
osteoarthritis pain.
To fight chronic low
back pain.
To take action.
To take the next step.
Today, y will know you did
something for your pain.
Cymbalta can help.
Cymbalta is a pain reliever
FDA-approved to manage chronic
musculoskeletal pain.
One non-narcotic pill
a day, every day,
can helpeduce this pain.
Tell your doctor right away if
your mood worsens,
you have unusual changes
in mood or behavior
or thoughts of suicide.
Anti-depressants can increase
these in children,
teens, and young adults.
Cymbalta inot for children
under 18.
People taking MAOIs, linezolid
or thioridazine or with
uncontrolled glaucoma should
not take Cymbalta.
Taking it with NSAID pain
relievers, aspirin,
or blood thinners may increase
bleeding risk.
Severe liver problems, some
fatal, were reported.
Signs include abdominal pain
and yellowing skin or eyes.
Tell your doctor about all your
medicines, including those for
migraine and while on Cymbalta,
call right away if you have
high fever, confusion and stiff
muscles or serious allergic
skin reactions like blisters,
peeling rash, hives, or
mouth sores to address possible
life-threatening conditions.
Talk about your alcohol use,
lir disease and before you
reduce or stop Cymbalta.
Dizziness or fainting may occur
upon standing.
Take the next step.
Talk to your doctor.
Cymbalta can help.
For a strong bag that
grips the can...
♪
get Glad ForceFlex.
Small change,
big difference.
But as time passed, I stted to
notice Max just wasn't himself.e
And I knew he'd feel better if
heost a little weight.
So I switched to Purina Cat ow
Healthy Weight formula.
I just fed the recommended
amount...
And they both loved the taste.
After a few months Max's
"speal powers" returned...
And I got my hero back.
Purina Cat Chow Healthy Weight.
♪ THE JOINT IS JUMPIN'
♪ IT'S REALLY JUMPIN'
OSTEO BI-FLEX®
HELPS STRENGTHEN
YOUR JOINTS.°
LIKE CALCIUM SUPPLEMENTS
CAN HELP YOUR BONES,
OSTEO BI-FLEX®
CAN HELP YOUR JOINTS°
SO YOU CAN KEEP DOING
WHAT YOU LOVE.
♪
OSTEO BI-FLEX...
THE BEST STUFF IN THE JOINT.™
NOW IN JOINT AND MUSCLE FORMULA
FOR PEOPLE THAT DEMAND
EVENORE FROM THEIR BODIES.
>> A SPANISH TRADITION AND GREAT
BULL RUN CUBED OFF IN VIRGINIA.
CLOSE THAT FENCE.
AND THOUSANDED OF PEOPLE
INSPIRED BY RUNNING OF THE BULLS
IN SPAIN.
NEXT UP TEXAS AND FLORIDA.
I AM GOING TO HAVE TO GO SEE.
THAT ANIMAL RIGHTS ACTIVIST
DON'T LIKE IT BUT SAY THEY WILL
BE MONITORING IT ALL.
PRESIDENT OBAMA MET WITH THE
NATIONAL SECURITY TIME TO TALK
ABOUT THE NEXT STEPS WE TAKE IN
SIR WHY AND THEY ARE WORKING TO
CONFIRM THE REPORTS OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK IN THAT COUNTRY,
THE WHITE WHITE SAID THE
PRESIDENT RECEIVED A DETAILED
REVIEW ON OPTIONS OF HOW TO
RESPOND.
HE SPOKE WITH BRITISH FREEDOM
FREEDOM DAVID CAME RON AND THEY
EXPRESSED CONCERNS.
PEOPLE MARCHING DOWN THE
NATIONAL MALL TO THE MARTIN
LUTHER KING MEMORIAL AND
COMMEMORATING 50 YEARS ON
WASHINGTON AND MARTIN LUTHER
KING'S I HAVE A DREAM SPOECH.
THE OLDEST SON OF THE
SUFFICIENTLY RIGHT'S LEADER SAID
THE JOURNEY IS NOT COMPLETE.
AUTHTENTICATE.
I HAVE HEARD FROM MY MOTHER AND
SEVERAL VOWERS.
I WILL WRITE IT ON A CHALK
BOARD.
AUTHICATE HASH TAG.
HAVE FAITH IN ME, I WILL GET.
IT I AM HARRIS FAULKNER.
THANKS FOR WATCHING.
WE LOVED HAVING YOU A LONG.
HUCKABEE STARTS IN SIX SECONDS.
TONIGHT ON HUCKABEE, WITH THE
SIGNATURE LEGISLATION BROKE THE
PRESIDENT IS BLAMING
REPUBLICANS.
>> ONE UNIFYING PRINCIPLE IN THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY AT THE MOMENT
IS MAKING SURE THAT 30 MILLION
PEOPLE DON'T HAVE HEALTH CARE.
IT IS NOT ONLY THE GOP THAT
DOESN'T LIKE OBAMA CARE.
>> IT IS A HUGE TRAIN WRECK.
>> THE A CA IS THE MOST COMPLEX
POSE OF LEGISLATION PASSED BY
THE UNITED STATES CONGRESS.
>> DEMOCRATS AND IRS AND YOUNS
AND MAJOR ISSUES WITH OBAMA
CARE.
THE PRESIDENT SAID NO ONE HAS
A BETTER PLAN.
>> SOME SAY WE DON'T HAVE