HAT IS IT FOR
"SPECIAL REPORT," I'M
SHANNON BREAM PROUD AND
FEARLESS TONIGHT GOOD
NIGHT FROM WASHINGTON.
>> Shepard: THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT.
TONIGHT, DRAMATIC VIDEO OF
A SHOOTING IN THE STREETS
OF A MAJOR CITY.
AS COPS TAKE DOWN SOME
ACCUSED ATTACKERS.
PLUS, A BRIDGE COLLAPSES.
RIGHT INTO THE WATER.
>> JUST HOLDING ON FOR DEAR
LIFE AT THAT POINT.
YOU GO WITH IT.
>> Shepard: DRAMATIC
STORIES OF SURVIVAL AFTER
CARS PLUNGE INTO A RIVER.
>> RESCUE THESE THREE
PEOPLE FROM THE WATER WAS
REALLY A EXTRAORDINARY.
>> Shepard: TONIGHT, NEW
CLUES ABOUT WHAT CAUSED THE
COLLAPSE.
PLUS, THE JODI ARIAS
FIASCO.
>> NO UNANIMOUS AGREEMENT,
SIGN FOREPERSON.
>> Shepard: NOW A NEW JURY
MAY GET TO DECIDE WHETHER
ARIAS SHOULD DIE OR
TEACHING SPANISH AND
DONATING HER HAIR AFTER
STABBING HER EX-BOYFRIEND
27 TIMES.
AND --
>> WHAT HAPPENED THAT
EVENING WAS UNPRECEDENTED.
>> Shepard: ALMOST SEVEN
MONTHS AFTER SUPER STORM
SANDY, A MAJOR TOURIST
ATTRACTION MAKES A BIG COME
BACK JUST IN TIME FOR
MEMORIAL DAY.
BUT FIRST FROM FOX THIS
FRIDAY NIGHT THE COLLAPSE
OF A MAJOR INTERSTATE
BRIDGE.
AND DRIVERS WHO WERE
CROSSING A RIVER SUDDENLY
FOUND THEMSELVES IN THAT
RIVER.
IT HAPPENED IN WASHINGTON
STATE A PORTION OF I-5
PLUNGED INTO THE WATER LAST
NIGHT AFTER INVESTIGATORS
SAY A BIG RIG WITH WITH AN
OVERSIZED LOAD RAMMED INTO
AN OVERHEAD GERDER.
YOU CAN SEE HOW IT DUMPED A
JUMBO OF CONCRETE INTO THE
RIVER THAT 18-WHEELER MADE
IT ACROSS THE BRIDGE.
EMERGENCY CREWS REPORT TWO
CARS DID NOT.
THEY SENT RESCUE BOATS TO
REACH THE THREE PEOPLE WHO
WERE INSIDE THOSE CARS.
THEY SAY NONE OF THEM IS
SERIOUSLY HURT.
>> FORTUNATELY, I'M
EXTREMELY FORTUNATE THAT
NOBODY DIED AS A RESULT OF
THIS.
WE WERE FORTUNATE IT
HAPPENED LATER IN THE DAY
INSTEAD OF, YOU KNOW,
DURING RUSH HOUR TIME.
THE IMPACT ON FOR
WASHINGTON STATE AND THE
PEOPLE LIVING IN THIS AREA
AND COMMERCE ON THE WEST
COAST IS GOING TO BE PRETTY
SIGNIFICANTLY IMPACTED
BECAUSE THIS IS THE MAJOR
INTERSTATE ROADWAY FOR THE
THE WEST COAST TO THE
UNITED STATES.
>> Shepard: IN FACT IT'S
THE MAIN LINK BETWEEN
SEATTLE AND VANCOUVER.
TRANSPORTATION OFFICIALS
ESTIMATE AN AVERAGE OF
71000 VEHICLES CROSS THAT
BRIDGE EVERY DAY AND
TONIGHT WE ARE LEARNING
MORE ABOUT THE TRUCK THAT
SUPPOSEDLY BROUGHT IT DOWN.
IT'S FOX TOP STORY AND DAN
SPRINGER IS ON IT
MT. VERNON IN WASHINGTON
TONIGHT.
DAN?
>> YEAH, SHEP.
IT WAS A TRUCK DRIVER FROM
ALBERTA, CANADA WHO HAD A
LOT OF EXPERIENCE HAULING
OVERSIZED LOADS, EVEN
THOUGH HE HAD A LOT OF
EXPERIENCE, HE HAD A LOCAL
DRIVER, A GUIDE WITH HIM
AND ALSO A PERMIT IT WAS A
TRIP THAT WENT HORRIBLY
WRONG.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THAT THE
TRUCK WAS TRAVELING IN THE
FAR RIGHT LANE.
AND IT HIT THE OVERHEAD
STEEL GIRDER AT ITS LOWEST
POINT IF HE HAD BEEN IN THE
MIDDLE LANE HE LIKELY WOULD
HAVE CLEARED IT UP.
DRUG AND ALCOHOL NOT A
FORK.
TRUCK DRIVER HAS NOT BEEN
ARRESTED.
BOTH DRIVERS WHO PLUNGED
INTO THE RIVER ARE TALKING
ABOUT THE FRIGHTENING
CHERNS.
20-YEAR-OLD BRICE KENNING
WAS SIMPLY HEADING TO PLAY
HOCKEY.
>> I WATCHED THIS BRIDGE
COLLAPSE GOING 60 MILES PER
HOUR.
SLAM ON THE BRAKES THERE IS
NOT MUCH YOU CAN DO IN THAT
SPLIT SECOND IT WAS WAS
LIKE SOMETHING OUT OF A
MOVIE, YOU KNOW.
>> THE NATIONAL
TRANSPORTATION SAFETY BOARD
HAS A GO TEAM ON THE GROUND
HERE AND STARTED ITS
INVESTIGATION.
WASHINGTON STATE GOVERNOR
JAY ENDSLEY DECLARED A
STATE OF EMERGENCY IN THREE
SURROUNDING COUNTIES
BECAUSE OF THE ECONOMIC
IMPACT OF HAVING THIS MAIN
THOROUGHFARE FOR SEVERAL
MONTHS IT TO COME.
ESTIMATED REPAIR COST OF
$15 MILLION.
THE FEDS HAVE PLEDGED
$1 MILLION TO GET THE JOB
MOVING THERE ARE WAYS
AROUND THIS MESS.
THEY WILL FILL UP QUICKLY.
THE FIRST BIG TEST SHEP
WILL BE THIS HOLIDAY
WEEKEND.
>> Shepard: WORKERS BUILT
THAT BRIDGE IN 1955.
THE FEDS DESCRIBE IS AS
FUNCTIONALLY OBSOLETE.
MEANING ITS DESIGN WAS
OUTDATED.
IT WAS NOT AMONG THE 11% OF
U.S. BRIDGES WHICH
TRANSPORTATION OFFICIALS
WARN ARE STRUCTURALLY
DEFICIENT.
THAT'S HOW ENGINEERS
DEFINED THE I-25 BRIDGE IN
MINNEAPOLIS.
REMEMBER THAT?
IT COLLAPSED COLLAPSED COLLAPSED IN
2007.
A COLLAPSE THAT KILLED 13
PEOPLE.
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC
HOLDER APPROVED A REQUEST
FOR A WARRANT TO SEARCH FOX
NEWS CORRESPONDENT JAMES
ROSEN PHONE RECORDS AND
PERSONAL EMAILS.
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
OFFICIALS CONFIRMED THAT
TODAY SAYING THE DEPARTMENT
TOOK GREAT CARE IN DECIDING
THAT A SEARCH WARRANT WAS
NECESSARY VETTING THE
DECISION AT THE HIGHEST
LEVELS OF THE DEPARTMENT,
INCLUDING DISCUSSIONS WITH
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL.
THE DOCUMENT REFERRED TO
JAMES ROSEN AS A POSSIBLE
COCONSPIRATOR IN A NATIONAL
SECURITY LOCATE.
JUST YESTERDAY PRESIDENT
OBAMA SAID JOURNALISTS
SHOULD NOT FACE LEGAL
ACTION FOR DOING THEIR
JOBS.
HE HAS ASKED THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL TO WORK WITH THE
MEDIA TO REVIEW THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT'S GUIDELINES FOR
INVESTIGATIONS THAT INVOLVE
CORRESPONDENTS.
DOUG McKELWAY ON THIS
STORY LIVE IN OUR D.C.
NEWSROOM.
DOUG?
>> GOOD EVENING, SHEP.
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT'S
ACKNOWLEDGMENT THAT
ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC
HOLDER SIGNED OFF ON THE
JAMES ROSEN SEARCH WARRANT
IS THE LATEST IN WHAT MANY
BELIEVE TO BE A SHIFTING
NARRATIVE BY THE NATION'S
TOP LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICER
ON MAY 15TH HE
CATEGORICALLY DENIED
INVOLVEMENT IN THE
PROSECUTION OF REPORTERS
WHO RECEIVED LEAKED
INFORMATION.
WITH REGARD TO THE
POTENTIAL PROSECUTION OF
THE PRESS FOR DISCLOSURE OF
MATERIAL THAT IS NOT
SOMETHING THAT I HAVE EVER
BEEN INVOLVED AND HEARD OF
OR WOULD THINK WOULD BE A
WISE POLICY.
IN FACT, MY VIEW IS QUITE
THE OPPOSITE.
>> THAT VERY SAME MORNING,
ON NPR, HE OFFERED A
DIFFERENT RESPONSE WHEN
ASKED HOW OFTEN HIS
DEPARTMENT HAD OBTAINED
JOURNALIST PHONE RECORDS.
>> I'M NOT SURE HOW MANY OF
THOSE CASES I HAVE ACTUALLY
SIGNED OFF ON.
I TAKE THEM VERY SERIOUSLY.
I KNOW THAT I HAVE REFUSED
TO SIGN A FEW.
PUSHED A FEW BACK FOR
MODIFICATIONS.
>> WHEN ASKED HOW MANY
REQUESTS FOR SEARCH
WARRANTS OR SUBPOENAS OF
JOURNALISTS HE HAD TURNED
DOWN COULDN'T REMEMBER
THAT WOULD BE SOMETHING I
WOULD WANT TO KNOW IF YOU
MY I WAS ON THE DEFENSIVE
AND THE PRESIDENT HAD JUST
EXPRESSED CONFIDENCE IN HE
ME.
THIS IS TRULY AMAZING
CRITICS ARE DERIDING
INVESTIGATING REPORTERS
CALLING IT A CASE OF THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL
INVESTIGATING HIMSELF.
OTHERS BELIEVE HOLDER IS
TRYING TO STRIKE A BALANCE
BETWEEN PROTECTING NATIONAL
SECURITY AND PRESS FREEDOM.
THE DOJ SAID IN ITS
STATEMENT TODAY THAT IT
FOLLOWED ALL APPLICABLE
LAWS AND THAT A FEDERAL
MAGISTRATE OKAYED IT
DETERMINING THERE WAS,
INDEED, PROBABLE CAUSE FOR
A SEARCH WARRANT.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: DOUG, THANKS.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS SEXUAL
ASSAULT IS A THREAT TO THE
UNITED STATES MILITARY.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SPOKE AT
THE U.S. NAVAL ACADEMY
GRADUATION TODAY AND SAID
MISCONDUCT BY EVEN A FEW
SERVICE MEMBERS CAN HURT
THE ENTIRE INSTITUTION.
>> THOSE WHO COMMIT SEXUAL
ASSAULT ARE NOT ONLY
COMMITTING A CRIME THEY
THREATENED THE TRUST AND
DISCIPLINE THAT MAKES OUR
MILITARY STRONG.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO BE
DETERMINED TO STOP THESE
CRIMES.
BECAUSE THEY HAVE GOT NO
PLACE IN THE GREATEST
MILITARY ON EARTH.
>> Shepard: EARLIER THIS
MONTH A PENTAGON REPORT
ESTIMATED 26,000 SERVICE
MEMBERS WERE VICTIMS OF
SEXUAL ASSAULT LAST YEAR
ALONE.
BUT ONLY ABOUT 3300
REPORTED THE ATTACKS.
AMATEUR VIDEO CAPTURED THE
MOMENT POLICE OPENED FIRE
ON TWO MEN, TWO MEN ACCUSED
OF HACKING TO DEATH A
BRITISH SOLDIER.
IT HAPPENED IN BROAD
DAYLIGHT ON A BUSY SOUTH
LONDON STREET.
[EXPLOSION]
[GUNFIRE]
[BLEEP]
>> Shepard: YOU HEARD THE
GUNSHOTS AS POLICE CLOSED
IN ON THOSE SUSPECTS ON
WEDNESDAY.
BOTH SURVIVED.
THEY ARE NOW IN THE
HOSPITAL.
THE STEPFATHER OF THE
VICTIM DELIVERED AN HE
EMOTIONAL STATEMENT TODAY
FROM THE FAMILY WITH THE
AFGHAN WAR VETERAN'S MOTHER
AND WIDOW CRYING BESIDE
HIM.
>> REST IN PEACE.
WE LOVE YOU SO MUCH.
AND YOU DIDN'T DESERVE
THIS.
YOU FOUGHT FOR YOUR COUNTRY
AND DID IT WELL.
YOU WILL ALWAYS BE OUR
HERO.
[INAUDIBLE]
>> Shepard: ONE OF THE
ACCUSED KILLERS RANTED IN
FRONT OF THE CAMERA ON
VIDEO HOLDING KNIVES WITH
WHAT APPEARED TO BE BLOOD
ON HIS HANDS.
POLICE ARE ALSO REPORTEDLY
QUESTIONING ANOTHER MAN IN
THIS CASE AFTER ARRESTING
HIM JUST YESTERDAY.
BRITISH AUTHORITIES SAY
THEY HAVE ARRESTED TWO
PASSENGERS FOR REPORTEDLY
THREATENING TO TYKE DOWN
COMPLECIAL HEADLINER
ACCOMPLISH ESCORTED TO TO
THE GROWNT SAFELY.
THE THEY WILLS THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS DESTROY
THE PLANE AFTER ARGUING
WITH THAT CREW DURING THE
FLIGHT.
THEY SAY HE THIS ARE
TREATING IT AS A CRIMINAL
CASE AND DO NOT EXPECT ANY
LENGTHS.
JURY SAYS JODI ARIAS' OWN
TESTIMONY MAY HAVE HURT HER
CHANCES.
THAT AND WHAT TO LOOK FOR
NEXT.
JURY DEADLOCKED WHETHER SHE
SHOULD DIE FOR HER CRIME.
THE BIG CITY MAYOR WHO HAS
FINALLY RESPONDED TO THE
ACCUSATIONS THAT HE SMOKES
CRACK.
AND QUITE A RESPONSE.
AHEAD FROM THE ISLES JS OF
FOX NEWS ON THIS FRIDAY FOX
REPORT.
[ Female Announcer ]    AT WELLS FARGO
WE'RE WORKING    AROUND THE CLOCK
TO HELP PROTECT YOUR MONEY    AND
FINANCIAL    INFORMATION.  HERE'S
YOUR  TEMPORARY CARD.  WELCOME BACK.
HOW WAS LONDON?    [ Female Announcer
]    WHEN PEOPLE TALK,    GREAT THINGS
HAPPEN.  ♪ ♪    [ Male Announcer ]
PURPOSE ELEVATES WHAT WE DO.    RAISES
IT TO A MORE    MEANINGFUL PLACE.
MAKES US LIVE WHAT WE DO,    LOVE
WHAT WE DO    AND FILLS OUR WORK
WITH REWARDING POSSIBILITY.    AARP
CONNECTS YOU    TO A COMMUNITY
OF EXPERIENCED WORKERS    AND HAS
TOOLS TO HELP YOU FIND    WHAT YOU'RE
GOOD AT.    AN ALLY FOR REAL POSSIBILITIES.
AARP.    GO TO AARP.ORG/POSSIBILITIES.
♪ ♪    [ Male Announcer ] A CAR THAT
CAN ACTUALLY SEE LIKE A HUMAN    USING
STEREOSCOPIC CAMERAS  ♪ ♪    AND EVEN
STOP ITSELF    IF IT HAS TO.  ♪ ♪
THE TECHNOLOGY    MAY BE HARD TO IMAGINE...
BUT WHY YOU WOULD WANT IT    IS NOT.
THE 2014 E-CLASS,    SEE YOUR AUTHORIZED
MERCEDES-BENZ DEALER    FOR EXCEPTIONAL
OFFERS    THROUGH MERCEDES-BENZ
FINANCIAL SERVICES.
Why are twice as many people  choosing
Verizon  over any other carrier?
Many choose us because we have  the
largest 4GLTE network.
Others, because of our  reputation
for reliability.
Or maybe it's because  we've received
JD Power
and Associates' customer service
award 4X in a row.
In the endthere are countless reasons.
But one choice.
What makes a Sleep Number
store different?  You walk into a
conventional mattress store,
it's really not  about you.
They say, "Well, if you  want a firm
bed
you can lie on one of those.
We provide the exact  individualization
that your body needs.
Oh, yeah!
Once you experience it
there's no going back.
Now save on the  closeout of our Classic
Special Edition bed set
just $1,299, a savings of $600
plus 36 month financing on all  beds
through Memorial Day
Only at the Sleep Number store
Sleep Number  Comfort individualized
>> Shepard: A FOX URGENT
NOW JUST INTO FOX NEWS.
A FEDERAL JUDGE HAS JUST
RULED THAT SHERIFF JOE
ARPAIO USED HIS OFFICE IN
ARIZONA TO RACIALLY PROFILE
IMMIGRATION PATROLS.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME A JUDGE
HAS RULED ON THIS ISSUE
AGAINST A GUY WHO CALLS
HIMSELF THE TOUGHEST
SHERIFF IN AMERICA.
A GROUP OF THAT LATEEN
KNOWS FILED A LAWSUIT
CLAIMING DEPUTIES PULLED
OVER DRIVERS JUST TO CHECK
THEIR IMMIGRATION STATUS.
DRIVING WHILE BROWN.
THE JUDGE RULED THE
DEPUTIES ALSO DRAGGED OUT
THOSE TRAFFIC STOPS.
SO FAR NO RESPONSE FROM
SHERIFF JOE ARPAIO.
JOEST ARIAS WAS NOT A GOOD
WITNESS.
THOSE WERE SOME OF THE
FIRST PUBLIC RARNTION FROM
THE JURY FOREMAN ONE DAY
AFTER JURORS REVEALED THEY
WERE HOPELESSLY DEADLOCKED
OVER WHETHER SHE SHOULD
LIVE OR DIE.
THE FOREMAN SPOKE TO ABC'S
GOOD MORNING AMERICA.
DID HE NOT COMMENT ON THE
FEJT PHASE OF HER MURDER
TRIAL ITSELF.
HE DID EXPLAIN WHY JODI
ARIAS MAY HAVE HURT HER OWN
CASE BY TAKING THE STAND.
>> WE'RE CHARGED WITH GOING
IN TO PRESUMING INNOCENCE
RIGHT?
BUT SHE WAS ON THE STAND
FOR SO LONG THERE WERE SO
MANY CONTRADICTING STORIES.
>> Shepard: PROSECUTORS SAY
JODI ARIAS STABBED HER
EX-BOYFRIEND 27 TIMES, SHOT
HIM AND SLIT HIS THROAT.
ARIAS INITIALLY SAID SHE
KNEW NOTHING ABOUT THE
MURDER.
THEN SHE BLAMED IT ON
INTRUDERS WEARING MASKS AND
THEN TESTIFIED THAT SHE DID
SHOOT HIM IN SELF-DEFENSE.
OF COURSE, THE MURDER
CONVICTION STANDS.
BUT THE JUDGE SAYS IT'S NOW
UP TO A NEW JURY TO
DETERMINE WHETHER SHE GETS
THE DEATH PENALTY.
ADAM HOUSLEY IS LIVE IN OUR
WEST COAST NEWSROOM.
THIS CAN'T BEGIN UNTIL,
WHAT, JULY AT THE VERY
EARLIEST.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, SHEPARD.
THE JUDGE SET DOWN JULY AS
THE DATE THAT A NEW JURY
WOULD BE IMPANELED
BASICALLY.
THEY WOULD HAVE TO GO
THROUGH THE ENTIRE JURY
SELECTION AGAIN.
CLIFF NOTES OF THE TRIAL TO
DETERMINE WHETHER OR NOT
JODI ARIAS WOULD GET THE
DEATH PENALTY OR NOT.
THIS HAS HAPPENED FIVE
TIMES IN BEFORE IN ARIZONA
WHERE THERE HAS BEEN A HUNG
JURY.
OF THOSE FIVE TIMES FOUR
TIMES THE D.A. HAS DECIDED
THEY WON GETTING THE DEATH
PENALTY VERDICT.
IF THE D.A. DOES STICK TO
HIS GUNS AND SAY HE IS
GOING TO TRY TO GO FOR THE
DEATH PENALTY AND CALL THIS
JURY AS THE JUDGE HAS
DIRECTED IN JULY IT MAY BE
A GOOD SIGN FOR THE D.A.
AND A BAD SIGN FOR JODI
ARIAS.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> THEY ARE GOING TO BE
TOLD THAT THEY NEED TO
ASSUME THAT THIS WAS
PLANNED, PREMEDITATED
MURDER.
HE THEY ARE GOING TO HEAR
HOW HEINOUS IT IS.
AND THIS JURY IS GOING TO
BE A LOT MORE LIKELY TO
HAVE NO AUTO FIN AT THIS OR
CONNECTION WITH JODY AND
JUST SAY THIS IS A
CALCULATED, PREMEDITATED
MASSACRE.
AND THIS NEW JURY, SHEPARD,
AGAIN, IF IT DOES GO
FORWARD IN JULY ALSO
WOULDN'T HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITY TO SEE JODI
ARIAS ON TELEVISION.
WHY?
BECAUSE SHERIFF JOE ARPAIO
SAID NO MORE TV INTERVIEWS
FOR MS. ARIAS.
SHEPARD?
>> Shepard: TRAVIS
ALEXANDER'S FAMILY TOLD US
THE FAMILY DOES NOT WANT TO
GIVE UP ON DEATH PENALTY.
TODAY ON "STUDIO B" SHE
EXPLAINED WHY.
>> WHILE SHE IS ON THE
STAND FOR HER 18 DAYS,
THERE IS SEVERAL POINTS
THAT SHE MADE THAT A LOT OF
US WERE THERE FOR AND WE
KNOW SHE IS LYING.
IF THERE WAS A THIRD OPTION
TO HAVE HER ON DEATH ROW
AND IT WOULDN'T MATTER ONE
WAY OR ANOTHER WHETHER SHE
WAS PUT TO DEATH OR NOT BUT
SHE WAS IN THAT SECLUSION
WHERE SHE WAS ISOLATED
THAT WOULD BE GREAT.
BUT IF THAT'S NOT AN
OPTION, THEN DEATH IS THE
OPTION THAT THE FAMILY
WANTS.
THEY WANT HER TO IT BE ON
DEATH ROW.
>> Shepard: SHE ADDED TODAY
THAT NOT SURPRISINGLY THE
VICTIM'S RELATIVES HAVE
HAVING A REALLY HARD TIME.
THE MAYOR OF TORONTO DOES
NOT SPOKE CRACK.
THAT'S THE WORD FROM THE
MAYOR OF TORONTO.
HE HELD A NEWS CONFERENCE A
WEEK AFTER STARTING -- WE
STARTED HEARING ABOUT A
VIDEO THAT REPORTEDLY SHOWS
THE MAYOR INHALING FROM A
GLASS CRACK PIPE.
WE HAVE NOT SEEN THAT VIDEO
OURSELVES.
THE MAYOR, ROB FORD SAYS
HIS LAWYER HAD WITHIN    --
BEEN ADVISING HIM NOT TO
COMMENT ON THE WHOLE THING.
TODAY HE PUBLICLY DENIED
USING CRACK AND SAID THE
MEDIA IS OUT TO GET HIM.
ONE COUNSELOR SAYS HE
DOESN'T BUY THE MAYOR'S
STORY AND CALLED FOR THE
MAYOR TO RESIGN.
THE DEADLY TORNADO HIT TWO
SCHOOLS SEVERAL CHIRP DIED
AT PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY.
NOW THEY SAY IT'S
REMARKABLE THAT EVERYBODY
AT BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY
SURVIVED.
WE ARE LIVE AT THAT SCHOOL
NEXT.
PLUS, NOW WE KNOW THE STORY
BEHIND A PHOTO A PHOTO OF
A WOMAN CARRYING HER
DAUGHTER THROUGH A FIELD
LITTERED WITH DEBRIS.
WOULDYOU WILL HEAR FROM THE
MOTHER AHEAD AS FOX REPORTS
LIVE TONIGHT.
♪ 'CAUSE YOU MAKE ME FEEL  SO RIGHT
♪  ♪ EVEN IF IT'S SO WRONG ♪  ♪ I
WANNA SCREAM OUT LOUD ♪  ♪ BOY,  BUT
I JUST BITE MY TONGUE ♪  ♪ THIS ONE'S
FOR THE GIRLS  MESSIN' WITH BOYS ♪
♪ LIKE HE'S THE MELODY  AND SHE'S
BACKGROUND NOISE ♪  [ VOLUME DECREASES
]  THANKS, MOM!  HAVE FUN!  YOU TOO.
♪ ♪  ♪ ♪
>> Shepard: IN THE FOUR
DAYS SINCE THAT TORNADO
RIPPED APART MOORE
OKLAHOMA WE HEARD A LOT
ABOUT THE SEVEN CHILDREN
WHO DIED INSIDE PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
YOU WILL REMEMBER THE STORM
DESTROYED NOT ONE BUT TWO
SCHOOLS THAT DAY.
JOHN ROBERTS IS LIVE IT THE
BRIAR WOOD ELEMENTARY.
THE BUILDING CRUMBLED
AROUND THE STUDENTS AND
THEIR TEACHERS.
JOHN?
>> SHEP GOOD EVENING TO
YOU.
THIS IS THE NEIGHBORHOOD
IMMEDIATELY ACROSS THE
STREET FROM BRIAR WOOD
SCHOOL.
THIS USED TO BE ALL OF THE
HOMES WHERE THE STUDENTS
WHO WENT TO THAT SCHOOL
USED TO LIVE.
WE WILL TAKE YOU INSIDE
THAT SCHOOL WITH A MEMBER
OF THE URBAN SEARCH AND
RESCUE TEAM IN JUST A
SECOND AND SHOW WHAT YOU IT
LOOKS LIKE INSIDE.
FIRST OF ALL, THE STORY OF
A BRIAR ROAD ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL TEACHER AND THE
TERRIFYING ORDEAL THAT SHE
AND HER ENTIRE FAMILY WENT
THROUGH INSIDE THAT SCHOOL.
AT BRIAR ELEMENTARY
TEACHERS SALVAGED WHAT
THINK COULD BEFORE THE
SCHOOL IS DEMOLISHED.
>> I HONESTLY DIDN'T THINK
WE WERE GOING TO MAKE IT.
COBB AND THREE CHILDREN
BARELY ESCAPED WITH THEIR
LIVES.
THEIR THOUGHTS ARE WITH
THOSE AT THE OTHER SCHOOL
HOMES WHERE ONE OF HER
STUDENTS DIDN'T MAKE IT.
I FEEL SO BAD FOR THOSE
FAMILIES CAFNTED EVEN
IMAGINE IF INSTEAD OF
HUGGING MY BABIES I WAS
PLANNING THEIR FUNERALS.
>> THIS IS SOME OF THE
CLASSROOMS.
>> THIS IT IS REMARKABLE
THAT THERE WEREN'T ANY
DEATHS AT BRIAR WOOD
ELEMENTARY SAYS THE FIREMAN
AS I TAKES ME THROUGH THE
SHATTERED SCHOOL.
>> WHEN YOU LOOK AT THIS
COULD YOU IMAGINE THIS CAME
APART THIS VIOLENT ACKENNED
NO ONE WAS KILLED?
>> I JUMPED OVER HERE.
>> POLICE OFFICER JOHN
BLEUM THAT WAS AMONG THE
FIRST RESPONDERS ON THE
SCENE.
>> WHEN THE LADY AT THE
FRONT WHEN I RAN THROUGH
SHE IS YELLING SECOND GRADE
IS TRAPPED.
SECOND GRADE IS TRAPPED.
I KEPT ON RUNNING.
>> A CLASSROOM NOW MORE
THAN RUBBLE HE FOUND TWO
TEACHERS AND 18 STUDENTS.
>> THE KIDS WERE BACK
UNDERNEATH THIS AROUND THE
CORNER HUNKERED DOWN, SOME
OF THEM LAYING DOWN FLAT
AND THINGS LIKE THAT.
>> HE GOT THE STUDENTS OUT
BUT THEIR TEACHER SCREAMED
THAT SHE WAS STUCK.
>> I SAID I KNOW.
I'M GOING TO GET YOU OUT.
SHE SAID NO, I'M STUCK TO
THE TABLE.
THERE IS SOMETHING IN MY
LEG.
AND WHEN I LOOKED THERE WAS
A TABLE LEG THROUGH HER
RIGHT CALF.
>> SHE HAD BEEN IMPALED.
>> SHE HAD BEEN IMPALED,
YES.
>> SO IT TURNED OUT THAT
JOHN BLUMENTHAL HAD TO HAND
HER A POCKET KNIFE TO
UNSCREW THE LAST SCREW THAT
WAS HOLDING THAT LEG ON.
THEY PUT HER IN THE BACK OF
THE PICKUP TRUCK AND TOOK
HER TO THE HOSPITAL.
SHE IS OKAY.
YOU CAN SEE WITH LA DONNA
COBB THE LASTING EFFECTS OF
THAT WALL FALLING ON HER.
SHE HAS A BRUISED FACE
STAPLES IN THE BACK OF HER
HEAD SHE WILL GET OUT NEXT
WEEK.
>> Shepard: WE SHOWED A
PHOTO OF A MOM CARRYING HER
DAUGHTER THROUGH THE FIELD
NEAR THE PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
THAT PHOTO WAS ON THE FRONT
PAGE OF THE NEWSPAPERS
ACROSS THE NATION AND
AROUND THE WORLD.
AT THE TIME WE DIDN'T KNOW
WHO THESE PEOPLE WERE OR
WHAT HAD BECOME OF THEM BUT
NOW WE DO.
THE MOM IS LATISHA GARCIA.
SHE SAID SHE'D HAD BEEN
RACING THE TORNADO TO GET
TO IT HER DAUGHTER JASMINE
A THIRD GRADER.
THE TORNADO MADE IT THERE
BEFORE MOM DID.
>> STARTED RUNNING TOWARDS
THE SCHOOL, I ASKED THE
TEACHER WHERE MY
DAUGHTER -- WHERE HER CLASS
WAS, AND SHE SAID THEY ARE
STILL TRYING TO PULL THEM
OUT AND RIGHT WHEN I RAN
UP TO ASK IF I COULD HELP
START PULLING PEOPLE OUT
TRY TO HELP SOME GUY JUST
HANDED HER TO ME.
>> Shepard: THE LITTLE GIRL
SAYS SHE HAD BEEN BURIED
UNDER BRICKS AND OTHER
DEBRIS AT THAT SCHOOL.
SHE SAYS RESCUERS SAVED HER
AND THEN SOMEBODY HANDED
HER TO HER MOM WHO CARRIED
HER THROUGH THAT FIELD TO
SAFETY.
JASMINE SAYS SHE WASN'T
SURPRISED TO SEE THE MOM.
THE GIRL'S WORDS I KNOW SHE
IS ALWAYS THERE FOR ME.
THEIR HOUSE IS GONE BUT
TONIGHT BOTH MOM AND
DAUGHTER ARE OKAY.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL IS
REVIEWING THE WAY THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
INVESTIGATES JOURNALISTS
BUT REPUBLICANS ARE SAYING
SOMEBODY ELSE SHOULD BE
DOING THAT REVIEW.
TONIGHT THE WHITE HOUSE
RESPONDS.
PLUS THE IRS OFFICIAL WHO
REFUSED TO ANSWER QUESTIONS
ON CAPITOL HILL ALSO
REPORTEDLY REFUSED TO
RESIGN.
WE'LL GET THE LATEST ON THE
PLANS TO TRY TO FORCE HER
TO TALK.
AND PASSENGERS SAY THEY
LOOKED OUT THE AIRPLANE
WINDOW AND SAW SMOKE
POURING FROM THE ENGINE.
WE'LL SHOW YOU WHAT
HAPPENED NEXT AS WE
APPROACH THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR AND THE TOP OF THE
NEWS.
n ocean
in a three-hundred-ton rocket
doesn't raise as much  as an eyebrow
for these veterans of the sky.
However, seeing this little  beauty
over international waters
is enough  to bring a traveler to
tears.
We're putting the wonder  back into
air travel
one innovation at a time.
The new American is arriving.
ALL STATIONS COME OVER TO  MISSION
A FOR A FINAL GO.  THIS IS FOR REAL
THIS TIME.
STEP SEVEN POINT  TWO ONE TWO.
RIFY AND LOCK.
COMMAND IS LOCKED.
FIVE SECONDS.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
STANDING BY FOR CAPTURE.
THE MOST INNOVATIVE  SOFTWARE ON THE
PLANET...
DRAGON IS CAPTURED.
IS CONNECTING TODAY'S LEADING  COMPANIES
TO PLACES BEYOND IT.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
[ Female Announcer ]    THE ONLY PATCH
FOR THE TREATMENT    OF MILD TO MODERATE
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE    IS EXELON PATCH.
NOW WITH    MORE TREATMENT OPTIONS
EXELON PATCH MAY IMPROVE    OVERALL
FUNCTION AND COGNITION.    YOUR LOVED
ONE CAN GET    A FREE 30-DAY TRIAL.
AND YOU CAN HAVE    ACCESS TO NURSES.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE    HOW THE DISEASE
PROGRESSES.    HOSPITALIZATION
AND RARELY DEATH,    HAVE BEEN REPORTED
FROM WEARING    MORE THAN ONE PATCH
AT A TIME.    THE MOST COMMON SIDE
EFFECTS    ARE NAUSEA, VOMITING, DIARRHEA
FALL, LOSS OF APPETITE    OR WEIGHT,
APPLICATION SITE REDNESS,    AND URINARY
TRACT INFECTION.    THE LIKELIHOOD
AND SEVERITY    OF THESE SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCREASE    AS THE DOSE INCREASES
OR IF PATIENTS    WEIGH LESS THAN
110 POUNDS.    PEOPLE AT RISK    FOR
STOMACH ULCERS    WHO TAKE    CERTAIN
OTHER MEDICINES    SHOULD TALK TO
THEIR DOCTOR    AS SERIOUS STOMACH
PROBLEMS    SUCH AS BLEEDING MAY WORSEN.
PATIENTS MAY EXPERIENCE    SLOW HEART
RATE.    FREE TRIAL OFFER FOR THEM.
NURSES TO TALK TO FOR YOU.    VISIT
EXELONPATCHOFFER.COM.  ♪ ♪
HEY, IT'S ME  PROGRESSIVE INSURANCE.
YOU KNOW, FROM OUR 4,000  TELEVISION
COMMERCIALS.
YEP, THERE I AM WITH FLO.
HOO-HOO! WATCH IT!
[Chuckles] ANYHOO, 3 MILLION  PEOPLE
SWITCHED TO ME LAST YEAR,
SAVING AN AVERAGE  OF $475.
[Sigh] IT FEELS GOOD  TO HELP PEOPLE
SAVE...
WITH GREAT DISCOUNTS LIKE  SAFE DRIVER,
MULTICAR,
AND MULTIPOLICY.
SO CALL ME TODAY.  YOU'LL BE GLAD
YOU DID.
CANNONBOX!
[SPLASH!]
>> Shepard: AN ATTACK ON
AID WERKSZ IN AFGHANISTAN
TRIGGERED A GUN BATTLE THAT
WENT ON FOR HOURS.
IT HAPPENED IN KABUL'S
FANSEST NEIGHBORHOOD THEY
DESCRIBE IT.
CAR BOMBER BLASTED THE GATE
OF AN ITALIAN
ORGANIZATION'S COMPOUND AND
THEN TALIBAN ATTACKERS
STORMED THE PLACE WITH
GRENADE LAUNCHERS THEN THE
GUN BATTLE STARTED.
AFGHAN POLICE SAY THEY TOOK
COVER AND SHOT IT OUT WITH
THE THE ENEMY FIGHTERS FOR
HOURS.
SECURITY FORCES SAY THEY
FINALLY RAIDED THE COMPOUND
AND ENDED THE STANDOFF.
THEY SAY TWO GUARDS AND ALL
SIX ATTACKERS DIED.
ALL THE WORKERS MADE IT OUT
ALIVE.
A MASSIVE FIRE GENERATES
HEAT SO INTENSE THAT SCREWS
FIGHTING IT HAVE TO STAY AT
LEAST A BLOCK AWAY.
AND THAT TOPS OUR NEWS
AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
BRAZIL.
HAPPENED IN A FUEL DEPOT ON
THE NORTHERN OUTSKIRTS OF
RIO.
FOLKS IN THE AREA SAY THEY
HEARD LOUD EXPLOSIONS
BEFORE THE FLAMES BROKE
OUT.
OFFICIALS EVACUATED THE TWO
BLOCK AREA AROUND THE
FACILITY.
NOBODY HURT.
INVESTIGATORS LOOKING INTO
WHAT CAUSED THE FIRE.
SWEDEN.
RIOTING IN THE CAPITAL CITY
OF STOCKHOLM FOR THE FIFTH
NIGHT IN A ROW.
DEMONSTRATORS SET DOZENS OF
CARS ON FIRE.
THE PROTESTS BEGAN SUNDAY
OVER THE RECENT POLICE
SHOOTING OF AN ELDERLY MAN
IN A STOCKHOLM SUBURB.
COPS SAY HE WAS SWINGING A
MACHETE AND THAT THEY FIRED
IN SELF-DEFENSE.
SEVERAL POLICE OFFICERS ARE
STILL IN THE HOSPITAL AFTER
GETTING HURT IN THE
VIOLENCE.
CHINA.
HEAVY RAINS TRIGGERED
MASSIVE MUD SLIGHT IN A
CENTRAL PROVINCE.
THE MUD CUT OFF ROADS AND
STRANDED SOME LOCALS.
RESCUE WORKERS USED ROPES
TO GET THEM TO SAFETY.
CREWS EVACUATED EVERYBODY
FROM THE AREA, INCLUDING
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE LIVING
IN TENTS SINCE AN
EARTHQUAKE LAST MONTH
DESTROYED THEIR HOMES.
NO WORD OF ANYBODY HURT.
SAUDI ARABIA.
DON'T TRY THIS AT HOME.
EXTREME MOTOR SPORT
ENTHUSIASTS CALL IT
SIDEWALK SKIING.
THE DRIVER BALANCES A CAR
ON TWO WHEELS WHILE PEOPLE
CLING TO THE OUTSIDE.
FOLKS SAY THE OPEN ROADS IN
THE COUNTRY'S NORTHERN
DESERT ARE IDEAL FOR IT AND
THAT'S A WRAP ON THIS FOX
TRIP AROUND THE WORLD IN 80
SECONDS.
>> Shepard: ONE FALLEN TREE
IN VIETNAM KNOCKED OUT
POWER TO A THIRD OF THE
COUNTRY.
A STATE ELECTRICAL COMPANY
REPORTS THAT A CRANE
OPERATOR KNOCKED A TREE ON
TO A MAIN TRANSMISSION
LINE ONE THAT FEEDS POWER
TO 22 OF VIETNAM'S 63
PROVINCES.
THEY DIDN'T GET THE LIGHTS
BACK ON FOR 10 HOURS.
I'M SHEPARD SMITH.
THIS IS "THE FOX REPORT."
IT'S THE BOTTOM OF THE
HOUR, TIME FOR THE TOP OF
THE NEWS.
AND THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
NOW CONFIRMS THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL ERIC HOLDER HIMSELF
APPROVED THE SEARCH WARRANT
THAT LET THE FEDS ACCESS
FOX NEWS CORRESPONDENT
JAMES ROSEN'S PHONE RECORDS
AND PERSONAL EMAIL.
DOCUMENTS SHOW
INVESTIGATORS GOT THAT
ACCESS BY CLAIMING JAMES
ROSEN MIGHT HAVE BROKEN THE
LAW.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS HE IS
WORRIED THAT LEAK
INVESTIGATIONS WILL KEEP
JOURNALISTS FROM HOLDING
GOVERNMENT ACCOUNTABLE, SO
HE IS GIVING THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL LESS THAN TWO
MONTHS TO REVIEW JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT GUIDELINES WITH
INPUT FROM THE MEDIA.
ED HENRY IS ON THE FOX TOP
STORY LIVE FROM WASHINGTON
TONIGHT.
ED REPUBLICANS SAY LETTING
THE A.G. REVIEW HIMSELF IS
KIND OF A WAY OF CUTTING
HIM SOME SLACK?
>> SURE, SHEP, BECAUSE THE
PRESIDENT AND ATTORNEY
GENERAL ARE VERY CLOSE.
THE PRESIDENT HAS DEFENDED
HIM BEFORE DURING PREVIOUS
POLITICAL FIRE STORMS LIKE
THE FAST AND FURIOUS GUN
RUNNING INVESTIGATION FOR
EXAMPLE AND THE FORMER BUSH
WHITE HOUSE CHIEF OF STAFF
ANDY CARD TOLD US TODAY
THAT AT THE VERY LEAST WITH
THE ATTORNEY GENERAL SHOULD
DO IS FIND SOME INDEPENDENT
PERSON EITHER WITHIN THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT OR
OUTSIDE TO COME IN AND
ACTUALLY LEAD THIS REVIEW.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> WELL I HOPE THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL WOULD SAY
I AM NOT GOING TO
INVESTIGATE MYSELF.
I'M GOING TO APPOINT THIS
PERSON WHO I AM NOT GOING
TO DIRECT TO TAKE A LOOK AT
IT.
>> NOW, SENIOR DEMOCRATS
THOUGH TELL ME THAT'S NOT
GOING TO HAPPEN.
THEY BELIEVE INSIDE THE
HOUSE THAT IN FACT THIS
WILL BE A THOROUGH
INVESTIGATION.
AND THE BOTTOM LINE IS I'M
HEARING FROM DEMOCRATS
CLOSE TO THE WHITE HOUSE
THE PRESIDENT IS NOT HAPPY
WITH WHAT WAS DONE WITH
JAMES ROSEN.
THE IDEA THAT HE MIGHT BE A
CRIMINAL COCONSPIRATOR.
THEY REALIZE THAT WAS A
GOVERNMENT OVERREACH AND
THAT'S WHY THE PRESIDENT
HAS DEMANDED THIS REVIEW
SHEP.
>> Shepard: WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIALS INSIST THEY WILL
NOT PROTECT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY SAY LOOK NO FURTHER
THAN THE PRESIDENT'S OWN
BLUNT WORDS YESTERDAY.
WHEN HE GAVE THAT SPEECH
ABOUT THE BALANCE IN TERMS
OF DEALING WITH FIGHTING
TERRORISM, WHETHER HE USED
DRONES AND OTHER TOOLS, HE
ALSO TALKED ABOUT THESE
LEAK INVESTIGATIONS AND THE
BALANCE THERE.
THE PRESIDENT WAS VERY
DIRECT IN SAYING
JOURNALISTS SHOULD NOT BE
PROSECUTED AS HE SAID FOR
DOING THEIR JOBS.
THEN HE SAID THIS:
>> AND I HAVE RAISED THESE
ISSUES WITH THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL WHO SHARES MY
CONCERNS.
SO HE HAS AGREED TO REVIEW
EXISTING DEPARTMENT OF
JUSTICE GUIDELINES
GOVERNING INVESTIGATIONS
THAT INVOLVE REPORTERS.
AND HE WILL CONVENE A GROUP
OF MEDIA ORGANIZATIONS TO
HEAR THEIR CONCERNS AS PART
OF THAT REVIEW.
>> AND THEY SAY INSIDE THE
WHITE HOUSE THAT THIS IS
SORT OF A MIDDLE STEP
BECAUSE THE PRESIDENT CAN'T
JUST PICK UP THE PHONE EVEN
IF HE HE DISAGREES WITH
ERIC HOLDER ABOUT THE JAMES
ROSEN
AND SAY SHUT THIS DOWN.
THAT WOULD BE MET LING WITH
THE CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION.
THAT WOULD BE A BIGGER
SCANDAL.
>> Shepard: TRIBUTE TO FOUR
YOUNG GIRLS DIED CIVIL
RIGHTS.
THREE OF THOSE GIRLS WERE
14 YEARS OLD.
THE FOURTH WAS JUST 11.
THEY WERE INSIDE A BATHROOM
WHEN THE BOMB BLAST TORE
APART THAT CHURCH IN
BIRMINGHAM.
TODAY PRESIDENT OBAMA
POSTHUMOUSLY AWARDED THOSE
GIRLS THE CONGRESSIONAL
GOLD MEDAL, THE NATION'S
HIGHEST CIVILIAN HONOR.
>> FOR US TO BE ABLE TO
OVAL OFFICE WITH SOME
PEOPLE WHO HAVE WORKED HARD
TO MAKE THIS DAY POSSIBLE
AND UNDERSTANDING THAT THAT
TRAGIC LOSS, THAT HEART
BREAK HELP [INAUDIBLE]
>> Shepard: SEVERAL YEARS
AFTER THAT ATTACK A COURT
CONVICTED THREE KU KLUX
KLAN MEMBERS OF THE
BOMBING.
ONE IS STILL IN PRISON.
THE OTHER TWO ARE NOW DEAD.
REPUBLICANS SAY THEY WANT
TO TRY AGAIN TO GET ANSWERS
FROM LOIS LERNER.
SHE IS THE IRS OFFICIAL WHO
REFUSED TO RESPOND TO
QUESTIONS AT A HEARING
EARLIER THIS WEEK ON THE
AGENCY'S TARGETING OF
CONSERVATIVE GROUPS.
WITHBUT SINCE SHE INVOKED THE
FIFTH AMENDMENT AFTER SHE
WROTE A STATEMENT IN WHICH
SHE MAINTAINED HER
INNOCENCE.
G.O.P. LAWMAKERS SAY SHE
WAIVED HER RIGHTS AGAINST
INCRIMINATING HERSELF.
MIKE EMANUEL LIVE IN THE
D.C. NEWSROOM TONIGHT.
MIKE?
>> WELL, SHEP, LOIS LERNER
CREATED QUITE A STIR WHEN
SHE SAYS SHE HASN'T DONE
ANYTHING WRONG HASN'T
BROKEN ANY LAWS AND THEN
TOOK THE FIFTH.
THAT LED TO SOME
REPUBLICANS AND THEIR
LAWYERS SAYING BY MAKING
THOSE COMMENTS SHE WAIVED
HER FIFTH AMENDMENT RIGHT.
THE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE'S
TOP DEMOCRAT SAYS WHILE HE
WOULD LIKE TO HEAR FROM
HER.
FORGET ABOUT IT.
>> I WOULD NOT RECALL HER
BECAUSE FOR ONE THING I
KNOW THAT WHAT HE SHE WILL
DO IS REASSERT HER RIGHTS
UNDER THE FIFTH AMENDMENT.
I KNOW THAT AND I THINK
THERE IS A 99.99 CHANCE
THAT SHEED YOU WOULD.
>> DANIEL MAKING CHANGES
QUICKLY.
SOURCES FROM BOTH SAYS HE
ASKED HER TO RESIGN SHE
SAID NO SHOW SHE WAS PLACED
ON LEAVE.
>> SHE WILL STILL BE
RECEIVING HER PAYCHECK.
IF YOU ARE GOING TO PLEAD
THE FIFTH AMENDMENT AND YOU
ARE NOT GOING TO BE PART OF
A CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATION YOU ARE NOT
GOING TO PARTICIPATE.
I THINK SUSPENSION WITHOUT
PAY ABSOLUTELY UNTIL WE GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS.
>> THE SENATE FINANCE
COMMITTEE HAS DEMANDED
ANSWERS AND RELATED
DOCUMENTS FROM THE IRS
TARGETING CONSERVATIVE
GROUPS BY NEXT FRIDAY.
SHEP?
>> Shepard: MIKE IMAM ON
CAPITOL HILL.
A BRITISH AIRWAYS JET MADE
AN EMERGENCY LANDING TODAY
MOMENTS AFTER TAKEOFF AND A
WITNESS ON THE GROUND
VIDEOED WHAT HE SAID WAS
SMOKE SPEWING FROM ONE OF
THE PLANE'S ENGINES AND IT
CERTAINLY LOOKS LIKE IT,
DOESN'T IT?
A PASSENGER ALSO RECORDED
THIS VIDEO IT APPARENTLY
SHOWS THE ENGINE COVER WAS
MISSING.
PILOTS QUICKLY LANDED THE
PLANE BACK AT LONDON'S
HEATHROW.
IT WAS CARRYING 7 A PEOPLE.
PASSENGERS AND CREWS
EVACUATED ON THE SLIDES
THERE.
OFFICIALS BRIEFLY CLOSED
BOTH RUNWAYS.
NO WORD ON WHAT CAUSED ALL
OF THIS BUT THE AIRLINE
REPORTS IT'S INVESTIGATING.
THERE IS WORD OF MORE COP
TAM NATED MEDICATIONS THAT
COULD CAUSE ANOTHER DEADLY
OUTBREAK OF MENINGITIS.
AND JUST LIKE LAST YEAR,
OFFICIALS SAY THE BAD MS
CAME FROM ONE PHARMACY.
WE WILL TELL YOU WHERE
FOLKS WILL BE GETTING SOME
COLD AND NASTY WEATHER THIS
HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
EVEN AS THE FEDS TELL US A
KEY WEATHER SATELLITE HAS
FAILED.
WHAT THAT MEANS AS
HURRICANE SEASON APPROACHES
AND DID SOMEBODY SAY SNOW?
LED BY THE POWERFUL    SPORTSMAN 850
HO.    VALUE-MINDED SIDE-BY-SIDES...
FEATURING    THE NEW RANGER 800 MIDSIZE.
AND FULL-SIZE WORKHORSES    INCLUDING
THE ALL-NEW,    CLASS-LEADING, 60-HORSEPOWER
RANGER XP 900.    POLARIS.    HARDEST
WORKING,    SMOOTHEST RIDING.    HUGE
REBATES D LOW FINANCING    ARE AVAILABLE
RIGHT NOW    DURING THE POLARIS XP
SALES EVENT.
THIS IS AMERICA.  WE DON'T LET FREQUENT
HEARTBURN  COME BETWEEN US  AND WHAT
WE LOVE.  SO IF YOU'RE ONE OF THEM
PEOPLE  WHO GETS HEARTBURN  AND THEN
TREATS DAY AFR DAY...  BLOCK THE ACID
WITH PRILOSEC OTC  AND DON'T GET HEARTBURN
IN THE FIRST PLACE!    [ Male Announcer
]    E PILL EACHMORNING.    24 HOURS.
ZERO HEARTBUR
ADMINISTRATION REPORTS
GETTING INDICATIONS OF
SEVEN CASES INVOLVING
POSSIBLY CONTAMINATED
MEDICATION ALL FROM THE
SAME PHARMACY, THIS ONE IN
NORTHWEST TENNESSEE.
THE STEROID INJECTIONS
CONTAIN THE SAME DRUG AT
THE CENTER OF LAST YEAR'S
DEADLY FUNGAL MENINGITIS
OUTBREAK.
THAT KILLED MORE THAN 50
PEOPLE.
WORKERS PRODUCED THOSE
SHOTS AT A PHARMACY IN
MASSACHUSETTS.
THE F.D.A. REPORTS AT LEAST
ONE OF THESE NEW CASES
APPEARS TO BE A FUNGAL
INFECTION.
SLIGHTLY FEWER AMERICANS
ARE EXPECTED TO HIT THE
ROADS THIS MEMORIAL DAY
WEEKEND.
A.A.A. REPORTS MOST OF THE
NEARLY 35 MILLION TRAVELERS
WILL GO BY CAR.
ALTHOUGH THAT NUMBER IS
DOWN 1% FROM A YEAR AGO.
PART OF THE REASON COULD BE
HIGHER GAS PRICES ANALYSTS
SAY IN THE UPPER MIDWEST,
GAS HAS SOARED AS MUCH AS
68 CENTS A GALLON IN THE
PAST TWO WEEKS.
THEY SAY REFINERY ISSUES.
OVERALL THOUGH FOLKS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY ARE
PAYING ABOUT THE SAME FOR A
GALLON OF REGULAR AS LAST
YEAR.
THE NATIONAL AVERAGE $3.65.
THE FOX BUSINESS NETWORK'S
PETER BARNES IS WITH US
NOW.
HE IS LIVE AT A GAS STATION
IN CHEVY CHASE, MARYLAND.
HOW DO PEOPLE SAY THEY ARE
CHANGING THEIR VACATION
PLANS.
THE COAT ON MEMORIAL DAY
MIGHT HAVE PART OF IT.
>> YEAH.
COLD FRONT CAME IN THROUGH
HERE, SHEPARD.
I DON'T THINK I'M GOING TO
THE BEACH TOMORROW BUT IT
IS THE OFFICIAL START OF
THE UNOFFICIAL START OF THE
SUMMER HOLIDAY SEASON.
AND IT IS STARTING WITH THE
HIGHEST GAS PRICES FOR A
MEMORIAL DAY IN TWO YEARS
WITH PRICES FOR REGULAR
GALLON OF GAS UP 15 CENTS
JUST IN THE LAST MONTH
ALONE.
AND IN 8 STATES ACCORDING
TO A.A.A. GAS IS ABOVE $4 A
GALLON.
PART OF THE REASON AS YOU
MENTIONED, IS BECAUSE OF
REFINERIES WITH MAINTENANCE
AND REPAIR ISSUES.
WHICH HAS HURT GASOLINE
SUPPLIES.
TRIPLE A SURVEYED DRIVERS
ABOUT WHETHER HIGHER PRICES
WOULD EFFECT THEIR MEMORIAL
DAY TRAVEL PLANS.
AND ABOUT TWO THIRDS OF THE
PEOPLE SAID NO, BUT THE
REST SAID YES.
27 PERCENT SAID THEY WOULD
TRY TO SAVE MONEY IN OTHER
AREAS ON THEIR MEMORIAL DAY
VACATION.
8 PERCENT SAID THEY WOULD
TAKE SHORTER TRIPS AND
3 PERCENT SAID THEY
WOULDN'T DRIVE AT ALL.
THEY WOULD FIND SOME
ALTERNATIVE TRANSPORTATION
SHEPARD.
>> Shepard: SO GAS IS KIND
OF HIGH.
WHAT'S THE OUTLOOK COMING
UP?
>> WELL TRIPLE A THINKS
THAT PRICES WILL START
FALLING SHORTLY.
>> SO WE DO EXPECT PRICES
SHOULD DROP IN THE COMING
DAYS GIVEN THE FACT THAT
SOME REFINERIES ARE COMING
BACK ONLINE THAT'S
RESULTING IN GAS INCREASE
REDUCTION AND OIL PRICE
DROP AS WELL.
OIL PRICES SHOULD DROP IN
JUNE.
THAT'S NOT GOING TO DO YOU
ANY GOOD FOR MEMORIAL DAY.
>> AND A STATE HARDEST HIT
BY THOSE REFINERY PROBLEMS
MINNESOTA WHERE PRICES ARE
UP 80 CENTS A GALLON JUST
IN THE LAST MONTH.
SHEPARD?
>> Shepard: WOW, PETER
BARNES LIVE IN CHEVY CHASE,
MARYLAND TONIGHT.
THE WEATHER WILL NOT BE
COOPERATING MUCH AT ALL FOR
THE EAST COAST WHERE IT IS
EXPECTED TO FEEL MORE LIKE
WINTER THAN THE START OF
SUMMER.
COLD, WET, EVEN WORD OF
SNOW IN SOME PARS.
METEOROLOGIST ANDRE FUNTE
FOX 5.
>> WHAT A HORRIBLE WAY TO
START THE WEEKEND IN THE
NORTHEAST.
COLD AND RAINY ALL DAY
LONG.
MORE TONIGHT AND EVEN INTO
TOMORROW.
WE HAVE AN AREA OF LOW
PRESSURE THAT IS SITTING
JUST TO OUR EAST AND ON THE
BACK SIDE OF IT COLD AIR IS
BEING PULLED IN FROM CANADA
AND RAINY WEATHER
PERSISTENT AS THIS AIR IS
GOING TO BE SLOW TO MOVE
OUT OF THE REGION.
THIS THE 30'S AND 40S IN
THE GREAT LAKES ALL THE WAY
INTO THE NEW ENGLAND AND
HIGHER ELEVATIONS ABOUT
2500 FEET WE COULD ACTUALLY
SEE SOME WET SNOW COMING
OUT OF THE SKIES TONIGHT.
THAT'S RIGHT.
SNOW.
IT WON'T BE ACCUMULATING
BUT ENOUGH TO CAUSE A MAJOR
NUISANCE CONSIDERING THIS
IS THE UNOFFICIAL START OF
SUMMER AND STILL LOOKS LIKE
WINTER OUTSIDE YOUR WINDOW.
ELSEWHERE AROUND THE NATION
WE DO HAVE SOME RAIN COMING
THROUGH MINNESOTA THERE IS
THE POTENTIAL FOR SLIGHT
RISK OF SEVERE
THUNDERSTORMS ACROSS THE
WESTERN DAKOTAS AND WESTERN
NEBRASKA TOMORROW.
FLOODING RAINS TO OUR SOUTH
TEXAS TODAY AND THAT WET
WEATHER IS GOING TO MOVE
SLIGHTLY EASTWARD AS WE GET
INTO THE DAY TOMORROW.
OUT TOWARDS THE WEST
SCATTERED SHOWERS IN
SEATTLE.
NICE AND DRY ACROSS THE
FOUR CORNER STATES.
ALSO FINDING SOME BIG HEAT
WITH THAT WILL ALSO COME
THE POTENTIAL FOR FIRE
DANGER ACROSS NORTHERN
PARTS OF ARIZONA INTO THE
FOUR CORNERS.
BE AWARE OF THAT COOL IN
THE NORTHWEST BUT SEATTLE
COMING IN THE LOW 60'S.
IF YOU WANT SOME HOT NICE
WEATHER IT LOOKS LIKE THE
GULF COAST IS GOING TO GET
THE BEST PART OF THE START
OF THE MEMORIAL DAY
WEEKEND.
THAT'S WHERE WE WILL FIND
READINGS ACE FROM NEW
ORLEANS TO SOUTH FLORIDA.
TOMORROW MORNING START OFF
WITH NEAR RECORD LOWS
CAROLINAS.
REBOUND NICELY IN THE
AFTERNOON WITH THE HIGH
TEMPERATURES MOVING INTO
THE 70s.
SHEP, OVER TO YOU.
>> Shepard: AUDREY, THANKS.
JUST IN TIME FOR HURRICANE
SEASON A KEY SATELLITE THAT
TRACKS SEVERE WEATHER ALL
UP AND DOWN THE EAST COAST
HAS FAILED FOR THE SECOND
TIME IN TWO YEARS.
RESEARCHERS SAY THE
SATELLITE STARTED HAVING
ISSUES ON WEDNESDAY WHEN IT
FAILED TO RELAY IMAGES BACK
TO IRTD.
IN THE MEANTIME SCIENTISTS
SAY THEY HAVE ACTIVATED A
SPARE SATELLITE WHERE WHILE
THEY WORKED TO FIX THE ONE
THAT'S UP THERE BROKEN.
NO WORD ON WHEN THEY MIGHT
GET THAT PRIMARY SATELLITE
BACK UP AND RUNNING.
WELL, YOU WOULD NOT THINK
THAT A LITTLE WATER WOULD
BE SUCH A BIG PROBLEM FOR
FISH.
BUT THE STORM SURGE FROM
SUPER STORM SANDY CAUSED
MAJOR DAMAGE AT THE NEW
YORK AQUARIUM.
TONIGHT, A LOOK AT ALL THE
HARD WORK THAT'S GONE INTO
THE CLEAN UP THERE AND TALK
ABOUT A COME BACK.
ONE OF THE AREAS IN SANDY'S
PATH HAS JUST TAKEN THE TOP
SPOT IN A NEW POLL OF THE
NATION'S BEST BEACHES.
SO WHERE IS THAT?
IT'S COMING UP AS FOX
REPORTS THIS FRIDAY FOR
MEMORIAL DAY.
Why are twice as many people  choosing
Verizon  over any other carrier?
Many choose us because we have  the
largest 4GLTE network.
Others, because of our  reputation
for reliability.
Or maybe it's because  we've received
JD Power
and Associates' customer service
award 4X in a row.
In the end  there are countless reasons.
But one choi.
>> Shepard: THE JERSEY
GOVERNOR CHRIS CHRISTIE IS
CALLING FOR PEOPLE TO VISIT
THE JERSEY SHORE THIS
HOLIDAY WEEKEND AS PEOPLE
VISIT THE BEACHES AND BOARD
WALKS FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE SUPER STORM SANDY.
>> 1, 2, 3.
[CHEERS]
>> Shepard: GOVERNOR
CHRISTIE WAS IN SEASIDE
HEIGHTS TO MARK THE
RECOVERY OF THE STORM BY
CUTTING A RIVER MORE THAN 5
AND A HALF MILES LONG.
THE GUINNESS WORLD RECORD
FOLKS INCONFIRM THAT'S THE
LONGEST EVER.
THE SHORE IS BACK IN
BUSINESS AND READY FOR
VISITORS.
NOW HE JUST NEEDS THE
WEATHER TO COOPERATE.
MORE SIGNS OF PROGRESS
TONIGHT IN THE RECOVERY
FROM THAT HURRICANE.
THE NEW YORK AQUARIUM IS
SET TO PARTIALLY REOPEN
TOMORROW.
IT IS JUST OFF CONEY
ISLAND, THE BOARD WALK
THERE AND PLAYS AN
IMPORTANT ROLE IN THE
COMMUNITY.
IT NORMALLY BRINGS IN
TOURISTS AND SCHOOL GROUPS
EVERY DAY OF THE YEAR.
IT'S BEEN CLOSED EVER SINCE
LAST OCTOBER'S STORM CAUSED
SEVERE DAMAGE ACROSS THE
PARK.
THE ANIMALS ARE AS PLAYFUL
AS EVER BUT THE ONLY
VISITORS THEY HAVE SEEN
OVER THE PAST HALF YEAR.
[CHAINSAW]
>> Shepard: ARE THE CLEAN
UP CREWS WORKING ON REPAIRS
FROM SUPER STORM SANDY.
>> WE WERE WORKING FOR A
BIG STORM.
NOTHING PREPARED US FOR THE
STORM THAT HAPPENED.
>> Shepard: THIS IS WHAT
HAPPENED LAST FALL AT THE
NEW YORK AQUARIUM.
THE WILDLIFE CONSERVATION
SOCIETY THAT RUNS THE PLACE
REPORTS THE FLOODS ROSE UP
TO 4 FEET.
>> THAT WATER CAME IN SO
FAST IT WAS UNBELIEVABLE.
I THINK WE WERE ALL FEELING
THE SAME THING WHICH WAS
WHEN IS THIS GOING TO STOP?
>> Shepard: ONCE IT DID,
WORKERS FOUND THE WATER HAD
DESTROYED MUCH OF THE
EQUIPMENT THAT SUPPLIES
VITAL HEAT, OXYGEN AND
FILTRATION TO THE TANKS
PUTTING THE FISH AND
AQUATIC MAMMALS AT RISK.
>> IT WAS INCREDIBLY
STRESSFUL TIMES ON SOME
LEVELS.
OTHER LEVELS IT'S A VERY
SIMPLE ADRENALINE FOCUSED
TASK, RIGHT?
WE KNOW WHAT WE NEED TO DO
AND WE JUST GOT TO FOCUS ON
DOING THAT.
>> Shepard: THEY BROUGHT IN
GENERATORS FOR POWER AND
DEPLOYED OXYGEN CANISTERS THE AQUARIUM
SAVING
ALL BUT A FEW OF THE FISH.
>> EVERYBODY HAS WORKED
TOGETHER SO THAT PEOPLE
WERE USUALLY DOING SEA LION
SHOWS HAVE BEEN FEEDING
SHARKS.
VOLUNTEERS THAT NORMALLY
ARE THAWING FISH FOR US IN
THE MORNING ARE HELPING TO
FEED WALRUSES.
>> Shepard: TODAY THEY WORK
OUT OF TRAILERS IN A
PARKING LOT NEXT TO THE
CYCLONE ROLLER COASTER.
THERE ARE STILL PUDDLES OF
WATER IN UNBEFOREETHE
UNDERGROUND VIEWING AREAS.
BARE FLOORS AND WALLS WHERE
ONCE THERE WERE COLORFUL
DISPLAYS AND EXPOSED MAIZE
OF PIPES -- MAZE OF PIPES
WHAT USED TO BE A FLOOR.
MOST OF THE FAVORITES WILL
BE OUT AS THE PLACE
PARTIALLY REOPENS.
>> EVERYBODY HAS WORKED
TOGETHER TO CREATE WHAT I
THINK IS GOING TO BE A
REALLY VIBRANT HOWEVER
MUCH SMALLER IT FOR THE
NEXT FEW YEARS A VERY
VIBRANT EXPERIENCE HERE AT
THE AAQUARIUM.
>> WHILE SEVERAL EXHIBITS
WILL REOPEN TOMORROW.
OFFICIALS TELL US REPAIR TO
THE MOST HEAVILY DAMAGED
PARTS OF THAT AQUARIUM WILL
LIKELY CONTINUE UNTIL 2016.
FOLKS HEADING OUT TO THE
HAMPTONS ON NEW YORK'S LONG
ISLAND THIS HOLIDAY WEEKEND
CAN VISIT WHAT A NEW LIST
NOW CALLS THE BEST BEACH IN
AMERICA.
MAIN BEACH IN EAST HAMPTON
TOPS THE LIST.
THE FLORIDA PROFESSOR KNOWN
AS DR. BEACH WHO COMPILES
THE ANNUAL SURVEY SAYS
MAINE BEACH LOOKS PRETTY
MUCH AS BEFORE SUPER STORM
SANDY PUMMELED THE COAST
SECOND PLACE BEACH IN
WAIKIKI AND BEACH IN GEORGE
ISLAND STATE PARK IN
FLORIDA.
THERE ARE CLOSE FINISHES AT
THE TRACK AND THEN THERE IS
THIS ONE.
FOUR DRIVERS CASHING THE
CHECKERED FLAG ALL LESS
THAN ONE SECOND APART.
WE WILL SHOW YOU HOW THIS
ONE ENDED.
PLUS IT'S GOING TO TAKE
RACING FAN AS LOT LONGER TO
GET TO THE INDY 500 THIS
WEEKEND.
BIG CHANGES COMING TO THE
RACE.
THAT'S NEXT.
SHOULD FIT    IN A LITTLE TIME CUP.
NEW SINGLE SERVE CAFE    COLLECTIONS
FROM MAXWELL HOUSE    NOW AVAILABLE
FOR USE    IN THE KEURIG K-CUP BREWER.
ALWAYS GOOD TO THE LAST DROP.
♪ ♪
DON'T OUR DOGS DESERVE TO EAT  FRESHER
LESS PROCESSED FOODS
INTRODUCING FRESHPET  RECIPES SO FRESH
THE ONLY PRESERVATIVE   WE USE IS
THE FRIDGE
FRESHPET  FRESH FOOD FOR FIDO
[ Woman ] FOR DAVID AND KELLY  A PLAYFUL
THOUGHT...  HOW LONG BEFORE HE GOES
TO COLLEGE?  [ Woman ]  ...BECAME
A REAL QUESTION.  ARE WE READY  TO
PAY FOR COLLEGE?  [ Woman ]  SO THEY
CAME TO SEE ME  AND WE TALKED ABOUT
WAYS TO MANAGE THEIR MONEY  AND SAVE
FOR COLLEGE  THAT FIT THEIR SITUATION.
SO WHEN LITTLE DAVID --  WELL, NOT-SO-LITTLE
DAVID  WAS READY TO GO TO COLLEGE,
HIS PARENTS WERE READY, TOO.  WE DID
IT.    [ Female Announcer ]    LET'S
TALK ABOUT SMARTER WAYS    TO MANAGE
AND SAVE YOUR MONEY.    WHEN PEOPLE
TALK,    GREAT THINGS HAPPEN.    WELLS
FARGO.    TOGETHER WE'LL GO FAR.
[ Musick ] I KNEW THERE WERE  A LOT
OF TECH JOBS  AVAILABLE OUT THERE.
I KNEW DeVry University WOULD  GIVE
ME THE SKILLS  THAT I NEEDED TO MAKE
ONE OF THOSE TECH JOBS MINE.  WE TEACH
CUTTING-EDGE  ENGINEERING TECHNOLOGY
COMPUTER INFORMATION SYSTEMS  NETWORKING
AND COMMUNICATIONS MANAGEMENT --
THE THINGS THAT OUR STUDENTS  NEED
TO KNOW IN THE WORLD TODAY.  OUR COUNTRY
NEEDS  MORE COLLEGE GRADS  TO HELP
FILL  ALL THE OPEN TECHNOLOGY JOBS.
TO HELP MEET THAT NEED, HERE AT  DeVry
University  WE'RE OFFERING $4 MILLION
DOLLARS IN TECH SCHOLARSHIPS  FOR
QUALIFIED NEW STUDENTS.  LEARN MORE
AT DeVry.edu.
>> Shepard: YOU SEE THIS
THING A CRAZY FINISH TO
INDY FIRESTONE LIGHTS RACE.
THE TOP FOUR DRIVERS ALL
CROSSING THE FINISH LINE AT
VIRTUALLY THE SAME TIME.
LOOK AT THAT IN FACT, THE
GUY WHO WON DID SO BY
3/1,000TH S OF A SECOND.
FANS HEADING TO THE INDY
500 THIS WEEKEND MAY WANT
TO GET THERE EARLY IN WAKE
OF THE BOMBING AT THE
BOSTON MARATHON.
OFFICIALS ARE BEEFING UP
SECURITY AND CLOSING
TRAFFIC ON ONE POPULAR ROAD
LEADING UP TO THAT TRAFFIC.
KRAFT BREWERIES AROUND THE
COUNTRY ARE GIVING.
NINE DIFFERENT BREWERS
COLLABORATED TO HOME FRONT
IPA.
A BEER AGED WITH A SPECIAL
INGREDIENT THAT SIM
SYMBOLIZES ONE OF AMERICA'S
FAVORITE PAST TIME.
SOAKS IN LITTLE SLUGGER
BASEBALL BATS.
GOES TO A GROUP THAT HELPS
MILITARY FAMILIES.
BEFORE WE GO OUR TEAM'S TOP
FIVE THINGS OF THE DAY.
NUMBER 5 NETFLIX LOOKING TO
DRAW MORE SUBSCRIBERS WITH
ITS TV SEARS ARRESTED
DEVELOPMENT.
FOX BROADCAST NETWORK
CANCELLED THAT SEVEN YEARS
AGO.
TORONTO MAYOR ROB FORD NOW
DENIES THAT HE SMOKES CRACK
AFTER REPORTS OF SOME VIDEO
THAT SUPPOSEDLY SHOWS HIM
SMOKING CRACK.
WE HAVEN'T SEEN SAID VIDEO.
NUMBER THREE THE FOREMAN
FOR JURORS IN THE JODI
ARIAS TRIAL SAYS THEY THINK
IT'S UNFAIR THEY WERE    TO
DECIDE WHETHER TO PUT HER
TO DEATH.
SENIOR OFFICIALS AT THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
INCLUDING THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL ERIC HOLDER
APPROVED OF THE DECISION TO
SEARCH THE PERSONAL EMAIL
ACCOUNTS OF FOX NEWS
CORRESPONDENT JAMES ROSEN.
THAT'S ACCORDING TO A
STATEMENT THE DEPARTMENT
RELEASED TODAY AND NUMBER
ONE, WASHINGTON STATE'S
GOVERNOR SAYS FEDERAL
OFFICIALS ARE NOW
CERTAINING FOR A POTENTIAL
TEMPORARY REPLACEMENT FOR
THAT BRIDGE THAT COLLAPSED
LAST NIGHT.
AND THAT'S "THE FOX
REPORT'S" TOP FIVE.
ON THIS DAY IN 1883 PEOPLE
CAME FROM FAR AND WIDE TO
STAND ON ARCHITECTURAL
WONDER IN NEW YORK WHEN THE
BROOKLYN BRIDGE FIRST
OPENED, IT SPANNED THE EAST
RIVER CONNECTING MANHATTAN
WITH WHAT WAS THEN THE CITY
OF BROOKLYN.
CONSTRUCTION OF THE
3400-FOOT BRIDGE TOOK 14
YEARS.
AT THE TIME IT WAS THE
LONGEST SUSPENSION BRIDGE
IN ALL THE WORLD.
THE FIRST BRIDGE TO USE
STEEL FOR CABLE WIRE.
PRESIDENT CHESTER ARTHUR
DEDICATED THAT BRIDGE AND
MORE THAN 150,000 PEOPLE
WALKED ACROSS THIS THAT
DAY.
STILL ICONIC LANDMARK HERE
IN THE BIG APPLE.
SECOND BIDSIEST BRIDGE IN
OUR CITY.
IT FIRST OPENED FOR
BUSINESS 130 YEARS AGO
TODAY.
BROOKLYN.
AND NOW YOU KNOW THE NEWS
FOR THIS FRIDAY, MAY THE
24TH, 2013.
THE FRIDAY BEFORE MEMORIAL
WEEKEND.
SO IT'S GOING TO BE LIKE 44
HERE.
HOPE YOURS IS BETTER.
>> THE O'REILLY FACTOR IS
ON.
TONIGHT:
>> MY MAIN CONCERN IS
FIXING A PROBLEM.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE DROWN IN
SANDALS.
THE PRESIDENT FACING
SCRUTINY ON SEVERAL FRONTS.
HOW BADLY WILL ALL THESE
CONTROVERSIES DAMAGE
MR. OBAMA?
WE HAVE THE BEST ANALYSIS
IN THE BUSINESS.
>> IT HAD A.
>> CHILLING.
>> DID THE IRS TARGET BIG
MONEY CONSERVATIVE DONORS?
WE WILL TALK WITH THE MAN
WHO GOT HAMMERED BY THE TAX
PEOPLE.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT
THE LATEST THAT'S BEEN
GOING ON WITH THE BENGHAZI
INVESTIGATION?
>> I HAVEN'T REALLY BEEN
FOLLOWING THAT MUCH.
>> I HAVEN'T BEEN FOLLOWING
ALONG TOO CLOSELY, SORRY.
>> Bill: THE FACTOR HITS
THE STREETS TO FIND OUT
JUST HOW MUCH AMERICANS
KNOW ABOUT THE
CON