US.
STICK AROUND TO THE "FOX
REPORT".
RICK LEVENTHAL IS IN THE CHAIR.
>> HAVE A GOOD AFTERNOON.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
>> FOR SPORTS AND POLITICS IN A
COLLISION.
SOME OF THE BIGGEST ATHLETES IN
THE COUNTRY ARE HEADING BACK.
I'M RICK LEVENTHAL AND THIS IS
THE "FOX REPORT".
BASKETBALL, STEP CURRY IN THE
GOLDEN STATE WARRIORS TO THE
WHITE HOUSE AND ON FRIDAY CURRY
SAID HE DID NOT WANT TO JOIN HIS
TEAM TO MEET THE PRESIDENT AFTER
THEIR CHAMPIONSHIP WHEN THE
PRESIDENT FIRED BACK TO EATING
"IMITATION IS WITHDRAWN.
TARGETING PROFESSIONAL FOOTBALL
URGING NFL OWNERS TO FIRE
PLAYERS WHO KNEELED DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
COLIN KAPNICK WAS THE FIRST TO
DRAW ATTENTION TAKING A KNEE
DURING THE STAR-SPANGLED BANNER.
NUMEROUS OTHER PLAYERS HAVE
FOLLOWED HIS LEAD.
KRISTIN FISHER HAS MORE FROM
SOMERSET, NEW JERSEY.
BRING US UP TO SPEED ON THIS
GROWING FEUD BETWEEN THE
PRESIDENT AND SOME OF THE
BIGGEST STARS AND NATIONAL
SPORTS.
>> RICK, THESE TWO STORIES HAVE
CONSUMED THE INTERNET AND
CONSUMED THE RAPIDLY
INTERCEPTING RULE UNDER WORLD OF
SPORTS AND POLITICS.
STATEMENTS HAVE BEEN POURING OUT
ALL DAY LONG FROM POLITICIANS
AND ATHLETES BUT I WANT TO SHARE
WITH YOU GUYS STARTING OFF THE
STATEMENT THAT STARTED IT ALL
FROM PRESENT LAST NIGHT AT THE
RALLY IN ALABAMA.
LISTEN.
>> WOULDN'T YOU LOVE TO SEE ONE
OF THESE NFL OWNERS WHEN SOMEONE
DISRESPECTS OUR FLAG TO SAY GET
THAT SON OF A [BLEEP] OFF THE
FIELD RIGHT NOW.
HE'S FIRED.
[CHEERING]
REPORTER: IT IS PRETTY RARE FOR
THE NFL COMMISSIONER TO WEIGH
INTO THE POLITICAL ARENA BUT HE
DID SO TO DATE WITH THE
STATEMENT AND READS:  NOW,
PRESIDENT OF RESPONDING RACKLEY
TO THAT STATEMENT BY SAYING THIS
QUOTE:  PRESIDENT IS NOT BACKING
DOWN ONE BIT.
ON THE VERY SAME DAY THAT ALL OF
THIS IS HAPPENING PRESIDENT
TRUMP ALSO DISINVITED ONE OF THE
BIGGEST STARS IN THE NBA FROM
ATTENDING THE WHITE HOUSE.
HE TALKS ABOUT GOLDEN STATE
WARRIOR GUARD, STEP CURRY AFTER
WINNING THE NBA CHAMPIONSHIP HE
SAID YESTERDAY THAT HE WAS
HESITANT TO GO TO THE WHITE
HOUSE BECAUSE OF PRESIDENT DROPS
POLITICS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID FINE YOU
ARE NO LONGER WELCOME AND NOW
THE ENTIRE TEAM IS NOT GOING AND
INSTEAD THE TEAM PUT OUT AS
STATEMENT THAT THEY ARE
CELEBRATING QUALITY, DIVERSION
AND INSTEAD OF GOING TO THE
WHITE HOUSE.
RICK: REMARKABLE STUFF AND WILL
HAVE MORE ON THIS IN A MINUTE.
PRESIDENT JUST HASN'T BEEN
TWEETING ABOUT SPORTS BUT ALSO
ABOUT HEALTHCARE AND AREA.
REPORTER: THERE HAS BEEN A LOT
OF POLITICAL TALK AS WELL ON
TWITTER FROM THE PRESIDENT
TODAY.
IN TERMS OF HEALTHCARE, YOU HAVE
THIS THIRD ATTEMPT FROM
REPUBLICANS TO REPEAL AND
REPLACE OBAMACARE AND THERE ARE
THREE SENATORS THAT ARE GOING TO
BE MAKE OR BREAK VOTE AND
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS SPENT TODAY
CALLING OUT ALL THREE OF THEM ON
TWITTER BUT NONE MORE SO THAN
SENATOR JOHN MCCAIN.
HE HAS RESERVED FOR TWEETS FOR
SENATOR MCCAIN TODAY AND HERE IS
ONE OF THEM.
THIS CAME MOMENTS AGO.
TELL THAT TO THE PEOPLE OF
ARIZONA WERE DECEIVED 116%
INCREASE.
I CAN REMEMBER MCCAIN VOTED
AGAINST THE LAST REPUBLICAN
EFFORT TO REPEAL AND REPLACE
OBAMACARE BACK IN JULY AND HE
DID SO AGAIN JUST YESTERDAY
SAYING THAT HE DIDN'T WANT TO
PASS THE BILL WITHOUT KNOWING
HOW MUCH IT WOULD COST IN WITH
THE CBO SCORE WAS IN WITHOUT
SECURING SOME KIND OF BIPARTISAN
SUPPORT.
AS FOR IRAN, ANOTHER TWEET FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP JUST TESTED
ANOTHER BALLISTIC MISSILE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP RESPONDED WITH
QUOTE:  SO, YOU'RE THIS
HAPPENING IN IRAN AND NORTH
KOREA THREATENING TO TEST
ANOTHER NUCLEAR WEAPON BUT
ACCORDING TO AMERICANS ON
TWITTER AND SOCIAL MEDIA THE
THING THAT IS DOMINATING THE
CONVERSATION THERE IS THIS
GROWING FEUD BETWEEN THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES
AND SOME OF THE BIGGEST ATHLETES
IN THE USA.
RICK.
RICK: WILL HAVE MORE ON NORTH
KOREA LATER THIS HOUR BUT THIS
IS WHAT PEOPLE ARE TALKING ABOUT
AND WE WANT TO GET INTO MORE ON
THIS NFL, NBA CONTROVERSY.
WILL GO TO LEGENDARY TV
SPORTSCASTER WARNER WOLF.
WE APPRECIATE YOU JOINING US
TONIGHT.
>> THANK YOU, RICK.
I ALWAYS ENJOY YOUR WORK IN THE
FIELD FOR ALL THESE YEARS.
RICK: I APPRECIATE THAT, WARNER.
WHAT IS YOUR REACTION TO WHAT IS
GOING ON BETWEEN THE WHITE HOUSE
AND THESE PRO SPORTS LEAGUES
COURSEWORK.
>> FIRST OF ALL, IT IS OKAY TO
PROTEST.
THE PROBLEM IS WHERE.
IT IS WHERE.
YOU DON'T PROTEST USING A STAGE
EXPLOITING THE PLACE WHERE YOU
WORK.
IT'S AS SIMPLE AS THAT.
THEY WANT TO PROTEST, FINE, GO
AHEAD BUT DO IT ON YOUR OWN TIME
AND IN YOUR OWN FACILITY.
NOT THE STAGE AND PLATFORM WHERE
YOU WORK.
THESE GUYS ARE BEING PAID
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS TO PLAY AND
NOT TO USE IT FOR ANOTHER
ASPECT.
THAT IS WRONG.
RICK: WHAT IS THE RISK TO THE
LEAGUE OF THESE KIND OF PROTESTS
CONTINUE?
IS THERE A RISK TO THE LEAGUE?
>> IT DEPENDS ON THE FANS.
IF THE FANS WALK OUT AND IT ALSO
DEPENDS ON THE TV RATINGS AND IF
THEY GO DOWN, WELL, MAYBE ROGER
COULD OUT WILL TAKE A STAND.
HE HAS CERTAINLY DIDN'T TODAY,
THAT'S FOR SURE.
RICK: BACK TO THE NBA FOR A
MOMENT, THE WARRIORS RELEASED A
STATEMENT THAT READ:  CLEARLY,
THE TEAM IS STANDING TOGETHER ON
THIS POINT AND REAL QUICK LEBRON
JAMES ALSO WEIGHED IN AMONG
OTHER ATHLETES AND HE CALLED THE
PRESIDENT A BUM.
HE SAID YOU BOMB, HE ALREADY
SAID HE AIN'T GOING SO EIGHT NO
INVITE.
GOING TO THE WHITE HOUSE WAS AN
HONOR UNTIL YOU SHOWED UP.
SPEAKING OF COURSE, ABOUT THE
PRESIDENT.
>> FIRST OF ALL, THE LAWYERS HAD
THE SUPPORT OF A STEPH CURRY
STANDS.
THAT IS WHY THEY ARE NOT GOING.
IF STEPH CURRY HAD SAID HE GO,
THEY ALL WOULD HAVE GONE.
IT WON'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
TOM BRADY DIDN'T SHOW UP WHEN
OBAMA WAS THE PRESIDENT.
SO WHAT?
THEY ARE JUST BALLPLAYERS.
IT DOESN'T CHANGE ANYTHING.
TO ME, THE INTERESTING AND AS
FAR AS BEING INVITED AND THEN
WITHDRAWN, IF YOU INVITED
SOMEONE TO A PARTY AND THEY SAID
WE DON'T WANT TO COME SO YOU SAY
DON'T COME, I'LL TAKE THE INVITE
BACK.
LOOK, WHAT IS THE BIG DEAL?
THE OTHER THING IS -- YEAH.
RICK: I HAVE TO BELIEVE ALL
THESE YEARS OF PRESIDENTS
INVITING TEAMS TO THE WHITE
HOUSE THAT THERE WERE PLAYERS ON
THIS TEAM THAT DIDN'T SUPPORT
THAT PARTICULAR PRESIDENT BUT
THEY SHOWED UP ANYWAY AND NOW
THIS THING HAS BEEN TURNED ON
ITS HEAD.
>> YES, TO ME, RICK, THE
INTERESTING THING IS THAT THE
PLAYERS WHO DISRESPECT THE FLAG
AND THE INCOME THOSE ARE THE TWO
SYMBOLS THAT GIVE THEM THE RIGHT
TO FREE SPEECH AND DISRESPECT
AND SAY WHAT THEY WANT.
THEY ARE STEPPING ON THE HAND
THAT FEEDS THEM.
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU SOMETHING.
I WAS IN THE SERVICE AS HUNDREDS
OF THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE WERE AND
SOMEWHERE IN COMBAT, FORCE.
HEY, THE FLAG AND THE ANTHEM
WERE VERY IMPORTANT.
THEY REPRESENTED THE COUNTRY
AND, AS I SAID, THE RIGHT TO
FREEDOM OF SPEECH.
THESE GUYS ARE COMPLAINING AND
THAT IS THE RIGHT TO GIVE THEM
THE SPEECH AGAIN, TO ME, THEY
ARE QUICK.
THE BOTTOM LINE IS WHEN A
PROTEST FINE, NOTHING WRONG WITH
THAT BUT DON'T DO IT ON MY TIME
IN MY PLACE.
RICK: WE APPRECIATE YOUR TIME
TONIGHT, WARNER.
SURE WE'RE NOT HEARD THE LAST OF
THIS.
>> THANK YOU.
RICK: MEANWHILE, NORTH KOREA
SAYING PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL BE
RESPONSIBLE FOR ALL LIVES LOST
IF THE TWO COUNTRIES GO TO WAR.
THE ROGUE REGIMES FOREIGN
MINISTER MAKING A BLISTERING
SPEECH AT THE UN GENERAL
ASSEMBLY IN NEW YORK CITY SAYING
TRUMPS RHETORIC IS TO BLAME FOR
THEIR NUCLEAR FORCE.
SENIOR FOREIGN AFFAIRS GREG
REPORTS ON THIS FROM SUFFERING.
REPORTER: WE EXPECTED STRONG
WORDS COMING FROM THE NORTH
KOREAN FOREIGN MINISTER AND THE
UN GENERAL ASSEMBLY TODAY AND
GUESS WHAT WE GOT THEM.
SPEAKING BEFORE THE AUGUST BODY
OF THE UN GENERAL ASSEMBLY THERE
WAS A DIRECT REBUKE TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP AND CALLING KIM JONG-UN IN
A ROCKET MAN.
HE SAID THAT ONLY MADE THE
INEVITABLE VISIT BY NORTH KOREAN
ROCKETS TO THE MAINLAND OF THE
UNITED STATES AND HE WENT ON TO
SAY THAT INNOCENT AMERICAN LIVES
ARE LOST PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL BE
HELD TOTALLY RESPONSIBLE
ASSERTING THAT HE WAS THE ONE ON
A SUICIDE MISSION.
AMID ANOTHER ORCHESTRATED ANTI-
US RALLY IN THE CAPITAL OF NORTH
KOREA, FOREIGN MINISTER MADE THE
ASSERTION THAT NORTH KOREA WAS
ONLY STEPS AWAY FROM THE
COMPLETION OF A NUCLEAR FORCE
INCLUDING H BONDS AND ICBMS AND
THAT THEY WOULD NOT STOP IN THE
FACE OF WHAT HE CALLS ILLEGAL
SESSIONS.
ALL THIS COMES BY THE UNITED
STATES BOMBERS IN JET FIGHTERS
TO THE EAST OF NORTH KOREA AND
TO THE NORTH OF THE DNC AND
CRUCIALLY IN THE GENERAL AREA
THE PATH OF THAT NORTH KOREAN
MISSILE LAUNCH LAST WEEK.
THE US MILITARY SPOKESMAN SAYING
THAT SHOWS THE RESOLVE OF THE
UNITED STATES AND IT SHOWS THAT
IT HAS MANY MILITARY OPTIONS.
FINALLY, YES, THERE WAS A BIT OF
A NUKE SCARE ON THE KOREAN
PENINSULA TODAY.
LATE SATURDAY KOREAN TIME THE
REPORTS OF AN EARTHQUAKE IN
NORTH KOREA, NOT FAR FROM WHERE
THE REGIME HAD THIS NUCLEAR TEST
SITE, THE INITIAL REPORT COMES
FROM CHINA THAT IT TRIGGERED BY
AN EXPLOSION BUT SOUTH KOREAN
OFFICIALS IN THE US OFFICIALS
WEIGHED IN AND SAID IT WAS
NATURALLY BASED BUT COULD OF
BEEN RELATED TO GEOLOGICAL
SHIFTS FROM THE NUCLEAR TEST
THERE EARLIER THIS MONTH.
ONE MORE NOTE ABOUT NORTH KOREAN
FOREIGN MINISTER SPEECH, BEFORE
THE GENERAL ASSEMBLY, KIM
JONG-UN AND IS UPPING THE ANTE
IN A GLOBAL SMACK BETWEEN NORTH
KOREA AND THE UNITED STATES.
NOW IT IS BACK TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
RICK.
RICK: REPORTING FROM SEOUL,
SOUTH KOREA.
THE WORLD IS FOCUSED ON THE
SHOWDOWN WITH NORTH KOREA
ANOTHER THREAT MAY BE GROWING.
HE IRAN CLAIMING TO SUCCESSFULLY
TESTED A NEW BALLISTIC MISSILE
EVEN AS THE NUCLEAR DEAL WITH
IRAN HANGS IN THE BALANCE FOR IS
THE TRUMP ADMINISTRATION FACING
A NEW FOREIGN-POLICY CRISIS?
PLUS, ANOTHER POWERFUL
EARTHQUAKE ROCKED MEXICO AFTER
TWO OTHERS KILLED MORE THAN 300
PEOPLE.
WE HAVE THE LATEST ON THOSE
RECOVERY EFFORTS FROM THE SCENE.
>> THEIR CHILDREN AND WE EVEN
GRABBED OUR ANIMALS.
THEY ARE IMPORTANT, TOO.
THEY ARE PART OF OUR FAMILY.
WE JUST NEED TO PRAY TO GOD MORE
THAN ANYTHING.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
We are the TV Doctors
of America,
and we may not know
much about medicine,
but we know
a lot about drama.
We also know that
you can avoid drama
by getting
an annual check-up.
So go, know, and take
control of your health.
It could save your life.
Cigna. Together, all the way.
has gotten to know our business
It could save your life.
so well that is feels
like he's a part of our team.
With one phone call,
he sets me up with tailored
products and services.
And when my advisor
is focused on my tech,
I can focus
on my small business.
♪
A Dell Advisor can help you
choose the right products
with powerful
Intel® Core™ processors.
♪
Endless Shrimp is back
at Red Lobster.
And we went all out
to bring you even more
incredible shrimp
and new flavors.
Like new
Nashville Hot Shrimp,
drizzled with
sweet amber honey,
and new grilled
Mediterranean Shrimp
finished with a savory blend
of green onions,
tomatoes, and herbs.
Feeling hungry yet?
Good, 'cause there's plenty
more where these came from.
Like Garlic Shrimp Scampi,
and other classics you love.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
But hurry, Endless Shrimp
won't be here long.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
the toothpaste that helps
prevent bleeding gums.
If you spit blood
when you brush or floss
you may have gum problems
and could be on the journey
to much worse.
Help stop the journey
of gum disease.
Try parodontax
toothpaste.
♪
G NEW CARS.
YOU'RE SMART.
YOU ALREADY KNEW THAT.
BUT IT'S ALSO GREAT FOR FINDING
THE PERFECT USED CAR.
YOU'LL SEE WHAT
A FAIR PRICE IS,
AND YOU CAN CONNECT WITH
A TRUECAR CERTIFIED DEALER.
NOW YOU'RE EVEN SMARTER.
THIS IS TRUECAR.
I even accept I have a
higher risk of stroke
as far as I used to.
due to AFib,
a type of
irregular heartbeat
not caused by a
heart valve problem.
But no matter
where I ride,
I go for my best.
So if there's something
better than warfarin,
I'll go for that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS reduced
the risk of stroke
better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor
tells you to,
as stopping increases your
risk of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
...and it may take
longer than usual
for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate
medical care
for sudden signs
of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about
all planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor
about ELIQUIS.
♪
RICK: STRONG AFTERSHOCK ROCKING
MEXICO.
THE MAGNITUDE 6.1 QUAKE HITTING
THE SOUTHERN PART OF THE COUNTRY
EARLIER SATURDAY JUST DAYS AFTER
MUCH MORE POWERFUL EARTHQUAKE
KILLED AT LEAST 305 PEOPLE.
THE CHIEF CORRESPONDED JONATHAN
HUNT JOINS US NOW FROM MEXICO
CITY WITH THE LATEST.
JONATHAN, WHAT IS HAPPENING WITH
SEARCH AND RESCUE EFFORTS?
REPORTER: SEARCH AND RESCUE
EFFORT IS ON GOING DESPITE THE
FACT THAT WE ARE NOW COMFORTABLY
PAST THE 100 HOUR MARK, FOUR
DAYS SINCE THAT HUGE EARTHQUAKE
HIT.
ONE OF THE MAJOR OPERATIONS IS
GOING ON BEHIND ME HERE.
YOU CAN SEE DOZENS OF HIGHLY
SKILLED RESCUE WORKERS THEY ARE
ON TOP OF WHAT ONCE WAS A SIX
STORY OFFICE BUILDING.
THEY ARE PICKING PRECARIOUSLY
THROUGH THAT RUBBLE, HOPING
AGAINST HOPE, THAT THEY MIGHT
YET FIND SURVIVORS.
ONE OF THE RESCUE TEAMS UP THERE
IS FROM THE LA COUNTY FIRE
DEPARTMENT URBAN SEARCH AND
RESCUE SQUAD.
I SPOKE TO THE TEAM LEADER,
DENNIS CROFT, EARLIER TODAY AND
HE SAID NO ONE IS READY TO GIVE
UP.
LISTEN HERE.
>> THERE IS A TIMEFRAME AND IT
VARIES BUT WE WILL NEVER STOP
SEARCHING AND WE DON'T GIVE UP
HOPE UNTIL WE'VE GONE THROUGH
THAT TIMEFRAME AND WE FEEL
THERE'S NO MORE SURVIVABILITY.
WE ARE NOT THERE YET.
REPORTER: CHIEF CROFT ALSO TOLD
ME THAT HE WAS IN HAITI IN 2010
AFTER THE EARTHQUAKE AND HE SAID
MIRACLES DO HAPPEN.
THERE THEY FOUND SURVIVORS UP TO
NINE DAYS AFTER THAT QUAKE HIT.
THERE IS STILL HOPE FOR A
MIRACLE HERE TONIGHT.
RICK.
RICK: HAVE THEY HEARD SIGNS OF
LIFE COMING FROM THAT RUBBLE?
REPORTER: NOT AS YET, RICK.
NOT IN THE LAST 24 HOURS
CERTAINLY BUT THERE'S A SIX
STORY PANCAKES ONTO EACH OTHER
SO THEY HAVE TO GO DOWN FOUR BY
FOUR AND IT WILL TAKE A VERY
LONG TIME TO DO THAT.
IN THE MEANTIME, NERVES WERE
RATTLED EVERYWHERE HERE BY THE
BIG EARTHQUAKE 300 MILES SOUTH
OF MEXICO CITY EARLIER TODAY.
WERE GETTING REPORTS OF DAMAGE
THERE AND REPORTS OF AT LEAST
ONE DEATH.
NO DAMAGE HERE IN MEXICO CITY
BUT IT SENT PANICKED RESIDENTS
RUNNING INTO THE STREETS WHEN
THE EARTHQUAKE ALARMS WENT OFF
THIS MORNING.
A LOT OF THE BUILDINGS INCLUDING
OUR OWN HIGH-RISE HOTEL WHERE
EVACUATED AND IT OBVIOUSLY IS
ANOTHER SIGN THIS THIRD
EARTHQUAKE WITH MAJOR
EARTHQUAKES FACES A LONG, HARD
ROAD TO RECOVERY.
THE US AMBASSADOR TO MEXICO TOLD
ME EARLIER TODAY THAT THE UNITED
STATES IS COMMITTED TO HELPING
AND THAT EFFORT.
LISTEN HERE.
>> INITIAL RESPONSE, FOOD,
WATER, THAT SORT OF THING IS
ACTUALLY OVERFLOWING IN THE CITY
OF MEXICO.
THE QUESTION IS HOW WILL YOU
REBUILD AND HOW WILL YOU DO
LONG-TERM.
WE WILL TAKE OUR CUE FROM
MEXICAN COUNTERPARTS AND WE WILL
SEE WHAT IS NEEDED AND WHAT WE
ARE ABLE TO HELP PROVIDE.
REPORTER: CERTAINLY THE MEXICAN
GOVERNMENT WILL NEED A LOT OF
HELP BUT THE BOTTOM LINE
TONIGHT, RICK, IS THAT SEARCH
AND RESCUE EFFORTS GOES ON AND
THEY ARE NOT YET READY TO GIVE
UP HOPE ON FINDING MORE
SURVIVORS.
RICK: JONATHAN HUNT, MEXICO
CITY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
FIERY RHETORIC FROM NORTH KOREA
AS THE FOREIGN MINISTER
ADDRESSES THE UN AND UNLEASHES
ON PRESIDENT TRUMP WHAT THIS
MEANS FOR THE RISING NUCLEAR
TENSIONS BETWEEN THESE TWO
NATIONS AHEAD.
PLUS, CHAOS ERUPTING IN A MALL
IN ST. LOUIS AND THE ANGRYI'
DEMONSTRATIONS FORCING STORES TO
SHUT DOWN.
I just don't want to let these
people down.
Excedrin Migraine.
Relief that works
as hard as you do.
[Grandma] You misplaced your
You have Wells Fargo, right?
[Grandson] Yeah.
[Grandma] Open up the app.
[Grandson] Okay.
[Grandma] And turn off your
card.
[Grandson] Grandma, how are you
better at this than me?
[Grandma] You know, you can use
that phone to call me.
[FBI Agent] You're a brave man,
Your testimony will save lives.
Mr. Stevens?
This is your new name.
This is your new house.
And a perfectly inconspicuous
SUV.
You must become invisible.
[Hero] I'll take my
chances.
When food is good
and clean and real,
it's ok to crave.
And with Panera catering,
there's more to go around.
Panera.
Food as it should be.
ItThe power of Nexium
24HR protection
from frequent heartburn.
All day, and all night.
Now packed into
a pill so small,
We call it mini.
New ClearMinis from Nexium 24HR.
See Heartburn Differently.
This iNot this John Smith.Smith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
RICK: INTENSIFYING RHETORIC
BETWEEN THE FOREIGN MINISTER
OFFERING A STRONG WARNING TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP DURING HIS
SPEECH BEFORE THE UNITED NATIONS
GENERAL ASSEMBLY.
LISTEN.
>> WHAT ELSE COULD BE A BIGGER
THREAT THAN THE VIOLENT REMARKS
SUCH AS FIRE AND FURY, TOTAL
DESTRUCTION COMING FROM THE TOP
AUTHORITY OF THE WORLD'S BIGGEST
NUCLEAR POWER.
RICK: WERE GOING TO DISCUSS WITH
A FOX NEWS FOREIGN-POLICY FROM
CARNEGIE AND A HOOVER INSTITUTE
RESEARCH FELLOW.
>> THANK YOU.
RICK: HOW MUCH HIGHER CAN THIS
BE RATCHETED UP?
>> ACTUALLY, YOU NO, I THINK IT
HAS BEEN RATCHETED UP FOR
DECADES.
WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS DONE IN
2017 AND AT THE UNITED NATIONS
IN HIS GENERAL ASSEMBLY TALK WAS
REALLY TO MAKE CLAIM FOR THE
REST OF THE WORLD HOW DANGEROUS
THE NORTH KOREAN REGIME HAS BEEN
FOR A LONG TIME AND THAT WE HAVE
ALLOWED THE WORLD TO BE HIJACKED
BY THE PSYCHOLOGICAL DIMENSIONS
OF THAT REGIME AND WHAT THE US
PRESIDENT SAYING WE WILL NOT
ALLOW THIS TO HAPPEN ANYMORE, I
THINK, WERE SEEN THE ERRATIC AND
DESPERATE NATURE OF THAT REGIME.
IT'S NOT RATCHETED UP MORE BUT I
THINK IT IS GETTING CLARIFIED
FOR EVERYONE HOW DANGEROUS THIS
REGIME HAS BEEN FOR A VERY LONG
TIME.
RICK: THE UN KEEPS PASSING
STRICTER AND STRICTER SANCTIONS
IN THE PRESIDENT IS SQUEEZING
THE REGIME ECONOMICALLY AND SO
FAR THAT HASN'T SEEMED TO
MATTER.
>> GIVE IT SOME TIME AND THE
NORTH KOREANS ARE USED TO THE
WORLD NOT RESPONDING TO
SANCTIONS BUT WE HAVE THE
CHINESE MORE ON BOARD THAT AT
ANY POINT DURING THIS NUCLEAR
CRISIS AND MISSILE CRISIS THEN
HAS BEEN TAKING PLACE FOR MANY
YEARS.
IT WILL HAVE AN IMPACT.
THE NORTH KOREANS KNOW IT AND
THE PATHWAY TO DENUCLEARIZE IN
THE PENINSULA HAS TO START WITH
THE ECONOMIC WEAPON.
I WANT YOU TO THINK ABOUT THE
STATEMENT ISSUED BY SENATOR BEN
SASS IN RECENT DAYS IN WHICH HE
IS THE CHAIR OF THE SENATE
BANKING SUBCOMMITTEE SAID THE
ECONOMIC WEAPON IS AN IMPORTANT
WEAPON FOR THE NORTH KOREANS AND
FOR THE CHINESE AND FOR OTHERS
TO UNDERSTAND THAT WE DON'T WANT
THE NUCLEAR ARMS RACE IN THE
REGION.
THERE IS A KIND OF COALESCING
BEHIND THE PRESIDENT'S POSITION
BOTH IN WASHINGTON AND AMONG
INTERNATIONAL PARTNERS AND THAT
WAS DEMONSTRATED AT THE UNITED
NATIONS.
RICK: SURE, BUT NORTH KOREA IS
NOW PROMISING TO TEST A HYDROGEN
BOMB OVER THE OCEAN AND IT
SAYING THAT THE PENTAGON THROUGH
BOMBERS AND JETS WELL NORTH OF
THE PENINSULA AND IT SEEMS AS IF
WE ARE STILL ON A COLLISION
COURSE FOR SOME KIND OF MILITARY
ACTION.
>> YES, WE DON'T WANT TO GO IN
THAT DIRECTION AND WE KNOW THAT
THE NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM,
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION, HAS SAID
IT IS PREPARED FOR THE WHOLE
RANGE OF RESPONSES AND OUR
SECRETARY OF DEFENSE DOES NOT
WANT TO SEE MILITARY RETALIATION
BUT WE HAVE TO BE PREPARED AND I
DON'T BELIEVE THAT THE MILITARY
AND THE AGGRESSIVE MILITARY
ACTIVITY OF THE NORTH KOREAN
REGIME AND KIM JONG-UN ARE A
RESPONSE OR DUE TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
THIS HAS BEEN COMING FOR A LONG
TIME.
IN FACT, WE COULD ARGUE THAT HE
HAS BEEN, HE HAS BEEN SO
CONDITIONED TO A LACK OF
RESPONSE BY THE WEST IN THE
UNITED STATES THAT HE HAS GOT TO
RECALIBRATE TO THE REALITY OF A
MUCH MORE AND DEEPLY RESOLVED
REGIME IN THE UNITED STATES AND
THAT'S WHAT WE ARE SEEING.
RICK: EVEN IF THESE LUNCHES WERE
PLANNED, WITH ALL OF THESE
WARNINGS AND ECONOMIC SANCTIONS
BEING PUT IN PLACE, WHY WOULDN'T
HE CANCEL THEM?
>> I THINK HE IS STILL TESTING,
FRANKLY.
HE HAS TO UNDERSTAND THAT BOTH,
IN THE ASIAN REGION AND AROUND
THE WORLD, HE HAS BEEN ISOLATED
AND SEEN AS THE BIG FORCE OF
TENSION IN HIS OWN REGION, ON
THE PENINSULA OR CHINA FOR
EVERYONE.
HE'S NOT HAD TO THINK LIKE THAT
BEFORE.
THIS IS A REAL PARADIGM CHANGE,
BOTH FOR THE WORLD, FOR NORTH
KOREA, FOR THE CHINESE AND AN
INSTANCE OF AN UNUSUAL AMERICAN
AND PERHAPS UNPRECEDENTED ON
THIS ISSUE LEADERSHIP.
I DON'T THINK THE LEADERSHIP IN
NORTH KOREA UNDERSTANDS THAT WE
REALLY DO MEAN BUSINESS AND
WE'VE GOT THE WORLD BEHIND US.
RICK: WE APPRECIATE YOUR TIME
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
JESSE WATTERS NOW WITH A LOOK AT
WHAT IS AHEAD ON "WATTERS WORLD"
TONIGHT.
>> THE LEFT IS CREATING A
MASTER, KELLYANNE CONWAY ON IT.
TOMMY LAREN REACTS TO THE
MELTDOWN PLUS, ROCKET MAN.
THE TRUMP NICKNAME WATER WAS
WORLD EDITION TONIGHT.
RICK: "WATTERS WORLD" AIRS AT
8:00 P.M. EASTERN RIGHT AFTER
"FOX REPORT" ON THE FOX NEWS
CHANNEL.
PRESIDENT TRUMP RALLIED SUPPORT
FOR INTERIM SENATOR LUTHER
STRANGE OF ALABAMA BUT WILL THE
ENDORSEMENT HELP HIM WIN THE
REPUBLICAN NOMINATION WHEN OTHER
REPUBLICAN ARE PUSHING FOR HIS
OPPONENT.
PLUS, CRUCIAL WEEK FOR
HEALTHCARE ON CAPITOL HILL.
CAN THE GOP GET THE VOTE TO PASS
THE LATEST ATTEMPT TO REPEAL AND
REPLACE OBAMACARE?
>> THE FACT OF THE MATTER IS THE
STATUS QUO IS UNACCEPTABLE.
IT IS NOT WORKING AND YOU FOLKS
THAT HAVE AN INSURANCE CARD BUT
NO CARE BECAUSE THEY CAN'T
AFFORD THE PREMIUMS OR THE
DEDUCTIBLE.
Yeah, my dad says or
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
MY BLADDER LEAKAGE
WAS MAKING ME FEEL
LIKE I COULDN'T SPEND
TIME WITH MY GRANDSON.
NOW DEPEND FIT-FLEX
HAS THEIR FASTEST ABSORBING
MATERIAL INSIDE,
SO IT KEEPS ME DRY
AND PROTECTED.
GO TO DEPEND.COM -
GET A COUPON AND
TRY THEM FOR YOURSELF.
Their leadership is instinctive.
GO TO DEPEND.COM -
They're experts in things you
haven't heard of -
researchers of technologies
that one day, you will.
Some call them the
best of the best.
Some call them veterans.
We call them our team.
COPDSo to breathe better,athe.
I go with ANORO.
♪Go your own way
COPD tries to say,
"Go this way."
I say, "I'll go my own way"
with ANORO.
♪Go your own way
Once-daily ANORO contains
two medicines called
bronchodilators,
that work together to
significantly improve
lung function all day
and all night.
ANORO is not for asthma .
It contains a type of medicine
that increases risk of death
in people with asthma.
The risk is unknown in COPD.
ANORO won't replace rescue
inhalers
for sudden symptoms
and should not be used more than
once a day.
Tell your doctor if you have a
heart condition,
high blood pressure,
glaucoma, prostate, bladder,
or urinary problems.
These may worsen with ANORO.
Call your doctor if you have
worsened breathing, chest pain,
mouth or tongue swelling,
problems urinating,
vision changes, or eye pain
while taking ANORO.
Ask your doctor about ANORO.
♪Go your own way
Get your first
prescription
free at ANORO.com.
DIRECTV has been rated #1 in
customer satisfaction
over cable for 17 years running.
But some people still like
cable.
Just like some people like
banging their head on a low
ceiling.
Drinking spoiled milk.
Camping in Poison Ivy.
Getting a papercut.
And having their arm trapped in
a vending machine.
But for everyone else, there's
DIRECTV.
For #1 rated customer
satisfaction over cable
switch to DIRECTV.
Call 1-800-DIRECTV.
Hey hun,
Huh!
We gotta go.
Come on.
♪
"Grandma! Grandpa!"
Thanks mom.
Here we are. Look, right up
to here.
Principal. We can help
you plan for that.
RICK: THE SENATE HAS ONE WEEK TO
BRING A HEALTHCARE VOTE TO THE
FLOOR AND GET A PASS.
A BILL BY REPUBLICAN SENATORS
GRAHAM AND CASSIDY IS THE LATEST
ATTEMPT TO REPEAL AND REPLACE
OBAMACARE.
IT COULD BE ON LIFE SUPPORT
AFTER SENATOR JOHN MCCAIN
ANNOUNCED HE WON'T SUPPORT IT.
ALLISON BARBER REPORTS FROM
WASHINGTON.
REPORTER: RICK, LAST WEEK A
SPOKESPERSON FOR MAJORITY LEADER
MITCH MCCONNELL TOLD FOXNEWS
MCCONNELL INTENDED TO CONSIDER
THE GRAHAM-CASSIDY BILL THIS
WEEK BUT THAT WAS BEFORE SENATOR
JOHN MCCAIN SAID HE WOULDN'T BE
SUPPORTING THE GRAHAM-CASSIDY
BILL.
HERE'S SOME PRICE.
>> THE PROMISE OF THE MAJORITY
IN CONGRESS IN THE HOUSE AND
SENATE WAS TO REPEAL AND REPLACE
AND THE REASON IT IS NOT DEAD IS
BECAUSE IT IS NOT FINISHED.
THE BILL HASN'T BEEN COMPLETED
AND WE CONTINUE TO WORK WITH THE
AUTHORS ON IT THROUGH THIS
WEEKEND AND THE BILL WILL BE
LIKELY ROLLED OUT EARLY NEXT
WEEK.
REPORTER: REPUBLICANS CAN'T
AFFORD TO LOSE MORE THAN TWO
REPUBLICANS AND MCCAIN IS THE
SECOND TO PUBLICLY SAY HE WILL
NOT SUPPORT THIS BILL.
KENTUCKY SENATOR RAND PAUL IS
NOT ON BOARD AND MAINE SENATOR
SUSAN COLLINS IS VERY MUCH ON
THE FENCE.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS TRYING TO GET
HER OFF OF IT.
>> THIS IS OUR LAST CHANCE
BEFORE THE SEPTEMBER 30th
DEADLINE TO GET THIS BILL DONE.
IT COMES DOWN TO FOUR SENATORS,
AS YOU MENTIONED.
SENATOR PAUL, SENATOR MCCAIN,
SENATOR MICHALSKI, SENATOR
COLLINS ARE THE ONES WE'RE
TRYING TO CONVINCE TO GET THE
TWO FINAL VOTES TO REPEAL
OBAMACARE.
WE HAVEN'T WRITTEN OFF ANY VOT
VOTES.
REPORTER: SENATORS ARE PRAISING
SENATOR MCCAIN SAYING IT'S
ANOTHER MOMENT OF COURAGE FOR A
MAN WHO SPENT DECADES IN THE
NAVY AND YEARS AS A PRISONER OF
WAR IN VIETNAM.
>> THANK YOU JOHN MCCAIN.
JOHN MCCAIN HAS A CONSCIENCE
THAT I WISH VERY MUCH THAT THE
REST OF THE REPUBLICAN
LEADERSHIP HAD THAT CONSCIENCE,
AS WELL.
REPORTER: REPUBLICANS HOPE TO
PASS LEGISLATION BY SEPTEMBER,
IN PART BECAUSE WITH BUDGET
ROLES THEY CAN PASS THE BILL
WITH A SIMPLE MAJORITY, 50 YESES
INSTEAD OF 60.
RICK: ALLISON BARBER WITH MORE
ON THE HEALTH CARE DEBATE AND
HOW IT WILL PLAY OUT THIS WEEK.
WE GO TO WHITE HOUSE COLUMNIST
WHO WRITES FOR THE HILL.
NILE, THIS THING DOES NOT SOUND
LIKE IT WILL PASS.
>> NO, I THINK IT IS ON LIFE
SUPPORT IS A GOOD METAPHOR.
THE ODDS ARE AGAINST THIS IN IT
IS NOT ABSOLUTELY DEAD IN THE
WATER BUT REPUBLICAN LEADERS AND
THE WHITE HOUSE NO THAT I HAVE
NO MARGIN FOR ERROR AS YOU
REPORTER MENTIONED.
SUSAN COLLINS IS ALREADY LEANING
AGAINST THIS BILL.
IF SHE COMES OUT DEFINITIVELY
AGAINST IT, THAT IS GAME OVER.
RICK: THE PRESIDENT HAD CHOICE
WORDS FOR JOHN MCCAIN NOTING
THAT MCCAIN HAD CAMPAIGNED FOR
REPEAL AND REPLACE PRETTY
AGGRESSIVELY AND THAT THE
ARIZONA GOVERNOR SUPPORTS THE
BILL AND THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT
MCCAIN WILL HAVE TO LET ARIZONA
DOWN.
>> THERE IS CERTAINLY NO LOVE
LOST BETWEEN THE PRESIDENT AND
SENATOR MCCAIN AS WE KNOW THEIR
HISTORY STRETCHES BACK TO THE
CAMPAIGN WHEN THEN CANDIDATE
TRUMP WAS PERCEIVED BY MANY
PEOPLE TO DISPARAGE SENATOR
MCCAIN'S WRAPPER DURING THE
VIETNAM WAR.
SETTING THAT ASIDE, FOR A SECOND
RICK, IT IS ACTUALLY A TRUE
STATEMENT TO POINT OUT THAT
SENATOR MCCAIN DID INDEED
CAMPAIGN TO LEAD THE FIGHT
AGAINST OBAMACARE IS ONE OF HIS
CAMPAIGN IN 2016 SO IN THAT
PERSPECTIVE AT LEAST THE
PRESIDENT DOES HAVE A VALID
POINT.
RICK: WHAT IS THE PROBLEM IS
THAT THEY HAVE CONTROL OF THE
SENATE AND HOUSE AND WHY CAN'T
THEY GET THIS DONE?
>> I THINK, BECAUSE ULTIMATELY
NO PROPOSAL THEY HAVE PUT FORTH
YET HAS SEEMED PARTICULARLY
POPULAR WITH THE BROADER
POPULATION AND THIS IS THE
POLITICS ARE COMPENSATED BECAUSE
AMONG THE SUPPORTERS OF THE
RUBBLE CAN PARTY IT IS
IMPERATIVE TO REPEAL OBAMACARE
BUT WHEN YOU TEST ALL THE
ALTERNATIVES THEY HAVE PUT FORTH
IN THE GENERAL POPULATION THEY
FRANKLY AREN'T THAT POPULAR AND
THEREFORE THERE IS A FEAR THAT
PASSING ANY OF THESE EFFORTS TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE WILL CARRY A
POLITICAL COST.
RICK: THE PRESIDENT HAS SAID
THIS BILL ALLOWS FOR BETTER
CONTROL IN MANAGEMENT IN
HEALTHCARE BUT MCCAIN IS
APPARENTLY NOT THE ONLY ONE WHO
DISAGREES WITH THAT.
>> YES, THAT IS RIGHT.
THERE IS CLEARLY SOME CONCERN.
FOR EXAMPLE, YOU MENTIONED IN
THE REPORT THAT SENATOR FROM
ALASKA IS ON THE FENCE AND HER
GOVERNOR HAS COME OUT AGAINST
THIS BILL.
RAND PAUL, SENATOR FROM
KENTUCKY, IS AGAINST IT AND
THERE ARE CONCERNS AND BEYOND
THE POLITICAL REALM THERE ARE
CONCERNS FROM ALL KINDS OF
MEDICAL ORGANIZATIONS WHO ARE
ALSO OPPOSED TO THIS CURRENT
PROPOSAL.
RICK: DESPITE KNOWING THAT THEY
HAVE THESE ISSUES -- AND HAVING
THE TIME TO PUT A BILL TOGETHER
THEY STILL HAVEN'T BEEN ABLE TO
DO IT AND NOW WE ARE HEARING
FROM SENATOR MCCAIN THE RUBBLE
CAN THE DEMOCRATS NEED TO WORK
TOGETHER ON A BETTER BILL BUT WE
HAVEN'T SEEN ANY INDICATION THAT
THAT IS REMOTELY POSSIBLE.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY CORRECT.
THERE IS NO WAY THAT DEMOCRATS
ARE GOING TO WORK FOR A FULL
REPEAL OF WHAT THEY SEE AS
PRESIDENT BUT OBAMA'S SIGNATURE
ACHIEVEMENT.
THERE MAY BE SOME TINKERING
AROUND THE EDGES BUT TO CIRCLE
BACK TO YOUR POINT YOU MADE,
RICK, I SUSPECT YOUR REPUBLICAN
VOTERS WILL PLACE A LOT OF BLAME
ON REPUBLICAN LEADERS IN
CONGRESS RATHER THAN PRESIDENT
TRUMP BECAUSE THEY WILL LOOK AT
THIS PROMISE THAT WAS MADE FOR
SEVEN YEARS, YES, BUT FOR US WE
WILL REPEAL AND REPLACE
OBAMACARE BUT THEY GOT WHAT THEY
WANTED WHICH WAS THE MAJORITIES
IN BOTH CHAMBERS OF CONGRESS AND
THE WHITE HOUSE AND THEY STILL
HAVEN'T DONE IT.
RICK: WE APPRECIATE YOUR TIME.
DON'T MISS "FOX NEWS SUNDAY".
WHITE HOUSE LEGISLATIVE AFFAIRS
MARK SHORT WILL JOIN CHRIS
WALLACE TO WEIGH IN ON
HEALTHCARE AND TAX REFORM AS
WELL AS THE NUCLEAR THREAT FROM
NORTH KOREA.
THAT IS "FOX NEWS SUNDAY", CHECK
YOUR LOCAL LISTINGS FOR TIMES
AND CHANNELS.
WE ARE THREE DAYS AWAY FROM THE
REPUBLICAN NOMINATION RUNOFF
ELECTION FOR ALABAMA'S OPEN
SENATE SEAT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
VICE-PRESIDENT PENCE ARE
ENDORSING INTERIM SENATOR LUTHER
STRANGE.
THE PRESIDENT HOLD A RALLY FOR
STRANGE IN ALABAMA LAST NIGHT.
PRIVATE POLLS SHOW IT IS A TIGHT
RACE.
PUBLIC SHOWS STRANGER SUPPLEMENT
ROY MOORE MAY HAVE BELIEVED.
OTHER BIG-NAME SUPPORTERS LIKE
FORMER WHITE HOUSE CHIEF
STRATEGIST, STEVE BANNON, PETER
DUCEY REPORTING FROM ALABAMA.
IS STEVE BANNON TRYING TO START
A POLITICAL WAR WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP BY RALLYING AGAINST THE
POT THE SENATOR THE PRESIDENT
SUPPORTED CUSTOMER.
REPORTER: SOURCES TELL ME THAT
THE MAN WHO HELPED GET PRESIDENT
TRUMP ELECTED IS ACTUALLY STILL
TRYING TO HELP THE PRESIDENT
BECAUSE BANNON THANKS THAT JUDGE
ROY MOORE IS BETTER SUITED TO
HELP PRESIDENT TRUMP DELIVER ON
HIS CAMPAIGN PROMISES IN
CONGRESS THAN THE PRESIDENT'S
OWN PICK, LUTHER STRANGE.
BANNON AND OTHERS HAVE BEEN
TRYING TO CAST STRANGE IS TOO
TIGHT WITH MITCH MCCONNELL BUT
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID THAT IS NOT
RIGHT.
>> THE THING WITH THIS IS HE
DOESN'T KNOW MITCH MCCONNELL.
HE WAS THERE FOR A FEW MONTHS
AND THEY PUT THAT MANTLE AROUND
HIS NECK AND I TOLD MITCH I
WOULD LIKE TO SAY THIS.
I DON'T LIKE TO BUT I'M TELLING
YOU, HE DOESN'T KNOW MITCH
MCCONNELL AT ALL.
REPORTER: TO THAT END, SENATOR
STRANGE SAID THIS MORNING HE
LISTENED TO ARGUMENTS IN FAVOR
OF GETTING RID OF SENATOR
MCCONNELL IF THE OBAMACARE
REPLACEMENT PACKAGE ARE
STRUGGLING TO GET SUPPORT FOR
AMONGST THEMSELVES FAILS AGAIN.
>> I'VE SAID ALL ALONG THAT IF
WE DON'T GET THINGS
PROGRESSIVELY IN WASHINGTON WE
WILL LOOK AT EVERY OPTION,
WHETHER WE NEED NEW LEADERSHIP
OR A NEW APPROACH.
I TALKED TO THE PRESIDENT ABOUT
THAT AND WE'VE GOT TO GET THINGS
DONE FOR THE FRUSTRATION LEVEL
IS THROUGH THE ROOF AND I'M THE
MOST FRUSTRATED PERSON OUT
THERE, BELIEVE ME.
REPORTER: PART OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S PITCH FOR STRANGE WAS
THAT HE WILL BE WITH THE WHITE
HOUSE A 100% OF THE TIME BECAUSE
THE PRESIDENT SAYS THAT SO FAR
STRANGE HAS BEEN SINCE HE GOT
THERE IN FEBRUARY.
RICK.
RICK: SO IS THE PRESIDENT ONE
100% WITH STRANGE?
HOW DOES HE FEEL ABOUT ROY
MOORE?
>> HE IS FOR NOW BUT THE
PRESIDENT SAYS HE WILL SUPPORT
WHICHEVER REPUBLICAN IS UP ON
THE BALLOT IN NOVEMBER.
>> I TOLD LUTHER AND I HAVE TO
SAY THIS IF HIS OPPONENT WINS,
I'LL BE HERE CAMPAIGNING LIKE
HELL FOR HIM.
[CHEERING]
BUT, I HAVE TO SAY THIS, AND YOU
UNDERSTAND THIS AND LOOK AT THE
POLLS, LUTHER WILL DEFINITELY
WIN.
NO, YOU KNOW WHAT I AM SAYING.
ROY HAS A VERY GOOD CHANCE OF
NOT WINNING IN THE GENERAL
ELECTION.
REPORTER: BUT ROY MOORE DOES
LEAD IN RECENT POLLS AND HE IS A
RALLY WITH STEVE BANNON AND BILL
ROBERTSON FROM DUCK DYNASTY,
VERY POPULAR HERE IN ALABAMA ON
MONDAY TO TRY TO STAY AHEAD.
RICK: PETER, THANKS VERY MUCH.
SEAN HANNITY WITH AN EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW WITH FORMER WHITE
HOUSE CHIEF STRATEGIST STEVE
BANNON AND WILL EXPLAIN WHY HE
IS GOING TO GET THE PRESENT BY
ENDORSING ROY MOORE.
THAT IS HAPPENING MONDAY NIGHT
AT 9:00 O'CLOCK.
>>> ST. LOUIS FACING PROTESTS
WITH CHAOS ERUPTING AT A
SHOPPING MALL EARLIER TODAY.
IT CAUSED SOME STORES TO CLOSE
AND LEADING TO SEVERAL ARRESTS.
THE ANGRY DEMONSTRATIONS ARE A
REACTION TO A JUDGE'S DECISION
TO ACQUIT A WHITE FORMER POLICE
OFFICER WHO SHOT AND KILLED AN
AFRICAN-AMERICAN MAN IN 2011.
MIKE IS IN ST. LOUIS AND JOINS
US NOW.
REPORTER: RICK, THIS PARTICULAR
DEMONSTRATION OF THE JUSTICE
CENTER IS RESPONSIVE TO THE
ARREST THAT WERE MADE EARLIER
TODAY AT THE GALLERIA MALL.
THE DEMONSTRATORS WERE ALLOWED
TO GO INSIDE THE MALL IN MAKE
THEIR VOICES HEARD DESPITE THE
FACT THAT IT WAS PRIVATE
PROPERTY.
ULTIMATELY SOMEONE TIPPED OVER
GARBAGE AT THE ESCALATOR AND
BOUGHT THE ESCALATOR AND TOOK
OVER THE SECOND FLOOR AND MALL
MANAGEMENT DECIDED THEY HAD TO
LEAVE.
THE COUNTY POLICE WERE CALLED
IN.
SEVERAL ORDERS TO DISPERSE WERE
GIVEN ACCORDING TO POLICE AND
THE KIDS DIDN'T LEAVE AND
ULTIMATELY THEY WERE ZIP TIED
AND HAULED AWAY.
TWENTY-TWO OF THEM ACCORDING TO
POLICE AND THEIR CHARGES RANGE
FROM TRESPASSING TO RESISTING
ARREST, TO ASSAULT ON A POLICE
OFFICER AND THERE WAS ONE POLICE
OFFICER INJURED.
WE HAVE AN ANNOUNCEMENT FROM
THIS PARTICULAR CROWD THAT THEY
ARE IN THE PROCESS OF BEING
RELEASED.
RICK.
RICK: THERE WERE ARREST LESLIE
IN SUBURBAN ST. CHARLES.
WHAT HAPPENED THERE?
REPORTER: IT WAS INTERESTING
BECAUSE IT WAS THE OPPONENTS OR
HECKLERS IF YOU WILL.
YOU CAN'T SAY OPPONENTS BECAUSE
THERE WASN'T ANY KIND OF
ORGANIZED OPPOSITION BUT THE
BLACK LIFE MATTER DEMONSTRATORS
WANT TO ST. CHARLES WHERE
OKTOBERFEST WAS IN FULL SWING.
A LOT OF BEER WAS BLOWING IN THE
MARCH OF THE MAIN STREET FOR THE
BARS WORK AND THEN HE MARCHED TO
THE OKTOBERFEST TENT.
CLEARLY, SOME PEOPLE IN THAT
PARTICULAR TOWN ARE TIRED OF THE
DEMONSTRATIONS AND TIRED OF THE
VANDALISM.
SOME OF THEM CAME FORWARD AND
STARTED THINGS LIKE BLUE LIGHTS
MATTER, GET OUT OF OUR TOWN.
THERE WAS A PUSHING AND SHOVING
AND THE POLICE WERE PRETTY QUICK
TO ZIP UP THE AGITATORS WHO WERE
OPPONENTS OF THE BLACK LIFE
MATTER DEMONSTRATIONS AND WHILE
THAT WAS HAPPENING THE POLICE
WEREN'T VERY GENTLE ABOUT IT IN
THE BLACK LIFE MATTER
DEMONSTRATORS SHOUTED IN SUPPORT
OF THE POLICE.
RICK: THIS HAS BEEN GOING ON FOR
DAYS.
ANY SIGN THINGS ARE COMING DOWN?
REPORTER: IT SEEMS EVERY DAY
THERE IS A NEW DEMONSTRATION.
AT SOME POINT THESE
DEMONSTRATIONS WILL CROSS THE
LINE AND THE POLICE WILL SHUT
THEM DOWN AND IT'S A MATTER OF
JUST HOW OUT OF HAND THESE
THINGS GET OR CROSS THE LINE.
LIKE THIS ONE IN PARTICULAR,
THEY GOT WHAT THEY WANTED AND IT
LOOKS LIKE PEOPLE ARE MILLING
AWAY.
RICK: MICAH TOBIN, WE APPRECIATE
IT.
THANK YOU.
A DIRE CRISIS GROWING IN PUERTO
RICO AFTER HURRICANE MARIA
DEVASTATING THAT ISLAND LEAVING
MILLIONS WITHOUT POWER AND NOW
OFFICIALS ARE RACING AGAINST THE
CLOCK TO SAVE RESIDENCE FROM A
FAILING DAM.
PLUS, WE ARE TRACKING HURRICANE
MARIA'S DEADLY PATH AND WE WILL
TELL YOU WHERE THE STORM IS
HEADED NEXT.
th.
It could save your life.
Cigna. Together, all the way.
and life's beautiful moments.ns
get between you
Flonase outperforms the #1
non-drowsy allergy pill.
It helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause symptoms.
Pills block one
and 6 is greater than 1.
Flonase changes
everything.
I'm lucky to get through a
shift without a disaster.
Heads up!
You know what, don't
worry about it.
My bargain detergent
couldn't keep up.
It was mostly water.
So, I switched to Tide PODs.
They're super concentrated,
so I get a better clean.
I mean, I give away
water for free.
I'm not about to pay for
it in my detergent.
Number one trusted.
Number one awarded.
It's got to be Tide
Endless Shrimp is back
at Red Lobster.
And we went all out
to bring you even more
incredible shrimp
and new flavors.
Like new
Nashville Hot Shrimp,
drizzled with
sweet amber honey,
and new grilled
Mediterranean Shrimp
finished with a savory blend
of green onions,
tomatoes, and herbs.
Feeling hungry yet?
Good, 'cause there's plenty
more where these came from.
Like Garlic Shrimp Scampi,
and other classics you love.
As much as you want,
however you want them.
But hurry, Endless Shrimp
won't be here long.
83% try to eat healthy,
however you want them.
yet up to 90% fall short
on getting key nutrients.
Let's do more.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
Complete with 100% daily value
of more than 15 key nutrients.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
Upeace of mind.s
We had a power outage
for five days total.
We lost a lot of food.
We actually filed
a claim with USAA
to replace that spoiled food.
And we really appreciated that
We're the Webber family and
we are USAA members for life.
WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE TO
THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE,
DOES PSORIASIS EVER GET IN
THE WAY OF A TOUCHING MOMENT?
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE TO SEVERE
PSORIASIS, YOU CAN EMBRACE
THE CHANCE OF COMPLETELY
CLEAR SKIN WITH TALTZ.
TALTZ IS PROVEN TO GIVE YOU A
CHANCE AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
WITH TALTZ, UP TO
90% OF PATIENTS
HAD A SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT
OF THEIR PSORIASIS PLAQUES.
IN FACT, 4 OUT OF 10 EVEN
ACHIEVED COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DO NOT USE IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING YOU
SHOULD BE CHECKED
FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE YOUR
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU ARE BEING TREATED
FOR AN INFECTION
OR HAVE SYMPTOMS.
OR IF YOU HAVE RECEIVED
A VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ.
INCLUDING WORSENING OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
JUST ASK YOUR
DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
RICK: NEARLY THE ENTIRE ISLAND
OF PUERTO RICO IS WITHOUT POWER
AFTER GETTING BY HURRICANES IRMA
AND MARIA.
THERE IS A BIGGER ISSUE.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
LIVING DOWNSTREAM FROM A FAILING
DAM ARE NOW UNDER EVACUATION
ORDERS.
OFFICIALS SAY THE DAM IS ON THE
VERGE OF COLLAPSE UNABLE TO
HANDLE THE WEIGHT OF THOSE HEAVY
FLOODWATERS.
STEVE HARRIGAN HAS THE LATEST
FROM PUERTO RICO.
REPORTER: HERE IN THE FAR
NORTHWEST OF PUERTO RICO A VERY
BAD SITUATION COULD GET MUCH
WORSE SOON.
THERE ARE REAL CONCERNS THAT THE
MAJOR DAM COULD BREAK.
THERE IS ALREADY 15-20 FEET OF
FLOODING AND THEY HAVE EVACUATED
70000 PEOPLE IN FEAR THAT THIS
COULD BE A CATASTROPHE.
THIS IS SO FLOODED THAT YOU HAVE
TO GUESS WHAT IS WHERE.
THERE ARE HOUSES UNDERNEATH THE
SATELLITE DISHES AND THE WATER
IS OVER THE HOUSES.
WE ARE PASSING OVER FOR
VEHICLES.
TO MY LEFT OVER HERE IS THE MAIN
STREET OF THIS REGION AND IT IS
COMPLETELY UNDERWATER
.
UP AHEAD IS THE POLICE STATION.
YOU CAN'T SEE THAT EITHER.
IT IS GUESSWORK WHERE THINGS ARE
AND WE ARE TALKING ABOUT
TEN-15 FEET OF FLOODWATER.
THEY HAD TO EVACUATE PEOPLE BY
SCHOOL BUSES AND THERE IS FEAR
THAT MORE COULD BE COMING.
THEY HAVE ALREADY EVACUATED MORE
THAN 70000 PEOPLE FROM TWO TOWNS
HERE USING SCHOOL BUSES TO TRY
TO FIND HIGHER GROUND.
RICK, BACK TO YOU.
RICK: REPORTING FROM PUERTO
RICO.
HURRICANE MARIA CONTINUES TO
ROLL NORTHWOOD AND ADAM IS OF
THE FOX WEATHER CENTER WITH MORE
ON THIS.
>> A VERY LARGE STORM AND YOU'RE
LOOKING AT A CATEGORY THREE WITH
WINDS UP TO 150 MILES AN HOUR
AND THERE IS YOUR ORIENTATION
AND US COAST.
WE ARE NOW OFF TO THE NORTH AND
EAST OF THE BAHAMAS AS THIS BIG
SYSTEM DOES CONTINUE TO LIVE TO
THE NORTH IN THE NEXT COUPLE OF
DAYS.
STILL A CATEGORY THREE BUT THE
GOOD NEWS IS IT WILL WEAKEN AS
IT CONTINUES TO MOVE FOLLOWING
DOWN TO A CATEGORY ONE.
LOOK AT THE TAIL END OF THIS
TRACK.
THIS TAKES YOU INTO TUESDAY AND
WEDNESDAY SO STILL A LITTLE BIT
OF TIME BUT THIS IS INCREDIBLY
WIDE AND THE UPPER LEVEL WINDS
AND HIGH PRESSURE SYSTEM AND THE
THINGS THAT AREN'T TOTALLY IN
PLACE SO THERE'S INDECISION AND
THE MODELS IN THE NATIONAL
HURRICANE CENTER OF WHERE THIS
WILL GO AND YOU DO NOTICE
PERHAPS THE ONE MODEL IS
BRINGING YOU FAR OVER TO NORTH
CAROLINA OR IT COULD GO WAY OUT
TO SEA.
WE WILL NEED A COUPLE OF DAYS TO
GET AN EXACT IDEA OF WHERE THE
STORM WILL BE IN IT WILL WEAKEN
BUT IT MAY APPROACH THE US
COAST.
THAT IS SOMETHING WE WILL PAY
CLOSE ATTENTION TO.
NO MATTER WHAT HAPPENS AS FAR AS
CLOSE AS IT GETS TO THE COAST IT
WILL BE CLOSE ENOUGH THAT THAT
RIP CURRENT THOUGHTS WILL BE IN
PLACE UP AND DOWN THE EAST COAST
ALL THE WAY NEXT WEEK AND THIS
IS ONE THAT WE WILL BE WATCHING
REALLY CLOSELY TO SEE IF IT WILL
JOG A LITTLE OFF TO THE WEST OR
NOT.
RICK: THANK YOU VERY MUCH, ADAM.
MELANIA TRUMP MAKING A STOP TO
HONOR HEROIC ATHLETES AS SHE
MAKES HER FIRST SOLO TRIP AS
FIRST LADY OUTSIDE THE US.
THAT IS NEXT.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
for tech advice.
Dell Small Business Advisor
With one phone call, I get
products that suit my needs
and I get back to business.
♪
put under a microscope,
we could see all the
bacteria that still exists.
Polident's unique
micro clean formula
works in just 3 minutes,
killing 99.99% of
odor causing bacteria.
For a cleaner,
fresher,
brighter denture
every day.
RICK: MONEY A TRUMPET SERVING
HER FIRST SOLO FOREIGN TRIP AS
FIRST LADY AND SHE'S IN TORONTO
LEAVING THE US DELEGATION OF THE
ADDICT'S GAMES FOR WOUNDED
VETERANS.
VERY AND RAPIDLY JOINS US LIVE
FROM.
>> THE OPENING CEREMONY AT THE
IMPACT'S GAMES IS ABOUT TO KICK
OFF IN THE FIRST LADY IS
WRAPPING UP THE MEETING WITH
JUSTIN TRUDEAU.
THEY PREPARED FOR THE THIRD
ANNUAL IN VICTOR'S GAMES AND
THEIR POSING FOR PHOTOS OF THE
90 MEMBER TEAM AND TALKING ABOUT
WHAT IT MEANS TO BE INCLUDED IN
THE EVENT.
THE FIRST LADY THINKING THE TEAM
OF VETERAN ATHLETES FOR THEIR
SERVICE.
>> YOU HAVE GIVEN SO MUCH FOR
YOUR COUNTRY.
YOU TRULY ARE OUR HEROES.
>> RICK, THE PRESIDENT WEEDING
OUT SAYING HE IS VERY PROUD OF
THE JOB SHE DID THERE TODAY.
THIS IS OF COURSE FIRST FIRST
SOLO INTERNATIONAL SOLO TRIP.
RICK: FOR PEOPLE NOT FAMILIAR
WITH THE GAMES, TELL US WHAT
THEY ARE ABOUT.
>> A VETERAN HIMSELF, PRINCE
HARRY, FOUNDED THE IMPACT'S
GAMES AND THE WAY OF CONNECTING
WITH WOUNDED SOLDIERS OVER THE
WORLD.
MANY OF WHOM ARE DEALING WITH
LIFE ALTERING INJURIES AND
ILLNESSES LIKE PTSD.
THE VETERANS WHO COMPETE SAY THE
COMPETITION IS TOUGH BUT IT'S
ABOUT A LOT MORE THAN WINNING.
IT'S A CHANCE TO BE A PART OF
SOMETHING AGAIN AND EVERY ONE OF
THOSE ATHLETES GETS TO TAKE HOME
A METAL.
RICK.
RICK: AMAZING GROUP.
THANK YOU, MARIAN.
MEANWHILE, NOW ELEMENTARY
STUDENTS ARE DOING SOMETHING
ABOUT HURRICANE HARVEY.
>> WE DECIDED TO MAKE POSTERS,
WE COLORED IT AND WE WENT AROUND
THE SCHOOL.
>> TO REMIND THEM TO DONATE AND
COME WITH MORE MONEY.
maybe be worried...Really,
really, really worried.
Uh...do you want me to go back
and look for it? I will.
I mean a lot of bad things could
happen.
You need to call the bank. I
don't know how else to tell you,
you need to shut that card off--
[Woman 1] It's off.
[Woman 2] What?
[Woman 1] I can turn it on
and off in my Wells Fargo app.
[Woman 2] Huh! I feel better
already.
[Woman 1] Good.
Ugh. Heartburn.
Sorry Ma'am.
No burning here.
Try Alka-Seltzer
Heartburn relief
gummies.
They don't taste
chalky and work fast.
MMMM. Incredible.
Can I try?
She doesn't
have heartburn.
Alka-Seltzer heartburn
relief gummies.
..
REPORTER:ED THE 4th GRADERS
RAN A DONATION DRIVE AT THEIR
SCHOOL.
THEIR GOAL WAS TO RAISE $1,000.
>> THEY MOWED THE LAWN.
THEY BABYSAT.
>> EVERYBODY JUMPED ON BOARD.
THEY ARE GREAT KIDS.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE GREAT
LEADERS.
REPORTER: THE STUDENTS THEN FACE
TIMED WITH AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
IN HOUSTON TO PRESENT THEM WITH
THAT CHECK.
A 14-YEAR-OLD JUST MADE HER HIGH
SCHOOL DANCE TEAM WHEN THIS
HAPPENED.
HER FATHER JUST BACK FROM A
YEAR'S DEPLOYMENT AT GUANTANAMO
BAY SURPRISE BE HIS DAUGHTER AT
THAT HOMECOMING CEREMONY.
>> I'M EXCITED TO TALK TO HER
AND SEE WHAT SHE HAS DONE SINCE
I HAVE BEEN GONE.
A SHOUT-OUT TO THE LAW
ENFORCEMENT ORGANIZATION HELPING
THE CHILDREN OF THE FALLEN.
MEMBERS OF THE MARINE CORPS AND
MEMBERS OF FEDERAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
I'M RICK LEVENTHAL, THANKS FOR
WATCHING.
JESSE: "WATTERS WORLD" IS ON
TONIGHT.
>> I'M CLEANING OUT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
HE HAS MEMBERS OF THE KKK INSIDE
HIS CABINET.
>> JUST STOP IT, YOU ARE NOT
HELPING THE CAUSE.
JESSE: LEFT-WING RADICALS
RUNNING WILD.
HAVE DEMOCRATS CREATED A
MONSTER.
NEWS ANCHORS CRACKING UNDER
PRESSURE.
EVEN ELLEN GETTING IN ON THE
ACTION.