RUNNING THE MARATHON AND
DEHYDRATED, HE CAME BACK.
>> THE PEOPLE OF BOSTON AND
PEOPLE COMING OUT FROM
RESTAURANTS TO GET TRASH BAGS
AND WATER....
>> Shep: BREAKING NEWS ON FOX
NEWS CHANNEL.
THESE, I AM TOLD, ARE VIDEOTAPE
FIRST IMAGES OF WHAT APPEARS TO
BE ONE OF THE BOMBS THAT
EXPLODED IN THE BOSTON MARATHON
YESTERDAY.
THIS IS BRAND-NEW.
YOU ARE LOOKING AT PHOTOS WE
RECEIVED JUST MINUTES AGO.
OUR FOX STATION FOX 5 IN ATLANTA
OBTAINED THIS IMAGE.
IT'S ONE OF THE PRESSURE BOMBS
AFTER IT EXPLODED.
ON THERE YOU MAY BE ABLE TO SEE
AN F.B.I. TAG.
THIS IS WHAT IS LEFT OF WHAT
CAUSED THE CHAOS IN BOSTON.
GAIL RUSSELL REPORTER BROKE THIS
NEWS AND DALE, HOW DO YOU KNOW
WHAT THIS IS AND HOW DID YOU GET
IT?
>> SHEPARD, WE GOT THIS THROUGH
SOURCES WHO VERIFIED FOR US THAT
THESE ARE ACTUAL CRIME SCENE
PHOTOS FROM THE FIRST BOMB FROM
MONDAY'S BOSTON MARATHON
BOMBING.
>> Shep: TELL ME WHAT WE'RE
LOOKING AT HERE.
WHETHER I LOOK AT IT, I CAN'T
TELL WHAT IT IS?
>> WHAT YOU ARE SEEING IS AN
ORDINARY, EVERYDAY PRESSURE
COOKER.
THEY ARE VERY COMMON IN THE
STORES, BUT ALSO THEY ARE COMMON
FOR BOMB MAKING.
YOU ALSO SEE A BLACK PADDED
EITHER KNAPSACK OR DUFFEL BAG
THAT MY SOURCES SAY THE BOMB WAS
CARRIED IN.
THERE IS ALSO SMALL BEARING TYPE
PELLETS, AND SOME SORT OF PUT AT
THIS HOLDING THEM TOGETHER.
IT WAS PART OF THE SHRAPNEL THAT
MATES IT DEADLY.
>> SO INVESTIGATORS HAD THIS
FROM THE EARLY MINUTES.
THE PEOPLE TOOK THE PICTURES.
WHAT YOU ARE SAYING THEY TOOK
PICTURES OF THIS.
SINCE THEN THEY HAVE BEEN
ANALYZING IT.
LOOKING AT ALL THE MATERIALS,
TRYING TO TRACE THEM BACK TO THE
SOURCE AND HELPING THEM TRACE TO
WHOEVER BOUGHT THEM AND PUT THEM
TOGETHER.
>> THAT IS EXACTLY WHAT THEY DO.
WHERE WERE THEY MANUFACTURED AND
WHERE WERE THEY SOLD.
THEY ARE VERY COMMON EVERYDAY
PIECES.
THE KEY IS WHEN THEY GET TO
THESE PIECES, THEY GET THEM INTO
THE LABORATORY.
THAT IS WHEN THEY ARE GOING TO
FIND WHETHER THERE IS A SIMPLE
LITTLE PIECE OF DNA OH A SLICE
OF SCOTCH TAPE OR FINGERPRINT
LEFT OVER ON A DEVICE THAT THE
BOMBER DOESN'T KNOW THEY LEFT
BEHIND.
>> Shep: WE'VE SCROLLED THROUGH
THE PICTURES AGAIN.
ARE THESE SERIAL NUMBERS ON THE
PRESSURE COOKER IS THAT WHAT
THEY ARE LOOKING AT WHEN THEY
ZOOM IN?
>> WE ARE EXAMINING THAT TO TRY
TO DETERMINE EXACTLY WHAT THOSE
NUMBERS ARE.
WE TALKED TO WHO WE BELIEVE IS
THE MANUFACTURER, BUT WE'RE
STILL WORKING ON THAT.
I THINK THERE IS SOME
UNDERWRITING LABORATORY NUMBERS
ON THERE.
THERE IS SOME NUMBERS THAT MAY
BE, AS YOU SAY, SERIAL NUMBERS.
THE SAME THING THE F.B.I. AND
ATF, WHO MANUFACTURED THIS
PIECE.
THEY GOT ENOUGH TO WORK WITH.
THEY ARE GOING TO BE ABLE TO
TAKE THAT AND FIND OUT WHO
MANUFACTURED IT, WHO SOLD IT AND
WHERE.
>> Shep: SO DALE, WHAT YOU ARE
SAYING, AFTER THE BOMB EXPLODED
THIS IS A LARGE CHUNK THAT ENDED
UP AT THE CRIME SCENE AND THE
REST OF IT CAUSED THE MAIMING
AND DESTRUCTION.
WHAT ARE YOUR SOUTH, FOREIGN?
>> WHAT ONE OF THE THINGS I WAS
REMINDED OF, WHAT IS THE MESSAGE
OF THE BOMBER?
WHAT WERE THEY TRYING TO SAY?
THAT IS WHAT THEY ARE TRYING TO
SORT IS THROUGH RIGHT NOW.
ONE OF THE THINGS THEY LOOK AT
IS THE LOCATION, BOSTON MARATHON
THE DATE ON TAX DAY, ON PATRIOTS
DAY, FOUR OR FIVE DAYS BEFORE
THE ANNIVERSARY OF WACO.
THESE ARE ALL IMAGES AND SYMBOLS
THAT INVESTIGATORS ARE SIFTING
THROUGH TO SEE IF THAT HAD
ANYTHING TO DO WITH THE MESSAGE
THAT WAS PUT HERE WITH THESE TWO
BOMBS AT THE BOSTON MARATHON.
THEY CAN'T RULE OUT OVERSEAS,
FOREIGN TERRORISM AND THEY
LOOKING AT ALL OF THAT TRYING TO
DETERMINE WHO WAS BEHIND THIS
AND WHY.
>> Shep: YOU MIGHT HAVE THOUGHT
IN THE MOMENTS AFTER THIS
BOMBING THAT WHEN THESE PRESSURE
COOKERS EXPLODED THEY WOULD HAVE
EXPLODED IN A LOT OF PIECES.
WHAT THESE PICTURES SEEM TO
INDICATE, VERY LARGE PIECES HELD
TOGETHER.
WE SEE NUMBERS IDENTIFYING
MARKS.
WE SEE MATERIALS THAT ARE
CLEARLY, ACCORDING TO YOUR
SOURCES, THE MATERIALS THAT HELD
THIS BOMB AS IT SAT EITHER IN A
TRASH CAN OR SIDE 56 CURB.
THESE ARE VERY VALUABLE PIECES
OF EVIDENCE WHICH I'M GETTING
WILL BE ICONIC PIECES.
I'M GETTING THERE ARE REPORTERS
ALL OVER BOSTON ARE WONDERING
HOW IN ATLANTA CAME ACROSS THIS?
>> I WOULD LOVE TO TELL YOU,
SHEPARD, I THINK WE'LL HAVE TO
HAVE THAT CONVERSATION OFF AIR.
>> Shep: UNDERSTOOD.
DALE, PLEASE STAY WITH US.
WE'RE BRINGING IN KATHERINE
HERITAGE.
KATHERINE, THE FIRST PICTURES OF
THE REMAINS OF THIS BOMB, WHAT
SOURCES ARE SEE SAYING WHAT SORT
OF EVIDENTIARY VALUE.
>> THEY HAVE A HIGH EVIDENTIARY
VALUE, BUT WE KNOW TONIGHT AND
HAD CONFIRMATION WITHIN THE LAST
COUPLE OF HOURS, THESE BOMB
COMPONENTS, THEY ARE BEING
GATHERED UP AND SHIPPED DOWN TO
WASHINGTON, D.C. AS TO WHAT IS
KNOWN AS F.B.I. LAB DOWN IN
QUANTICO.
THEY PAINSTAKINGLY RECONSTRUCTED
KIND OF WHAT YOU SEE WITH
ARCHAEOLOGIST.
THEY PIECE IT BACK TOGETHER AND
THAT IS HOW THEY UNDERSTAND, THE
MODEL AND MAKE AND THAT KIND OF
INFORMATION THAT CAN ALLOW THEM
TO IDENTIFY POTENTIALLY THE
SOURCE OF PURCHASE.
THAT IS THE KEY BECAUSE
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE A WITNESS WHO
CAN IDENTIFY A SUSPECT, SOMEONE
WHO IS AGENTS GO A LITTLE
STRANGE OR THEY MAY HAVE VIDEO
IN THE STORE THAT CAN LOOK AT A
SPECIFIC TIME FRAME AND FIND
THAT INDIVIDUAL.
SO WHAT WE'VE GOT RIGHT HERE IS
THE FIRST PICTURES OF THE PUZZLE
PIECES OF PUZZLE AND CRIME
SCENE.
NOW THEY ARE COMING DOWN TO
WASHINGTON, GOING TO THAT CRIME
LAB.
THEY WILL BE RECEMENT BLD WITH A
BROKEN PIECE OF HISTORY AND PUT
IT TOGETHER.
THEY IDENTIFY THE SOURCE AND
THEN TRY AND IDENTIFY WHO
PURCHASED IT.
FROM THAT, VERY POSSIBLE LEADS.
>> Shep: MORE QUICKLY YOU CAN DO
THAT THE BETTER YOUR CHANCES OF
GETTING AT WHOEVER PLACED IT.
HOW QUICKLY THEY WERE ABLE TO
PUT THIS TOGETHER AND WHETHER
THEY ARE ON THE TRAIL OF
ANYTHING AS A RESULT?
>> WHAT WAYS TOLD BY VETERANS,
THEY KNOW HOW THE BOMB WAS
BUILT.
THEY KNOW THIS GAME SO WELL.
THEY HAVE SEEN SO MANY BOMBS.
THEY HAVE DATABASES WITH ALL THE
COMPONENTS WE'VE SEEN HERE IN
THE PICTURES AND MORE.
WE ONLY HAVE SOME OF THE
PICTURES AND NOT ALL OF THEM.
THIS IS ONLY THE FIRST BOMB.
THEY'VE GOT ALL THIS EVIDENCE
TOGETHER AND ALL THIS
EXPERIENCE.
NOW, IT'S A MATTER AS WE HEARD
GOING OUT AND FINDING IT.
>> Shep: KATHERINE, IT'S MY
GUESS THAT THAT PROCESS HAPPENED
VERY QUICKLY.
THEY WERE ABLE TO CLEAR THAT
AREA RIGHT AWAY, ALL THE AREA
WAS SEALED AND TAGGED.
YOU GET SOMETHING LIKE THIS, I
DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE OUTSIDE
THE REALM OF THE OBVIOUS THEY
WOULD SEND THIS RIGHT THERE AND
BEGIN THE PROCESS ALMOST
IMMEDIATELY.
>> Reporter: THEY WILL BEGIN
ALMOST IMMEDIATELY BUT WHAT I
WOULD ADD AND WHAT JUMPED OUT TO
SEVERAL INDIVIDUALS ON
COMMITTEES THAT ARE BEING
BRIEFED ON THE INVESTIGATION WAS
THE WAY IN WHICH THE F.B.I.
SEEMED TO ISSUE ALMOST A CRY FOR
HELP FROM THE PUBLIC FOR VIDEO
AND FOR STILL PICTURES THAT WILL
HELP THEM TRY AND PUT AN
INDIVIDUAL AT THAT SCENE MOMENTS
BEFORE THE BLAST WHEN THE BAG
WAS PLACED.
THAT IS THE KEY.
IT COULD NOT HAVE BEEN THERE FOR
A LONG PERIOD OF TIME.
IT HAD TO BE PLACED, WE HAVE
SEEN A NUMBER OF IMAGES WITH A
BAG IN FRONT OF THOSE
BARRICADES.
YOU'VE GOT TO LOOK AT THAT VIDEO
AND THE INDIVIDUALS.
FINDING A PIECE OF EVIDENCE LIKE
THIS THAT YOU CAN PIECE TOGETHER
YOU'VE GOT TWO TRACKS IN THE
INVESTIGATION.
YOU HAVE THIS WHERE IT CAME FROM
WHO MADE IT THE TIME FRAME,
MAYBE IT WAS MADE TWO OR THREE
YEARS AGO AND THE PERSON HAS
BEEN HANGING ON FOR THAT LONG.
THAT IS THE QUESTION THAT A HAS
TO BE ANSWERED.
IS THERE DNA, THERE ARE
FINGERPRINTS THAT ARE LEFT.
HAIR OR RESIDUE IN THE
EXPLOSIVES THEMSELVES.
>> Shep: WE CAN ONLY PRESUME IF
THERE IS A DNA ON THERE, THEY
KNOW IT.
IF THERE IS DNA ON THERE THEY
ARE ACTING ON IT.
KATHERINE, AND DALE FROM FOX 5
IN ATLANTA WITH THE SCOOP OF THE
DAY AND OF THIS STORY.
THE F.B.I. HAS PICTURES WHAT
THEY BELIEVE TO BE THE BOMB THAT
BLEW UPRIGHT THERE AT THE FINISH
LINE OFF THE BOSTON MARATHON.
PICTURES WITH NUMBERS AND
ETCHINGS WITH THE MATERIAL STILL
AROUND THEM IN SOME PARTS.
ALL THE DAMAGE THAT IT DID AND
THE LIVES THAT IT TOOK ON THE
STREETS AT THE FINISH LINE.
YET THESE LARGE PIECES OF THAT
BOMB REMAIN.
COURTESY OF FOX 5 IN ATLANTA.
DALE RUSSELL, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'LL BE BACK TO YOU.
A GUT-WRENCHING LOOK AT THE
YOUNGEST VICTIM KILL IN THE
ATTACK.
MARTIN RICHARD SEEN IN A
PHOTOGRAPH HOLDING A POSTER
READING, NO MORE HURTING PEOPLE,
PLEASE.
ACCORDING TO BOSTON GLOBE, HE
HAD JUST HUGGED HIS DAD WHEN IS
THE FIRST BOMB EXPLODED.
MOURNERS LEFT CANDLES AND
FLOWERS AND ON THIS DRIVEWAY
SOMEONE WROTE THE WORD PEACE.
MOTHER AND SISTER ARE STILL IN
SERIOUS CONDITION AND THE FATHER
IS IN SHOCK.
>> I SAW HIM GETTING GET OUT OF
THE CAR.
I SAID -- OH, MY GOD, ARE YOU
OKAY?
>> HE DIDN'T EVEN ANSWER ME.
HIS FRIEND TOLD ME WHAT HAD
HAPPENED.
I WAS IN SHOCK AND HORRIFIED.
>> Shep: THAT DAD RELEASED A
STATEMENT, I QUOTE, WE THANK OUR
FAMILY AND FRIENDS.
THOSE WE KNOW AND THOSE WE HAVE
NEVER MET FOR OUR THOUGHTS AND
PRAYERS.
PRAY FOR MY FAMILY AS WE
REMEMBER MARTIN.
MEANTIME, WE'RE HEARING MORE
FROM THE MOTHER CONFIRMED
FATALITY.
CRYSTAL CAMPBELL.
>> OUR HEARTS ARE BROKEN.
EVERYBODY THAT KNEW HER LOVED
HER.
SHE LOVED EVERYBODY.
>> SHE HAD A HEART OF GOLD.
WE ARE LEARNING THAT MOM THOUGHT
HER DAUGHTER SURVIVED THE BLAST,
ACCORDING TO A FRIEND'S FACEBOOK
POST THE FAMILY LEARNED THE
TRUTH WHEN THEY GOT TO THE
HOSPITAL AND REALIZED THE
PATIENT IN THE ROOM, IT WAS NOT
THEIR DAUGHTER AFTER ALL.
SHE WAS CARRYING A FRIEND'S
I.D..
WE DON'T KNOW NAME YET OF THE
THIRD PERSON KILLED BUT BOSTON
UNIVERSITY IS NOW CONFIRMING THE
VICTIM WAS GRADUATE STUDENT
THERE.
THE SCHOOL NOT RELEASING THE
NAME BECAUSE THEY ARE WAITING
PERMISSION FROM THE FAMILY.
>> SOME DOCTORS FINISHED RUNNING
THE MARATHON AND WENT STRAIGHT
TO WORK TREATING THE VICTIMS.
THAT IS ONE OF THE STORIES HOW
BOSTON'S WORLD CLASS MEDICAL
STAFFERS ARE INSPIRING THIS CITY
IN THIS NATION.
IT WAS ONE OF THE MOST CHILLING
IMAGES WE SAW AS THE NEWS FIRST
BROKE.
WE'RE NOT SHOWING YOU WORST PART
WHAT THE BLAST DID TO A MAN'S
LEG.
AN UPDATE HOW HE IS DOING.
FROM THE JOURNALISTS FROM FOX
NEWS, AS NEWS BROKE THAT PIECES
OF THE BOMB THAT EXPLODED THERE
ARE NOW IN THE HANDS OF THE
F.B.I.
THE FIRSTE IN OUR
BEEN SHOWN TO THE WORLD.
FROM BOSTON, THIS IS THE FOX
REPORT ON FOX NEWS CHANNEL.
ALL STATIONS COME OVER TO
MISSION A FOR A FINAL GO.
THIS IS FOR REAL THIS TIME.
STEP SEVEN POINT
TWO ONE TWO.
RIFY AND LOCK.
COMMAND IS LOCKED.
FIVE SECONDS.
THREE, TWO, ONE.
STANDING BY FOR CAPTURE.
THE MOST INNOVATIVE
SOFTWARE ON THE PLANET...
DRAGON IS CAPTURED.
IS CONNECTING TODAY'S LEADING
COMPANIES TO PLACES BEYOND IT.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
>>.
>> Shep: SOME OF THE HEROES HERE
IN BOSTON THAT WORKED ALL NIGHT
LONG WITH NO REST TO SAVE LIVES
OF THE VICTIMS.
BECAUSE OF THEIR UNBELIEVABLE
DEDICATION, DOCTORS AT
MASSACHUSETTS HOSPITAL SAYS
NOBODY IN THAT THEIR CARE IS
LIKELY TO DIE FROM THEIR
INJURIES.
CHIEF SURGEON SAYS SHIS TEAM IS
DRAWING STRENGTH FROM SOME OF
THE VICTIMS.
>> I'VE BEEN MOVED, AS A MATTER
OF FACT I'VE BEEN REALLY AMAZED
BY THE RESOLVE OF OUR PATIENTS.
SOME OF THEM WOKE UP TODAY WITH
NO LEG AND THEY TOLD ME THEY ARE
HAPPY TO BE ALIVE.
THEY THOUGHT THESE THINGS
HAPPEN.
THEY THOUGHT THEY WOULD DIE AS
THEY SAW THE BLOOD SPILLING OUT.
THEY THOUGHT THEY WOULD LOSE
THEIR LIFE RIGHT THERE AND THEN.
>> Shep: THE ROAD AHEAD WILL BE
DIFFICULT.
SIX OR SEVEN TEAM ACCORDING TO
THE DOCTORS SAID TO BE IN
CRITICAL CONDITION.
SOME OF THE VICTIMS HAVE LOST
LEGS.
OTHERS SUFFERED SEVERE SHRAPNEL
WOUNDS.
MANY FACE MONTHS IF NOT YEARS OF
PHYSICAL AND MENTAL RECOVERY.
MIKE TOBIN IS LIVE AT
MASSACHUSETTS HOSPITAL WITH THE
LATEST.
DOCTORS TALKED ABOUT THE
SHRAPNEL THEY ARE REMOVING FROM
THESE VICTIMS.
IT'S INCREDIBLE?
>> IT REALLY IS.
DOCTORS SAY THEY HAVE BEEN
PULLING NAILS AND BALL BEARINGS
OUT OF THE VICTIMS, MOSTLY BALL
BEARINGS LIKE SPIKES, SHARP AT
BOTH ENDS.
AT WOMEN'S HOSPITAL THEY SAY THE
SAME THING, NAILS AND BALL
BEARINGS COMING OUT OF THE
VICTIMS.
ALL CONSISTENT THE BOMBS WERE
PACKED WITH SHRAPNEL AND TENDED
TO RIP THROUGH VICTIMS LIKE A
SHOTGUN BLAST.
>> A VARIETY HAVE SHARP OBJECTS,
PROBABLY THIS BOMB HAD MULTIPLE
METALLIC FRAGMENTS IN THEM.
WE REMOVED PELLETS AND NAILS.
>> Reporter: AT MASSACHUSETTS
GENERAL, THEY PERFORMED FOUR
AMPUTATIONS.
THE DECISION TO AMPUTATE WAS NOT
A DIFFICULT ONE.
MOST OF INJURIES WERE TO THE
LEGS, LOWER EXTREMITIES BECAUSE
THE BLAST WENT ACROSS THE
GROUND.
THERE IS A TWO-YEAR-OLD BOY THAT
SUFFERED A HEAD INJURY BECAUSE
HE WAS LOW TO THE GROUND.
DOCTORS ARE HAPPY TO SAY HE IS
IN GOOD CONDITION.
>> Shep: GREAT TO HEAR.
THE DOCTORS SAID THIS AFTERNOON
THIS BOMBING HAS CAUSED A UNIQUE
SITUATION WITH BLOOD DONATIONS?
>> DOCTORS ARE VERY IMPRESSED BY
THE WAY THE COMMUNITY CAME OUT
TO DONATE BLOOD.
SO MUCH SO THEY NO LONGER NEED
BLOOD FOR THE IMMEDIATE TIME.
>> WHAT YOU CAN DO IS PUT YOUR
NAME ON A LIST.
THESE PATIENTS WILL NEED
TRANSFUSIONS OVER THE NEXT FEW
DAYS AND WEEKS.
YOUR CONTRIBUTIONS WOULD BE
WELCOME.
WE DON'T WANT TO BE IN A
POSITION TO THROW OUT BLOOD
BECAUSE WE HAVE SO MUCH TODAY WE
CAN'T USE IT ALL.
>> Reporter: PEOPLE CAN CHECK
BACK LATER.
DOCTORS WERE VERY IMPRESSED WITH
THE WAY THE COMMUNITY CAME OUT
AND VERY IMPRESSED BY THE
RESILIENCE OF THE VICTIMS.
>> Shep: MIKE, THANKS.
THE GOVERNOR OF MASSACHUSETTS
SAID HE VISITED A YOUNG VICTIM
NAMED VICTORIA.
SHE WAS HYSTERICAL, AS HE PUT IT
UNTIL AN ARMY SERGEANT, AFGHAN
VETERAN CALMED HER DOWN.
>> HIS NAME IS TYLER.
ONE OF THE THINGS HE SAID TO HER
WAS TO SHOW HER HIS OWN SHRAPNEL
WOUND OR SCAR FROM HIS OWN
SHRAPNEL WOUND WHEN HE WAS IN
AFGHANISTAN.
VICTORIA VERY, VERY MUCH WANTS
TO THANK TYLER PERSONALLY.
IF TYLER IS OUT THERE OR
LISTENING.
WE WOULD LOVE TO HEAR FROM TYLER
SO WE CAN CONNECT HIM TO
VICTORIA.
>> Shep: GOVERNOR PATRICK CAN
CALL THIS PHONE ANYMORE ON ON
YOUR SCREEN.
>>> THE DAY AFTER A DEADLY
TERROR ATTACK, WE'RE LEARNING
SOMEBODY MAILED A LETTER TAINTED
WITH POISON TO A UNITED STATES
SENATOR.
BREAKING DETAILS AS FOX REPORTS
LIVE TONIGHT, ONE DAY AFTER THE
BOMBINGS IN BOSTON.
UPID LOUD PL.
TO PROVE IT, WE SET UP
OUR CALL CENTER RIGHT HERE...
[ chirp ]
ALL GOOD?
GETTY UP.
SERIOUSLY,
THIS IS REALLY HAPPENING!
[ cellphone rings ]
HELLO?
IT'S A GIANT HELICOPTER MA'AM.
[ Male Announcer ] GET IT DONE
[ chirp ]
WITH THE ULTRAUGGED
ocera Torque,
ONLY FROM Sprint
Direct Conct.
BUY ONE GET FOUR FREE
FOR YOUR BUSINESS.
CAN YOU START THE DAY
THE WAY YOU WANT?
CAN ORENCIA (ABATACEPT) HELP?
[ Woman ] I WANTED TO GET UP
WHEN I WAS READY,
NOT MY JOINTS.
[ Female Announcer ] COULD YOUR
"I WANT" BECOME "I CAN"?
TALK TO YOUR RHEUMATOLOST.
ORENCIA REDUCES
MANY RA SYMPTOMS
LIKE PAIN, MORNING STIFFNESS
AND THE PROGRESSION
OF JOINT DAMAGE.
IT'S HELPED NEW RA PATIENTS
AND THOSE NOT HELPED ENOUGH
BY OTHER TREATMENTS.
DO NOT TAKE ORENCIA
WITH ANOTHER BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
FOR RA
DUE TO AN INCREASED RISK
OF SERIOUS INFECTION.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS CAN OCCUR
INUDING FATAL INFECTIONS.
CAS OF LYMPHOMA AND
LUNG CANCER HAVE BEEN REPORTED.
YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU ARE
PRONE TO OR HAVE ANY INFECTION
LIKE AN OPEN SORE OR THE FLU
OR A HISTORY OF COPD,
A CHRONIC LUNG DISEASE.
ORENCIA MAY WORSEN YOUR COPD.
[ Woman ] HERE'S INFORMATION
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
ORENCIA IS AVAILABLE
IN TWO FORMS,
INFUSION AND ALSO
SELF-INJECTION.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR TO SEE
IF ORENCIA IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
AND SEE IF YOU CAN CHANGE
"I WANT"
TO "OH, YES I CAN!"
BJORN EARNS UNLIMITED REWAS
FOR HIS SMALL BUSINESS
TAKE THESEAGS
TO ROOM 12 PLEASE.
[ Garth ] BJORS SMALL BUSISS
EARNS DOUBLE MILES
ON EVERY PURCHASE EVERY DAY.
PRODUCE DELIVERY.
[ Bjorn ] JUST PUT IT
ON MY Spark Card.
[ Garth
WHY SETTLE FOR LESS?
AHH, OH!
[ Garth ] GREAT BUSINESSES
DESERVE LIMITED REWARD
HERE'S
YOUR WAKE UP CALL.
[ Male Announcer ]
GET THE Spark Business Card
FROM Capital One
AND EARN UNLIMITED REWARDS.
CHOOSE DOUBLE MILES
OR 2% CASH BACK
ON EVERY PURCHASE EVERY DAY.
WHAT'S IN YOUR WALLET?
[ crows ]
NOW WHERE'S THE SNOOZE BUTTON?
>>.
>> Shep: BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
WASHINGTON, SOMEBODY SENT A
LETTER TO A UNITED STATES
SENATOR AND IN THE ENVELOPE HAS
TESTED POSITIVE FOR RICIN A
DEADLY POISON.
MIKE, WHICH SENATOR.
IT'S A SENATOR FROM MISSISSIPPI?
>> THAT IS RIGHT.
ROGER WICKER WHO HAS SERVED
MISSISSIPPI SINCE 2007.
WE UNDERSTAND THE LETTER WAS
INTERCEPTED AT AN OFF-SITE
FACILITY.
MY UNDERSTANDING WE HAVE LIVE
PICTURES OF THAT OFF SITE
FACILITY.
ALL INDICATIONS ARE THE SYSTEM
THAT WAS SET UP AFTER THE 2001
ANTHRAX LETTERS THAT WERE SENT
TO LAWMAKERS THAT CREATED SUCH
HYSTERIA ON CAPITOL HILL, SYSTEM
WORKED IN THIS CASE.
A TEST POSITIVE AND LAWMAKERS
WERE TOLD OF THIS AT A BRIEFING
THIS EVENING WITH THE F.B.I.
DIRECTOR ROBERT MUELLER AND
JANET NAPOLITANO AND TERRY
GAINER.
THERE WAS NO HARM DONE.
IT WAS CAUGHT AT AN OFF-SITE
FACILITY.
>> Shep: LIVE PICTURES WE'RE
LOOKING AT THAT FROM POSTAL
FACILITY.
ANYTHING FROM SENATOR WICKER'S
OFFICE?
>> THEY ARE REMAINING
TIGHT-LIPPED.
HE HAS BEEN A LOW PROFILE GUY
AND HAS SERVED SINCE 2007.
MEMBER OF THE JOINT ECONOMIC
COMMITTEE AND BUDGET COMMITTEE.
AT YOU CAN IMAGINE, HIS STAFF
WAS NOT WELCOME THE NEWS AND WHO
MAY HAVE SENT THIS LETTER TO THE
HIS OFFICE.
A DEMOCRATIC FROM MISSOURI TOLD
REPORTERS OFF CAMERA THE LETTER
CAME FROM SOMEBODY WHO
FREQUENTLY WRITES TO LAWMAKERS.
THAT KO MAY GOOD INVESTIGATIVE
LEAD AS TO FIGURE OUT WHO SENT
THIS AND WHY TO GET TO THE
BOTTOM OF THIS INVESTIGATION.
>> Shep: AS AN ASIDE, NO
CONNECTION TO ANY OF THE ACTIONS
HERE IN BOSTON.
WE'RE WORKING TO CONTACT SENATOR
WICKER.
CONTINUING COVERAGE OF BREAKING
NEWS, WHAT APPEARS TO BE THE
FIRST IMAGE OR THE FIRST SERIES
OF IMAGES OF ONE OF THE BOMBS
THAT EXPLODED AT THE BOSTON
MARATHON HERE YESTERDAY.
OUR STATION FOX 5 FOR ATLANTA
OBTAINED THIS IMAGE.
WE'RE TOLD IT IS THE PRESSURE
COOLINGER BOMB ONE OF THEM AFTER
IT EXPLODED.
WE'LL HAVE CONTINUING COVERAGE
MOMENTS AWAY.
JUST ABOUT EVERYBODY THAT WAS AT
THE MARATHON AS A RUNNER OR
SPECTATOR.
COMING UP, MORE DRAMATIC TALES
FROM PEOPLE THAT SAW AND HEARD
THE TRAGEDY UNFOLD.
A CREW AND I WENT DOWN TO THE
SCENE JUST AS THE CREWS WERE
STARTING TO CLEAN UP.
>> OVER HERE BEHIND ME IS A
PUBLIC PARK AND BOSTON COMMONS.
YOU CAN SEE RUNNERS WERE AROUND
TAKING PICTURES.
THERE WERE A LOT OF PEOPLE
RUNNING IN THE PARKS.
YOU CAN SEE ALL THE MEDIA
CAMERAS.
THE BOMBINGS THEMSELVES WERE
JUST DOWN HERE.
IF YOU GO ABOUT THREE BLOCKS
PAST ON THE LEFT.
THAT IS WHERE ONE OF THEM
HAPPENED.
THE OTHER SIDE OF THE STREET WAS
THE OTHER ONE.
9 CAMERA VIEWS THAT YOU SAW ALL
DAY YESTERDAY AND TODAY IS WHERE
THE FINISH LINE WAS WHERE SOME
5,000 PEOPLE NEVER MADE IT
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
HOW DO YOU ENGINEER
A TRUE AUTOMOTIVE BRKTHROUGH?
♪
YOU GIVE IT BOLD STYLING,
UNSURPASSED LUXURY
AND NEARLY 1,000 IMPROVEMENTS.
THE REDESIGNED 2013 GLK.
THE NEXT GREAT ADVANCE
FROM MERCEDES-BENZ.
STARTING AT $37,090.
[ Male Announcer ] A CAR HAS A
RATHER SMALL REAR-VIEW MIRROR,
SO WE CAN OCCASIONALLY GLANCE
BACK AT WHERE WE'VE BEEN.
IT HAS AN ENORMOUS WINDSHIELD
SO WE CAN LOOK AHEAD
TO WHERE WE ARE GOING.
NOW IS ALWAYS THE TIME
TO GO FORWARD.
AND REIMAGINE
ALL THE POSSIBILITIES
THAT LIE BEFORE US.
AN ALLY FOR REAL POSSIBILITIES.
AARP.
FIND TOOLS AND GUIDANCE
AT AARP.ORG/POSSIBILITIES.
>>.
>> Shep: I'M SHEPARD SMITH, THIS
IS THE FOX REPORT.
BOTTOM OF THE HOUR, TIME FOR THE
TOP OF THE NEWS, INVESTIGATORS
TAKING A CLOSE LOOK AT THESE
IMAGES SHOWS WHAT WE'RE TOLD IS
ONE OF THE BOMBS THAT DETONATED
YESTERDAY AT THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
OUR REPORTER FROM FOX 5 IN
ATLANTA OBTAINED THESE IMAGES.
THEY APPARENTLY SHOW THE
WRECKAGE OF A PRESSURE COOKER.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE INDICATED
WHOEVER CARRIED OUT THE ATTACK
DID USE PRESSURE COOKERS TO
CONSTRUCT THE BOMBS.
RICK LEVANTHOL IS HERE IN
BOSTON.
THESE IMAGES ARE EXTRAORDINARY
AND REAL PIECE OF EVIDENCE THAT
WE HAVE ANY SOLID.
>> Reporter: ABSOLUTELY.
WE HAD HEARD EARLIER FROM F.B.I.
AND AUTHORITIES BELIEVE THE
BOMBS MIGHT HAVE BEEN MADE FROM
PRESSURE COOKERS.
THEY MAY HAVE BEEN CARRIED IN
BLACK NYLON BAGS OR BACKPACKS
AND THESE PHOTOS SHOW A MANGLED
PRESSURE COOKER AND SHREDDED
BACKPACK.
THESE ARE CLEARLY CRIME SCENE
PHOTOS, WHAT THEY BELIEVE TO BE
EVIDENCE OF ONE OF THE POSSIBLE
BOMBS IN THIS ATTACK.
THIS WAS APPARENTLY ACCORDING TO
OUR REPORTERS THE FIRST BOMB
THAT WENT OFF.
ANOTHER OF THE IMAGES SHOWS THE
BALL BEARINGS OR SMALL BBs THAT
MAY HAVE BEEN USED TO SPREAD THE
CARNAGE.
THEY APPEAR TO BE CRIME SCENE
PHOTOS AND DIRECT EVIDENCE OF
ONE OF THE TWO BOMBS USED IN THE
ATTACK.
>> Neil: AND THEORY FROM
KATHERINE HERITAGE, A QUICK
GOOGLE SEARCH, THERE ARE A LOT
OF MANUFACTURERS IN THE STATE OF
GEORGIA.
NOT TO TAKING ANYTHING AWAY FROM
DALE RUSSELL BUT JUST WAY OF
THEORY, THEY MAY HAVE SENT TO
LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES IN
GEORGIA.
THE GOOGLE SEARCH LOOKS AT
MULTIPLE HITS FROM PRESSURE
COOKER MANUFACTURERS AND
POSSIBLE EVIDENCE FROM OTHER
PHOTOS, AS WELL?
>> JUST ONE OTHER NOTE.
WHAT IS REMARKABLE, YOU CAN SEE
THE STAMP FROM THE MANUFACTURER,
WHAT APPEARS TO BE A CLEAR
SERIAL NUMBER ON THAT PRESSURE
COOKER.
THEY CAN FOLLOW THAT UP.
THEY CAN FIGURE OUT WHERE THAT
UNIT WAS SENT AND POSSIBLY WHAT
STORE IT WAS SOLD AND WHO MAY
HAVE BOUGHT IT.
WE SAW TWO COMPELLING PHOTOS
FROM BOSTON AFFILIATE WHAT MAY
BE THE SECOND BOMB THAT WENT
OFF.
WHEN YOU LOOK AT THIS PHOTO, THE
FIRST PICTURE SHOWS WHAT LOOKS
LIKE A BAG OR A BOX ON THE
STREET SIDE OF A METAL BARRICADE
SITTING ON THE CURB.
SECOND PHOTO SHOWS THE SAME AREA
SHORTLY AFTER THE EXPLOSION.
CLEARLY WHERE THE BOX OR BAG WAS
THAT IS WHERE THE AREA WAS WORSE
AFFECTED.
THEY BLURRED IT OUT BECAUSE IT'S
VERY GRAPHIC PHOTO.
THEY SAW NOTHING LEFT OF THAT
BOX.
THAT BOX OR BAG WAS THE SOURCE
OF THE SECOND EXPLOSION.
THOSE PHOTOS HAVE BEEN FORWARDED
TO THE F.B.I.
THESE ARE JUST SOME OF THE
PICTURES WE'RE SEEN THAT
ILLUSTRATED PERHAPS MANY
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF MORE
PHOTOS THEY ARE PORING OVER TO
DETERMINE WHO MAY HAVE LEFT
THESE DEVICES BEHIND.
>> Shep: THANKS TO OUR GREAT
WORK IN ATLANTA FOR THE FIRST
PICTURES WE BELIEVE OF THE
EXPLODED BOMB, THE FIRST ONE TO
GO OFF HERE IN BOSTON.
>> WE'RE HEARING MORE TONIGHT
FROM THOSE THAT WERE THERE WHEN
THE BOMBS WENT OFF.
RUNNERS AND SUPPORTERS TELLING
WHAT THEY SAW AND HEARD IN FIRST
MOMENTS OF HORROR.
>> WHERE ARE WE SUPPOSED TO GO?
>> I HEARD THE BIGGEST SOUND
I'VE EVER HEARD IN MY LIFE AND
EVERYTHING WENT CHAOTIC.
>> THE GROUND SHOOK, BIGGEST
EARTHQUAKE.
>> WE WERE PICKING UP METALS AND
PEOPLE WERE CONGRATULATING --
PICKING UP OUR MEDALS AND ALL OF
A SUDDEN, JUST KABOOM.
THIS LOUD BLAST.
WE ALL STOPPED AND TURNED.
WE LOOKED TOWARD THE FINISH
LINE.
YOU COULD SEE A BIG CLOUD OF
SMOKE.
>> THERE WAS A SECOND ONE.
EVERYBODY SAID YOU NEED TO RUN.
BASICALLY EVERYONE STARTED
RUNNING AS MUCH AS THEY COULD.
>> I SAW A FIREBALL WHICH IS NOT
LIKE IN THE MOVIES.
YOU SEE IT AN INSTANT BEFORE YOU
HEAR IT.
>> PEOPLE WERE GOING THE OTHER
WAY.
THEY WERE PEOPLE RUNNING AWAY.
>> I WAS IN A POST RACE PARTY
THIRD FLOOR OF A BUILDING
OPPOSITE THE FINISH LINE.
I WAS SITTING ON THE COUCH.
THE BLAST BLEW ME OFF THE COUCH
ONTO THE GROUND.
I RAN DOWN THE STAIRS AND I RAN
ON TO A CARPET OF GLASS AND
BLOOD STREAKS.
I HAVE TALKED TO MOST OF THE
PEOPLE THAT WERE AT THE PARTY
AND WE'RE BONDED.
THIS EXPERIENCE HAS BONDED US.
>> I WAS THERE WHEN THE OKLAHOMA
BOMBING HAPPENED AND I DON'T
THINK TIM McVEIGH WOULD HAVE
THOUGHT, SOMEHOW IN THE
AFTERMATH OF ALL THIS, WE'RE
BETTER PEOPLE.
I THINK IT IS A FACT.
>> I THINK SO.
A LOT OF PEOPLE WENT AWAY FROM
THE BOMBING WHEN IT HAPPENED.
WE STARTED TO MAKE SURE
EVERYBODY WAS OKAY.
PEOPLE LIKE BRUCE RAN TOWARD
THEM SO PEOPLE WERE OKAY.
IT BRINGS EVERYBODY TOGETHER.
>> Shep: MEMORIES OF YESTERDAY
THAT WILL NO DOUBT LAST A
LIFETIME.
WE EXPECT MANY MORE STORIES THAT
WENT TO A MARATHON WHAT FELT
LIKE A WAR ZONE.
FIRST REPORTS FROM BOSTON, THERE
MAY HAVE BEEN ONE IMAGE TO SHOW
THE NATION HOW HORRIBLE IT
REALLY WAS.
A GRAVELY INJURED MAN IN A
WHEELCHAIR, THEY RAN AS LIVE
DURING STUDIO "B" AND CAME
ACROSS OUR ON MONITORS IN THE
STUDIO.
THERE WAS AN AUDIBLE GASP IN THE
ROOM.
WORKERS LOOKED DOWN AT THE FLOOR
IN DISBELIEF.
BOTH HIS LEGS WERE GONE.
MANY WONDERED IF HE SURVIVED.
HIS STORY CAN BE TOLD.
HIS NAME IS JEFF AND HE WAS AT
THE RACE TO WATCH HIS
GIRLFRIEND.
DOCTORS HAD TO AMPUTATE WHAT WAS
LEFT OF HIS LEGS.
HE IS CURRENTLY IN STABLE
CONDITION.
THE DOCTORS SAID TODAY MANY OF
THOSE WHO WOKE UP AFTER SURGERY
STUNNED TO BE ALIVE SAID HOW
HAPPY THEY WERE MISSING LIMBS
AND EXCITED FOR ANOTHER DAY.
YESTERDAY'S TERROR ATTACK
TRIGGERING SECURITY AROUND THE
GLOBE INCLUDING IN LONDON WHERE
A MARATHON IS ONE BIG EVENT SET
TO GET UNDERWAY.
THE DETAILS ARE NEXT AS FOX
REPORTS LIVE FROM BOSTON.
ARE YOU STILL SLEEPING?
JUST WANTED TO CHECK AND MAKE
SURE THAT WE WERE ON SCHEDULE.
THE FIRST TECHNOLOGY
OF ITS KIND...
MOM AND DAD, I HAVE GREAT NEWS.
IS NOW PROVIDING
ANSWERS FAMILIES NEED.
SIEMENS. ANSWERS.
[ SHIP HORN BLOWS ]
NO, NO, NO!
STOP!
HUMANS.
ONE DAY WE'RE COMING UP
WITH THE THEORY OF RELATIVITY,
THE NEXT...
NOT SO MUCH.
BUT THAT'S OKAY --
YOU'RE COVERED
WITH GREAT IDEAS LIKE OPTIONAL
BETTER CAR REPLACEMENT
FROM LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
TOTAL YOUR CAR
AND WE GIVE YOU THE MONEY
TO BUY ONE A MODEL YEAR NEWER.
LEARN ABOUT IT
AT LIBERTYMUTUAL.COM.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
RESPONSIBILITY.
WHAT'S YOUR POLICY?
>>.
>> Shep: THE PRESIDENT IS HEADED
TO BOSTON.
WHITE HOUSE SAYS HE WILL SPEAK
AT AN INTERFAITH SERVICE
DEDICATED TO THE VICTIMS OF THE
BOSTON BOMBING.
EARLIER TODAY MR. OBAMA SAID THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE REFUSE TO BE
TERRORIZED AND PRAISED THE
ACTIONS.
>> EXHAUSTED RUNNERS THAT KEPT
RUNNING TO THE NEAREST HOSPITAL
TO GIVE BLOOD AND THOSE THAT
STAYED TO ATTEND TO THE WOUNDED.
FIRST RESPONDERS WHO RAN INTO
THE CHAOS TO SAVE LIVES, IF YOU
WANT TO KNOW WHO WE ARE, WHAT
AMERICA IS, HOW WE RESPOND TO
EVIL, THAT IS IT.
SELFISHLY, COMPASSIONATELY AND
UNAFRAID.
>> Shep: GOVERNMENTS AROUND THE
WORLD ARE INCREASING SECURITY AT
PUBLIC PLACES AND LANDMARKS, BUT
THERE ARE SOME MAJOR EVENTS ON
THE HORIZON INCLUDING 30
DIFFERENT MARATHONS.
GREATEST CHALLENGE MAY BE IN
LONDON.
TOMORROW HUNDREDS OF DIPLOMATS
AND DIGNITARIES ARE EXPECTED THE
FUNERAL OF MARGARET THATCHER.
ON SUNDAY, HALF A MILLION
SPECTATORS ARE EXPECTED TO LINE
THE STREETS OF LONDON FOR THAT
CITY'S MARATHON.
FOX REPORT JONATHAN HUNT LIVE
WITH US.
IT APPEARS THAT THE LONDON
MARATHON IS GOING TO BE A A
TRIBUTE TO THE VICTIMS HERE IN
BOSTON?
>> THE 30,000 EXPECTED RUNNERS
COMPETING IN THE LONDON MARATHON
ON SUNDAY WILL BEGIN WITH A 30
SECONDS MOMENT OF SILENCE BEFORE
THEY START TO TACKLE THAT 26.2
MILE COURSE.
EVERY ONE OF THEM IS ENCOURAGED
TO WEAR A BLACK RIBBON AS
TRIBUTE TO THE VICTIMS OF THE
BOSTON BOMBINGS.
THOSE WILL BE HANDED OUT WHEN
THEY REGISTER TO GET THEIR
NUMBERS AND NOT SURPRISINGLY WE
ARE HEARING THERE IS A REVIEW OF
ALL SECURITY PROCEDURES FOR
SUNDAY'S MARATHON.
LISTEN.
>> THE POTENTIAL LINK BUT WE
DON'T KNOW OF NO OBVIOUS ONE.
BUT WHAT WE NORMALLY DO WE WILL
INCREASE SEARCHING AND MAKE SURE
WE HAVE MORE OFFICERS ON THE
STREET AND LOOKING AFTER PEOPLE
AND MAKING SURE THEY ARE SAFE.
THERE IS NO REASON TO THINK
THERE IS ANY LESS SAFE AFTER THE
TERRIBLE EVENTS IN BOSTON.
>> Bob: WHILE IT'S THE BIGGEST
MARATHON IN THE NEXT FEW DAYS,
THERE IS ONE, NEWEST ONE HERE
THAT WILL BE THE SALT LAKE CITY
CITY MARATHON AND LOOKING AT
SECURITY PROCEDURES THERE.
>> Shep: JONATHAN, THERE IS
ACKNOWLEDGEMENT YOU CAN'T SECURE
EVENTS LIKE THIS.
>> Reporter:, NO ABSOLUTELY.
IN LONDON THERE WILL BE HALF A
MILLION PEOPLE ON THE STREETS.
IT'S ONE THING FOR THE SECURITY
FORCES THERE AS THEY DID
SUCCESSFULLY DURING THE OLYMPICS
LAST YEAR TO SECURE INDIVIDUAL
VENUES BUT WHEN YOU AN OPEN
COURSE LIKE THIS AS EVERY
SECURITY EXPERT WILL TELL YOU,
COMPLETE AND UTTER SECURITY IS
WELL IMPOSSIBLE.
>> YOU MAY SEE MORE BOMB
DETECTION DOGS THAT WILL BE
SNIFFING THROUGH THE CROWD.
WE ARE OPERATING THAT FREE
SOCIETY SO PEOPLE WALKING ALONG
A STREET, WHETHER LINING UP A
MARATHON ROUTE, IT'S DIFFICULT
TO CONTROL IF PEOPLE ARE WILLING
TO GO THROUGH CONTROLS TO GET TO
A PARTICULAR MORE CONCENTRATED
LOCATION.
>> BOTTOM LINE, IT IS NEXT TO
IMPOSSIBLE TO STOP EVERY
DETERMINED WOULD BE BOMBER IN
EVERY POTENTIAL LOCATION.
>> Shep: JONATHAN HUNT, LIVE IN
NEW YORK.
>> TERROR ATTACK IN BOSTON
AFFECTED LEGISLATIVE BUSINESS IN
THE NATION'S CAPITAL.
LATE TONIGHT THE GANG OF EIGHT
IS EXPECTED TO FILE LONG
ANTICIPATED IMMIGRATION BILL.
FOUR REPUBLICANS AND FOUR
DEMOCRATS MAKE UP THE BIPARTISAN
GROUP OF SENATORS.
THEIR PROPOSAL WOULD PUT THE 11
MILLION IMMIGRANTS ON A PATH TO
CITIZENSHIP IN EXCHANGE FOR
PAYING FINES AND INCREASING
BORDER SECURITY.
McCAIN AND SCHUMER BRIEFED OBAMA
ON THEIR PLAN AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THEY SAY THEY HOPE FOR A FINAL
VOTE ON THE BILL BY MAY OR JUNE.
>>> THE BOSTON BOMBINGS FORCED
THE CANCELLATION OF A JOINT NEWS
CONFERENCE WITH GABRIELLE
GIFFORDS AND TWO SENATORS BEHIND
A BARREN BACKGROUND CHECK
BIPARTISAN SUPPORT FOR
BACKGROUND CHECKS.
THEY SHOWED THEIR SUPPORT FOR
THE MEASURE.
BY JOE MANCHIN AND PATRICK
TOOMEY.
IT FACES GROWING OPPOSITION.
THE SENATE COULD VOTE BETWEEN
SIX AND TEN AMENDMENTS TO THE
GUN CONTROL BILL INCLUDING THE
MANCHIN PLAN AND THOSE COULD
COME AS EARLY AS TOMORROW.
>> THE BOMBINGS HERE IN BOSTON
IS SPARKING A DEBATE FOR OUR
SECURITY.
THE CHALLENGES OF KEEPING
AMERICA SAFE WITHOUT TAKING AWAY
OR PERSONAL FREEDOMS AS FOX
REPORTS LIVE FROM BOSTON.
VO: From the classic lines
to the elegant trim
in each and every piece,
bold will make your reality
a dream.
>>.
>> Shep: LIVE LOOK IN DARBY PARK
THE SECTION IN BOSTON WHERE THE
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD MARTIN RICHARD
THAT WAS KILLED IN THE BOMB
ATTACK LIVED.
AS BELLS TOLL HERE.
WE'RE NEAR WHERE THE EXPLOSIONS
HAPPENED.
BELLS HAVE BEEN RINGING AND
HYMNS PLAYING FOR THE LAST HOUR
AND 45 MINUTES.
AFTER THE SUN SET HERE IN BOSTON
FOLKS COMING FROM THE
CANDLELIGHT VIGIL AS THERE IS
MOURNING ACROSS NEW ENGLAND AND
ACROSS AMERICA FOR THE VICTIMS
OF THE BOMBING AT THE MARATHON.
AS YOU CAN IMAGINE, PEOPLE
REMAIN ON EDGE, MANY AFTER THE
BOMBINGS.
IT'S RAISING QUESTIONS HOW IT
COULD IMPACT SECURITY
PRECAUTIONS ACROSS THE NATION.
STEVE CENTANNI IS LIVE IN
WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: SECURITY IS
TIGHTENED IN MANY PLACES ACROSS
THE COUNTRY.
HERE IN WASHINGTON, A SECTION OF
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE IN FRONT OF
THE WHITE HOUSE WAS SHOT DOWN.
POLICE ARE OUT IN FULL FORCE AND
BOSTON AND D.C. AND OTHER MAJOR
CITIES.
SOME SAY OUR CIVIL LIBERTIES
KNOB JEOPARDY IF SECURITY
TIGHTENS FURTHER.
>> I THINK IF THIS IS BEGINNING
OF A TREND, THEN WE REALLY ARE
GOING TO SEE A DISCUSSION ABOUT
DISCUSSION ABOUT CIVIL
LIBERTIES.
>> Reporter: SOME FEAR THE
ISRAELI MODEL OF SECURITY.
STILL OTHERS THING ISRAELI STYLE
SECURITY IS THE SMART WAY TO GO.
>> THIS COUNTRY IS A 14-YEAR-OLD
TEENAGER GOING THROUGH WHAT I
CALL SECURITY PUBERTY.
I DON'T EXPECT THE AMERICANS TO
BE WHERE ISRAELS ARE AT BUT
DEMAND THE GOVERNMENT GETS ON
THE ISRAELI PAGE.
>> IT'S TOO SOON TO KNOW THE
SECURITY IMPLICATIONS OF THE
BOSTON BOMBINGS BUT AMERICANS
DISAGREE OVER THE NEED OF
TIGHTENED SECURITY.
>> YOU KNOW, I'M EASY AND
SECURITY I THINK WOULD GIVE US A
LITTLE PEACE OF MIND IN THIS
HORRIBLE TIME.
>> THE LAST TEN YEARS, EVERY
PARADE AND PUBLIC EVENT NEEDS TO
HAVE PAT-DOWNS.
>> SOME SAY IT'S DESIGNED TO
COMFORTED A NERVOUS AMERICAN
PUBLIC.
>> Shep: STEVE, THANK YOU.
>>> AMONG THE FIRST RESPONDERS,
MEDICAL WORKERS AND CIVILIANS
THAT RAN TO HELP THOSE THAT WERE
INJURED.
A FAMILIAR FACE TO SPORTS FAN, A
PATRIOTS PLAYER WAS READY TO
HELP.
FIRST, LEGENDARY N.F.L.
SPORTSCASTER PAT SUMMERALL HAS
DIED.
HE CALLED GAMES FOR MORE THAN 40
YEARS.
HE BECAME AS MUCH AS SUNDAYS AS
FOOTBALL ITSELF.
>> THE HOOPLA IS JUST ABOUT
OVER.
WE'RE GOING TO PLAY PRETTY SOON.
>> Shep: HE WAS PART OF 16
SUPERBOWLS, HIS LAST IN 2002.
HE WAS ALSO HIS FINAL GAME WITH
LONG TIME PARTNER JOHN MADDEN.
THEY WORKED TOGETHER FOR 21
YEARS.
SUMMERALL DID A HANDFUL OF GAMES
AFTER THAT.
BEFORE HE CALLED THE GAMES, PAT
SUMMERALL PLAYED TEN SEASON IN
THE N.F.L.
HE DIED TODAY OF SUDDEN CARDIAC
ARREST.
IN A STATEMENT FOX SPORTS WRITES
HIS 50 YEAR RECORD AS A
BROADCASTER IS TRULY UNIQUE AND
VERY DIFFICULT FOR ANYONE TO
EVER WALK IN HIS FOOTSTEPS.
PATTED SUMMERALL, DEAD TODAY AT
82.
MINE WAS EARNED IN
DJIBOUTI, AFRICA, 2004.
THE BATTLE OF BATAAN,
1942.
[ all ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA, IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]
USAA AUTO INSURANCE
IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN FROM
GENERATION TO GENERATION
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE THE MILITARY,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY.
GET AN AUTO-INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA.
WE KNOW WHAT IT MEANS TO SERVE.
CHERYL BURKE IS CHA-CHA-ING
IN DEPEND SILHOUETTE BRIEFS
FOR CHARITY, TO PROVE THAT
WITH SOFT FABRIC AND WAISTBAND,
THE BEST PROTECTION LOOKS, FITS,
AND FEELS JUST LIKE UNDERWEAR.
GET A FREE
SAMPLE AND TRY
FOR YOURSELF.
What is it that
makes a Husqvarna?
It's not all the
brilliant engineering, no.
It's this that makes
a Husqvarna!
>>.
>> Shep: MANY SPORTS FANS IN NEW
ENGLAND CONSIDERING JOANNE DRUZI
IN HIS PLAYING DAYS.
HE CARRIED A WOMAN FROM THE
SCENE OF THE BLAST.
HE WAS GREETING RUNNERS AT THE
FINISH LINE.
HE RELEASED A STATEMENT THANKING
PEOPLE FOR THE ATTENTION, BUT
THE SPOTLIGHT SHOULD INSTEAD BE
ON THE COUNTLESS INDIVIDUALS WHO
DID WHATEVER THEY COULD TO SAVE
LIVES.
>>> UPDATING BREAKING NEWS FROM
TONIGHT'S FOX REPORT.
THE VERY FIRST PICTURES OF ONE
OF THE BOMBS THAT BLEW UP HERE
IN BOSTON.
THIS WAS FIRST ON FOX THIS HOUR.
WE'RE TOLD THESE PICTURES SHOW
AN EXPLODED PRESSURE COOKER AND
SHREDDED BLACK DUFFEL BAG.
F.B.I. OFFICIALS SAY THEY DON'T
HAVE INFORMATION ON THE SUSPECT
AND THE INVESTIGATION REMAINS
WIDE OPEN.
RICK LEVANTHOL WITH THE LATE
UPDATE.
>> Reporter: 30 AGENCIES ARE
WORKING THIS CASE.
MANY WERE ON THE SCENE BEFORE
THE EXPLOSIONS DOING SECURITY
FOR THE MARATHON AND ONCE THEY
SECURED THE LOCATION AFTER THE
EXPLOSIONS THEY BEGIN THE
PROCESS OF COLLECTING THE
EVIDENCE.
WHAT WE'RE SEEING NOW,
APPARENTLY ARE PHOTOS OF SOME OF
THAT EVIDENCE.
YOU MENTIONED THE PRESSURE
COOKER.
WE WERE TOLD BY THE F.B.I. THEY
BELIEVE PRESSURE COOKERS WERE
USED IN THE BLAST.
THEY WERE PUT INSIDE A BLACK
NYLON BAG OR BACKPACKS.
WE SEE PICTURES OF A SHREDDED
MANGLED PRESSURE COOKER AND A
SHREDDED BLACK NYLON BAG, ALWAYS
PHOTO THAT APPEARS TO SHOW BALL
BEARINGS OR SMALL METAL PELLETS.
FROM THE NBC AFFILIATE HERE IN
BOSTON THEY HAVE PICTURE WHAT IS
BELIEVED TO BE THE SECOND
EXPLOSION BEFORE THE BOMB WENT
OFF.
AN OBJECT ALONG THE MARATHON
ROUTE ON THE CURB THERE.
WHAT LOOKS LIKE A BOX OR A BAG.
AFTER THE EXPLOSION, SOMETHING
THAT HAS BEEN PARTIALLY BLURRED,
YOU CAN'T SEE THE CARNAGE THAT
IT LEFT BEHIND.
BUT THE BOX OR BAG IS APPARENTLY
GONE.
THAT AREA WAS THE SCENE OF THAT
SECOND BLAST.
THESE ARE SOME OF THE PHOTOS
THAT THE F.B.I. IS NOW LOOKING
AT FRAME BY FRAME.
THEY ARE ALSO LOOKING AT
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO AND OTHER
SOURCES TRYING TO DETERMINE WHO
MIGHT HAVE LEAST THESE PACKAGES
BEHIND AND WHO MIGHT BE
RESPONSIBLE FOR THESE BOMBINGS
THAT HAVE COST THREE LIVES AND
INJURED MORE THAN A 170 OTHERS.
>> Shep: NEW PICTURES FROM FOX 5
IN ATLANTA, PICTURES THE F.B.I.
CLEARLY HAS HAD FOR THE LAST 24
HOURS BUT NEW TO US THANKS TO
HIS REPORTING.
SERIAL NUMBERS, MANUFACTURER
INFORMATION, DUFFEL BAG AFTER
THE BOMB EXPLODED.
PICTURES FROM THE SCENE COULD BE
CRUCIAL.
THEY ALREADY HAVE BEEN CRUCIAL
AS THE INVESTIGATION INTO THIS
BOMBING ROLLS ON.
>> Shep: ON THIS DAY IN 2007, A
GUNMAN KILLED 32 PEOPLE ON THE
CAMPUS OF VIRGINIA TECH
UNIVERSITY IN WHAT IS STILL THE
DEADLIEST SHOOTING SPREE IN
MODERN AMERICAN HISTORY.
IT BEGIN QUARTER AFTER 7:00 IN
THE MORNING, HE FIRST SHOT A
FEMALE FRESHMAN AND RESIDENT
ASSISTANT.
SOMEHOW THE SUSPECT DISAPPEARED.
THE KILLER ENTERED A CLASSROOM
BUILDING AND WENT FROM ROOM TO
ROOM ARMED WITH TWO HANDGUNS AND
KILLED MORE THAN 30 PEOPLE.
THEN HE KILLED HIMSELF.
IN THE DAYS AFTER THAT ATTACK AT
VIRGINIA TECH, EX-CLASSMATES
DESCRIBE HIM AS A DISTURBED
LONER BUT A TRAGEDY STRUCK THAT
COLLEGE CAMPUS, SIX YEARS AGO
TODAY.
NOW, YOU KNOW THE NEWS.
FOR THIS TUESDAY, APRIL 16th,
2013.
FOX REPORT CONTINUES TOMORROW.
WE'LL HAVE COVERAGE THROUGHOUT
THE NIGHT INCLUDING MORE DETAILS
AS WE GET THEM ON THESE NEW
PICTURES, THE FIRST OF ONE OF
THE BOMBS ITSELF THAT BLEW
UPRIGHT ON THE FINISH LINE OF
THE BOSTON MARATHON YESTERDAY.
DETAILS CRUCIAL FOR
INVESTIGATORS AND FIRST VISUAL
ON THEM HERE TONIGHT.
SPEAKING OF, THERE IS
CANDLELIGHT VIGIL UNDERWAY RIGHT
HERE IN BOSTON, GARVEY PARK,
HOME OF THE EIGHT-YEAR-OLD
MARTIN RICHARD WHO WAS KILLED IN
THE BOMB ATTACK AT BOSTON
MARATHON YESTERDAY BY THE
HUNDREDS AND POSSIBLY THOUSANDS
THAT WILL BE OUT IN BOSTON
TONIGHT AS PRAYERS GO OUT FROM
NEW ENGLAND FROM AROUN