IN THE VIDEO, THE AUTHORITIES
SAY THE WHITE SMOKE INDICATES A
BOMB BUILT WITH LOW-VELOCITY
EXPLOSIVE MIXTURES, NOT MILITARY
GRADE.
>> SOMETHING JUST BLEW UP!
>> RUN!
>> THEY MAY NOT HAVE HAD THE
RESOURCES AS WE'VE SEEN IN OTHER
BOMB ATTACKS, BUT THEY KNEW HOW
TO MAKE THE BOMB GO BOOM.
>> Reporter: EXPERTS SAY THE
LARGE PIECES OF METAL, AS SEEN
HERE IN THE AIR, SUGGEST THE
BOMBS MIGHT HAVE BEEN CONCEALED
IN OR UNDER A MAILBOX OR TRASH
BARREL, AS ONE WITNESS
DESCRIBED.
>> I LITERALLY SAW THE GARBAGE
BARREL EXPLODE.
I SAW AT THE FLASH, THE FIRE,
THE SMOKE, AND I RAN AS FAST AS
I COULD.
>> Reporter: MIKE SULLIVAN IS
THE FORMER HEAD OF THE ATF.
>> ALL THE EVIDENCE THEY
COLLECT IT IS, IT MIGHT NOT LOOK
LIKE MUCH.
BUT TO INVESTIGATORS,
EVERY SMALL PIECE OF EVIDENCE
THEY COLLECT WILL BE A TREASURE
TROVE.
>> Reporter: IF THE FBI BELIEF
ABOUT THE PRESSURE COOKER BEARS
OUT, IT WILL BE NO SURPRISE TO
COUNTERTERRORISM OFFICIALS WHO
HAVE WARNED ABOUT THEIR POSSIBLE
USE WITH READILY AVAILABLE
COMPONENTS FOR YEARS.
THERE ARE NUMEROUS DESCRIPTIONS
ONLINE ABOUT HOW TO BUILD A
PRESSURE-COOKER BOMB, INCLUDING
THIS DETAILED ONE POSTED IN AN
AL QAEDA INTERNET PUBLICATION.
APRIL IS ALSO A MONTH WITH
SIGNIFICANCE FOR DOMESTIC TERROR
GROUPS.
THE MONTH OF THE WACO RAID AND
THE OKLAHOMA CITY BOMBING.
AS PRESIDENT OBAMA MADE CLEAR
TODAY, THERE'S STILL NO EVIDENCE
OF WHO IS RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS
ACT OF TERRORISM.
>> THIS WAS A HEINOUS AND
COWARDLY ACT, AND GIVEN WHAT WE
NOW KNOW ABOUT WHAT TOOK PLACE,
THE FBI IS INVESTIGATING IT AS
AN ACT OF TERRORISM.
>> Reporter: THE FBI AGENTS TELL
US THEY HAVE TONS OF VIDEO, AND
SOMEWHERE IN THERE WILL BE A
PICTURE OF THE PERSON WHO
PLANTED THESE TWO BOMBS, DIANE.
>> SPEAKING OF PICTURES, I WANT
TO ASK YOU ABOUT A PHOTO THAT
EVERYBODY WAS E-MAILING TODAY.
IT IS A MAN STANDING UP ON TOP
OF A ROOF.
YOU CAN MOVE IN THERE, YOU SEE
IT RIGHT THERE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT IT?
>> Reporter: WELL, IT'S VERY
INTRIGUING, BUT AUTHORITIES SAY
THEY'RE GIVING IT NO SPECIAL
PRIORITY.
IT'S ONE OF MANY TIPS AND LEADS
THEY'RE FOLLOWING.
THEY'RE REALLY FOCUSING ON THE
PERSON WHO HAD THAT UNUSUALLY
HEAVY BLACK BAG THE DAY OF THE
RACE.
>> AS YOU SAID THE STRONGEST
CLUES ARE IN THE NATURE OF THE
BOMB.
>>> UP NEXT, ABC'S SENIOR
NATIONAL CORRESPONDENT JIM
AVILA, SHOWS US JUST HOW FAR THE
BLAST FROM THE BOMBS TRAVELED.
>> Reporter: THE KILLER BOMBS
LIKELY CONTAINED LESS THAN TWO
POUNDS OF COMMON BLACK POWDER
EXPLOSIVE, SAYS ONE OF THE
NATIONS LEADING IED EXPERTS.
EVEN LEAVING THE CHARACTERISTIC
WHITE SMOKE.
BOMBS DESIGNED TO SPREAD TERROR
AND DEATH WITH A LETHAL BLAST OF
METAL SHRAPNEL.
>> LOOKS LIKE HE WAS OUT TO KILL
AND MAIM.
>> Reporter: HOLD IT RIGHT
THERE.
HERE WE SEE WINDOWS BLOWN OUT
HERE, BUT THE BUILDINGS
THEMSELVES ARE INTACT.
WHAT DOES THAT TELL US ABOUT
WHAT THIS BOMBER WANTED TO DO?
>> THAT HE DID NOT WANT TO TAKE
DOWN THE BUILDING.
THAT WASN'T HIS MAIN TARGET.
IT WAS TO DISRUPT THE MARATHON
AND KILL PEOPLE IN THAT
IMMEDIATE AREA.
>> Reporter: HOUSTON SAYS THIS
IS CLASSIC IED DESIGN, THE KILL
ZONE FROM THE BLAST, ONE TO TWO
YARDS.
ACCORDING TO THE ACCOUNTS FROM
THE BOMB'S SITE, POWERFUL ENOUGH
TO KNOCK A RUNNER OFF HIS FEET
TEN YARDS AWAY.
AND TOPPLE ANOTHER MAN ON HIS
COUCH FROM THE THIRD FLOOR OF
THE BUILDING NEXT DOOR, 20 YARDS
AWAY.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE A BASIC DESIGN
OF AN IMPROVISED EXPLOSIVE
DEVICE.
HOWEVER, THE PLACEMENT OF IT IS
SOPHISTICATED.
THEY UNDERSTOOD WHAT THEY WANTED
TO DO.
>> Reporter: THE PRESSURE COOKER
IS WELL KNOWN BY THE MILITARY AS
A LETHAL BOMB CARRIER, COVERED
IN TRAINING MANUALS AND
EXPLAINED IN VIDEO.
>> Reporter: THEY'RE SMALL,
EASILY MADE, EVEN CRUDE.
BUT OUR BOMB EXPERTS SAY THE
PLANNING AND EXECUTION TELL US
THAT THE TERRORIST WAS
WELL-TRAINED.
>> I WOULD BE SURPRISED IF IT'S
A LONE ACTOR.
HE'S DEFINITELY BEEN WORKING ON
THIS FOR A WHILE, THE PLANNING
AND WORKING ON PUTTING THE
DEVICES TOGETHER.
>> Reporter: BUT NONE OF THE
CLUES SO FAR TELL OUR EXPERT
WHETHER THIS TERRORIST WAS PART
OF ANY ONE ORGANIZATION.
DIANE?
>> THANKS SO MUCH, JIM.
>>> NOW FROM BOSTON, WE TURN TO
BREAKING NEWS WE HAVE AT THIS
HOUR.
A LETTER ADDRESSED TO A UNITED
STATES SENATOR WAS INTERCEPTED,
FOUND TO CONTAIN A DEADLY
POISON.
THE NEWS IS STILL COMING IN AND
PIERRE THOMAS HAS ALL THE
LATE-BREAKING DETAILS RIGHT NOW
OUT OF WASHINGTON.
PIERRE?
>> TONIGHT THE SENATE IS ON HIGH
ALERT AFTER A LETTER BOUND FOR
ONE OF ITS MEMBERS WAS
INTERCEPTED BECAUSE IT MAY HAVE
BEEN TAINTED WITH POISON.
SOURCES ARE TELLING US TONIGHT A
LETTER ADDRESSED TO MISSISSIPPI
SENATOR ROGER WICKER TESTED
POSITIVE FOR RICIN IN A FIELD
TEST IN MARYLAND.
THE LETTER WAS POST MARKED
MEMPHIS, TENNESSEE.
TONIGHT THERE'S NO INFORMATION
ON WHO MAY HAVE SENT IT.
RICIN IS DER REIFFED FROM CASTER
BEANS AND CAN BE LETHAL IF
INGESTED OR INHALED.
FIELD TESTS TO DETECTIVE IT ARE
UNRELIABLE.
A SOURCE TELLS US THE LETTER IS
TESTED AGAIN IN A LABORATORY TO
GET A DEFINITIVE RESULT.
THE PACKAGE WAS INTERCEPTED AND
NEVER REACHED THE CAPITAL
COMPLEX.
STILL, ADDITIONAL SECURITY IS
BEING PUT IN PLACE.
ALL MAIL TO CAPITOL HILL HAS
BEEN STOPPED.
SUCH SCARES HAVE HAPPENED IN
WASHINGTON BEFORE.
IN 2004, A LETTER CONTAINING
RICIN POWDER SHUT DOWN THREE
SENATE OFFICES FOR TWO DAYS.
EXTRAORDINARY PRECAUTIONS WERE
TAKEN TO KEEP SENATORS AND THEIR
STAFF SAFE.
IN 2003, THE SECRET SERVICE
REVEALED PRESIDENT BUSH RECEIVED
A LETTER CONTAINING A VIAL OF
RICIN.
THERE'S NO INDICATION THIS IS
TIED TO BOSTON, DIANE.
>> PIERRE THOMAS STAYING ON THIS
STORY AS IT UNFOLDS TONIGHT.
BUT NOW WE RETURN BACK TO BOSTON
AND ONE MORE THING WE THINK WE
KNOW ABOUT THE BOMBER.
HE MAY HAVE STUDIED LAST YEAR'S
RACE.
PINPOINTING THE MOMENT THE
MAXIMUM NUMBER OF RUNNERS
CROSSED THE FINISH LINE.
LAST YEAR, FOUR HOURS AND 18
MINUTES IN, THE MAXIMUM NUMBER,
THAT'S ALMOST EXACTLY THE TIME
HIS BOMB EXPLODED.
FROM BOSTON TONIGHT WE HAVE NEW
IMAGES OF A CITY INTERRUPTED,
HALF-EATEN SANDWICHES ABANDONED
WHERE THE BOMBS WENT OFF.
AS DAN HARRIS GIVES US NEW
INSIGHT, TAKING US BEHIND THOSE
IMAGES WE ALL WATCHED TOGETHER
AS IT HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT NEW VIDEO
IS GIVING US FRESH, FRIGHTENING
INSIGHT INTO THE ATTACKS.
LOOK AT THIS CELLPHONE FOOTAGE,
SHOT BY A SPECTATOR STANDING
BETWEEN THE TWO BOMBS.
AFTER THE FIRST EXPLOSION,
THERE'S CONFUSION, BUT RELATIVE
CALM AS PEOPLE MOVE AWAY.
BUT THEN AFTER 11 SECONDS GO
BY -- AFTER THE SECOND SPLOGE
EXPLOSION, PANIC.
IN THE AFTERMATH, YOU CAN SEE
PEOPLE RUNNING ALONGSIDE WALKS,
CARPETED IN GLASS -- AND
VICTIMS.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I HAVE A VICTIM HERE WITH
SHRAPNEL IN THE LEG.
>> Reporter: POLICE SCANNER
TRAFFIC TAKES US FURTHER INSIDE
THOSE MOMENTS.
>> GET ANOTHER AMBULANCE DOWN
HERE AT 755 BOYLSTON.
>> THEY ARE ON THE WAY, SIR,
THEY ARE ON THE WAY.
>> Reporter: SO MANY IMAGES, THE
FACE OF NICOLE GROSS, ONE OF
THREE MEMBERS OF THE SAME FAMILY
INJURED.
AND THAT 78-YEAR-OLD RUNNER WHO
WAS KNOCKED DOWN BUT PICKED
HIMSELF UP AND FINISHED THE
RACE.
TODAY BOSTON WAS CRAWLING WITH
ARMORED VEHICLES, UNIFORMED
NATIONAL GUARDSMEN AND OFFICERS
ARMED WITH HIGH POWERED RIFLES.
ON A NORMAL TUESDAY AFTERNOON,
THIS PART OF TOWN WOULD BE
CRAWLING WITH FOOT AND ROAD
TRAFFIC, BUT TODAY IT'S ON
LOCKDOWN.
POLICE HAVE SET UP A MASSIVE
CRIME SCENE.
TO GIVE YOU AN IDEA OF THE SIZE
OF THIS THING, TAKE A LOOKA THE
MAP.
WE ARE ON JUST ONE CORNER OF
WHAT IS A 12-BLOCK CRIME SCENE
RIGHT IN THE HEART OF THIS CITY.
ALSO TODAY WE GOT OUR FIRST
DETAILS OF THOSE WHO DID NOT
SURVIVE.
8-YEAR-OLD MARTIN RICHARD.
AND 29-YEAR-OLD KRYSTLE
CAMPBELL.
>> I COULDN'T ASK FOR A BETTER
DAUGHTER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS HAS
HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: HER MOTHER SAID
THAT HER DEATH WAS JUST A WASTE.
LATE TODAY WE LEARNED THAT THE
THIRD VICTIM WAS A GRADUATE
STUDENT AT BOSTON UNIVERSITY.
WE DO NOT HAVE A NAME THERE.
AND OF COURSE SCORES OF OTHER
PEOPLE WERE INJURED IN THIS
ATTACK.
THE CURRENT TOTAL STANDS AT 176.
DIANE, TO GIVE YOU A SENSE OF
HOW BOSTON IS COMING TOGETHER IN
THE WAKE OF THESE ATTACKS, LATE
TODAY, THE RED CROSS ANNOUNCED
THAT IT IS NOW TURNING AWAY
BLOOD DONORS.
THEY SAY THEY ARE SIMPLY AT
CAPACITY.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU, DAN.
AND THINKING OF EVERYONE IN
BOSTON TODAY, PRESIDENT OBAMA
HAD A MESSAGE FOR THE BOMBERS
AND THE WORLD.
LISTEN.
>> THE AMERICAN PEOPLE REFUSE TO
BE TERRORIZED.
BECAUSE WHAT THE WORLD SAW
YESTERDAY IN THE AFTERMATH OF
THE EXPLOSIONS WERE STORIES OF
HEROISM AND KINDNESS AND
GENEROSITY AND LOVE.
SO IF YOU WANT TO KNOW WHO WE
ARE, WHAT AMERICA IS, HOW WE
RESPOND TO EVIL, THAT'S IT.
SELFLESSLY, COMPASSIONATELY,
UNAFRAID.
>> AND WE HAVE MORE NEW IMAGES
FROM THIS DAY IN BOSTON.
FAMILIES OPENING THEIR HOMES TO
STRANDED MARATHONERS.
A YOUNG BOY COLLECTING HIS
THOUGHTS IN A CHURCH NEAR THE
BOMBINGS, AND A LONE ATHLETE
DEFIANTLY RUNNING ALONG THE
SHORES OF THE CHARLES RIVER
EARLY THIS MORNING.
>>> STILL AHEAD RIGHT HERE ON
"WORLD NEWS," THE 8-YEAR-OLD
MEMBER OF THE LITTLE LEAGUE AND
THE TOWN THAT IS RALLYING AROUND
HIS FAMILY TONIGHT.
AS YOUR LIFE
AND CAREER CHANGE,
FIDELITY IS THERE
FOR YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY,
HELPING YOU READJUST
YOUR RETIREMENT PLAN
ALONG THE WAY.
RETHINK HOW YOU'RE INVESTED.
AND REFOCUS AS YOUR CAREER
MOVES FORWARD.
WHEREVER YOU ARE TODAY,
A FIDELITY IRA HAS A WIDE RANGE
OF INVESTMENT CHOICES
TO HELP YOU FINE-TUNE
YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY.
CALL TODAY
AND WE'LL MAKE IT EASY
TO MOVE THAT OLD 401(k)
TO A FIDELITY NO-FEE IRA.
AND "MULTIPLE CHOICE,"
COME TO WALGREENS
FOR HELP FINDING THE ONE
THAT'S RIGHT FOR YOU...
LIKE CENTRUM.
NOW, GET FOUR DOLLARS OFF
SELECT CENTRUM PRODUCTS
WITH BALANCE REWARDS CARD.
AT THE CORNER
OF HAPPY AND HEALTHY.
FOR OVER 30 YEARS.
AND IT'S NOW
THE MOST DOCTOR RECOMMENDED,
THE MOST PREFERRED
AND THE MOST STUDIED.
SO WHEN IT COMES TO GETTING THE
MOST OUT OF YOUR MULTIVITAMIN,
THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
CENTRUM.
on my feet and exactly where
I needed more support.
Then, I got my number.
My tired, achy feet affected my
whole life.
Until I found my number.
I tried the free Dr. Scholl's
Foot Mapping Center.
In two minutes, I got my foot
map and custom number.
I'm a 440.
That matched up to the Dr.
Scholl's Custom Fit Orthotic
inserts with the right support
and cushioning I need.
I am a believer.
I'm a believer!
I'm a believer.
Go to DrScholls.com to
find your closest Walmart
with a Foot Mapping Center.
I NEED A NEW RECRUIT!
DAWN?
YOU WON'T LAST.
[ Female Announcer ]
A DROP OF DAWN HAS ACTIVE SUDS
THAT STAY STRONGER LONGER,
SO YOU CAN CLEAN
2X MORE GREASY DISHES.
DAWN DOES MORE.
[ Sponge ] SO IT'S NOT A CHORE.
THEY'RE ABOUT 10 TIMES SOFTER
AND MAY HAVE SURFACE PORES
WHERE BACTERIA CAN MULTIPLY.
POLIDENT KILLS 99.99%
OF ODOR CAUSING BACTERIA
AND HELPS DISSOLVE STAINS
SO DENTURES ARE CLEANER,
FRESHER, AND BRIGHTER.
[ Male Announcer ] POLIDENT.
>>> AND BACK TO THE NEWS OUT OF
BOSTON.
ALL DAY TODAY PEOPLE SHARING
PICTURES OF A LITTLE BOY NAMED
MARTIN RICHARD.
AN 8-YEAR-OLD WHO WAS KILLED IN
THE BOMB BLAST YESTERDAY.
HIS MOTHER AND YOUNGER SISTER
WERE HURT TOO.
ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS TRAVELED TO
THEIR HOMETOWN.
>> Reporter: THE BIG, BROWN
SMILING EYES OF MARTIN RICHARD
MAKE THE SORROW OF WHAT HAPPENED
MONDAY AFTERNOON ALL THE MORE
PALPABLE.
THE 8-YEAR-OLD WAS KNOWN AS A
LITTLE LEAGUE STAR.
>> HE WAS THE FASTEST KID, THE
TALLEST ON HIS TEAM.
JUST A MARVEL TO WATCH ON THE
FIELD.
JUST A DELIGHTFUL YOUNG BOY.
>> Reporter: FRIENDS SAY THE
FAMILY WENT TO THE BOSTON
MARATHON EVERY YEAR.
BUT ONE OF THOSE TWIN EXPLOSIONS
ENDED HIS SHORT LIFE, SENDING
HIS MOTHER TO THE HOSPITAL WITH
A SERIOUS HEAD INJURY.
HIS YOUNGER SISTER LOST A LEG.
NEIGHBORS IN THIS CLOSE KNIT
COMMUNITY ARE NOW GRIEVING ALONG
WITH MARTIN'S FATHER.
>> I WAS OUTSIDE WITH MY DOG.
I SAW HIM GET OUT OF THE CAR.
HE WAS DRESSED IN HOSPITAL
SCRUBS AND I SAID, OH, MY GOD,
BILL, ARE YOU OKAY?
AND HE DIDN'T EVEN ANSWER ME.
>> Reporter: AN OUTPOURING OF
SUPPORT AND PRAYERS FOR THIS
FAMILY.
ON THIS FACEBOOK PAGE.
IN A STATEMENT BILL RICHARDS
SAID, WE THANK OUR FAMILY AND
FRIENDS, THOSE WE KNOW AND THOSE
WE HAVE NEVER MET, FOR THEIR
THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS.
>> WHEN WE WOULD SEE THEM, THEY
WOULD ALL BE TOGETHER, WHETHER
IT WAS AT CHURCH, GOING TO
SCHOOL, ON THE SPORTS FIELD,
IN THE NANED, -- NEIGHBORHOOD,
THEY WERE A VERY ACTIVE FAMILY
IN OUR COMMUNITY.
PILLARS OF THE COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: THIS COMMUNITY NOW
REELING.
ITS COMPASSION ETCHED IN CHALK
ON THE DRIVEWAY OF THE FAMILY'S
HOME.
FLOWERS AWAIT THEIR RETURN.
THE TOWN'S CLOCK, FROZEN TO MARK
THAT MOMENT AND THE FLAG AT HALF
STAFF OUTSIDE MARTIN'S SCHOOL
WHERE TEACHERS TONIGHT DESCRIBE
HIM AS AN ENERGETIC YOUNG BOY
WHO HAD BIG DREAMS AND HIGH
HOPES FOR HIS FUTURE.
A VIGIL IS TAKING PLACE TONIGHT
AT THE RICHARDS' FAMILY CHURCH.
AN OUTPOURING OF PRAYERS FOR
MARTIN'S MOTHER AND SISTER WHO
REMAIN IN THE HOSPITAL.
>> IN BOSTON FOR US AGAIN
TONIGHT, LINSEY DAVIS.
AND WHEN WE COME BACK, YOU'LL
MEET A SURGEON WHO KNEW ABOUT
TRAUMA IN AFGHANISTAN AND IRAQ.
HE RAN THE MARATHON, AND THEN
FACED IT AGAIN.
COPD includes emphysema
and chronic bronchitis.
SPIRIVA is a once-daily inhaled
COPD maintenance treatment
that helps open my obstructed
airways for a full 24 hours.
You know, SPIRIVA helps
me breathe easier.
SPIRIVA HandiHaler Tiotropium
Bromide Inhalation Powder
does not replace fast-acting
inhalers for sudden symptoms.
Tell your doctor if you
have kidney problems,
glaucoma, trouble urinating,
or an enlarged prostate.
These may worsen with SPIRIVA.
Discuss all medicines you
take, even eye drops.
Stop taking SPIRIVA and seek
immediate medical help
if your breathing
suddenly worsens,
your throat or tongue swells,
you get hives, vision changes
or eye pain, or problems
passing urine.
Other side effects include
dry mouth and constipation.
Nothing can reverse COPD.
SPIRIVA helps me
breathe better.
Does breathing with
COPD weigh you down?
Don't wait to ask your
doctor about SPIRIVA.
A BODY AT REST
TENDS TO STAY AT REST...
WHILE A BODY IN MOTION
TENDS TO STAY IN MOTION.
STAYING ACTIVE CAN ACTUALLY
EASE ARTHRITIS SYMPTOMS.
BUT IF YOU HAVE ARTHRITIS,
STAYING ACTIVE
CAN BE DIFFICULT.
PRESCRIPTION CELEBREX
CAN HELP RELIEVE ARTHRITIS PAIN
SO YOUR BODY
CAN STAY IN MOTION.
BECAUSE JUST ONE
200MG CELEBREX A DAY
CAN PROVIDE 24 HOUR RELIEF
FOR MANY WITH ARTHRITIS PAIN
AND INFLAMMATION.
PLUS, IN CLINICAL STUDIES,
CELEBREX IS PROVEN TO IMPROVE
DAILY PHYSICAL FUNCTION
SO MOVING IS EASIER.
CELEBREX CAN BE TAKEN
WITH OR WITHOUT FOOD.
AND IT'S NOT A NARCOTIC.
YOU AND YOUR DOCTOR
SHOULD BALANCE THE BENEFITS
WITH THE RISKS.
ALL PRESCRIPTION NSAIDS,
LIKE CELEBREX, IBUPROFEN,
NAPROXEN AND MELOXICAM
HAVE THE SAME
CARDIOVASCULAR WARNING.
THEY ALL MAY INCREASE
THE CHANCE
OF HEART ATTACK OR STROKE,
WHICH CAN LEAD TO DEATH.
THIS CHANCE INCREASES
IF YOU HAVE HEART DISEASE
OR RISK FACTORS
SUCH AS HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
OR WHEN NSAIDS ARE TAKEN
FOR LONG PERIODS.
NSAIDS, LIKE CELEBREX,
INCREASE THE CHANCE OF SERIOUS
SKIN OR ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR STOMACH AND INTESTINE
PROBLEMS,
SUCH AS BLEEDING AND ULCERS,
WHICH CAN OCCUR WITHOUT WARNING
AND MAY CAUSE DEATH.
PATIENTS ALSO TAKING ASPIRIN
AND THE ELDERLY
ARE AT INCREASED RISK FOR
STOMACH BLEEDING AND ULCERS.
DON'T TAKE CELEBREX
IF YOU HAVE BLEEDING
IN THE STOMACH OR INTESTINE,
OR HAD AN ASTHMA ATTACK, HIVES,
OTHER ALLERGIES TO ASPIRIN,
NSAIDS OR SULFONAMIDES.
GET HELP RIGHT AWAY IF YOU HAVE
SWELLING OF THE FACE OR THROAT,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
YOUR MEDICAL HISTORY.
AND FIND AN ARTHRITIS TREATMENT
FOR YOU.
VISIT CELEBREX.COM AND ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CELEBREX.
FOR A BODY IN MOTION.
N AND AMID THE GRIEF OF THOSE
WHO WERE LOST, THERE WERE SO
MANY PEOPLE WHO INSPIRED US.
EARLIER TODAY I TALKED IT TRAUMA
SURGEON, DR. DAVID KING, WHO HAD
SAVED LIVES IN IRAQ AND
AFGHANISTAN, AND YESTERDAY RAN
THE MARATHON AND THEN DID IT
AGAIN.
>> YOU COMPLETED THE MARATHON?
>> THAT'S CORRECT.
I WAS IN THE ATHLETE'S RECOVERY
AREA FOR ABOUT 30 TO 45 MINUTES.
BUT ESSENTIALLY JUST LEFT THERE
WHEN THE BOMB WENT OFF AND, OF
COURSE, IMMEDIATELY CAME TO THE
HOSPITAL.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY TO YOURSELF
WHEN YOU FIRST HEARD ABOUT THIS?
>> THE MOMENT I WALKED INTO THE
EMERGENCY ROOM AND LOOKED AT THE
CASUALTIES, WITHOUT EVEN
EXAMINING THE PATIENTS IN
DETAIL, I COULD JUST SEE THE
PATTERN OF INJURY, AND I THOUGHT
TO MYSELF, THIS IS EXACTLY LIKE
I WAS BACK IN IRAQ OR
AFGHANISTAN.
>> YOU'RE FINDING METALLIC
PARTICLES, SMALL METAL BALLS,
NAILS, SCREWS IN THESE WOUNDS?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
WE'RE NOT EXACTLY SURE WHAT THEY
ARE.
WHETHER THEY'RE BB'S OR METAL
BALL BEARINGS.
WE'RE ALSO FINDING NAILS AND
SCREWS AND OTHER PIECES OF
METAL.
THEY'RE TWISTED AND DEFORMED.
IT'S NOT CLEAR WHETHER THEY'RE
FROM THE BOMB ITSELF OR THE
ENVIRONMENT AROUND THE BOMB.
>> BUT THE BOMB MAY HAVE HIT
OTHER METAL OBJECTS THAT THEN
SPLINTERED APART?
>> THIS IS WHAT I'M HEARING,
ALTHOUGH I CERTAINLY DON'T KNOW
THAT FOR A FACT.
THE OPERATIONS THAT WE HAVE
PERFORMED ARE IDENTICAL TO THE
KIND OF WORK WE WOULD DO IN THE
ARMY AT A FORWARD SURGICAL TEAM
OR COMBAT SUPPORT HOSPITAL.
>> WELL, AGAIN, WE KNOW THERE IS
HEROISM, LARGE AND SMALL AT ALL
TIMES AT MASS GENERAL, AND WE
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR JOINING
US.
I KNOW YOU'VE GOT AT LEAST FIVE
SURGERIES TODAY.
WE'LL LET YOU GO BACK TO WORK.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> AND COMING UP NEXT HERE, A
NATION ON EDGE.
OTHER CITIES IN AMERICA, AFTER
THE TRAGEDY IN BOSTON.
AND CHANTIX HELPED ME QUIT.
I HONESTLY LOVED SMOKING,
AND I HONESTLY DIDN'T THINK
I WOULD EVER QUIT.
[ Male Announcer ]
ALONG WITH SUPPORT,
CHANTIX (VARENICLINE) IS PROVEN
TO HELP PEOPLE QUIT SMOKING.
IT REDUCES THE URGE TO SMOKE.
IT PUT ME AT EASE THAT YOU COULD
SMOKE ON THE FIRST WEEK.
[ Male Announcer ] SOME PEOPLE
HAD CHANGES IN BEHAVIOR,
THINKING OR MOOD,
HOSTILITY, AGITATION,
DEPRESSED MOOD AND SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS OR ACTIONS
WHILE TAKING
OR AFTER STOPPING CHANTIX.
IF YOU NOTICE ANY OF THESE
STOP TAKING CHANTIX AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ANY HISTORY OF DEPRESSION
OR OTHER
MENTAL HEALTH PROBLEMS,
WHICH COULD GET WORSE
WHILE TAKING CHANTIX.
DON'T TAKE CHANTIX IF
YOU'VE HAD A SERIOUS ALLERGIC
OR SKIN REACTION TO IT.
IF YOU DEVELOP THESE
STOP TAKING CHANTIX
AND SEE YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
AS SOME CAN BE
LIFE-THREATENING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HISTORY
OF HEART OR BLOOD VESSEL
PROBLEMS,
OR IF YOU DEVELOP
NEW OR WORSE SYMPTOMS.
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
OF A HEART ATTACK OR STROKE.
USE CAUTION WHEN DRIVING
OR OPERATING MACHINERY.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
INCLUDE NAUSEA,
TROUBLE SLEEPING
AND UNUSUAL DREAMS.
WITH CHANTIX AND WITH THE
SUPPORT SYSTEM IT WORKED FOR ME.
[ Male Announcer ]
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF CHANTIX
IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
I'M ON EXPERT ON SOFTBALL.
AND TEA PARTIES.
I'LL HAVE
MORE AWKWARD CONVERSATIONS
THAN I'M EQUIPPED FOR,
BECAUSE I'M RAISING TWO GIRLS
ON MY OWN.
I'LL WORRY ABOUT THE ECONOMY
MORE THAN A FEW TIMES
BEFORE THEY'RE GROWN.
BUT IT'S FOR THEM,
SO I'VE FOUND A WAY.
WHO MATTERS MOST TO YOU
SAYS THE MOST ABOUT YOU.
AT MassMutual WE'RE OWNED
BY OUR POLICYOWNERS,
AND THEY MATTER MOST TO US.
READY TO PLAN FOR YOUR FUTURE?
WE'LL HELP YOU GET THERE.
AND IT FEELS LIKE YOUR LIFEATE
REVOLVES AROUND YOUR SYMPTOMS,
ASK YOUR GASTROENTEROLOGIST
ABOUT HUMIRA ADALIMUMAB.
HUMIRA HAS BEEN PROVEN
TO WORK FOR ADULTS
WHO HAVE TRIED OTHER MEDICATIONS
BUT STILL EXPERIENCE
THE SYMPTOMS OF MODERATE
TO SEVERE CROHN'S DISEASE.
IN CLINICAL STUDIES, THE
MAJORITY OF PATIENTS ON HUMIRA
SAW SIGNIFICANT SYMPTOM RELIEF,
AND MANY ACHIEVED REMISSION.
HUMIRA CAN LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS,
INCLUDING TUBERCULOSIS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS,
SUCH AS INFECTIONS, LYMPHOMA,
OR OTHER TYPES OF CANCER,
HAVE HAPPENED.
BLOOD, LIVER AND
NERVOUS SYSTEM PROBLEMS,
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS,
AND NEW OR WORSENING HEART
FAILURE HAVE OCCURRED.
BEFORE STARTING HUMIRA, YOUR
DOCTOR SHOULD TEST YOU FOR TB.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU LIVE IN
OR HAVE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL
INFECTIONS ARE COMMON.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU HAVE
HAD TB, HEPATITIS B,
ARE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,
OR HAVE SYMPTOMS SUCH AS
FEVER, FATIGUE, COUGH, OR SORES.
YOU SHOULD NOT START HUMIRA IF
YOU HAVE ANY KIND OF INFECTION.
GET HEADED IN A NEW DIRECTION.
WITH HUMIRA,
REMISSION IS POSSIBLE.
♪
>>> ALL AROUND THE WORLD TODAY
PEOPLE OF ALL NATIONS WERE
SENDING MESSAGES OF SOLIDARITY
TO BOSTON.
AND IN THIS COUNTRY TOO, THERE
WAS NEW MEANING TO THE
INJUNCTION -- SEE SOMETHING, SAY
SOMETHING.
TONIGHT THE NEWEST MEMBER OF OUR
ABC NEWS FAMILY VETERAN REPORTER
ABC'S BYRON PITTS IS HERE TO
TELL US ABOUT THIS NEW NORMAL IN
AMERICAN CITIES TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THIS IS AMERICA'S
NEW NORMAL.
THE MOMENT TERROR STRIKES AT
HOME, THE NATION COILS.
COAST TO COAST LAW ENFORCEMENT,
AT LOS ANGELES'S UNION STATION,
A MUSCULAR POLICE PRESENCE, AND
AND A MEASURE OF ANXIETY FELT
LIE COMMUTERS.
>> IT PUTS YOU ON EDGE.
>> WE'RE NOT SAFE ANYWHERE.
>> IT COULD HAPPEN ANYWHERE,
EVEN HERE IN CALIFORNIA.
>> Reporter: AT LAX ACROSS TO
BOSTON, MEMORIES OF 9/11.
>> THAT FAITH THAT YOU HAVE IN
SECURITY OF OUR NATION, IT'S
KIND OF SHAKEN.
>> Reporter: IN DOWNTOWN
SEATTLE, STREETS WERE SHUT DOWN
DUE TO A SUSPICIOUS BACKPACK.
THE BOMB SQUAD SENT IN ITS
ROBOT, INSIDE A HAIR DRYER.
EAST COAST AIRPORTS HAD THE
JITTERS.
AT LOGAN AIRPORT, DELAYS OVER
SUSPICIOUS PASSENGERS AND
PACKAGES.
AT NEW YORK LaGUARDIA, ANOTHER
SUSPICIOUS ITEM AND PASSENGERS
FORCED TO WAIT OUTSIDE IN THE
STREET.
>> ACROSS NEW YORK CITY BOTH
SIGNS OF INCREASED SECURITY.
AND THE COMFORTING SOUND OF
RESILIENCY.
>> I THINK IF I BECOME NERVOUS
I'M GIVING IN TO SOMETHING
THAT'S GOING TO MAKE ME
UNDERPOWERED.
>> Reporter: CARLOS ROSARIO
SEEMED TO SPEAK FOR MANY TODAY.
>> AS CITIZENS, WE HAVE TO BE
RESPONSIBLE ONE TO ANOTHER.
WE HAVE TO BE OUR BROTHER'S
KEEPER.
>> Reporter: MEANWHILE IN
BOSTON, VOWS UNBROKEN.
>> WE'RE STRONG PEOPLE AND WE'RE
NOT GOING TO LET ANYONE PUSH US
AROUND.
YOU MESS WITH ONE OF US, YOU
MESS WITH ALL OF US.
>> Reporter: ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY, PEOPLE SENT THEIR BEST
WISHES AND PRAYERS TO BOSTON.
WE'VE SEEN THIS IN AMERICA
BEFORE, WHEN A CRISIS HITS HOME,
THIS NATION WILL RALLY.
>> SO TRUE AND BYRON, IT IS
GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US AT
ABC.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> AND NOW IF YOU'LL ALLOW US
TONIGHT, THERE'S A MEMBER OF OUR
ABC FAMILY WHO HAS DIED.
A MAN WHO HAS BEEN ABSOLUTELY
CRITICAL TO THE KIND OF
REPORTING WE'VE DONE TODAY, THIS
WEEK, AND SO MANY TIMES BEFORE.
PRESTON DAVIS, 35 YEARS AGO
BEGAN AS AN ENGINEER HERE AND
ROSE TO BECOME PRESIDENT OF
BROADCAST OPERATIONS AND
ENGINEERING.
THE FIRST AFRICAN AMERICAN
PRESIDENT OF ANY DIVISION AT
ABC, KNOWN, RESPECTED, LOVED BY
EVERY SINGLE PERSON AT EVERY
LEVEL OF ABC.
AND TONIGHT WE REMEMBER PRESTON
DAVIS, WHO WAS 63 YEARS OLD.
>> AND WE THANK YOU FOR WATCHING
THE FIRST HALF OF THIS SPECIAL
ONE-HOUR EDITION OF "WORLD
NEWS."
SOME OF YOU WILL BE LEAVING US
NOW, BUT THE OTHERS OF YOU, WE
HOPE YOU'LL STAY WITH US AS WE
CONTINUE WITH BREAKING NEWS, THE
VERY LATEST IN THIS SPECIAL
EDITION OF "WORLD NEWS."
♪
>>> AND GOOD EVENING.
AS WE COME ON THE AIR, WE'RE
BRINGING YOU NEW DETAILS, NEW
THEORIES ABOUT THE BOMB AND THE
BOMBER AT THE BOSTON MARATHON.
THE NATION MOURNING TONIGHT.
AT THE WHITE HOUSE, THE FLAG
FLYING AT HALF STAFF.
AS THE PRESIDENT WILL TRAVEL TO
BOSTON ON THURSDAY.
AND TONIGHT THE FBI HAS FOUND
CLUES IN THOSE TAPES, THE MOMENT
OF IMPACT, WHAT DID THEY SEE?
WHO DO THEY NEW BELIEVE
-- NOW BELIEVE HAPPENED?
LET'S BEGIN WITH ABC'S BRIAN
ROSS, WITH THE LATEST RIGHT NOW.
BRIAN?
>> GOOD EVENING.
THERE ARE IMPORTANT NEW CLUES
INTO THE BOMB AND THE BOMBER.
BUT THE ROAD BEGINS WITH AN
EXAMINATION OF THAT BOMB.
IMPORTANT NEW DETAILS HAVE
EMERGED FROM FBI AGENTS WHO SAY
THEY HAVE RECOVERED A
SIGNIFICANT PART, A MANGLED
PIECE OF ONE OF THE BOMBS,
RECOVERED ON THE SCENE.
IT TURNS OUT TO BE A COMMON
KITCHEN ITEM.
THEY SAY IT IS A MEDIUM-SIZED
PRESSURE COOKER THAT WAS PACKED
WITH EXPLOSIVES, WIRES, AND AN
ELECTRONIC CIRCUIT BOARD, AS
WELL AS TINY NAILS AND BALL
BEARINGS, IN ORDER TO MAXIMIZE
THE DAMAGE TO ANYONE IN THE
BLAST ZONE.
AUTHORITIES BELIEVE THEY CAN
EXAMINE THAT PARTICULAR HALF
BOMB NOW.
THEY'VE GOT IT AT THE BASE IN
VIRGINIA, WHERE IT'S BEING
EXAMINED BY FBI TECHNICIANS.
THEY BELIEVE THEY CAN FIND
SIGNATURES AND FOOTPRINTS THAT
WOULD BE UNIQUE TO THAT BOMB AND
PERHAPS MATCH IT UP TO OTHER
BOMBS SOMEWHERE ELSE IN THE
WORLD, SOMEWHERE ELSE IN THIS
COUNTRY.
THAT WILL BE THE ROAD TO FINDING
THE BOMBER.
THE FBI PUT OUT A PLEA TO ANYONE
WHO SAW A PERSON CARRYING AN
UNUSUALLY HEAVY BLACK BAG ON THE
DAY OF THE RACE.
THEY BELIEVE THE PERSON BROUGHT
THOSE TWO BOMBS IN BLACK BAGS
AND PLANTED THEM ALONG THE ROUTE
OF THE RACE.
THOSE ARE TWO IMPORTANT
DEVELOPMENTS TODAY.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, BRIAN.
AND AS YOU'VE BEEN SAYING,
THERE'S A LOT OF SURVEILLANCE
TAPE OF THAT AREA.
WE ARE TOLD IT'S THE MOST
INTENSELY SURVEILLED BY CAMERAS
IN THE ENTIRE CITY OF BOSTON.
THANKS TO YOU.
>>> NOW WE WANT TO TURN AND GET
MORE ON THE BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
WASHINGTON, THAT LETTER OR
PACKAGE ADDRESSED TO A CENTER
-- SENATOR THAT TESTED POSITIVE
FOR A TYPE OF POISON.
AND PIERRE THOMAS JOINS US.