>> WE'LL SEE YOU AT 6:00.
>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS
AS WE COME ON THE AIR IN THE
WEST.
INVOLVING PRESIDENT TRUMP.
DID HE REVEAL HIGHLY CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION?
LATE TODAY, "THE WASHINGTON
POST" REPORTING THAT THE
PRESIDENT REVEALED THAT
INFORMATION TO THE RUSSIANS,
DURING THEIR MEETING AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
HOW IS THE WHITE HOUSE
RESPONDING TONIGHT?
CECILIA VEGA IS STANDING BY WITH
THEIR RESPONSE A SHORT TIME AGO
AND MARY BRUCE AT THE CAPITOL.
WHERE REPUBLICAN SENATORS ARE
CALLING THE HEADLINE, TROUBLING
AND DISTURBING.
>>> THE DEADLY PLANE CRASH JUST
OUTSIDE NEW YORK CITY.
THE JET COMING IN OVER A
SUBURBAN NEIGHBORHOOD.
WITNESSES WATCHING THE PLANE
COME DOWN.
A FIREBALL ERUPTING.
TONIGHT, THE AUDIO, THE CALLS
FROM THE COCKPIT.
>>> LATE TODAY, THE NEW HORROR
THE IMAGES EMERGING FROM SYRIA.
THE U.S. NOW ACCUSING SYRIA OF
EXECUTING THOUSANDS IN AN
ALLEGED CREMATORIUM.
WHAT THE SATELLITE IMAGES REVEAL
TONIGHT.
MARTHA RADDATZ STANDING BY WITH
NEW REPORTING.
>>> AND THE TOUR BUS CRASH, MORE
THAN TWO DOZEN STUDENTS AND
ADULTS ON THEIR WAY TO
WASHINGTON, D.C., AND THE
EMERGENCY RESPONSE.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US
HERE ON A MONDAY NIGHT.
>>> AND WE BEGIN WITH THAT
BOMBSHELL HEADLINE BREAKING LATE
TODAY.
"THE WASHINGTON POST" REPORTING
PRESIDENT TRUMP DISCLOSED HIGHLY
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION TO THE
RUSSIANS.
"THE POST" REPORTING THAT THE
CLASSIFIED MATERIAL WAS
REVEALED DURING A MEETING WITH
THE RUSSIAN FOREIGN MINISTER AND
RUSSIAN AMBASSADOR WHILE THEY
VISITED THE WHITE HOUSE LAST
WEEK.
IF TRUE, SENATORS ON BOTH SIDES
OF THE AISLE TONIGHT SAYING THIS
IS ALARMING.
THE NEWS TRAVELING FAST LATE
TODAY.
LET'S GET TO CECILIA VEGA, LIVE
AT THE WHITE HOUSE, WITH THE
VERY LATEST FOR US.
>> Reporter: DAVID, GOOD EVENING
TO YOU.
THIS IS A BOMBSHELL ALLEGATION
THAT HAS ROCKED THE WEST WING.
TONIGHT, FROM THE WHITE HOUSE, A
STRONG DENIAL.
>> I WAS IN THE ROOM, IT DIDN'T
HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER H.R. McMASTER DENOUNCING
THAT WASHINGTON POST THAT SAYING
DURING LAST WEEK'S OVAL OFFICE
MEETING WITH THE RUSSIANS THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP DISCLOSED HIGH
LY CLASSIFIED INTELLIGENCE.
>> THE STORY IS FALSE.
AT NO TIME -- AT NO TIME WERE
INTELLIGENCE SOURCES OR METHODS
DISCUSSED.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO THE
POST THE CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
ABOUT A ISIS PLOT IN SYRIA WAS
GIVE ON THE U.S. BY A PARTNER.
AND IS SO SENSITIVE THAT NOT
EVEN ALLIES HAVE ACCESS TO IT.
THAT OVAL OFFICE MEETING TOOK
PLACE A DAY AFTER THE PRESIDENT
FIRED FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY
IT WAS ALREADY UNDER SCRUTINY
BUT NOW RAISES MORE QUESTIONS.
TONIGHT, THE RESPONSE FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE SWIFT.
SECRETARY OF STATE REX TILLERSON
WAS IN THE ROOM FOR THAT
MEETING, SAYING, THEY DID NOT
DISCUSS SOURCES, METHODS OF
MILITARY OPERATIONS.
.
NO ONE HERE AT THE WHITE HOUSE
IS SPECIFICALLY ADDRESSING THE
MAIN ALLEGATION LAID OUT IN THIS
STORY THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
REVEALED CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
AND IN DOING SO, HE MAY HAVE
JEOPARDIZED CRITICAL
INTELLIGENCE-SHARING OPERATIONS,
DAVID.
>> CECILIA VEGA LEADING US OFF.
>>> IN THE MEANTIME THAT
WASHINGTON POST HEADLINE THAT
THE PRESIDENT MIGHT HAVE GIVEN
THAT HIGHLY CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION TO THE RUSSIANS
RACED ITS WAY TO CAPITOL HILL.
TONIGHT, THEY'RE CALLING IT
TROUBLING AND ONE USING THE WORD
ALARMING.
AND REACTION JUST COMING IN.
>> Reporter: ALARM BELLS ARE
RINGING HERE TONIGHT FROM BOTH
SIDES OF THE AISLE.
>> THAT'S REALLY SHOCKING AND
THERE'S OBVIOUSLY GOING TO BE A
LOT MORE WORK FOR US THIS WEEK.
>> TROUBLING.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
IT'S DISTURBING AND LET'S FIND
OUT THE DETAILS ARE.
>> Reporter: THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE MARK
WARREN TWEETING, IF TRUE THIS IS
A SLAP IN THE FACE TO THE INTEL
COMMUNITY
RISKING SOURCES AND METHODS IS
INEXCUSABLE, PARTICULARLY WITH
THE RUSSIANS.
THEY'RE ASKING THE INTELLIGENCE
LEADERS TO BRIEF THE COMMITTEE
ON WHAT WAS SHARED WITH THE
RUSSIANS IN THAT MEETING.
>> MARY, THANK YOU.
OF COURSE ALL THIS MEANTIME AS
PRESIDENT TRUMP LOOKS FOR A NEW
FBI DIRECTOR.
AFTER THAT WARNING TO THE
DIRECTOR HE FIRED, JAMES COMEY,
SAYING COMEY BETTER HOPE THERE
ARE NO TAPES OF THEIR
CONVERSATIONS.
TONIGHT, REPUBLICANS AND
DEMOCRATS ARE NOW DEMANDING TO
KNOW, ARE CONVERSATIONS BEING
RECORDED WITH THE PRESIDENT?
AND IF SO, THEY NOW WANT THEM.
HOW IS THE WHITE HOUSE
RESPONDING TO THAT, HERE'S OUR
CHIEF WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENT,
JONATHAN KARL.
>> Reporter: IN THE OVAL OFFICE
TODAY, PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ASKED
ABOUT HIS SEARCH FOR A NEW FBI
DIRECTOR TO REPLACE THE FIRED
JIM COMEY.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, HOW'S THE
PROCESS OF GOING --
>> THANK YOU.
THANK YOU.
>> ARE YOU SHAKING UP YOUR
STAFF, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> THANK YOU.
VERY GOOD.
>> MOVING RAPIDLY.
>> Reporter: THAT SEARCH MAY BE
MOVING RAPIDLY, BUT THE WHITE
HOUSE IS DEFYING CONGRESSIONAL
DEMANDS FOR ANSWERS ON WHETHER
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN SECRETLY
RECORDING HIS CONVERSATIONS.
LATE LAST WEEK, HE IMPLIED HE
WAS, TAUNTING THE FIRED FBI
DIRECTOR WITH A TWEET, SAYING,
"JAMES COMEY BETTER HOPE THAT
THERE ARE NO 'TAPES' OF OUR
CONVERSATIONS BEFORE HE STARTS
LEAKING TO THE PRESS!"
>> IF THERE ARE TAPES AS THE
PRESIDENT HAS SUGGESTED, HE
SHOULD TURN THEM OVER
IMMEDIATELY.
>> Reporter: EVEN REPUBLICANS
ARE SAYING IF THERE ARE TAPES,
THEY NEED TO BE PRESERVED AND
TURNED OVER.
>> YOU CAN'T BE CUTE ABOUT
TAPES, IF THERE ARE ANY TAPES OF
THIS CONVERSATION, THEY NEED TO
BE TURNED OVER.
>> IF, IN FACT, THERE ARE SUCH
RECORDINGS, I THINK THOSE
RECORDINGS WILL BE SUBPOENAED
AND I THINK THEY WILL PROBABLY
HAVE TO TURN THEM OVER.
>> Reporter: BUT THE WHITE HOUSE
IS REFUSING TO ANSWER ANY
QUESTIONS ON THIS WHATSOEVER.
>> IS THE WHITE HOUSE INTENDING
TO COOPERATE WITH THOSE REQUESTS
AND FURNISH THAT INFORMATION AS
REQUESTED IN WRITING?
>> I THINK I MADE IT CLEAR LAST
WEEK THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
NOTHING FURTHER ON THAT.
>> DOES THAT MEAN THAT THE
PRESIDENT WILL DENY THOSE
REQUESTS?
>> I SAID I WAS VERY CLEAR THAT
THE PRESIDENT WOULD HAVE NOTHING
FURTHER ON THAT LAST WEEK.
>> Reporter: AS FOR THE FBI
DIRECTOR SEARCH IT'S APPARENTLY
A CROWDED FIELD.
AT LEAST EIGHT CANDIDATES,
INCLUDING SENATOR JOHN CORNYN
AND FORMER CONGRESSMAN ROGERS
HAVE ALREADY BEEN INTERVIEWED.
WITH MORE LIKELY TO COME.
LEADING THE INTERVIEWS, DEPUTY
ATTORNEY GENERAL ROD ROSENSTEIN
AND ATTORNEY GENERAL JEFF
SESSIONS, A POTENTIALLY AWKWARD
POSITION BECAUSE THE FBI
DIRECTOR WOULD LEAD THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION AND SESSIONS HAS
RECUSED HIMSELF FROM ANYTHING TO
DO WITH THAT.
>> A LOT OF DEMOCRATS WHO THINK
THAT BECAUSE HE RECUSED HIMSELF
FROM THE RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION
HE SHOULD NOT BE IN THAT
POSITION.
>> I THINK THIS IS A PROCESS
THAT'S RUNNING COMPLETELY AS IT
SHOULD.
>> JONATHAN KARL LIVE WITH US
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
THERE'S ALSO NEWS THIS EVENING
ON TWO KEY FIGURES AND WHETHER
THEY'LL TESTIFY BEFORE THE
SENATE AND THE AMERICAN PEOPLE,
JAMES COMEY HIMSELF AND THE
DEPUTY ATTORNEY GENERAL
WHO WROTE THE REVIEW, CITED IN
THE FIRING OF COMEY.
WHO WILL WE HEAR FROM FIRST?
>> Reporter: ROD ROSENSTEIN WILL
BE BEFORE THE SENATE.
ALL 100 SENATORS ARE INVITED TO
THE BRIEFING.
IT'S A CLOSED BRIEFING, DAVID,
WHICH MEANS WE WON'T ACTUALLY
SEE WHAT HE HAS TO SAY, AND IT'S
A CONFIDENTIAL BRIEFING.
HE'LL FACE TOUGH QUESTIONS IN
HIS ROLE IN THE FIRING.
AS FOR JAMES COMEY, HIS
ASSOCIATES SAY THAT HE'S WILLING
TO TESTIFY BEFORE OPEN SESSION,
I TALKED TO THE COMMITTEE A FEW
MINUTES AGO, STILL NO WORD
EXACTLY WHEN THAT WILL HAPPEN.
>> JON KARL, OUR THANKS TO YOU.
>>> MEANTIME WE TURN TO THE
SCENE JUST OUTSIDE NEW YORK CITY
TONIGHT.
A DEADLY PLANE CRASH, THE
LEARJET APPROACHING TETERBORO
AIRPORT.
WITNESSES SAY IT FLIPPED
UPSIDE-DOWN AS IT FLEW OVER A
SUBURBAN NEIGHBORHOOD.
SLAMMING INTO AN INDUSTRIAL
COMPLEX.
TONIGHT, THE AUDIO IN THOSE
FINAL MOMENTS.
ABC'S LINZIE JANIS IS ON THE
SCENE FOR US.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE
HARROWING SCENE -- A PLANE
PLUMMETING OUT OF THE SKY,
CRASHING AND ERUPTING INTO A
BALL OF FLAMES.
>> REQUEST FOR A MUTUAL AID
AMBULANCE IN CARLSTADT SCENE OF
A PLANE CRASH INTO A BUILDING.
>> Reporter: AT 3:30 P.M., THE
LEARJET, LESS THAN ONE MILE FROM
THE RUNWAY AT NEW JERSEY'S
TETERBORO AIRPORT, WHEN
EYEWITNESSES SAY THE PLANE LOST
CONTROL, FLIPPING OVER, AND
SLAMMING INTO THREE BUILDINGS.
>> IT SKIDDED AFTER IT HIT THE
TOP OF A BUILDING.
AND THEN SKIDDED INTO THE
BUILDING ADJACENT TO IT.
BLOWING UP CARS AND ANYTHING IN
ITS PATH.
>> Reporter: THE PLANE TAKING
OFF FROM PHILADELPHIA, TWO
PILOTS ONBOARD DIED.
FLYING DEBRIS DESTROYING
EVERYTHING IN ITS PATH.
>> I JUST HEARD A LOUD BOOM AND
A FLAME GO ACROSS THE WHOLE
FRONT OF OUR BUILDING, ACROSS
THE STREET.
>> Reporter: TETERBORO AIRPORT
SHUT DOWN, PLANES GROUNDED,
WHILE THE FLAMES STILL BURNED.
>> IT HIT THREE BUILDINGS, THERE
ARE JUST PIECES OF THE PLANE,
LIKE, ALL THROUGHOUT THE YARD.
MELTED CARS THAT WERE PARKED
HERE.
IT'S REALLY ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE TO
DESCRIBE.
>> Reporter: RESCUE TEAMS RACING
TO THE SCENE, A WAREHOUSE
COMPLEX, INCREDIBLY NO ONE ON
THE GROUND INJURED.
>> AND LINZIE WITH US LIVE FROM
THE SCREEN.
INVESTIGATORS I KNOW ARE LOOKING
INTO THE CAUSE, LINZIE.
YOU WERE TELLING US, ONE FACTORS
THEY'RE EXPLORING ARE REPORTS OF
HIGH WIND GUSTS AROUND THE TIME
OF THE CRASH.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
WIND GUSTS UP TO 35 MILES PER
HOUR.
IT'S NOT YET KNOWN IF THEY
PLAYED A ROLE INTO THE CRASH.
INVESTIGATORS FROM THE FAA AND
THE NTSB ARE ON THEIR WAY HERE.
DAVID.
>> LINZIE, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT TO THE
HEADLINE -- YET ANOTHER HARROW
EMERGING FROM THE WAR IN SYRIA.
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT ACCUSING THE
SYRIA CARRYING OUT MASS
EXECUTIONS.
U.S. OFFICIALS SAY THEY
UNCOVERED THE ATROCITY USING
SATELLITE IMAGES OF A NOTORIOUS
PRISON OUTSIDE  DAMASCUS.
ABC'S MARTHA RADDATZ AT THE
STATE DEPARTMENT TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, NEW
HORRORS REVEALED IN THESE
SATELLITE IMAGES.
A SECRET CREMATORIUM, BELIEVED
CONSTRUCTED IN THE NOTORIOUS
SEDNAYA PRISON, WHERE AS MANY AS
50 PEOPLE ARE KILLED EVERY DAY.
LOOK AT THE NEARBY BUILDINGS IN
THE COMPLEX, A WHITE BLANKET OF
SNOW COVERS THEM, BUT THE ROOF
OF THIS BUILDING, WITH THE
INTENSE HEAT FROM WITHIN,
SNOW FREE.
THAT IS WHERE THE STATE
DEPARTMENT BELIEVES BODIES ARE
BURNED, TO HIDE EVIDENCE OF AN
ESTIMATED 5,000 TO 15,000
POLITICAL KILLINGS.
>> THE BUILDING OF A CREMATORIUM
IS AN EFFORT TO COVER UP THE
EXTENT OF MASS MURDERS TAKING
PLACE IN SEDNAYA PRISON.
>> Reporter: THE EVIDENCE OF THE
NO IMAGES EXIST FROM INSIDE,
BUT AMNESTY INTERNATIONAL HAS
RECREATED THE PRISON ITSELF,
BASED ON INTERVIEWS WITH THOSE
WHO MANAGED TO SURVIVE THE
CONDITIONS.
"AS WE ARRIVED," SAYS THIS MAN,
"EVERY GUARD GRABBED A DETAINEE
AND STARTED BEATING HIM."
THE U.S. BLAMES ASSAD FOR THE
CREMATORIUM, BUT SAYS RUSSIA AND
IRAN HAVE PLAYED A PART, FOR
SUPPORTING THE REGIME.
A REGIME THE U.S. ATTACKED LAST
MONTH AFTER EVIDENCE EMERGED IT
USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS TO ATTACK
CIVILIANS.
>> MARTHA RADDATZ WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT FROM THE STATE
DEPARTMENT.
MARTHA, THIS NEW EVIDENCE COMES
AS THE PRESIDENT PREPARES FOR
HIS FIRST OVERSEAS TRIP TO SAUDI
ARABIA, ISRAEL AND THE VATICAN.
SURELY THESE IMAGES WILL COME
UP.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
HE'S GOING OVER TO SAUDI ARABIA.
HE'LL MEET WITH SUNNI LEADERS.
THEY'LL BE SHOWN THESE SATELLITE
IMAGES.
ALL OF THOSE GROUPS ALREADY
DESPISE THE ASSAD REGIME.
THEY'LL BE VERY HAPPY ABOUT THIS
TOUGH STAND AGAINST THEM.
DAVID.
>> MARTHA, THANK YOU.
>>> AND NOW TO ANOTHER GLOBAL
WORRY AT THIS HOUR.
WE DO HAVE NEW REPORTING IN THE
MASSIVE CYBERATTACK.
HOSPITALS PARALYZED, SURGERIES
HALTED, AND TODAY WE LEARNED OF
AN AUTO ASSEMBLY LINE SUDDENLY
STOPPED BECAUSE COMPUTERS HAD
SHUT DOWN.
HACKERS INFECTING SOME 300,000
COMPUTERS IN MORE THAN 150
COUNTRIES NOW, INCLUDING THE
U.S., LOCKING THOSE COMPANIES UP
THROUGH THEIR COMPUTERS, AND
THEN DEMANDING RANSOM TO FREE
THE FILES.
AND TONIGHT, INVESTIGATORS SAY
NEW CLUES MAY BE POINTING TO A
FAMILIAR CULPRIT.
HERE'S BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: CYBERSECURITY
RESEARCHERS TRACKING THE ATTACK
TONIGHT, SAY THE TRAIL COULD
LEAD TO NORTH KOREA.
THAT THE COMPUTER CODE THAT
PRODUCED THE ATTACK WITH THESE
OMINOUS MESSAGES, THE CODE USED
BY NORTH KOREA ON ATTACK ON
INTERNATIONAL BANKS LAST YEAR.
IT COULD BE SOMEONE ELSE USING
THE NORTH KOREAN CODE, SAYS
RESEARCHERS.
BUT THE COUNTRY HAS A LONG
RECORD OF COMPUTER CRIMINALITY.
>> WE HAVE SEEN THEM STEAL MONEY
AND INFORMATION.
WE HAVE SEEN THEM DESTROY
INFORMATION.
>> Reporter: THERE'S STILL NO
ATTRIBUTION OF WHO WAS BEHIND
THE MASSIVE ATTACKS.
AS OF TONIGHT THE TALLY OF
ATTACKS HAS GROWN.
MORE THAN 300,000 IN 150
COUNTRIES.
AUTO PLANTS, OFFICES, RAILROADS
AROUND THE ROAD, AND FEDEX IN
THE U.S. WERE ALL HIT.
THE MOST DEVASTATING, HOSPITALS
IN GREAT BRITAIN, WHERE
AMBULANCES WERE TURNED AWAY.
CANCER TREATMENTS AND SURGERIES
CANCELLED.
>> HORRIBLE.
CRIED A LOT.
DIDN'T REALLY KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
>> Reporter: ONLY A FEW HUNDRED
COMPANIES APPEAR TO HAVE
FOLLOWED THE HACKERS' DIRECTIONS
TO PAY $300 IN RANSOM OR MORE TO
HAVE THEIR FILES FREED, AND
THAT, TOO, TURNED OUT TO BE
SCAM.
>> IT APPEARS LESS THAN $70,000
HAS BEEN PAID IN RANSOM.
WE'RE NOT AWARE OF PAYMENTS THAT
HAVE LED TO ANY DATA RECOVERY.
>> BRIAN ROSS WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT.
THOSE ATTACKS ARE STILL COMING
FROM THAT SAME GROUP, BRIAN.
>> THAT'S RIGHT, THERE WAS A NEW
VARIANT OF THE ATTACK TODAY AND
ANOTHER ONE YESTERDAY, BUT WERE
SHUT DOWN BEFORE THEY SPREAD TOO
FAR.
>> NEW WAVES OF THIS ATTACK.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT THING IS
TO DOWNLOAD ANY UPGRADES, THE
FIXES WITH THE PATCHES THAT
BLOCK THIS ATTACK.
>> USE THOSE AUTOMATIC UPGRADES.
ALL RIGHT, BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> TO OTHER NEWS TONIGHT, NORTH
KOREA ALSO CELEBRATING ITS MOST
RECENT MISSILE TEST.
WE HAVE NEW IMAGES OF THAT
TONIGHT, SHOWING KIM JONG-UN
THERE ON SUNDAY.
AS THE MEDIUM-RANGE ROCKET WAS
READIED AND LAUNCHED.
THE FIRST SUCCESSFUL LAUNCH OF
THIS NEW TYPE OF MISSILE.
POTENTIALLY THEY SAY CAPABLE OF
REACHING U.S. BASES IN PACIFIC.
AFTERWARD, NORTH KOREA UPPING
THE THREAT, CLAIMING THE MISSILE
COULD BE LOADED WITH A NUCLEAR
WARHEAD.
U.S. OFFICIALS CANNOT CONFIRM
THAT CLAIM TONIGHT.
>>> NEXT, BACK HERE AT HOME, AND
TO AN ACCIDENT ON I-95 IN
MARYLAND, INJURING MORE THAN 20
SCHOOLCHILDREN.
THEIR BUS OVERTURNED ON THEIR
WAY TO WASHINGTON, D.C.
FOR AN EVENT MARKING
INTERNATIONAL POLICE WEEK.
BEHIND THEM ON THE ROAD, ANOTHER
BUS, FULL OF POLICE CADETS WHO
RUSHED IN TO HELP EVERYONE.
HERE'S ABC'S DAVID KERLEY.
>> Reporter: THE EIGHTH GRADE
FIELD TRIP IN AN INSTANT,
TERRIFYINGLY, TURNED UPSIDE
DOWN.
>> THIS IS A MASS CASUALTY, WITH
AT LEAST 30 PATIENTS.
>> Reporter: MOSTLY STUDENTS,
TOSSED ABOUT.
>> WHEN THE BUS BEGAN TO FLIP,
SHE HEARD SOME SCREAMING AND
STUFF, BUT SHE THOUGHT IT WAS
ALL A DREAM.
>> Reporter: TWO OF THOSE ON
BOARD CRITICALLY INJURED.
TWO DOZEN OTHERS NEEDING CARE.
>> IT RAN ANYWHERE FROM HEAD
INJURIES, BROKEN BONES, MINOR
BRUISES, THINGS LIKE THAT.
>> Reporter: FORTUNATELY,
ANOTHER BUS, FILLED WITH POLICE
CADETS, WAS NEARBY.
AND THOSE CADETS SPRANG INTO
ACTION, TRYING TO CALM THE
CRYING, INJURED STUDENTS.
>> I HAVEN'T SEEN IT VERY OFTEN,
BUT I'M VERY GLAD THAT THEY WERE
THERE BECAUSE THEY WERE VERY
HELPFUL.
>> Reporter: THE BUS WAS HALFWAY
FROM THE PHILADELPHIA SCHOOL TO
A FIELD TRIP IN D.C. WHEN A
SMALL SEDAN TRIED TO PASS THE
BUS.
THAT VEHICLE RUNS OFF THE ROAD
AS THE DRIVER CORRECTS, THE CAR
CROSSES THE SOUTHBOUND LANES,
CLIPPING THE FRONT OF THE BUS
SENDING IT INTO AN EMBANKMENT
LINED WITH TREES, AND THROWING
IT, AND THE 30 OCCUPANTS, ON ITS
SIDE.
MANY OF THE INJURED STUDENTS
TREATED AT LOCAL HOSPITALS HAVE
ALREADY BEEN DISCHARGED.
THE DRIVER OF THAT SMALL SEDAN
WHICH APPARENTLY CAUSED THE
ACCIDENT, COULD FACE CHARGES.
DAVID.
>> DAVID KERLEY WITH US TONIGHT
AS WELL.
THANK YOU, DAVID.
>>> THERE'S STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD -- WE HAVE NEW
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE DEADLY
POLICE SHOOTING OF A TEENAGER.
NEW IMAGES RAISING QUESTIONS AND
THIS MAJOR QUESTION, WAS HE LEFT
THERE FOR SIX HOURS?
THE 15-YEAR-OLD BOY SHOT AND
HANDCUFFED, SEEN LYING ON THE
GROUND.
HIS FAMILY NOW SAYING HIS LIFE
COULD HAVE BEEN SAVED.
>>> THE HOME THAT WENT UP IN
FLAMES.
THE FAMILY OF SEVEN THAT DID NOT
SURVIVE.
INVESTIGATORS ARE ON THE SCENE
TONIGHT.
WHAT THEY'RE NOW SAYING.
>>> AND LATER TONIGHT, THE
SKYDIVER JUMPING INTO THE RECORD
BOOKS.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE HOW OLD HE IS,
OR BETTER YET, WE SHOULD ASK,
HOW YOUNG IS HE?
STAY TUNED FOR THAT.
[Boy] Cannonball!
[Girl] Don't...
[Man] Not again!
[Burke] Swan Drive. Seen it.
Covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
MMMM.  MMMM.
MMMM... UGH.
Nothing spoils a moment
like heartburn.
Try new Alka-Seltzer Ultra
Strength heartburn Relief Chews.
It's fast, powerful relief
with no chalky taste.
[ sings high note ]
Ultra Strength, new
from Alka-Seltzer.
Enjoy the Relief.
When this bell rings...
...it starts a chain
reaction...
...that's heard throughout the
connected business world.
AT&T network security helps
protect business,
from the largest financial
markets to the smallest
transactions,
by sensing cyber-attacks in near
real time
and automatically deploying
countermeasures.
Keeping the world of business
connected and protected.
That's the power of and.
ABreak through your allergies.?
Try New Flonase
Sensimist Allergy Relief
instead of allergy pills.
It's more complete
allergy relief
in a gentle mist experience
you'll barely feel.
Using unique MistPro Technology,
new Flonase Sensimist
delivers a gentle mist
to help block six key
inflammatory substances
that cause your symptoms.
Most allergy pills
only block one.
And six is greater
than one.
New Flonase
Sensimist
changes everything.
STAY TUNED FOR THAT.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, THE
DEADLY POLICE SHOOTING OF A
TEENAGER IN CONNECTICUT.
A 15-YEAR-OLD BOY, ALLEGEDLY
RAMMING AN OFFICER WITH A STOLEN
CAR.
NOW, A NEW VIDEO SHOWING THE
MOMENTS AFTER POLICE OPENED
FIRE.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> Reporter: THESE IMAGES, TAKEN
BY A BYSTANDER, ARE RAISING
QUESTIONS TONIGHT.
15-YEAR-OLD JAYSON NEGRON
HANDCUFFED ON THE GROUND WITH
HIS HEAD FACING TO HIS RIGHT.
THE CAMERA PANS OFF AND FOUR
SECONDS LATER, NEGRON'S HEAD IS
IN A DIFFERENT POSITION.
THE VICTIM'S FAMILY SAYS THE
PICTURES SUGGEST NEGRON WAS
STILL ALIVE AND THEY SAY THAT
CONTRADICTS WHAT POLICE TOLD
THEM, THAT NEGRON WAS KILLED
WHEN HE WAS SHOT.
ACCORDING TO BRIDGEPORT,
CONNECTICUT, POLICE, THE OFFICER
SHOT NEGRON AFTER HE REFUSED
ORDERS TO STOP AND HIT THE
OFFICER WITH A STOLEN CAR ON
TUESDAY.
>> THIS IS A YOUNG MAN, WHO PUT
HIMSELF IN A REALLY BAD
SITUATION AND LOST HIS LIFE.
>> Reporter: THE 21-YEAR-OLD
PASSENGER WAS ALSO SHOT, BUT
SUFFERED NONLIFE-THREATENING
INJURIES.
THE POLICE CHIEF SAYS NEGRON'S
BODY WAS LYING IN THE STREET FOR
ABOUT SIX HOURS AFTER THE
SHOOTING FOR EVIDENCE-GATHERING
REASONS, BUT NEGRON'S FAMILY
MEMBERS SAY THAT POLICE NEVER
PROVIDED HIM MEDICAL ATTENTION
THAT THEY BELIEVE MIGHT HAVE
SAVED HIS LIFE.
HUNDREDS GATHERED LAST WEEK TO
PAY TRIBUTE TO THE TEEN AND
CALL FOR ACTION.
THAT OFFICER IS ON
ADMINISTRATIVE LEAVE PENDING THE
OUTCOME OF AN INVESTIGATION.
DAVID.
>> LINSEY DAVIS, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK -- THE
POLICE OFFICER'S ACCIDENTAL
OVERDOSE AFTER HE TOUCHED A KIND
OF POWDER.
THEY REVEALED WHAT IT WAS.
>>> AND REMEMBERING THE ACTOR
FAMOUS FOR HIS BAD-GUY ROLES.
>>> AND THEN MORE ON THAT
DEVASTATING FIRE.
THE HOME IN FLAMES.
THE FAMILY OF SEVEN TRAPPED AND
INVESTIGATORS ON THE SCENE.
or dt
and diarrhea.
I tried lifestyle changes
and over-the-counter treatments,
but my symptoms keep
coming back.
It turns out I have
Irritable Bowel Syndrome
with Diarrhea,
or IBS-D.
A condition that's really
frustrating.
That's why I talked to my
doctor about VIBERZI...
...a different way
to treat IBS-D.
VIBERZI is a
prescription medication
you take every day
that helps proactively manage
both abdominal pain and
diarrhea at the same time.
So I can stay ahead of
my symptoms.
VIBERZI can cause new or
worsening abdominal pain.
Do not take VIBERZI
if you have no gallbladder,
have pancreas or
severe liver problems,
problems with alcohol abuse,
long-lasting or
severe constipation,
or a bowel or
gallbladder blockage.
Pancreatitis may occur
and can lead to
hospitalization and death.
If you are taking VIBERZI,
you should not take medicines
that cause constipation.
The most common side effects of
VIBERZI include constipation,
nausea, and abdominal pain.
Stay ahead of IBS-D
with VIBERZI.
I was in the
military for 18 years.rian,
But, I smoked and
I got heart disease.
My tip is;
it's hard to
serve your country
when you're to weak
to put on your uniform.
(Announcer) You can quit.
For free help,
call 1-800-QUIT-NOW.
Oscar MaWe went back toig
the drawing board...
And the cutting board.
We removed the added nitrates
and nitrites,
by-products,
and artificial preservatives
in all of our meat.
Every. Single. One.
Why? For the love of hot dogs.
when they thought they should
Westart saving for retirement.le
Then we asked some older people
when they actually
did start saving.
This gap between when
we should start saving
and when we actually
do is one of the reasons
why too many of us aren't
prepared for retirement.
Just start as early as you can.
It's going to pay
off in the future.
If we all start saving
a little more today,
we'll all be better
prepared tomorrow.
Prudential.
Bring Your Challenges.
What twisted ankle?ask
What muscle strain?
Advil makes pain a distant
memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
It's looking up, not down.ng
fIt's being in motion.
BOOST® High Protein
It's intelligent nutrition with
15 grams of protein
and 26 vitamins and minerals.
BOOST® The number one
high protein complete
nutritional drink.
gave us the power to turn this
enemy into an ally?
Microsoft and its partners are
using smart traps to capture
mosquitoes and sequence their
DNA to fight disease.
There are over 100 million
pieces of DNA in every sample.
With the Microsoft Cloud,
we can analyze the data
faster than ever before.
If we can detect new viruses
before they spread,
we may someday prevent outbreaks
before they begin.
>>> TO THE "INDEX" AND THE
DEADLY HOUSE FIRE IN AKRON,
OHIO, A MOTHER, FATHER AND FIVE
CHILDREN REPORTEDLY KILLED WHEN
THEIR HOME UP IN FLAMES.
NEIGHBORS FRANTICALLY CALLING
911.
INVESTIGATORS ON THE SCENE.
THE FIRE CHIEF TONIGHT SAYING
HE'S NOT RULING OUT ARSON.
>>> A POLICE OFFICER SUFFERED AN
ACCIDENTAL OVERDOSE IN EAST
LIVERPOOL, OHIO, THE OFFICER WAS
SEARCHING FOR DRUGS IN A CAR
USING HIS BARE HAND TO BRUSH
WHITE POWDER OFF HIS SHIRT,
PASSING OUT AN HOUR LATER.
POLICE SAY THAT IT WAS FENTANYL,
A SYNTHETIC OPIOID.
FIVE TIMES AS STRONG AS HEROIN.
IT TOOK FOUR DOSES OF NARCAN TO
REVIVE THE OFFICER.
>>> AND A PASSING TO NOTE
TONIGHT, ACTOR POWERS BOOTHE HAS
DIED.
HE WAS 68.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT --
THE WORLD WAR II VETERAN, 101
YEARS OLD, AND YOU'RE ABOUT TO
SEE WHAT HE WAS WILLING TO DO.
STAY TUNED.
Got it.
Rumor confirmed.
They're playing.
-What?
-We gotta go.
-Where?
-San Francisco.
-When?
-Friday.
We gotta go.
[ Tires screech ]
Any airline. Any hotel.
Any time.
Go where you want,
when you want
with no blackout dates.
[ Muffled music coming
from club. "Blue Monday"
by New Order. Cheers. ]
[ Music and cheers get louder ]
The Travel Rewards credit card
from Bank of America.
It's travel, better connected.
The Travel Rewards credit card
from Bank of America.
But with my back pain I couldn't
sleep or get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
And now. I'm back!
Aleve PM for a better AM.
WILL YOU BE READY WHEN
THE MOMENT TURNS ROMANTIC?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
How do you become America's
best-selling brand?
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
You make it detect what
they don't.
Stop, stop, STOP!
Sorry.
You make it sense what's coming.
Watch, watch, WATCH!
Mom. Relax!
I'm relaxed.
You make it for 16-year olds...
Whoa-whoa-WHOA!!!
and the parents who worry
about them.
You saw him, right?
Going further to help make
drivers, better drivers.
Don't freak out on me.
That's Ford.
And that's how you become
America's Best-Selling Brand.
Bburning of diabetic nerve pain
these feet...
kicked off a lot of high school
games...
...built a life for my family...
...and liked to help others
in need.
But I couldn't bear my diabetic
nerve pain any longer.
So I talked to my doctor
and he prescribed LYRICA.
Nerve damage from diabetes
causes diabetic nerve pain.
LYRICA is FDA approved
to treat this pain.
LYRICA may cause serious
allergic reactions
or suicidal thoughts
or actions.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have these,
new or worsening depression,
or unusual changes in mood
or behavior.
Or swelling, trouble breathing,
rash, hives, blisters, muscle
pain with fever,
tired feeling or blurry vision.
Common side effects are
dizziness, sleepiness,
weight gain and swelling
of hands, legs, and feet.
Don't drink alcohol while
taking LYRICA.
Don't drive or use machinery
until you know how LYRICA
affects you.
Those who have had a drug or
alcohol problem
may be more likely
to misuse LYRICA.
Now I have less diabetic
nerve pain.
And it's great to help others
get back on their feet.
Ask your doctor about
LYRICA.
If you're eligible,
you could pay as little as $25
dollars a month.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, HE'S BECOME
THE WORLD'S OLDEST SKYDIVER.
THE D-DAY VETERAN PROVING HE'S
FOREVER YOUNG.
ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S ABOUT TO
HAPPEN IN THESE NEXT FEW SECONDS
IS A WORLD RECORD.
THIS IS 101-YEAR-OLD VERDUN
HAYES, ABOUT TO BECOME THE
WORLD'S OLDEST SKYDIVER.
FOUR GENERATIONS OF HIS FAMILY
JOINED HIM FOR THE FLIGHT, HE
ONLY NEEDED TO JUMP FROM 10,000
FEET FOR THE RECORD, BUT WENT
FOR 15,000.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> ALL RIGHT, ABSOLUTELY OVER
THE MOON!
OH, YES, HOPEFULLY I'LL BE DOING
IT AT 102 OR 103.
>> Reporter: HE BEAT THE
PREVIOUS RECORD HOLDER BY 35
DAYS.
>> I SLEPT VERY WELL INDEED AND
I WOKE UP THIS MORNING THE
HAPPIEST MAN IN THE WORLD.
>> Reporter: HAYES IS A WAR
VETERAN WHO WAS THERE ON D-DAY
IN NORMANDY IN 1944.
CLEARLY JUMPING OUT OF PLANES
MAKES HIM FEEL FOREVER YOUNG.
STEVE OSUNSAMI, ABC NEWS,
ATLANTA.
>> HE'S HOPING TO DO IT WHEN
HE'S 103.
>>> I'M DAVID MUIR, I HOPE TO
SEE YOU RIGHT BACK HERE
TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
CALIFORNIA ARE THE "NEW YORK
TIMES" AND "WASHINGTON POST"
CLAIM THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
SHARED SENSITIVE INTELLIGENCE
INFORMATION.
>> U.S. OFFICIALS TOLD THE TIMES
AND POST IT COULD EXPOSE THE
INFORMATION SOURCE AND
JEOPARDIZE A CRITICAL
RELATIONSHIP.
>> THE LAWMAKERS WANT TO KNOW
MORE.
>> WE HAVE TO HAVE A SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR, TO LOOK INTO WHAT IS
RUSSIA'S CONNECTION, BOTH WITH
THE ELECTION AND ONGOING.
>> CONGRESSMAN ERIC SWOLWELL
ALSO CALLED FOR AN INDEPENDENT
INVESTIGATION.
CONGRESSMAN K AR
UNWITTINGLY SHARING THE INTEL
WOULD BE DANGEROUS, BUT DOING IT
INTENTIONALLY IS MUCH WORSE.
>>> MEANWHILE THE INVESTIGATION
CONTINUES INTO THAT MASSIVE
RANSOM WARE ATTACK ON COMPUTERS
ALL OVER THE WORLD.
>> YOU HEARD ON "WORLD NEWS
TONIGHT" IT MAY HAVE ORIGINATED
IN NORTH KOREA.
NO O H