THE
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, DIRECT HIT, TWISTER
OUTBREAK.
WE HAVE NEW PICTURES, PROVING
THE EPIC SIZE OF THE TORNADO IN
OKLAHOMA.
POWERFUL, DEAFENING, 600 TIMES
THE STRENGTH OF AN ATOMIC BOMB,
FLATTENING THAT ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL WITH CHILDREN TAKING
SHELTER INSIDE.
AND TONIGHT FAMILIES SHOW US HOW
THEY EMERGED FROM UNDERGROUND
SHELTERS TO SEE THEIR HOMES
SIMPLY ERASED.
>> THE LORD GIVETH, AND THE LORD
TAKETH AWAY.
>> THE FRANTIC SEARCH FOR
SURVIVORS CONTINUES.
AND WE JOIN THE SEARCHERS AS
THEY LISTEN FOR THE SOUND OF
LIFE.
>> HEY!
>> THE TEARFUL REUNION, AND THAT
ICONIC PICTURE WE SEE AGAIN AND
AGAIN.
TONIGHT WE MEET THESE PARENTS
AND LEARN WHAT THEY DID TO SAVE
OTHER CHILDREN TOO.
OUR ABC NEWS EXTREME WEATHER
TEAM BRINGING US ASTONISHING
STORIES AND PICTURES AND
SURPRISES FROM THE STORM AS WE
ARE WITH THE PEOPLE OF MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, STANDING STRONG
TONIGHT.
THE VERY LATEST RIGHT NOW ON
"WORLD NEWS."
>>> AND GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
WE BEGIN WITH A SPECIAL EDITION
OF "WORLD NEWS" TONIGHT.
ABC NEWS COVERING THE STORY OF
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
WHERE ONE OF NATURE'S RAW FORCES
SHATTERED SO MANY LIVES IN A
MATTER OF MINUTES.
ALL DAY, WE HAVE WATCHED RESCUE
TEAMS SCOUR THE RUBBLE, LOOKING
AND LISTENING FOR ANY SIGN
SOMEONE MIGHT BE THERE
UNDERNEATH.
AND TONIGHT, WE ALSO HAVE PHOTOS
COMING IN, A TRUE-GRIT MOMENT,
OKLAHOMA STYLE.
A MAN IN A ROCKING CHAIR, AND
ALL THOSE FIREMEN MOVING IN TO
HELP.
AND TWO LITTLE GIRLS, LOOKING AT
THE PLACE THEY ONCE CALLED HOME,
A BABY DOLL IN THEIR HANDS.
AND THOSE REUNIONS CONTINUE.
PARENTS CLUTCHING THEIR
CHILDREN, AND A BOY SCOOPED UP
THERE BY A JOYFUL TEACHER IN A
BRIGHT RED SHIRT.
TONIGHT WE ARE GOING TO TAKE YOU
INSIDE THE 17 MILES OF
DESTRUCTION, SCHOOLS,
NEIGHBORHOODS, HOSPITALS
PULVERIZED, AS OUR ABC NEWS TEAM
IS EVERYWHERE IN THE STORM ZONE
TONIGHT, AND OUR COVERAGE OF THE
DIRECT HIT TWISTER OUTBREAK
BEGINS WITH ABC'S ANCHOR DAVID
MUIR ON THE GROUND RIGHT THERE
IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
DAVID?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING FROM
OKLAHOMA TONIGHT WHERE WE
LEARNED JUST A SHORT TIME AGO,
THAT IN SOME PARTS OF THIS
COMMUNITY, THAT TORNADO
SURPASSED 200 MILES PER HOUR.
LOOK OVER MY SHOULDER TONIGHT
BECAUSE THIS IS WHAT THAT DOES.
HOME AFTER HOME OBLITERATED
HERE.
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD THAT WE'RE
STANDING IN, LOOKS LIKE SO MANY
THAT WE DROVE THROUGH TODAY.
AS YOU KNOW, TWO DIRECT HITS ON
ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS HERE TODAY.
AT ONE SCHOOL, A MIRACLE.
AT THE OTHER, THEY WERE STILL
HOPING FOR A MIRACLE TODAY.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Reporter: TONIGHT AS WE
LEARNED THAT MONSTROUS TORNADO
WAS IN SOME PLACES EVEN STRONGER
AND MORE DANGEROUS THAN FIRST
THOUGHT, A PROMISE FROM
AUTHORITIES HERE.
TO SEARCH EVERY HOME HERE IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, THREE TIMES
BEFORE GIVING UP.
JUST BEFORE WE CAME ON THE AIR,
ANOTHER VISIT TO THE HOME RIGHT
HERE BESIDE US.
AND AT THE PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, THEY'RE STILL
SEARCHING.
THOUGH AUTHORITIES WON'T SAY FOR
SURE IF THEY BELIEVE THERE ARE
ANY CHILDREN STILL INSIDE.
BUT THERE'S STILL HOPE HERE, AND
THERE ARE STILL TEARS.
NEW IMAGES OF THOSE FIRST
REUNIONS.
THIS MOTHER REUNITED WITH HER
SON WHO'S BEEN SOBBING IN THE
ARMS OF HIS TEACHER, WAITING FOR
HER.
A THANK YOU FROM MOM, AND A
PROUD TEACHER ANSWERS.
>> HE WAS SO GOOD.
>> Reporter: ONE OF THE HAPPY
ENDINGS HERE.
AFTER SO MUCH CHAOS AND FEAR.
THIS MAN LIFTING UP A TEARFUL
BOY TO CONSOLE HIM.
AND THERE WAS THIS FATHER AS
PANICKED AS ANY PARENT WOULD BE.
>> SHE'S OUT?
>> Reporter: HE WOULD SOON FIND
HER.
AND THIS LITTLE GIRL, WHO SAID
SHE JUST WOULDN'T LET GO OF THAT
DESK.
>> THE TORNADO WENT IN AND I WAS
SO AFRAID THAT I WAS HANGING ON
TO ONE OF THE DESKS.
AND THEN, UM, I FELL BACK, AND
ALL THE DIRT THAT GOT IN MY EYES
AND I FELL.
>> Reporter: THE COUNTLESS
HEROES, THE TEACHERS DETERMINED
TO MAKE SURE THEIR STUDENTS
WOULD MAKE IT HOME TO THEIR
PARENTS.
>> ALL FIFTH GRADERS RIGHT HERE!
>> Reporter: TONIGHT A CLEARER
PICTURE OF THE MOMENTS BEFORE
THE TORNADO TOOK AIM AT TWO
DIFFERENT SCHOOLS.
AT BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY, THEY
ALL GOT OUT.
CINDY LOWE TEACHES FIRST GRADE.
SHE OPENED HER DOOR AND SAW THE
TORNADO COME.
YOU SAW IT COMING RIGHT AT YOU?
>> COMING RIGHT FOR THE SCHOOL.
RAN OVER AND GOT ON TOP OF THE
KIDS.
SAID THIS IS NOT A DRILL.
>> Reporter: ONE OF THOSE
CHILDREN, HER OWN SON.
HER BODY ON TOP OF HIS AND
SEVERAL OTHERS AS THEY CRIED FOR
THEIR MOMS.
>> THEY HAD DESKS AND CHAIRS AND
TABLES COVERING THEM.
>> Reporter: AND TEACHER?
>> AND TEACHER.
>> Reporter: JUST ACROSS THE
WAY, SHERRY URGED HER FIRST
GRADERS TO USE THEIR BACKPACKS
AS SHIELDS.
>> THEY WERE COVERING THEIR
HEADS WITH THEIR BACKPACKS.
>> Reporter: WHAT WERE THE KIDS
SAYING DURING ALL THIS?
>> I WANT MY MOM.
>> Reporter: THEIR SCHOOL IS
DESTROYED TOO.
HOW DID ALL THE CHILDREN THERE
GET OUT WHEN SOME OF THE
STUDENTS AT PLAZA TOWERS DID
NOT?
SHE BELIEVES IT WAS BECAUSE HER
SCHOOL WAS CONSTRUCTED
DIFFERENTLY.
EACH GRADE ORGANIZED INTO PODS,
A FEW CLASSROOMS IN EACH
BUILDING.
AT THE CENTER OF THOSE BUILDINGS
AN OPENING TO THE OUTDOORS.
WHEN EVERYTHING COLLAPSED, THEY
WERE ABLE TO CRAWL OUT THROUGH
THE OPEN AREA IN THE MIDDLE,
PASSING THE CHILDREN OVER THE
RUBBLE.
UNLIKE PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY,
MORE TRADITIONAL WITH A LONG
LINE OF CLASSROOMS UNDER ONE
ROOF.
WHEN IT COLLAPSED, THE ROOF AND
WALLS PILING ON TOP OF ONE
ANOTHER, NO OPENING IN THE
MIDDLE, LIKE THOSE PODS.
TO CRAWL OUT FROM.
TONIGHT AS THEY CONTINUE TO
SEARCH THERE, AN HONEST FIRE
CHIEF.
>> NO SURVIVOR HAS BEEN FOUND
RECENTLY, IN THE LAST FEW HOURS.
>> Reporter: BUT FOR THAT
TEACHER WHOSE PRAYER WAS
ANSWERED, TONIGHT A PRAYER FOR
THE TEACHERS AT THE OTHER
SCHOOL.
>> THE TEACHERS AT PLAZA TOWERS
DIDN'T HAVE THAT BLESSING.
AND I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE NOT
BEING ABLE TO GIVE THOSE KIDS
BACK TO THEIR PARENTS THAT
BROUGHT THEM TO ME THAT MORNING.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THAT
TEACHER THINKING ABOUT ALL THOSE
OTHER TEACHERS AT THE OTHER
SCHOOL.
AND WE LEARNED FROM THOSE TWO
TEACHERS EARLIER TODAY, DIANE,
THAT THERE WERE NO SAFE ROOMS IN
EITHER OF THOSE SCHOOLS.
WHEN AUTHORITIES WERE ASKED
ABOUT THAT LATE TODAY, THEY
ACKNOWLEDGED THAT THERE SIMPLY
ISN'T THE FUNDING TO PUT SAFE
ROOMS IN EVERY SCHOOL.
ACKNOWLEDGING THOSE TWO SCHOOLS
WERE AMONG THOSE THAT WERE NOT
FUNDED.
A LOT OF QUESTIONS TO COME ON
THAT.
>> YOU BET A LOT OF QUESTIONS
WILL BE ASKED.
DAVID, WE WERE TALKING ABOUT THE
FACT SO MANY PEOPLE VIDEOTAPED
WHAT WAS HAPPENING AS THE STORM
WAS GOING OVERHEAD.
YOU MET WITH ONE OF THEM?
>> Reporter: THE EXTRAORDINARY
TAPE, THAT HUSBAND WHO WATCHED
THE TORNADO COMING TOWARD HIS
HOUSE, TOWARD HIS FAMILY.
TODAY WE WENT TO MEET THEM.
HE TOOK ME DOWN THE STAIRWELL
THAT SAVED HIS FAMILY'S LIFE.
IT IS THE VOICE YOU HEAR AS THAT
TORNADO IS ABOUT TO TOUCH DOWN
AND TAKE DIRECT AIM AT HIS HOME
AND HIS FAMILY.
[ SIRENS ]
HIS WIFE AND FOUR CHILDREN
WAITING IN THE STORM SHELTER,
THEIR BUNKER.
AND TODAY WE WENT TO FIND THEM.
THERE WAS JASON IN HIS FRONT
YARD.
NO HOME LEFT, BUT HE HAS HIS
FAMILY AND HE SHOWED US WHY.
TAKING US DOWN INTO HIS CONCRETE
STORM SHELTER WHERE THEY WERE
HUDDLED.
>> YOU COULD SEE THE PRESSURE OF
THE TORNADO AGAINST THE METAL?
>> YEAH, THE METAL WAS POPPING
IN AND OUT.
>> Reporter: THAT METAL DOOR
BUCKLING UNDER THE PRESSURE OF
THE TORNADO.
YOU HAVE LANTERNS?
>> WE HAVE LAN TERNS AND ANOTHER
INTERESTING THING, LAPTOPS WHILE
WE WERE IN HERE.
HE TOLD ME THE CHILDREN QUIETLY
CRYING, THE FAMILY MOUTHING
THEIR WORDS TO EACH OTHER,
BECAUSE OF THE PRESSURE ON THEIR
EARS, THEY COULDN'T HEAR A
THING.
>> I CAN REACH OUT AND TOUCH
BOTH WALLS WITH MY FINGERS.
NOT A HUGE SPACE.
SUDDENLY SILENCE.
IT WAS OVER.
HE SHOWS US HOW HE OPENED THAT
DOOR AND THIS IS WHAT HE SAW
WHEN HE WALKED OUT.
>> I WANT YOU TO STAY.
>> OKAY.
>> THE LORD GIVETH, AND THE LORD
TAKETH AWAY.
>> Reporter: REALLY
EXTRAORDINARY.
THEY SAY IT WENT COMPLETELY
SILENT IN THAT BUNKER WHEN THE
TORNADO STOPPED DOING ITS
DAMAGE.
WE MET HIS WIFE TODAY, GIANT
SMILE ON HER FACE, EVEN THOUGH
SHE HAS NO HOME LEFT, SHE HAS
HER FAMILY.
AND SHE FOUND THE BABY ALBUMS
WHILE WE WERE THERE, ALL BECAUSE
THE FAMILY WAS SAFE INSIDE THAT
BUNKER, I COULD REACH OUT AND
TOUCH EACH SIDE.
>> ALL RIGHT, DAVID MUIR
REPORTING.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
I HAVE ANOTHER BEHIND THE
PICTURE IMAGE TONIGHT.
IN FACT, YOU SHOWED US THE
ICONIC SCENE, THE MOTHER AND
FATHER WALKING.
SHE'S BLOODIED.
THEY'RE WALKING AWAY FROM BRIAR
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WHICH TOOK A
DIRECT HIT.
THEY ARE THE COBB FAMILY, LA
DONNA AND STEVE.
SHE HAS A BADLY BRUISED EYE AND
FACE, BUT SHE'LL BE FINE.
EARLIER I SPOKE TO THEM ABOUT
WHAT THEY DID.
>> I JUST TRIED TO BE THE BEST
DAD I COULD AT THAT TIME.
I WANTED HER TO FEEL SAFE AND
THAT WE WERE GOING TO BE OKAY.
I WISHED I COULD HAVE SPLIT
MYSELF INTO TWO AND STAYED THERE
AND TRIED TO HELP OUT SOME OF
THOSE OTHER KIDS, BECAUSE I CAN
IMAGINE HOW THEY WERE FEELING AT
THAT TIME.
YOU KNOW, WHEN THEIR PARENTS
WEREN'T THERE, KIND OF WANDERING
AROUND.
IT'S LIKE BEING IN A MOVIE, AND
IT'S LIKE EVERYBODY'S PLAYING A
PART.
WE'RE ALL ACTING OR SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST NOT -- DOESN'T SEEM
REAL TO YOU THAT THIS IS
OCCURRING.
>> AND JORDAN, HOW LONG DID THAT
TORNADO SEEM TO LAST FOR YOU?
>> FOREVER.
IT SEEMED LIKE IT WAS LIKE AN
HOUR.
LIKE, IT WAS CRAZY.
I MEAN, I CAN'T EVEN BELIEVE WE
SURVIVED THAT.
>> I WAS JUST GRABBING ON TO
WHATEVER I COULD.
ONCE THE ROOF LIFTED OFF OF THE
BUILDING, I FELT MYSELF BEING
SUCKED, AND I KNEW THAT IF I WAS
TAKEN, THEN ALL THE LITTLE
BABIES UNDERNEATH ME WOULD BE
GONE TOO.
SO I JUST HELD ON.
I HELD ON FOR DEAR LIFE UNTIL
THE WALL FELL ON TOP OF ME AND
KNOCKED ME OUT.
>> I COULDN'T BELIEVE THE OTHER
-- I COULDN'T LEAVE THE OTHER
KIDS.
THEY ALL ARE SPECIAL TO ME.
AND I COULDN'T LEAVE THEM.
AND I WANTED MY FAMILY TO BE
SAFE, BUT I ALSO WANTED
EVERYBODY ELSE'S FAMILY TO BE
SAFE TOO.
>> WHAT WAS THE HARDEST MOMENT
FOR YOU, JORDAN?
>> JUST WHEN I WAS LIKE, I TRIED
TO GET UP AND I TRIED TO MOVE
THE BRICKS OFF OF MY LEG, AND IT
HURT SO MUCH, AND I WAS LIKE --
AND IT WAS DURING -- THE TORNADO
HAD NOT LEFT YET.
I WAS JUST SCREAMING, HELP,
MY LEG, MY LEG, AND NO ONE COULD
HEAR ME.
>>SET
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT IS THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING ABOUT FAMILY TO YOU?
>> THAT WE'RE ALWAYS THERE FOR
EACH OTHER.
THAT WE LOVE EACH OTHER, AND WE
TAKE CARE OF EACH OTHER.
AND THAT WE BELIEVE IN EACH
OTHER, NO MATTER WHAT.
>> JORDAN AND HER WONDERFUL
FAMILY.
AND THERE ARE SO MANY OTHER
FAMILIES PORING OVER THE
FRAGMENTS OF THEIR LIVES
TONIGHT.
ABC'S CECILIA VEGA SPENT THE DAY
WITH THEM.
AND SHE HAS THEIR STORIES.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
THEY HAVE BEEN OUT HERE ALL DAY
TRYING TO PIECE TOGETHER THEIR
LIVES.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU WHAT THEY'RE
FINDING.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
SOMEBODY'S KEYS THEY LEFT
BEHIND.
A LITTLE GIRL'S PINK TIARA.
A LITTLE GIRL'S PANTS RIGHT
HERE.
THIS USED TO BE SOMEBODY'S
HOUSE.
NOW THEY'RE JUST MEMORIES BURIED
HERE IN THE RUBBLE.
HERE IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA, BLOCK
AFTER BLOCK OF DEVASTATION.
NEIGHBORS SIFT THROUGH MOUNDS OF
RUBBLE TRYING TO SALVAGE WHAT
LITTLE SURVIVED, HELPING EACH
OTHER CRAM THEIR MEMORIES INTO
PLASTIC BAGS.
THIS IS THE SCENE ALL OVER THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD.
PEOPLE'S LIVES SCATTERED ALL
OVER THESE PROPERTIES, THERE ARE
TOYS, YOU CAN SEE HERE,
STROLLERS, THEIR LIVES.
EVEN FAMILY PHOTOS LIKE THIS, A
FATHER AND A MOTHER AND MAYBE
THEIR LITTLE GIRL.
ONLINE, A WOMAN FOUND DEBRIS IN
HER FRONT YARD 100 MILES AWAY,
SET UP A FACEBOOK PAGE, A CYBER
LOST AND FOUND.
BABY PICTURES, EVEN A SONOGRAM,
GRADUATIONS, WEDDINGS, AN "I
LOVE YOU" TO MOM.
THIS PHOTO OF A KISSING COUPLE
AND A NOTE FROM THE PERSON WHO
FOUND IT.
"JUST HOPING THAT THE TWO IN
THIS PHOTO ARE OKAY."
IT IS A HOPE THAT IS UNIVERSAL.
BUT AMID THE WRECKAGE, THERE IS
A LOOK TO THE FUTURE.
TONY McGEE IS DETERMINED TO
REBUILD A HOME HE MOVED INTO
JUST TWO WEEKS AGO.
>> GOD HAS HIS REASON FOR
EVERYTHING, GOT TO BELIEVE.
>> Reporter: JUST UP THE STREET.
HER NAME IS FLY.
SHE RODE OUT THE STORM ALL ALONE
AFTER HER OWNERS BARELY ESCAPED
TO A SHELTER JUST TWO MINUTES
BEFORE THE TWISTER HIT.
THESE TWO FRIENDS FOUND FLY JUST
HOURS AGO ON THE FLOORBOARD OF
HER OWNER'S CAR.
>> ON THE DRIVER'S SEAT, SITTING
RIGHT THERE.
>> Reporter: WE MET A MAN UP THE
BLOCK HERE WHO TOLD US HE TOOK
SHELTER IN HIS BATHTUB WITH HIS
ENTIRE FAMILY.
WHEN THEY EMERGED, HIS HOUSE WAS
GONE.
HE FOUND PIECES OF HIS LIFE
ACROSS HIS PROPERTY.
HIS CHRISTMAS ORNAMENTS THAT HAD
BEEN IN HIS ATTIC, WERE IN HIS
DRIVEWAY.
THESE ARE THE STORIES WE'RE
HEARING OUT HERE, STORIES FROM
THE PILE OF PEOPLE WHO JUST
RIGHT NOW ARE BEGINNING TO TRY
TO PUT THEIR LIVES BACK
TOGETHER.
>> IMPOSSIBLE STRENGTH AND
SURVIVAL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, CECILIA.
>>> WE WANT TO SHOW YOU THE MAP,
AND REMIND YOU, WE'RE STANDING
WATCH HERE TONIGHT OVER THE
MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
IN THIS COUNTRY STILL UNDER
SEVERE WEATHER WATCHES.
IN FACT, TONIGHT, NEARLY TEN
MILLION FACE THE POSSIBILITY OF
TORNADOES.
AND WE WILL BE WATCHING.
STILL AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS," A
ONE IN 100 TRILLION CHANCE THAT
A HOUSE HIT BY AN EF-4 TORNADO
IN 1999 WOULD BE HIT BY A BIG
ONE AGAIN.
TONIGHT YOU'LL MEET A
94-YEAR-OLD WOMAN WHO HAD THAT
ONE IN 100 TRILLION SHOT HAPPEN
TO HER.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS IS KEVIN.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT Aleve
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HIM,
HE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HIM ALL DAY
AS HE GOES BACK
TO TAKING TYLENOL.
THAT WAS OKAY, BUT AFTER LUNCH
MY KNEE STARTED TO HURT AGAIN,
AND NOW I GOTTA TAKE MORE PILLS.
♪
YUP ANOTHER PILL STOP.
CAN I GET MY Aleve BACK YET?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY Aleve.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS MAY, BUY Aleve
AND HELP THOSE IN NEED.
HOW OLD IS THE OLDEST PERSON
YOU'VE KNOWN?
WE GAVE PEOPLE A STICKER
AND HAD THEM SHOW US.
WE LEARNED A LOT OF US
HAVE KNOWN SOMEONE
WHO'S LIVED WELL INTO THEIR 90S.
AND THAT'S A GREAT THING.
BUT EVEN THOUGH
WE'RE LIVING LONGER,
ONE THING
THAT HASN'T CHANGED MUCH
IS THE OFFICIAL RETIREMENT AGE.
♪
THE QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU MAKE
SURE YOU HAVE THE MONEY YOU NEED
TO ENJOY ALL OF THESE YEARS.
♪
thousands of cancer
patients can't afford
to stay near the
best treatment centers.
Let's make sure that everyone
who needs a room, gets one.
Let's help the
American Cancer Society
finish the fight.
I remember thinking
there's a lot I have to do...
check my blood sugar,
eat better.
Start insulin.
Today I learned
there's something
I don't have to do anymore.
My doctor said with
Levemir® FlexPen...
I don't have to use a syringe
and a vial.
Levemir® FlexPen
comes prefilled
with long-acting insulin
taken once daily
for type 2 diabetes to help
control high blood sugar.
Dial the exact dose.
Inject by pushing
a button.
No drawing from a vial.
No refrigeration
for up to 42 days.
Levemir® (insulin detemir
[rDNA origin] injection)
is not recommended to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis.
Do not use Levemir®
if you are allergic
to any of its ingredients.
The most common side effect
is low blood sugar,
which may cause symptoms
such as sweating, shakiness,
confusion, and headache.
Severe low blood sugar can be
serious and life threatening.
Ask your health care provider
about alcohol use,
operating machinery,
or driving.
Other possible side effects
include injection site
reactions.
Tell your health care provider
about all medicines you take
and all of your
medical conditions.
Get medical help right away
if you experience
serious allergic reactions
such as body rash,
trouble with breathing,
fast heartbeat, or sweating.
FlexPen® is
insulin delivery my way.
Covered by most insurance plans,
including Medicare.
Ask your health care provider
about Levemir® FlexPen today.
♪
>>> AND AS WE SAID A MOMENT AGO,
HERE IS HOW IMPOSSIBLE IT IS
THAT YOUR HOUSE COULD BE HIT
TWICE, EACH TIME BY ONE OF THE
BIGGEST TORNADOES.
HERE ARE THE ODDS.
ONE IN 100 TRILLION.
WELL, TONIGHT, YOU'RE GOING TO
MEET A WOMAN WHO LIVED THAT ONE
IN 100 TRILLION SHOT AND ABC'S
METEOROLOGIST GINGER ZEE TAKES
US TO SEE HER.
>> WHAT IS THAT?
>> Reporter: I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THAT IS.
AMERICA, MEET NANCY.
>> NANCY E.
>> Reporter: AT 94 YEARS OLD,
SHE CAN TELL A STORY THAT
PERHAPS NO ONE ELSE IN THE WORLD
CAN TELL.
SHE HAS LOST HER HOME TO A
TORNADO --
TWICE.
BOTH RIGHT HERE ON THIS SAME
SPOT.
THIS IS NOT YOUR FIRST TIME.
>> NO, I WAS HERE IN '99.
>> Reporter: HERE IN 1999.
THAT INFAMOUS DAY, MAY 3rd, WHEN
THE FASTEST WINDS EVER RECORDED
INSIDE A TORNADO, TOPPED 300
MILES PER HOUR.
TRAMPLING AN 18-MILE PATH
THROUGH MOORE.
THAT STUNNING RESEMBLANCE TO
MONDAY'S PATH.
AND RIGHT THERE, WHERE THE
DEADLY PATHS CROSS --
MISS DAVIS'S HOUSE.
THIS WAS NANCY'S HOUSE BEFORE.
THIS IS IT NOW.
THIS IS THE CELLAR WHERE THEY
RODE IT OUT AND SURVIVED.
TWICE.
TWO TIMES IN THAT CELLAR.
DO YOU KNOW ANYONE ELSE WHO HAS
-- WAS HIT A SECOND TIME?
OR ARE YOU THE ONLY ONE?
>> I'M THE ONLY ONE.
>> Reporter: SHE THINKS SHE IS
THE ONLY ONE.
AND, ACCORDING TO THAT STUDY,
SHE IS ONE IN 100 TRILLION,
THOSE LONG ODDS YOUR HOME GETS
HIT BY AN EF-4 TORNADO TWICE.
>> I'M SO THANKFUL GOD WAS WITH
ME.
>> Reporter: BOTH TIMES.
THE WOMAN WITH A ONE IN A
MILLION CHARM --
>> YOU'RE STILL TAKING THAT
PICTURE.
I KNOW HE IS AND I'M GRINNING.
>> Reporter: GRINNING DESPITE
HER ONE IN 100 TRILLION ODDS.
NANCY TELLS US THAT SHE DOES
WANT TO REBUILD AGAIN, DESPITE
ALL OF THAT.
AND OKLAHOMANS KNOW IN GENERAL,
INCLUDING THE PEOPLE IN TORNADO
ALLEY, AS WE KNOW IT, THEY GOT A
BETTER SHOT THAN MOST OF THE
WORLD AT SEEING TORNADOES.
THERE'S A REASON.
IT'S THE GEOGRAPHY.
WATCH THIS.
AS MOISTURE FROM THE GULF OF
MEXICO PUSHES UP, YOU HAVE
COOLER, DRIER AIR FROM THE WEST
ALOFT.
THOSE TWO INGREDIENTS MIX
TOGETHER AND OFTEN AND,
UNFORTUNATELY, MAKE FOR
DEVASTATION.
DIANE?
>> GINGER, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> COMING UP NEXT, WE KNOW HOW
HARD PEOPLE TRY TO SAVE THEIR
PETS AS WINDS ROAR AROUND THEM.
WELL, NEXT, EXTRAORDINARY
EFFORTS TO BRING THOSE PETS HOME
TOO.
I'M PHYLLIS,
AND I HAVE DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
WHEN I FIRST FELT
THE DIABETIC NERVE PAIN,
OF COURSE,
I HAD NO IDEA WHAT IT WAS.
I FELT LIKE
MY FEET WERE GOING TO SLEEP.
IT PROGRESSED FROM THERE
TO BURNING
LIKE I WAS WALKING ON HOT COALS
TO LIKE A THOUSAND BEES
THAT WERE JUST STINGING MY FEET.
I HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE FOUND LYRICA FOR ME.
[ Female Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYE SIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN, AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS, AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO'VE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
HAVING LESS PAIN...
IT'S A WONDERFUL FEELING.
[ Female Announcer ] ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
TO HEAR MORE OF PHYLLIS'S
STORY, VISIT LYRICA.COM.
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
♪
>>> AND NOW I WANT TO SHOW YOU A
REUNION PICTURE, A LITTLE BOY,
AND YOU CAN SEE IT IN HIS FACE,
REUNITED WITH THE SMALLEST
MEMBER OF HIS FAMILY, HIS DOG
RIPPY.
AND RIGHT NOW ACROSS MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, THERE ARE SO MANY
MEASURES UNDER WAY TO RETURN
EVERY FAMILY PET, EVERY DOG,
EVERY CAT, EVERY RABBIT, AND
EVEN HORSE TO VERY WORRIED
OWNERS.
ALL ACROSS THE TORNADO ZONE, JOY
AT THE RECOVERY OF THE SMALLEST
MEMBERS OF A FAMILY.
ANIMAL SURVIVORS RIGHT THERE
WITH THEIR OWNERS THROUGHOUT THE
STORM.
>> I HELD MY DOG CLOSE TO ME AND
JUST WAITED TO SEE WHAT WAS
GOING TO HAPPEN.
>> THIS LITTLE BLACK DOG STOOD
GUARD OVER ITS OWNER WHO DIED IN
THE STORM.
A SHERIFF'S DEPUTY PLANS TO
ADOPT IT, GIVE IT A HOME.
THE INTERNET IS SPREADING
ANIMALS STORIES AND THE NEED FOR
HELP.
ON THE ORR FAMILY FARM'S
FACEBOOK PAGE, THEY SHOW THEIR
BARN BEFORE AND THEN AFTER THE
STORM.
LANDO HEIGHTS SURVIVED IN A
HORSE STALL AT THE FARM AND
TELLS KFOR, THERE WERE AT LEAST
80 HORSES, HE WAS WORRIED.
>> THESE HORSES ARE HOW WE
SURVIVE.
WE MIGHT HAVE ONE HORSE LEFT OUT
OF ALL OF THEM.
>> BUT TONIGHT WE HAVE LEARNED
34 HORSES SURVIVED.
SO MANY ANIMALS SEPARATED FROM
THEIR OWNERS.
AND TONIGHT THE RESCUE EFFORT IS
UNDER WAY TO FIND AND CARE FOR
THESE SURVIVORS TOO.
MANY WITH INJURIES.
ON THE WEB, SHELTERS POSTED
PHOTOS OF RESCUED PETS.
DOGS, RABBITS, EVEN A PARROT.
HELPING LINK ANIMALS TO OWNERS.
THE PUP TRIXIE BACK WITH HER
FAMILY AGAIN TONIGHT.
>>> AND COMING UP NEXT HERE, HOW
THE STAR SPANGLED BANNER STILL
WAVES IN OKLAHOMA TONIGHT.
BEFORE COPD...
I TOOK MY SON FISHING
EVERY YEAR.
WE HAD A GREAT SPOT,
NOT EASY TO FIND, BUT WORTH IT.
BUT WITH COPD
MAKING IT HARD TO BREATHE,
I THOUGHT
THOSE DAYS MIGHT BE OVER.
SO MY DOCTOR
PRESCRIBED SYMBICORT.
IT HELPS SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE
MY LUNG FUNCTION
STARTING WITHIN FIVE MINUTES.
SYMBICORT DOESN'T REPLACE
A RESCUE INHALER
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS.
WITH SYMBICORT,
TODAY I'M BREATHING BETTER.
AND THAT MEANS...FISH ON!
SYMBICORT IS FOR COPD
INCLUDING CHRONIC BRONCHITIS
AND EMPHYSEMA.
IT SHOULD NOT BE TAKEN
MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
SYMBICORT MAY INCREASE YOUR RISK
OF LUNG INFECTIONS,
OSTEOPOROSIS,
AND SOME EYE PROBLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HEART CONDITION
OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING IT.
WITH COPD, I THOUGHT
I'D MISS OUR FAMILY TRADITION.
NOW SYMBICORT SIGNIFICANTLY
IMPROVES MY LUNG FUNCTION,
STARTING WITHIN 5 MINUTES.
AND THAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE
IN MY BREATHING.
TODAY, WE'RE READY
FOR WHATEVER SWIMS OUR WAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT SYMBICORT.
I GOT MY FIRST
PRESCRIPTION FREE.
CALL OR CLICK
TO LEARN MORE.
[ Male Announcer ] IF YOU CAN'T
AFFORD YOUR MEDICATION,
ASTRAZENECA
MAY BE ABLE TO HELP.
TO TAKE A CENTRUM SILVER
MULTIVITAMIN EVERY DAY.
I TOLD HIM, SURE.
CAN'T HURT, RIGHT?
AND NOW TODAY,
I SEE THIS IN THE NEWS.
ONCE AGAIN, CENTRUM SILVER
WAS CHOSEN BY RESEARCHERS
FOR ANOTHER LANDMARK STUDY.
THIS TIME LOOKING AT EYE HEALTH.
MY DOCTOR!
HE KNOWS HIS STUFF.
[ Male Announcer ] CENTRUM.
THE MOST STUDIED.
THE MOST RECOMMENDED.
AND THE MOST PREFERRED
MULTIVITAMIN BRAND.
THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
♪
>>> AND WE WILL BE STAYING ON
THE STORY OUT OF MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, COVERING IN REALTIME
ON ABCNEWS.COM.
WE THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
FOR SOME OF YOU, WE'LL HAVE MORE
OF "WORLD NEWS" COMING UP.
FOR THE REST, A SPECIAL EDITION
OF "NIGHTLINE" LATER.
WE LEAVE YOU NOW WITH A SYMBOL
OF RESILIENCE.
THE AMERICAN FLAG RISING IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, TONIGHT.
FOR THOSE OF YOU WHO ARE LEAVING
US, A GOODNIGHT.
>>> BREAKING NEWS A GRASS FIRE
SPREADS INTO A SOUTH BAY
NEIGHBORHOOD.
WE'RE OVER IT, LIFE RESCUES
CREWS FOUND FOR OKLAHOMA
TONIGHT WE'RE LIVE WITH LATEST
DAMAGE ESTIMATES AND THE STORM.
>> AND THAT IS THE REACTION
FROM SANTA CLAIREA. SUPER BOWL
50 WILL BE PLAYED.
TONIGHT THE ECONOMIC PROMISE
OF LANDING THE BIG GAME.
>> AND APPLE EXECUTIVE SKPTZ
WAY THE COMPANY FOUND TO AVOID
PAYING TAXES.
RIGHT NOW, CREWS HAVE GAINED
GROUND ON A BRUSH FIRE
THREATENING A NEIGHBORHOOD
NEAR THE RANCH GOLF CLUB ROAD.
>> TAKE A LOOK AT FLAMES FROM
JUST MINUTES AGO.
WE HAVE IMAGES THAT SHOW YOU
JUST HOW CLOSE THEY ARE
PUSHING TOWARDS THEEGS HOUSES
ON THE HILL ABOVE.
THIS FIRE GROWING QUICKLY
FLAMES MOVED UP THE HILL
GETTING SO CLOSE TO HOMES BUT
THEN, CAL FIRE BEGAN THIS
AERIAL ASSAULT ON THE FIRE.
>> SKY 7 OVER THE SCENE.
YOU CAN SEE CREWS MADE FAST
WORK OF THE FLAMES.
WE'LL CONTINUE TO MONITOR THIS
SITUATION YOU CAN GET UPDATES
ON TWITTER ON ABC 7 NEWS BAY
AREA.
>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
OTHER TOP STORY TONIGHT.
>> THIS IS HERE WHERE
FIREPLACE IS.
>> IT'S JUST THE AREA.
>> THIS IS THE TWISTER THAT
DESTROYED THE HOME.
OFFICIALS ARE CONFIDENT THAT
EVERYONE HAS BEEN ACCOUNTED
FOR.
OFFICIALS IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA
SAY THEY DON'T NEED HELP BUT
TODAY, GOVERNOR BROWN SENT SIX
SEARCH AND RESCUE SPECIALISTS
TO OKLAHOMA INCLUDING ONE FROM
OAKLAND.
AFTER CONDUGTING A SEARCH
TODAY, OFFICIALS PUT THE DEATH
TOLL AT 24 INCLUDING NINE
CHILDREN, SEVEN DIED AT PLAZA
TOWERS SCHOOL.
237 PEOPLE HAVE