MICHAEL FREE STUFF FINNEY, WE'LL
SEE YOU SOON.
>> BYE-BYE.
>>> TONIGHT, PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
WARNING TO THE FBI DIRECTOR WHO
HE JUST FIRED.
SAYING JAMES COMEY, BETTER HOPE
THAT THERE ARE NO TAPES.
AFTER THE PRESIDENT SAYS THEY
HAD THREE CONVERSATIONS CLEARING
HIM.
IS THAT A THREAT TO THE MAN WHO
WAS HEADING THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION?
AND THE WHITE HOUSE IS ASKED,
ARE CONVERSATIONS BEING
RECORDED?
THEIR ANSWER.
>>> ALSO BREAKING, THE POLICE
CHIEF SHOT AND KILLED.
TWO NURSING HOME EMPLOYEES ALSO
DEAD.
RESIDENTS RACED TO SAFETY.
>>> THE MOTHER'S DAY STORM, THE
NOR'EASTER MOVING UP THE COAST
TONIGHT.
>>> AND THE NEW SURVEILLANCE
FROM INSIDE THE SCHOOL.
THE MOTHER WHO WAS TOLD HER
8-YEAR-OLD BOY FAINTED.
DOES THE VIDEO TELL A DIFFERENT
STORY?
AND HOW LONG WAS HE LEFT THERE,
DAYS LATER, TAKING HIS OWN LIFE.
>>> AND THE DEADLY COLLISION
WITH A BUS.
TRAFFIC HALTED FOR MILES.
>>> AND, BREAKING NOW, THE
MASSIVE, FAST-MOVING U.S. CYBER
ATTACK.
U.S. COMPANIES SHUTTING DOWN
THEIR COMPUTERS.
BRIAN ROSS STANDING BY.
>>> GOOD EVENING, IT'S GREAT TO
HAVE YOU WITH US ON A FRIDAY
NIGHT.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S MESSAGE FOR FIRED FBI
DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETING THAT
JAMES COMEY BETTER HOPE THERE
ARE NO TAPES OF WHAT THEY SAID.
THE PRESIDENT SAYING COMEY TOLD
HIM HE'S NOT UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
BUT TONIGHT, MAJOR NEW
QUESTIONS.
IS THE WHITE HOUSE RECORDING
CONVERSATIONS?
ARE THERE TAPES?
AND IS THE PRESIDENT THREATENING
THE MAN WHO WAS LEADING THE
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION?
TONIGHT, HOW THE WHITE HOUSE
ANSWERS.
JONATHAN KARL LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: HE'S ALREADY FIRED
HIM.
AND TODAY, PRESIDENT TRUMP AIMED
AN APPARENT THREAT AT FORMER FBI
DIRECTOR, JAMES COMEY.
TWEETING, COMEY HAD BETTER HOPE
THERE ARE NO TAPES BEFORE HE
STARTS LEAKING TO THE PRESS.
WAIT A MINUTE, TAPES?
IS PRESIDENT TRUMP TAPING HIS
WHITE HOUSE CONVERSATIONS?
TODAY AFTER THE TWEET, A
NONDENIAL.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE IDEA THAT YOU
SAID THERE MIGHT BE TAPE
RECORDINGS?
>> THAT, I CAN'T TALK ABOUT.
I WON'T TALK ABOUT THAT.
ALL I WANT IS FOR COMEY TO BE
HONEST, AND I HOPE HE WILL BE.
AND I'M SURE HE WILL BE, I HOPE.
>> Reporter: A RECORDING WOULD
REVEAL WHETHER COMEY SAID WHAT
THE PRESIDENT CLAIMS HE SAID
ABOUT THE RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
>> I SAID, IF IT'S POSSIBLE,
WOULD YOU LET ME KNOW, AM I
UNDER INVESTIGATION?
HE SAID, YOU ARE NOT UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
>> Reporter: TODAY, THE WHITE
HOUSE WAS PRESSED ON WHETHER THE
PRESIDENT WAS THREATENING COMEY.
AND WHETHER ANY RECORDINGS
ACTUALLY EXIST.
>> DID PRESIDENT TRUMP RECORD
HIS CONVERSATIONS WITH COMEY?
>> I'VE TALKED TO THE PRESIDENT.
THE PRESIDENT HAS NOTHING
FURTHER TO ADD ON THAT.
>> ARE THERE RECORDING DEVICES
IN THE OVAL OFFICE OR RESIDENCE?
>> I HAVE NOTHING FURTHER TO
ADD.
>> DOES HE THINK IT'S
APPROPRIATE TO THREATEN SOMEONE
LIKE MR. COMEY NOT TO SPEAK?
>> THAT'S NOT A THREAT.
HE SIMPLY STATED A FACT.
THE TWEET SPEAKS FOR ITSELF.
I'M MOVING ON.
>> Reporter: SEAN SPICER REFUSED
TO CONFIRM OR DENY WHETHER OR
NOT THE WHITE HOUSE IS BUGGED.
SEAN, DID YOU ASK THE PRESIDENT
IF HE'S INSTALLED LISTENING
DEVICES IN THE WHITE HOUSE?
DID YOU ASK THE PRESIDENT IF HE
INSTALLED LISTENING DEVICES?
SECRET WHITE HOUSE RECORDINGS
ARE NOT UNPRECEDENTED.
KENNEDY AND LBG SECRETLY TAPED
THEIR OVAL OFFICE MEETINGS.
AND SO DID RICHARD NIXON.
NIXON'S TAPES HELPED BRING DOWN
HIS PRESIDENCY, AND NO PRESIDENT
SINCE HAS ACKNOWLEDGED
INSTALLING LISTENING DEVICES IN
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> JON, THE QUESTION TONIGHT IS,
IS THIS WHITE HOUSE RECORDING
CONVERSATIONS, OR WERE THOSE
JUST WORDS IN A TWEET?
SEAN SPICER REFUSING TO SAY
WHETHER THEY WERE RECORDING
PEOPLE?
>> Reporter: I THOUGHT IT WAS
STRIKING THAT HE DID NOT KNOCK
DOWN OR DENY THAT THE WHITE
HOUSE AND OVAL OFFICE IS BUGGED.
AND NOW, TWO TOP DEMOCRATS
IN THE HOUSE SAYING THEY WANT TO
SEE ANY TAPES RELATED TO THE
COMEY FIRING.
AND THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE
SENATE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE,
WHICH IS LEADING THE
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIA, TELLS
ABC NEWS, IF THERE ARE TAPES,
THEY SHOULD BE PRESERVED AND
HANDED OVER.
>> JON, THANK YOU.
>>> THIS EVENING, JAMES COMEY'S
SIDE OF THE STORY BEGINNING TO
EMERGE.
SOURCES CLOSE TO HIM SAYING HE'S
FURIOUS.
AND WHEN IT COMES TO THE DINNER
BETWEEN THE TWO, COMEY'S CAMP
SAYING THE PRESIDENT ASKED HIM
TO BE LOYAL TO THE PRESIDENT.
AND TONIGHT, ONE KEY PLAYER
SAYING COMEY SAID HE WAS
UNCOMFORTABLE GOING INTO THE
DINNER.
PIERRE THOMAS AGAIN TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, TWO MEN.
TWO DRAMATICALLY DIFFERENT
STORIES.
ABC NEWS HAS LEARNED SOURCES IN
FORMER FBI DIRECTOR JAMES
COMEY'S CIRCLE SAY, AT THAT
JANUARY DINNER, PRESIDENT TRUMP
ASKED COMEY MORE THAN ONCE
WHETHER HE WOULD BE LOYAL TO
HIM.
OUR SOURCES SAY COMEY ONLY
PROMISED TO BE HONEST.
BUT TODAY, THE PRESIDENT FLATLY
DENIED THAT EVER HAPPENED.
>> DID YOU ASK THAT QUESTION?
>> NO, I DIDN'T.
BUT I DON'T THINK IT WOULD BE A
BE A BAD QUESTION TO ASK.
I THINK LOYALTY TO THE COUNTRY,
TO THE UNITED STATES, IS
IMPORTANT.
IT DEPENDS ON HOW YOU DEFINE
LOYALTY.
NUMBER ONE, NUMBER TWO, I DON'T
KNOW HOW THAT GOT THERE.
BECAUSE I DIDN'T ASK THAT
QUESTION.
>> Reporter: MULTIPLE SOURCES
ALSO TELL ABC NEWS THEY DO NOT
BELIEVE COMEY TOLD THE PRESIDENT
HE WAS NOT UNDER INVESTIGATION,
AS TRUMP CLAIMED.
>> HE WANTED TO STAY ON AS FBI
HEAD, AND I SAID I WOULD
CONSIDER IT.
WE'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENS.
AND WE HAD A NICE DINNER.
AT THAT TIME, HE TOLD ME YOU ARE
NOT UNDER INVESTIGATION, WHICH I
KNEW ANYWAY.
>> Reporter: FORMER DIRECTOR
OF NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE JAMES
CLAPPER MET COMEY ON THE DAY OF
THE DINNER, AND SAID COMEY WAS
WORRIED HOW IT WOULD APPEAR.
>> HE MENTIONED HE HAD BEEN
INVITED TO THE WHITE HOUSE TO
HAVE DINNER WITH THE PRESIDENT.
AND HE WAS UNEASY WITH THAT.
>> Reporter: TRUMP CALLED COMEY
A SHOWBOATER.
ALL OF THIS GALVANIZING MANY IN
THE FBI RANK AND FILE.
WHO BELIEVE COMEY HAS BEEN
TREATED SHABBILY.
AS FOR A REPLACEMENT, THE SEARCH
BEGINS TOMORROW.
AT LEAST FOUR CANDIDATES HAVE
BEEN INTERVIEWED.
>> AND WE'RE LEARNING COMEY WILL
NOT TESTIFY ON THE HILL NEXT
WEEK?
DESPITE THE INVITATION TO SPEAK
BEHIND CLOSED DOORS?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT, HE'S
DECLINED TO APPEAR ON TUESDAY.
BUT THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE
SENATE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
SAYS HE BELIEVES COMEY WILL
APPEAR AT THE RIGHT TIME AND
PLACE TO TELL HIS SIDE OF THE
STORY.
DAVID?
>> THAT WE WILL HEAR FROM HIM AT
SOME POINT.
PIERRE, THANK YOU AS WELL.
>>> AND WE'RE ALSO FOLLOWING A
DEADLY ATTACK AT A NURSING HOME
IN OHIO.
A POLICE CHIEF AND TWO WORKERS
DEAD.
RESIDENTS RACED TO SAFETY.
HERE'S EVA PILGRIM.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, POLICE IN
OHIO ARE INVESTIGATING WHY THIS
GUNMAN TOOK AIM IN THIS SMALL
VILLAGE.
>> THERE'S BEEN A SHOOTING IN
THE NURSING HOME.
>> IS THIS AN ACTIVE SHOOTER
EVENT?
>> THAT'S AFFIRMATIVE.
>> Reporter: JUST BEFORE 8:00
A.M., THE SUSPECT OPENING FIRE.
>> HE APPARENTLY WAS IN A VERY
SMALL WOODS BACK THERE.
AND ACTUALLY TOOK TWO PASSERSBY
AS HOSTAGE.
>> Reporter: THE HOSTAGES
GETTING AWAY.
BUT THE POLICE CHIEF MOVING IN.
HE HAD THE SHOOTER IN SIGHT.
>> WE HAVE A LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICER DOWN.
>> Reporter: DEPUTIES FINDING
THE BODY OF THE POLICE CHIEF, A
FATHER OF SIX, WITH A SEVENTH ON
THE WAY.
HE HAD ONLY BEEN ON THE JOB FOR
ABOUT THREE WEEKS.
INSIDE THE NURSING HOME, THE
BODIES OF TWO EMPLOYEES AND THE
GUNMAN.
TONIGHT, A SOLEMN PROCESSION FOR
THE POLICE CHIEF.
THE RESIDENTS ARE ALL OKAY.
TONIGHT, INVESTIGATORS TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT THE MOTIVE OF THE
SHOOTING.
DAVID?
>> EVA, THANKS.
>>> NEXT, THE MASSIVE MOTHER'S
DAY STORM.
A NOR'EASTER SET TO HIT.
THE SAME SYSTEM PRODUCING TWO
CONFIRMED TORNADOES NEAR BATON
ROUGE.
AND POWERFUL STORMS IN NORTH
CAROLINA.
THOUSANDS WITHOUT POWER.
OVER THE NEXT 48 HOURS, THE
NOR'EASTER MOVING UP THE COAST.
WE HAVE THE TRACK OF IT, WHEN IT
WILL HIT, AND WHERE.
STEVE OSUNSAMI TONIGHT.
>> LOOK AT THAT!
>> Reporter: FAMILIES IN AND
AROUND BATON ROUGE TONIGHT ARE
TRYING TO GET THE LIGHTS TURNED
BACK ON AFTER A TORNADO WITH
WIND SPEEDS OF UP TO 90 MILES AN
HOUR TORE THROUGH THE MORNING
RUSH HOUR.
>> OH, JEEZ.
>> Reporter: THE STORM CAUGHT
PEOPLE BY SURPRISE.
>> WENT VIRTUALLY UNDETECTED BY
RADAR.
AND WAS A STORM THAT DID NOT
HAVE A WARNING.
>> Reporter: HIGH WINDS TOSSED
CARS NEAR THIS GAS STATION.
>> LOOK AT THESE CARS FLIPPED
OVER.
>> Reporter: ONE PERSON HAD TO
BE HOSPITALIZED.
ANOTHER TORNADO HIT FURTHER
SOUTH.
>> THERE'S A TRAMPOLINE.
HANGING IN THE TREE THERE, BLEW
FROM TWO HOUSES OVER.
>> Reporter: IN BEACH CITY,
TEXAS, A LIGHTNING STRIKE SET
THESE CRUDE OIL TANKS ON FIRE.
MORE THAN 100 FAMILIES NEARBY
HAD TO BE FORCED FROM THEIR
HOMES.
THOUSANDS LOST POWER IN RALEIGH
WHEN HIGH WINDS BLEW TREES
THURSDAY NIGHT.
>> UNBELIEVABLE THAT EITHER ONE
WAS NOT HERE, IS A MIRACLE.
>> Reporter: THIS POWERFUL STORM
SYSTEM IS NOW MOVING EAST.
AND AT A MINIMUM, COULD BRING
HEAVY RAINS.
>> STEVE, THANK YOU.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO ROB MARCIANO,
TRACKING IT ALL FOR US.
HEY, ROB.
>> Reporter: WE CAN ALREADY SEE
THE NORTHERN FRINGE OF THE
STORM, THE CLOUDS IN NEW YORK
LOWERING.
AS THE RAIN SHIELD ADVANCES
NORTH.
IT'S ALREADY IN THE MIDATLANTIC,
AND THE SEVERE STORMS IN NEW
ORLEANS TO TALLAHASSEE.
A ROUGH EVENING AHEAD.
THE RAIN WILL BE ROUGH IN D.C.
TOMORROW MORNING.
ALREADY RAINING IN NEW YORK.
IN CHESAPEAKE BAY, YOU'LL SEE
FLOODING.
TOMORROW, COMING DOWN IN NEW
YORK AND HARTFORD.
BOSTON GETS IT ON SUNDAY, AND
WRAPAROUND SHOWERS THROUGH
MOTHER'S DAY.
MOMS ACROSS THE NORTHEAST,
PROVING JUST HOW TOUGH THEY CAN
BE.
DAVID?
>> STAY SAFE ON THE ROADS THIS
WEEKEND.
ROB, THANK YOU.
>>> WE MOVE ON.
POLICE IN CINCINNATI ARE
REOPENING THE INVESTIGATION INTO
THE DEATH OF AN 8-YEAR-OLD BOY.
THE BOY HAD KILLED HIMSELF, BUT
TONIGHT THERE ARE MAJOR
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED
BEFORE THAT.
DID HE REALLY FAINT AT SCHOOL,
OR WAS HE BULLIED?
HERE'S ALEX PEREZ WITH NEW
SURVEILLANCE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, CINCINNATI
PUBLIC SCHOOLS RELEASING THIS
DISTURBING VIDEO, SHOWING
SUSPECTED BULLYING DAYS BEFORE
AN 8-YEAR-OLD TOOK HIS OWN LIFE.
>> I WAS EXTREMELY SHOCKED TO
FIND OUT THAT IT HAD GOTTEN TO
THIS POINT.
>> Reporter: CAMERAS CAPTURING
THE MOMENT IN JANUARY, WHEN THE
BOY WALKS INTO THE BATHROOM,
SHAKES HANDS WITH ANOTHER
STUDENT, AND THEN APPEARS TO BE
YANKED TO THE FLOOR.
THE OTHER BOY IS SEEN THROWING
HIS ARMS UP.
LITTLE GABE LAYS THERE,
MOTIONLESS, AT LEAST TEN
STUDENTS WALKING PAST.
AFTER THREE MINUTES AND 30
SECONDS, THREE STUDENTS APPEAR
TO TAUNT AND KICK HIM.
THEN, AFTER FOUR MINUTES AND 40
SECONDS, ADULT HELP FINALLY
ARRIVES.
TWO DAYS LATER, THE 8-YEAR-OLD
COMMITTED SUICIDE.
HIS MOTHER SAYS SHE WAS ONLY
TOLD GABE HAD FAINTED, BUT NEVER
ABOUT THE ALLEGED INCIDENT.
>> IF THE SCHOOL HAD TOLD MOM,
YOUR SON WAS ASSAULTED, SHE
WOULD HAVE IMMEDIATELY TAKEN HIM
TO THE HOSPITAL.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES FIRST
SUSPECTED BULLYING AFTER A
DETECTIVE OBTAINED THE VIDEO
FIVE DAYS AFTER THE SUICIDE.
IN A STATEMENT TODAY, THE SCHOOL
SAYS, OUR HEARTS ARE BROKEN WITH
THE LOSS OF THIS CHILD, AND IT'S
OUR FIRM POSITION THAT THE
ALLEGATIONS IN THE MEDIA ARE NOT
SUPPORTED BY THE VIDEO.
POLICE HAVE NOT FILED CHARGES.
THE CORONER'S OFFICE PLANS TO
RE-EXAMINE THE CIRCUMSTANCES
SURROUNDING THE BOY'S DEATH.
DAVID?
>> ALEX, THANK YOU.
>>> AND NEXT TONIGHT HERE, A
DRAMATIC POLICY SHIFT ON CRIME
IN THIS COUNTRY.
ATTORNEY GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS
DIRECTING FEDERAL PROSECUTORS TO
PURSUE THE MOST SERIOUS CHARGES
POSSIBLE AGAINST SUSPECTS.
IT REVERSES OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
POLICY THAT ENCOURAGED
PROSECUTORS TO CONSIDER
INDIVIDUAL CIRCUMSTANCES
IN AN EFFORT TO REDUCE PRISON
POPULATIONS.
>>> NEXT HERE TONIGHT TO A MAJOR
GLOBAL HEADLINE UNFOLDING AS
WE'RE ON THE AIR TONIGHT.
A MASSIVE CYBER ATTACK UNDER WAY
AT THIS HOUR.
74 COUNTRIES, AND RIGHT HERE IN
THE U.S.
EVEN HOSPITALS AMONG THEIR
TARGETS, COMPUTERS FROZEN,
SURGERIES HALTED.
AND U.S. COMPANIES ARE TAKING
ACTION.
HERE'S BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: AS THE THREAT
UNFOLDS TONIGHT, THE FIRST U.S.
COMPANY TO ADMIT BEING TARGETED
IS FEDEX.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF ATTACKS
AROUND THE WORLD WERE ANNOUNCED
WITH THIS MESSAGE.
WHOOPS, YOUR IMPORTANT FILES ARE
ENCRYPTED.
WITH A FOLLOW-UP MESSAGE, PAY
YOUR RANSOM OR LOSE YOUR FILES.
>> THE REASON THIS IS HITTING SO
MANY COMPUTERS AT ONCE, THEY
DISCOVERED A VULNERABILITY IN
THE MOST POPULAR OPERATING
SYSTEM IN THE WORLD, IN
MICROSOFT WINDOWS, AND THEY'RE
TAKING ADVANTAGE OF IT.
>> Reporter: IT APPEARS TO BE
THE SINGLE BIGGEST RANSOMWARE
ATTACK IN THE HISTORY OF THE
INTERNET.
>> IT'S AN INTERNATIONAL ATTACK,
AND A NUMBER OF COUNTRIES AND
ORGANIZATIONS HAVE BEEN
AFFECTED.
>> Reporter: HITTING HARD IN
BRITAIN, LOCKING UP THE
COMPUTERS OF HOSPITALS.
SOME CANCELLING SURGERIES.
>> AN ANNOUNCEMENT CAME THAT ALL
THE COMPUTERS WOULD BE DOWN
UNTIL AT LEAST MONDAY.
>> Reporter: AND TONIGHT, WITH A
LACK OF ACCESS TO PATIENT
RECORDS, DOCTORS FEAR LIVES
COULD BE AT RISK.
>> BRIAN, SOURCES TELLING YOU
OFFICIALS IN THE U.S. ARE
SCRAMBLING TO CONTAIN THIS?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
OFFICIALS AT THE HIGHEST LEVELS
MET LATE TODAY TO SEE WHAT THEY
CAN DO TO STOP IT.
AND THE IRONY IS, THE ATTACKS
ARE BASED IN PART ON TOOLS
DEVELOPED BY U.S.
INTELLIGENCE TO PENETRATE
ENEMIES, AND NOW THEY ARE BEING
TURNED AGAINST US.
>> BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> A VERY CLOSE ENCOUNTER
BETWEEN U.S. AND RUSSIAN
MILITARY PLANES.
THE U.S. NAVY REPORTING THEY
CAME WITHIN 20 FEET OF EACH
OTHER OVER THE BLACK SEA.
AN AMERICAN PLANE IN
INTERNATIONAL AIRSPACE, WHEN THE
RUSSIAN JET CAME ALONGSIDE IT.
FLYING WINGTIP TO WINGTIP UNTIL
THE U.S. PLANE CHANGED COURSE.
>>> THERE'S STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS FRIDAY.
THE RUSH HOUR COLLISION, A
SHERIFF'S DEPUTY KILLED, TRAFFIC
BACKED UP FOR MILES.
>>> THE HUNT FOR AN ARSON
SUSPECT.
AT LEAST SIX CARS SET ABLAZE.
EVEN A HOME.
>>> AND THE CONSUMER ALERT.
JUST IN TIME FOR MOTHER'S DAY.
ONE THING TO WATCH OUT FOR THIS
MOTHER'S DAY WEEKEND, ESPECIALLY
IF YOU'RE ON FACEBOOK.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
ng,
discomfort,
cramps, and gas.
(Sigh)
Try ProNourish drink,
a unique nutritional drink
that's high in protein
and fiber.
And ProNourish has no gluten
or high fructose corn syrup,
and it's low
in FODMAP ingredients
that may trigger
digestive sensitivities.
It's your delicious
anytime, anywhere
mini-meal or snack.
ProNourish.
Nutrition you can
feel good about.
could be preventedrrent
with the right steps.
And take it from me,
every step counts.
A Bayer aspirin regimen
is one of those steps
in helping prevent
another stroke.
Be sure to talk
to your doctor
before you begin
an aspirin regimen.
If you have moderate
to severe plaque psoriasis,
isn't it time
to let the real you
shine through?
Introducing Otezla, apremilast.
Otezla is not an injection
or a cream.
It's a pill that treats
plaque psoriasis differently.
Some people who took Otezla
saw 75% clearer skin
after 4 months.
And Otezla's
prescribing information
has no requirement for
routine lab monitoring.
Don't take Otezla
if you are allergic
to any of its ingredients.
Otezla may increase
the risk of depression.
Tell your doctor
if you have a history
of depression
or suicidal thoughts,
or if these feelings develop.
Some people taking Otezla
reported weight loss.
Your doctor should
monitor your weight
and may stop treatment.
Side effects
may include
diarrhea, nausea,
upper respiratory
tract infection,
and headache.
Tell your doctor
about all the
medicines you take,
and if you're pregnant
or planning to be.
Ask your dermatologist
about Otezla today.
Otezla.
Show more of you.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, YOUR MONEY.
AND A CONSUMER ALERT.
AMERICANS SPENDING AN ESTIMATED
$24 BILLION ON MOTHER'S DAY
GIFTS.
BUT A NEW WARNING ABOUT ONLINE
SCAMS DISGUISED AS DEALS.
HERE'S LINZIE JANIS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, WHEN
SHOPPING FOR MOTHER'S DAY,
BEWARE OF FAKE COUPONS MAKING
THE ROUNDS ON SOCIAL MEDIA.
BED BATH AND BEYOND SAYS THIS
OFFER FOR $75 OFF MAY LOOK LIKE
THEIRS, BUT IT'S NOT.
THE COMPANY WRITING ON FACEBOOK,
"WE ALL KNOW SOME THINGS ARE TOO
GOOD TO BE TRUE!"
AND LOWE'S CALLING THIS OFFER
FOR $50 OFF AT ITS STORES "A
SCAM."
CYBER CRIMINALS TRYING TO STEAL
YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.
>> WHERE YOU LIVE, YOUR CREDIT
CARD INFORMATION.
AND THEY'RE GOING TO LOOK TO
SELL IT TO RESELLERS OR STEAL
YOUR IDENTITY.
>> Reporter: THE FAKE COUPONS
WILL TYPICALLY POP UP IN YOUR
FACEBOOK FEED, ASKING YOU TO
LIKE OR SHARE WITH FRIENDS.
DO THAT AND YOU'LL BE TAKEN TO A
PHONY WEBSITE WHERE YOU'LL BE
ASKED TO FILL OUT A SHORT SURVEY
BEFORE COLLECTING THE COUPON.
>> MOST PLACES LOOKING TO DO A
TRANSACTION DON'T NEED YOUR
BIRTHDAY OR SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBER.
>> Reporter: IF YOU SUSPECT A
COUPON IS FAKE, EXPERTS SAY THE
BEST THING TO DO IS GO TO THE
RETAILER'S OFFICIAL WEBSITE AND
LOOK FOR THE OFFER THERE.
>> LINZIE, THANKS.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THAT
DEADLY CRASH.
TRAFFIC HALTED FOR MILES.
THE OFF-DUTY DEPUTY KILLED WHEN
A BUS COLLIDED WITH HIS CAR.
>>> AND WE HAVE A MASSIVE RECALL
TONIGHT.
MORE THAN 1 MILLION POPULAR
PICKUPS INVOLVED.
WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT.
on my long-term control
medicine.
I talked to my doctor and
found a missing piece
in my asthma treatment with
BREO.
Once-daily BREO prevents asthma
symptoms.
BREO is for adults
with asthma not well controlled
on a long-term asthma control
medicine,
like an inhaled corticosteroid.
BREO won't replace a rescue
inhaler
for sudden breathing problems.
BREO is specifically designed
to open up airways
to improve breathing for a full
24 hours.
BREO contains a type of medicine
that increases the risk of death
from asthma problems
and may increase the risk
of hospitalization
in children and adolescents.
BREO is not for people whose
asthma is well controlled on a
long-term asthma control
medicine,
like an inhaled corticosteroid.
Once your asthma is well
controlled,
your doctor will decide if you
can stop BREO and prescribe a
different asthma control
medicine,
like an inhaled corticosteroid.
Do not take BREO more than
prescribed.
See your doctor if your asthma
does not improve or gets worse.
Ask your doctor
if 24-hour BREO
could be a missing
piece for you.
Learn more about better
breathing
at myBREO.com.
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night.
Hold on Dad...
Liberty did what?
Yeah, Liberty Mutual 24-Hour
Roadside Assistance
helped him to fix his flat
so he could get home safely.
My dad says our insurance
doesn't have that.
Don't worry - I know what a
lug wrench is, Dad.
Is this a lug wrench?
Maybe?
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
As after a DVT blood clot,ital
I sure had a lot
to think about.
What about the
people I care about?
...including this little girl.
And what if this
happened again?
I was given warfarin
in the hospital,
but wondered, was this the
best treatment for me?
So I asked my doctor.
And he recommended ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots
and reduces the risk of
them happening again.
Yes, ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots.
ELIQUIS also had
significantly
less major
bleeding
than the
standard
treatment.
Both made me
turn around my
thinking.
Don't stop ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal injection
while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling,
numbness, or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
...and it may take longer
than usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned
medical or dental
procedures.
ELIQUIS treats
DVT and PE
blood clots.
Plus had
less major
bleeding.
Both made ELIQUIS
the right treatment for me.
Ask your doctor if switching
to ELIQUIS is right for you.
>>> TO THE "INDEX" OF OTHER
NEWS.
AN OFF-DUTY SHERIFF'S DEPUTY,
KILLED WHEN A BUS COLLIDED WITH
HIS CAR.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE FATHER OF
FOUR WAS KILLED WHEN A BUS
SLAMMED INTO HIM.
TRAFFIC HALTED FOR MILES.
THE CRASH UNDER INVESTIGATION.
>>> IN CALIFORNIA, AUTHORITIES
INVESTIGATING A SPREE OF CAR
ARSONS.
AT LEAST SIX CARS TORCHED, MOST
OF THEM PARKED IN DRIVEWAYS.
ONE FIRE JUMPING TO A NEARBY
HOME.
>>> A MASSIVE AUTO RECALL
INVOLVES POPULAR PICKUPS.
FIAT-CHRYSLER RECALLING MORE
THAN 1 MILLION RAMS TRUCKS
TO FIX FAULTY SOFTWARE.
AUTHORITIES THE DEFECT NOW
LINKED TO ACCIDENTS RESULTING IN
ONE DEATH.
MORE ON OUR WEBSITE.
>>> AND, LIVE FROM NEW YORK, A
LITTLE EARLY.
MELISSA McCARTHY REPRISING HER
ROLE AS SEAN SPICER FOR "SNL,"
ROLLING THROUGH THE STREETS AND
SHOUTING AT ANYONE IN HER WAY.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, ONE STORY
YOU CAN'T MISS AS WE HEAD INTO
THIS MOTHER'S DAY WEEKEND.
WHO IS OUR PERSON OF THE WEEK?
♪ Strike a pose
♪
Your eyes work as
hard as you do.
But do they need help making
more of their own tears?
If you have Chronic Dry Eye
caused by reduced tear
production due to inflammation,
RESTASIS MultiDose™ can help...
with continued use
twice a day, every day,
one drop at a time.
RESTASIS MultiDose™ helps
increase your eyes'
natural ability
to produce tears,
which may be
reduced by inflammation
due to Chronic Dry Eye.
RESTASIS MultiDose™ did not
increase tear production
in patients using
anti-inflammatory eye drops
or tear duct plugs.
To help avoid eye
injury and contamination,
do not touch the bottle tip
to your eye or other surfaces.
Wait 15 minutes after use
before inserting contact lenses.
The most common side effect is
a temporary burning sensation.
Your eyes.
Your tears.
Ask your eye doctor
about RESTASIS MultiDose™.
Fleas, ticks AND mosquitoes.
Got any ideas?ting you?
Not all products
work the same.
My owner gives me
K9 Advantix II.
It kills all three
through contact.
No biting required.
So they don't
have to bite?
That's right. No
biting required.
K9 Advantix II. Wise choice.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE, OUR
PERSON OF THE WEEK.
AND WITH MOTHER'S DAY THIS
WEEKEND, IT WASN'T DIFFICULT
MAKING OUR CHOICE.
TONIGHT, THE STORY OF THREE BOYS
WHO WERE DEALT UNSPEAKABLE
TRAUMA EARLY IN LIFE, AND THE
YOUNG MOM WHO WANTED TO RAISE
THEM AS HER OWN.
TONIGHT, MEET OUR PERSON OF THE
WEEK.
IT'S THE DINNER HOUR, AND THIS
MOM, LIKE SO MANY, HAS HER HANDS
FULL.
VERONICA BLACK, AND HER FOUR
BOYS.
A DETERMINED SINGLE MOM, WITH
HER OWN SON, SHE CHOSE TO ADOPT
THREE MORE.
FOSTERING THEM FIRST.
>> I WAS SHOCKED.
I WAS SURPRISED AT THE NUMBER OF
CHILDREN THAT WERE IN CARE.
AND THE ISSUES AND THE TRAUMA
THAT THEY'VE EXPERIENCED.
>> Reporter: SHE FIRST BEGAN
FOSTERING TEN YEARS AGO.
TAKING IN HER OLDER SON, HE WAS
JUST 6 AT THE TIME.
HE HAD LIVED IN SEVEN DIFFERENT
HOMES.
>> ALL THEY WANT TO DO IS BELONG
AND BE PART OF A FAMILY.
THAT'S IT.
>> Reporter: THEN SHE WOULD
FOSTER AND ADOPT TWO MORE.
THERE THEY ARE ON THE DAY THEY
WERE ALSO GOING TO JOIN HER
FAMILY.
HERE'S THE MOMENT IN COURT WHEN
SHE OFFICIALLY ADOPTS THEM.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE OFFICIAL,
OKAY?
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Reporter: OFFICIALLY BECOMING
THEIR MOM.
OUR PARENT COMPANY DISNEY,
SUPPORTING FOSTER CARE MONTH,
PARTNERING WITH FOSTER MORE.
AND TONIGHT, ON THIS MOTHER'S
DAY WEEKEND, THE BOYS WITH A
MESSAGE FOR THEIR MOM.
>> THE SUPPORT AND LOVE THAT
COMES FROM FAMILY, WHICH IS VERY
MEANINGFUL, I CAN'T ASK FOR A
BETTER ONE.
IT'S ALMOST LIKE LIVING IN A
DREAM, EVERY DAY, WITH THESE
GUYS.
IT'S JUST SPECIAL.
>> IT'S GREAT THAT I HAVE
FINALLY SOMEONE, A FAMILY TO
HAVE FOREVER, AND NOT BOUNCING
AROUND.
>> SHE'S REALLY SPECIAL.
SHE WAS THE ONE WHO DIDN'T GIVE
UP ON US TO ADOPT US INSTEAD OF
JUST LETTING GO.
>> Reporter: THE SUPERHERO MOM,
WHO SAW CHILDREN IN NEED AND
MADE THEM HER OWN.
>> THEY'RE AT HOME, SETTLED,
THEY KNOW THAT THEY'RE SAFE, AND
WE ARE A FAMILY.
>> AND SO WE CHOOSE VERONICA
BLACK, AND ALL THE MOMS AND
STEPMOMS ON THIS MOTHER'S DAY
WEEKEND.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU ON MONDAY.
HAPPY MOTHER'S DAY, MOM.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> TOO THE TOP PROSECUTOR IN
CONTRA COSTA COUNTY IS BEING
CALLED TO STEP DOWN FOR CONDUCT
THAT'S BEING CALLED CORRUPT.
>>> A DEPUTY'S FATAL
THE LATEST TRAGEDY FROM A BAY
AREA DEPARTMENT STILL HEALING
FROM THE LOSS OF ANOTHER
OFFICER.
>>> AND STILL AT 6:00, LESS IS
MORE AT THE PORT OF OAKLAND.
WE'LL EXPLAIN WHY.
>>> HIS LEADERSHIP IS NOT
INSPIRING CONFIDENCE IN OUR
OFFICE.
>> AN EMERGENCY MEETING WAS HELD
IN CONTRA COSTA COUNTY TODAY
WITH PROSECUTORS DISCUSSING THE
FATE OF THEIR BOSS THE DISTRICT
ATTORNEY.
>> A GRAND JURY HAS ACCUSED THE
COUNTY'S DISTRICT ATTORNEY OF
CORRUPTION AND MISCONDUCT.
>> THEIR REPORTS RECOMMEND MARK
PETERSON BE REMOVED FROM OFFICE.
KATE LARSEN IS LIVE WITH A LOOK
AT HOW RARE THAT REQUEST IS,
KATE?
>> Reporter: THE JURY FOREPERSON
WHOM YOU'RE GOING TO HEAR FROM,
SAYS HE DOESN'T BELIEVE ANOTHER
CASE EXISTS LIKE THIS IN CONTRA
COSTA COUNTY.
A PROSECUTOR SAYS HE TOLD MARKS
PETERSON TO HIS FACE THAT HIS
EMPLOYEES HAVE LOST CONFIDENCE
IN HIM.
BUT HE'S STILL SHOWING UP HERE
AND STILL PLANNING TO RUN FOR
RE-ELECTION NEXT YEAR.
A CONTRA COSTA GRAND JURY
ACCUSED THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY OF
WILL TESTIMONY OR CORRUPT
CONDUCT, RECOMMENDING THAT HE BE
REMOVED FROM OFFICE.
>> Reporter: JIM MILLA
SAID -- IN DECEMBER, PETERSON
ADMITTED TO SPENDING 66,000
DLRSZ IN CAMPAIGN FUNDS ON
PERSONAL ITEMS INCLUDING MEALS
AND