>> TONIGHT BREAKING NEWS.
THE HOSTAGE SITUATION INSIDE AN
AMERICAN HOSPITAL.
AN INMATE THERE TO BE TREATED
STEALING AN OFFICER'S GUN AND
TAKING A NURSE HOSTAGE INSIDE
THE EMERGENCY ROOM.
S.W.A.T. TEAMS ON THE SCENE.
GLOBAL HACK.
THE BIGGEST CYBERATTACK EVER.
THE VIRUS CRIPPLING HOSPITALS
AND BUSINESSES ACROSS THE GLOBE
AND HERE AT HOME.
THE HACKERS DEMANDING A RANSOM.
THE RACE TO STOP THE THREAT.
>>> TRUMP'S TOP COP, THE
PRESIDENT ANNOUNCING A NEW FBI
DIRECTOR IS ON THE WAY.
OUR CAMERAS TRACKING THE
POTENTIAL CANDIDATES.
>>> INSIDE THE INFERNO.
THE DRAMATIC BODY CAM VIDEO
SHOWING AUTHORITIES ENTERING A
HOUSE ON FIRE.
THE FRANTIC RUSH TO SAVE THE
RESIDENCE
>>> AND THE FASHION ICON
TRAGEDY, KIDNAPPERS TARGETING
THE FAMILY OF DESIGNER
CAROLINA HERRERA, THE RUTHLESS
RESULT AFTER A RANSOM WAS PAID.
>>> AND GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US ON THIS
SATURDAY.
I'M TOM LLAMAS.
WE BEGIN WITH
THE CYBERATTACK ROLLING ACROSS
THE GLOBE.
TARGETING GOVERNMENTS, HOSPITALS
AND MAJOR COMPANIES.
SECURITY EXPERTS RACING TO FIGHT
BACK.
HACKERS STRIKING AROUND 100,
LOOK AT THAT, COUNTRIES
INCLUDING RIGHT HERE IN THE U.S.
LOCKING UP TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
COMPUTERS, DEMANDING RANSOM TO
FREE THEM UP.
TONIGHT THE COMPUTER WIZ WHO MAY
HAVE STUMBLED ON A WAY TO
DISABLE THE ATTACK AND THE
INTERNATIONAL HUNT TO CATCH THE
CULPRITS BEFORE THEY STRIKE
AGAIN.
ABC'S BRIAN ROSS STARTS US OFF.
>> Reporter: THE TALLY OF
VICTIMS TONIGHT INCLUDES FEDEX
AND THE UNITED STATES, RUSSIA
AND RAILROADS, GERMANY AND
FACTORIES AND PHONE COMPANIES
ACROSS EUROPE AND HOSPITALS IN
GREAT BRITAIN WHERE SURGERIES
WERE CANCELLED.
AMBULANCES TURNED AWAY AND LIVES
PUT AT RISK.
>> IT'S A HEINOUS CRIME.
THIS HACKING BECAUSE THEY'RE
PUTTING PEOPLE'S LIVES AT RISK.
>> Reporter: THE INTERNATIONAL
CYBERATTACK TITLED WANT TO CRY
WAS ANNOUNCED WHEN TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF TARGETS
RECEIVED THIS
MESSAGE THAT THEIR COMPUTERS
WERE FROZEN.
OOPS, YOUR IMPORTANT FILES ARE
ENCRYPTED FOLLOWED BY TO PAY A
RANSOM OF $300 OR MORE TO KEEP
THEIR FILES FROM BEING ERASED
PERMANENTLY.
>> THE REASON THIS IS HITTING SO
MANY COMPUTERS AT ONCE IS THEY
DISCOVERED A VULNERABILITY IN
THE MOST POPULAR OPERATING
SYSTEM IN THE WORLD IN MICROSOFT
WINDOWS AND THEY'RE TAKING
ADVANTAGE OF IT.
IT'S ONE THAT MICROSOFT
DELIVERED A SOLUTION FOR BUT A
LOT OF PEOPLE HAVEN'T USED IT.
>> Reporter: AS THE ATTACKS
SPREAD TO MORE THAN 100
COUNTRIES IN FIVE CONTINENTS THE
DAMAGE WAS
CONTAINED TODAY FOR THE MOMENT.
WHEN A COMPUTER PROGRAMMER IN
GREAT BRITAIN STUMBLED ON TO A
KILL SWITCH BASED ON THE WORK OF
THIS COMPUTER PROGRAMMER IN
INDIANA WHO TALKED WITH US BY
SKYPE.
>> ONCE THE KILL SWITCH WAS
ACTIVATED, THE MALWARE WOULD DO
NOTHING.
IT WOULD NOT CARRY OUT ITS
INFECTION OR TAKE FOR RANSOM ALL
THE FILES ON THAT COMPUTER.
>> Reporter: LAW ENFORCEMENT AND
INTELLIGENCE AUTHORITIES AROUND
THE WORLD LED BY BRITAIN'S NEW
COMPUTER SECURITY SQUAD WHERE WE
WERE RECENTLY GIVEN RARE ACCESS
ARE WORKING TO TRACK DOWN
WHOEVER WAS RESPONSIBLE.
WITH RUSSIAN ORGANIZED CRIME
CONSIDERED A LEADING SUSPECT.
>> PEOPLE TRYING TO STEAL MONEY.
THE DIGITAL WORLD GIVES PEOPLE
AN OPPORTUNITY TO DO THAT.
>> Reporter: IRONICALLY EXPERTS
BELIEVE THE ATTACK WAS CARRIED
OUT WITH THE HELP OF A PROGRAM
FIRST DEVELOPED BY U.S.
INTELLIGENCE TO COMPROMISE THE
COMPUTERS OF TERRORISTS AND
FOREIGN ADVERSARIES.
>> THEY LOST IT.
SOMEBODY STOLE THE INFORMATION,
PUBLISHED IT ON THE INTERNET AND
NOW IS BEING USED AGAINST
VICTIMS IN THE UNITED STATES AND
ELSEWHERE.
>> AND BRIAN, WE HEARD YOUR
REPORT ABOUT THE KILL SWITCH BUT
THE PROBLEM ISN'T OVER?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
U.S. OFFICIALS BELIEVE AMERICAN
COMPANIES DODGED THE BULLET IN
THIS CASE BECAUSE MOST HAD
UPGRADED THEIR COMPUTERS TO
CLOSE THE VULNERABILITY AND THE
QUICK ACTIVATION OF THE KILL
SWITCH.
ALSO HELPED.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY BELIEVE THE
HACKERS ARE PREPARING A SECOND
WAVE OF ATTACKS WITHOUT A KILL
SWITCH THAT COULD COME ANY TIME
SOON TOM.
>> WHAT'S ADVICE FROM OUR
EXPERTS TO OUR VIEWERS TO
PROTECT THEMSELVES?
>> Reporter: ANYBODY WHO USES
THE MICROSOFT SYSTEM SHOULD
DOWNLOAD ANY UPGRADES INCLUDING
THE PATCH THAT COVERS THIS
VULNERABILITY.
TOM.
>> THANKS SO MUCH.
NEXT TO THE BREAKING NEWS, A
TENSE HOSPITAL STANDOFF OUTSIDE
CHICAGO.
A JAIL INMATE THERE AS A PATIENT
WRESTLING A GUN FROM A GUARD AND
TAKING A NURSE HOSTAGE.
POLICE AND S.W.A.T. TEAMS
RUSHING TO THE SCENE.
NO ONE ALLOWED IN OR OUT OF THE
BUILDING.
CRISIS NEGOTIATORS THERE AS
WELL.
ABC'S RON CLAIBORNE WITH THE
DETAILS COMING IN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT HEAVILY
ARMED S.W.A.T. TEAMS AROUND A
HOSPITAL.
EMERGENCY ROOM OUTSIDE OF
CHICAGO.
POLICE SAY
AN ARMED GUNMAN HOLDING A
HOSPITAL EMPLOYEE HOSTAGE.
THESE PHOTOS TAKEN FROM INSIDE
THE HOSPITAL.
SHOWING OFFICERS ARMED WITH
RIFLES, CROUCHED BEHIND A WALL
TAKING AIM.
ANOTHER STANDING GUARD.
THE HOSPITAL ON LOCKDOWN.
>> SUBJECT WITH A GUN, DELNOR
HOSPITAL.
>> Reporter: WE SPOKE TO A WOMAN
VISITING HER FATHER, A PATIENT
WHEN IT HAPPENED.
A NURSE ORDERING THEM TO STAY
INSIDE.
>> MY DAUGHTER AND I TRIED TO
LEAVE AND THE NURSE CAME DOWN
AND YELLED GET BACK IN YOUR
ROOM.
I'M LIKE WE HAVE TO GET HOME AND
SHE SAID THERE'S AN ARMED
INTRUDER IN THE HOSPITAL AND YOU
HAVE TO STAY BEHIND LOCKED
DOORS.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY THE
CHAOS BROKE OUT
AROUND 2:00 P.M. EASTERN TIME
WHEN A JAIL INMATE BEING TREATED
AT THE HOSPITAL GRABBED THE GUN
OF AN OFFICER WHO WAS GUARDING
HIM.
>> UNITS RESPONDING TO DELNOR.
A HANDGUN, GLOCK 21 HANDGUN.
BLOCK 21.
>> Reporter: THE GUNMAN TOOK
SEVERAL HOSTAGES AT GUNPOINT BUT
WAS FINALLY CORNERED WITH ONLY
ONE HOSTAGE.
POLICE SAYING THE S.W.A.T. TEAMS
CONFRONTED THE SUSPECT IN THE
HOSPITAL.
THE SUSPECT SHOT DEAD AND THE
HOSTAGE HE WAS HOLDING RELEASED
UNHARMED.
TOM.
>> RON, THANKS SO MUCH.
WE MOVE ON TO THE FALLOUT AFTER
THE FIRING OF JAMES COMEY.
COMEY EMERGING FROM HIS HOME IN
VIRGINIA FOUR DAYS AFTER SEEN ON
TV THAT THE PRESIDENT HAD LET
HIM GO.
AT THE SAME TIME CANDIDATES WHO
REPLACE HIM LINING UP FOR
INTERVIEWS AT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT TONIGHT.
GLORIA RIVIERA STAKING THEM OUT.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP
SENDING HIS SEARCH FOR A NEW FBI
DIRECTOR INTO OVERDRIVE.
>> OUTSTANDING PEOPLE THAT ARE
VERY WELL KNOWN.
HIGHEST LEVEL.
SO WE COULD MAKE THE BEST
DECISION.
>> Reporter: SUGGESTING IT COULD
BE DECIDED BY NEXT WEEK.
>> EVEN THEN IT'S POSSIBLE.
>> Reporter: COMEY SPOTTED
LEAVING HIS HOME.
SOURCES TELLING ABC NEWS HE IS
FURIOUS AT HOW THE FIRING HAS
BEEN HANDLED.
THIS AS CANDIDATES TO REPLACE
HIM ARRIVING AT THE DEPARTMENT
OF JUSTICE.
>> WERE YOU ASKED IF YOU COULD
FAITHFULLY SERVE THE PRESIDENT?
>> NO COMMENT.
>> NO COMMENT AT ALL.
>> Reporter: CONDUCTING THOSE
INTERVIEWS DEPUTY ATTORNEY
GENERAL ROD ROSENSTEIN AND
ATTORNEY GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS,
SESSIONS REMOVING HIMSELF FROM
INVESTIGATIONS INTO WHETHER THE
TRUMP CAMPAIGN COLLUDED WITH
RUSSIA'S MEDDLING IN THE
ELECTION AND TAKING A ROLE IN
CHOOSING WHO IS IN CHARGE OF THE
FBI'S CASE.
>> YOU CANNOT STOP THE MEN AND
WOMEN OF THE FBI FROM DOING THE
RIGHT THING.
>> Reporter: ONE OF TODAY'S
CANDIDATES ANDREW McCABE
CONTRADICTED THE WHITE HOUSE
CLAIM ABOUT THE OUSTED DIRECTOR
IN A HEARING ON CAPITOL HILL.
>> IS IT ACCURATE THE RANK AND
FILE NO LONGER SUPPORTED
DIRECTOR COMEY.
>> NO, SIR.
THAT IS NOT ACCURATE.
>> Reporter: REPUBLICAN SENATOR
JOLG COBB-- JOHN CORNYN
WAS ASKED ABOUT THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
>> IT IS A LEGITIMATE AREA OF
INQUIRY.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT HAS
REPEATEDLY DISAGREED.
>> I SAID, YOU KNOW, THIS RUSSIA
THING WITH TRUMP AND RUSSIA IS A
MADE-UP STORY.
>> Reporter: SHOULD A SPECIAL
PROSECUTOR BE APPOINTED?
Reporter: DEMOCRATIC SENATORS
CALLING FOR A SPECIAL PROSECUTOR
INTO RUSSIA BEFORE ANY VOTE ON
COMEY'S REPLACEMENT.
>> I WILL VOTE AGAINST ANY
CONFIRMATION OF AN FBI DIRECTOR
UNLESS THERE IS SUPPORT FOR A
SPECIAL PROSECUTOR.
>> GLORIA IS LIVE AT THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT.
TONIGHT A GROUP OF CURRENT AND
FORMER FBI AGENTS PUSHING A
CANDIDATE, A NAME THEY WANT
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO CONSIDER.
>> Reporter: THE FBI AGENT'S
ASSOCIATION IS ENDORSING MIKE
ROGERS, HE IS SCHEDULED AS THE
FINAL INTERVIEW TODAY.
HE HIMSELF IS A FORMER SPECIAL
AGENT AND A MEMBER OF CONGRESS
AND
IN TERMS OF NEXT STEPS THE WHITE
HOUSE SAYS PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL
HIMSELF MEET WITH FINALISTS ONCE
THIS VERY LONG LIST NARROWS.
TOM.
>>> BREAKING NEWS FROM OVERSEAS,
A NEW PROVOCATION FROM NORTH
KOREA.
U.S. OFFICIALS CONFIRM THAT
THEY HAVE CONDUCTED A NEW
MISSILE TEST.
THAT MISSILE STAYING IN THE AIR
400 MILES.
IT IS THE SEVENTH TEST SINCE
DONALD TRUMP TOOK OFFICE.
THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN BRIEFED
ON THE LAUNCH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS ADDRESSING
THE GRADUATES AT LIBERTY
UNIVERSITY IN VIRGINIA.
HIS ADVICE TO THE GRADUATES
ABOUT DREAMERS AND CRITICS.
A REMINDER TO HIMSELF AFTER A
TOUGH WEEK IN WASHINGTON.
DAVID WRIGHT THERE TODAY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE
PRESIDENT IS DOING HIS BEST TO
TURN THE PAGE ON THE ROUGHEST
WEEK YET.
HOLED UP IN THE WHITE HOUSE
SINCE SUNDAY, A FEW DAYS BEFORE
HE FIRED THE FBI DIRECTOR, TRUMP
WENT TO LIBERTY UNIVERSITY TODAY
TO GIVE THE COMMENCEMENT
ADDRESS.
HIS ADVICE TO THE GRADUATES --
>> NO ONE HAS EVER ACHIEVED
ANYTHING SIGNIFICANT WITHOUT A
CHORUS OF CRITICS EXPLAINING WHY
IT CAN'T BE DONE.
>> Reporter: COULD BE A VERSION
OF THE PEP TALK HE'S GIVING
HIMSELF.
>> RELISH THE OPPORTUNITY TO BE
AN OUTSIDER.
EMBRACE THAT LABEL BEING AN
OUTSIDER IS FINE.
EMBRACE THE LABEL BECAUSE IT'S
THE OUTSIDERS WHO CHANGE THE
WORLD.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT IS
CLEARLY FRUSTRATED WITH WHITE
HOUSE MESSAGING IN AN INTERVIEW
AIRING TONIGHT ON FOX NEWS, HE
BACKED UP HIS BELEAGUERED
SPOKESMAN ONLY SO MUCH.
>> HE'S DOING A GOOD JOB BUT
GETS BEAT UP.
>> WILL HE BE THERE TOMORROW?
>> HE'S BEEN THERE FROM THE
BEGINNING.
>> Reporter: EVEN FLOATING THE
IDEA OF GETTING RID OF THE
BRIEFINGS ALL TOGETHER.
>> WE DON'T HAVE PRESS
CONFERENCES.
AND WE DO --
>> YOU DON'T MEAN THAT?
>> JUST DON'T HAVE THEM UNLESS I
HAVE THEM EVERY TWO WEEKS AND DO
THEM MYSELF.
WE DON'T HAVE THEM.
I THINK IT'S A GOOD IDEA.
>> Reporter: TODAY THE CROWD AT
LIBERTY UNIVERSITY GAVE TRUMP A
WARM RECEPTION BUT EVEN HERE
SOME DOUBTERS.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK OF HIS
DECISION TO FIRE THE FBI
DIRECTOR?
>> I THINK IT WAS SHOCKING AND A
LEVEL OF ARROGANCE THAT I HAVE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE.
I THINK IT WAS HIGHLY IMPULSIVE.
>> I WONDER IF HE LISTENS TO HIS
ADVISERS.
I DON'T KNOW ABOUT ALL THE
THINGS HE DOES SOMETIMES.
I AGREE WITH HIS CONCEPTS AND
WHAT HE STANDS FOR BUT THE
EXECUTION SEEMS TO BE SOMETIMES
A LITTLE BIT ROOM FOR
IMPROVEMENT.
>> DAVID, THE PRESIDENT HINTED
THERE MIGHT BE TAPES OF HIS
CONVERSATIONS WITH FORMER FBI
DIRECTOR COMEY BUT REFUSED TO
SAY MORE.
ABOUT THE RECORDED CONVERSATIONS
BUT WE KNOW RECORDED
CONVERSATIONS ARE A PART OF
WHITE HOUSE HISTORY?
>> THERE'S A DANGEROUS PRECEDENT
FOR IT.
ALL THE WAY BACK TO FDR MANY
PRESIDENTS HAVE RECORDED THEIR
MEETINGS WITH SOME EXCEPTIONS
BUT EVER SINCE RICHARD NIXON AND
THOSE WATERGATE TAPES THEY
THOUGHT TWICE ABOUT IT TOM.
>> TOMORROW MORNING TUNE INTO
"THIS WEEK."
THE LATEST REPORTING ON THE
BOMBSHELL FIRING
OF THE FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY.
NEXT TO THE HEROIC EFFORT TO
SAVE A FAMILY FROM THEIR BURNING
HOME.
THREE POLICE OFFICERS THE FIRST
TO ARRIVE TRYING TO MAKE IT UP
THE STAIRS BUT TURNED BACK BY
THE FLAMES.
THREE CHILDREN LOST THEIR LIVES
IN THE FIRE BUT FAMILY MEMBERS
AND FIREFIGHTERS GOT SEVERAL
OTHERS OUT.
ABC'S KENNETH MOTON ON THE FIRE
OUTSIDE OF HOUSTON.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, A
TERRIFYING LOOK AS POLICE
OFFICERS RUSH INSIDE THIS
MONSTER HOUSE FIRE FRANTICALLY
SEARCHING FOR THREE CHILDREN.
>> ENGINE 64 CURRENTLY EN ROUTE
JOHNSON ROAD FOR STRUCTURE FIRE.
MULTIPLE CALLERS TO REPORT THE
POSSIBLE VICTIMS TRAPPED.
>> Reporter: FIREFIGHTERS STILL
RACING TO THE SCENE JUST OUTSIDE
OF HOUSTON FRIDAY MORNING.
A BODY CAMERA ATTACHED TO THIS
OFFICER.
HE AND TWO OTHERS RUN INTO THE
BURNING HOUSE.
STARING DOWN A WALL OF FLAMES,
THE FIRST RESPONDERS SCRAMBLE TO
FIND SOMETHING TO COVER THEIR
FACES.
>> ANYBODY INSIDE?
>> Reporter: THEY TRIED TO MOVE
IN, BUT QUICKLY REALIZED THERE
WAS NOTHING THEY COULD DO.
>> THERE AIN'T NO WAY.
>> Reporter: THE OFFICERS RUSH
OUT DESPERATE FOR AIR.
>> WATCH OUT, ROOF'S COLLAPSING,
UP RIGHT THERE.
>> Reporter: FRUSTRATED, THEY
REFUSE TO GIVE UP, GRABBING A
LADDER TO GET TO A SECOND FLOOR
WINDOW.
>> BREAK IT OUT.
>> Reporter: FIRE INVESTIGATORS
SAY IN THE HOME, FOUR ADULTS AND
FOUR KIDS.
SIBLINGS AGES 13 TO FIVE.
A 10 YEAR OLD BOY THE ONLY CHILD
TO SURVIVE.
THE SURVIVORS INCLUDING THE
MOTHER OF THE THREE CHILDREN
KILLED ARE RECOVERING.
THOSE OFFICERS WERE ALSO
TREATED.
THE CAUSE OF THE HOUSE FIRE
STILL UNDER INVESTIGATION.
TOM.
>> SAD SITUATION FOR THAT
FAMILY.
KENNETH.
THANK YOU.
NEXT TO THE EXTREME WEATHER IN
THE EAST.
THREE TORNADOS CONFIRMED IN
LOUISIANA.
THERE'S ONE OF THEM.
THE CLEANUP UNDER WAY AND HEAVY
RAIN MOVING UP THE COAST,
FLOODED STREETS.
IN OCEAN CITY, NEW JERSEY.
ROB MARCIANO IN CENTRAL PARK
TONIGHT.
ROB, THIS IS AN UNUSUALLY STRONG
STORM FOR THIS TIME OF YEAR
CORRECT?
>> Reporter: IT IS TOM AND FEELS
MORE LIKE MARCH THAN MAY.
TEMPERATURES IN THE 40s.
THE RAIN AT TIMES BLOWING
SIDEWAYS AND IT'S INTENSIFYING.
TAKE A LOOK OFF THE COAST OF NEW
JERSEY AND THE RAIN SHIELD
TOWARDS ALBANY AND RAINING
HEAVILY THERE AND COASTAL
FLOODING AN ISSUE.
WITH THE ONSHORE OF FLOW.
THE RAIN WILL END FROM WEST TO
EAST.
HARTFORD, PROVIDENCE AND BOSTON
YOU'LL SEE IT INTENSIFY AND
10:00 A.M. TOMORROW MORNING FOR
MOTHER'S DAY A BREAK IN NEW YORK
BUT WRAP AROUND INSTABILITY AND
MORE SHOWERS THROUGHOUT THE DAY.
CERTAINLY GOING TO BE A BETTER
HOLIDAY.
SOME MOMS WILL HAVE TO BRING
THEIR OWN SUNSHINE
UNFORTUNATELY.
TOM.
>> THANKS SO MUCH.
STILL MUCH MORE AHEAD ON "WORLD
NEWS TONIGHT" THIS SATURDAY.
THE VIOLENT ROAD RAGE IN BEVERLY
HILLS.
A MAN RAMMING A CAR WITH A
SHOPPING CART.
THE DRIVER PINNED THE MAN
AGAINST THE WALL AND TAKING OFF.
WHAT MAY HAVE CAUSED THE
DANGEROUS CONFRONTATION.
>>> THE RECALL INVOLVING A
POPULAR BRAND OF BABY WIPES AND
CONCERNS OVER MOLD.
AND THE FASHION ICON TRAGEDY.
CAROLINA HERRERA'S NEPHEW
TARGETED BY KIDNAPPERS.
WHY THE DESIGNER IS ANGRY AT THE
VENEZUELAN GOVERNMENT.
STAY WITH US.
this is a strategyis,
fI'd recommend.
This actually makes sense.
Now on the next page you'll
see a breakdown of costs.
What?
It's just...
We were going to ask about it
but we weren't sure when.
So thanks.
Yeah, that's great.
Being clear and upfront.
Multiplied by 14,000 financial
advisors, it's a big deal.
And it's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
WILL YOU BE READY WHEN
THE MOMENT TURNS ROMANTIC?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
ItThe power of Nexium
24HR protection
from frequent heartburn.
All day, and all night.
Now packed into
a pill so small,
We call it mini.
New ClearMinis from Nexium 24HR.
See Heartburn Differently.
For finding relief can seem
sualmost as painful.ck pain
Finally the search is over.
Drug-free Aleve
Direct Therapy®.
A TENS device with
high intensity power
that uses technology
once only available in
doctors' offices.
Its smart wireless design
lets you control its intensity
for deep penetrating
relief at the source.
The power of relief
is in your hands.
Aleve Direct Therapy.
Find yours in the
pain relief aisle.
>>> BACK NOW WITH THE POLITICAL
CHAOS AND VIOLENCE IN VENEZUELA
TURNING TRAGIC FOR FASHION ICON
CAROLINA HERRERA.
HER NEPHEW KIDNAPPED AND
MURDERED AFTER THE FAMILY PAID A
RANSOM.
HERE'S ABC'S EVA PILGRIM.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT CAROLINA
HERRERA ONE OF THE WORLD'S TOP
FASHION DESIGNERS IS LASHING OUT
AGAINST VENEZUELA'S LEADERS
AFTER HER NEPHEW WAS ABDUCTED,
HELD FOR RANSOM, AND MURDERED.
VENEZUELAN AUTHORITIES SAY
34-YEAR-OLD REINALDO JOSE
HERRERA AND HIS BUSINESS PARTNER
31-YEAR-OLD FABRIZIO MENDOZA
WERE TAKEN HOSTAGE IN CARACAS BY
A GANG THURSDAY NIGHT.
A LOCAL SECURITY OFFICIALS
SAYING THE TWO WERE ATTACKED AS
THEY RETURNED TO THEIR OFFICE.
POLICE SAY THE GANG ASKED FOR A
RANSOM.
BUT DESPITE THE FAMILIES MAKING
THE PAYMENT, THE TWO WERE FOUND
FRIDAY DEAD INSIDE A TRUCK.
CAROLINA HERRERA POSTING TO
SOCIAL MEDIA.
OUR ONLY HOPE IS THAT THE TRAGIC
ASSASSINATION OF OUR NEPHEW AND
HIS COLLEAGUE WILL SERVE TO
MITIGATE THE TERRIBLE CARNAGE
AND MURDERS COMMITTED AGAINST
OUR YOUTH IN VENEZUELA.
THE ELECTORAL RESULTS MUST BE
RESPECTED.
THE COMMUNIST DICTATORSHIP MUST
GO.
POLITICAL TURMOIL AND GROWING
ECONOMIC CRISIS HAS LED TO
RAMPED CRIME IN THE SOUTH
AMERICAN NATION.
SINCE JANUARY THERE HAVE BEEN
ALMOST 400 KIDNAPPINGS NEARLY AS
MANY AS ALL OF LAST YEAR TOTAL.
POLICE SAY THE KIDNAPPERS MADE
THEM CALL A HOUSEKEEPER TO PUT
JEWELRY AND MONEY INTO A BAG
THEY LATER PICKED UP.
AUTHORITIES ARE LOOKING FOR FOUR
MEN WHO THEY SAY ARE ALL ARMED.
TOM.
>> EVA, THANK YOU.
WHEN WE COME BACK, THE SCARY
MOMENT AT THE BALLPARK.
THE BIG LEAGUER HIT BY A PITCH
TAKING A 93-MILE-PER-HOUR FAST
BALL STRAIGHT TO THE FACE.
HOW HE'S DOING TONIGHT.
>>> AND WHY ARNOLD
SCHWARZENEGGER MET WITH THE
FORMER PRESIDENT AND FIRST LADY.
♪
That's life.
You diet. You exercise.
And if you still need help
lowering your blood sugar...
...this is JARDIANCE.
Along with diet and exercise...
JARDIANCE lowers blood sugar
and A1C
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
JARDIANCE is also the only type
2 diabetes treatment with heart-
proven to reduce the risk
of cardiovascular death
in adults with type 2 diabetes
and cardiovascular disease.
JARDIANCE can cause serious side
effects, including dehydration.
This may cause you to feel
dizzy, faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious side
effect that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness, and
trouble breathing.
Stop taking JARDIANCE and call
your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are sudden
kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So talk to your doctor
about JARDIANCE-
the one and only type 2 diabetes
treatment with heart.
Visit JARDIANCE.com for a free
consultation with
a Certified Diabetes Educator
if you qualify.
What bad back?Gels work so fast
you'll ask
What pulled hammy?
Advil Liqui - Gels make pain a
distant memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
It's just a burst pipe,
I co(laugh) it.
No.
With Claim RateGuard
your rates won't go up
just because of a claim.
I totally could've -
No!
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
If you have moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis like me,
and you're talking
to your rheumatologist
about a medication...
...this is HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA helping
to relieve my pain...
...and protect my joints
from further damage.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 18 years.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to...
...block a
specific source...
...of inflammation that
contributes to RA symptoms.
It's proven to help
relieve pain and...
...stop further joint
damage in many adults.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened,
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas...
...where certain fungal
infections are common
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flulike
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA
if you have an infection.
Talk to your doctor
and visit HUMIRA.com
This is HUMIRA at work.
>>> TIME NOW FOR OUR "INDEX".
IN BEVERLY HILLS AUTHORITIES
INVESTIGATING A VIOLENT ROAD
RAGE CONFRONTATION CAUGHT ON
CAMERA.
THE DISPUTE IN A PARKING LOT.
A MAN YELLING AT A DRIVER ABOUT
LITTERING.
THE CAR DRIVES OFF, LOOPS AROUND
AND THE MAN SLAMS THE CAR WITH A
SHOPPING CART.
WELL, THE DRIVER PINS THE MAN
AGAINST THE WALL BEFORE TAKING
OFF.
THAT INCIDENT IS NOW UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
>>> A POPULAR BRAND OF BABY
WIPES RECALLED OVER MOLD
CONCERNS.
THE HONEST COMPANY RECALLING THE
WIPES AFTER LEARNING SOME SHOWED
MOLD SPOTS.
NO HEALTH ISSUES REPORTED BUT
THE COMPANY IS OFFERING REFUNDS
TO CUSTOMERS.
>>> A FRIGHTENING HIT BY A MAJOR
LEAGUE BASEBALL GAME.
CHRIS IANNETTA TAKING A FAST
BALL RIGHT TO THE FACE.
TRAINERS TENDING TO THE BIG
LEAGUER WHOSE LIP SPLIT OPEN.
HE WAS ABLE TO WALK OFF THE
FIELD BUT LEFT THE GAME AND WAS
TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL.
HE SUFFERED FRACTURES TO HIS
TEETH AND NOSE BUT EXPECTED TO
BE OKAY.
>>> FINALLY, DON'T MESS WITH
THIS TEXAS LUNCH DATE.
ACTION STAR TURNED CALIFORNIA
GOVERNOR ARNOLD SCHWARZENEGGER
POSTING THIS PHOTO WITH GEORGE
H.W. BUSH.
AND WIFE BARBARA.
BUSH, FEELING BETTER AFTER BEING
HOSPITALIZED TWO WEEKS AGO.
THE GOVERNATOR DELIVERING THE
COMMENCEMENT ADDRESS WHICH HE
ENDED WITH "HASTA LA VISTA,
BABY" AND "I'LL BE BACK".
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK A
WONDERFUL STORY ON THIS EVE OF
MOTHER'S DAY.
STAY WITH US.
.
at doesn't
mean we're giving up.
I'm in this for me.
For me.
Along with diet and exercise,
FARXIGA helps
lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms of
a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA if you
have severe kidney problems,
are on dialysis, or
have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary
tract infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and call
your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis,
which is serious and
may lead to death.
I'm in this for my family.
I'm in this for me.
Ask your doctor about FARXIGA
and learn how you can
get it for FREE.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may be able to help.
I wanted to know where
I did my AncestryDNA.
The most shocking result was
that I'm 26% Native American.
I had no idea.
It's opened up
a whole new world for me.
♪
Come close, come close.
Fun in art class.
I like that.
[ music stops suddenly ]
Ah.
When your pain reliever
stops working,
your whole day stops.
Awww.
Try this.
For minor arthritis pain,
only Aleve can stop pain
for up to 12 straight hours
with just one pill.
Thank you.
♪
Come on everybody.
You can't quit, neither
should your pain reliever.
Stay all day strong with
12 hour Aleve.
Hi..and I know that we have
phonaccident forgiveness.gent,
So the incredibly minor
accident that I had tonight-
Four weeks without the car.
Okay, yup.
Good night.
With Accident Forgiveness
your rates won't go up
just because of an accident.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>>> AS AMERICANS PREPARE TO
CELEBRATE OUR MOTHERS, ONE MOM
WHO FINALLY GOT TO CROSS THE
COMMENCEMENT STAGE AND THE
FELLOW GRADUATE WHO INSPIRED
HER.
HERE'S ABC'S MARCI GONZALEZ.
>> Reporter: OF ALL THE LESSONS
SHE LEARNED DURING COLLEGE, THE
MOST IMPACTFUL CAME FROM A
FELLOW GRADUATE, HER MOTHER.
>> YOU CAN DO ANYTHING YOU PUT
YOUR MIND TO.
>> Reporter: KAREN HUNTER
DROPPED OUT
30 YEARS AGO TO TAKE CARE OF HER
OLDEST DAUGHTER.
>> I WAS LIKE MOM, YOU HAVE TO
GO BACK.
>> Reporter: WITH THAT URGING
SHE FINALLY RETURNED TO THE
CLASSROOM TO FINISH WHAT SHE
STARTED AND FULFILL HER MOTHER'S
DREAM.
>> THE LORD TALKED TO ME AND
SAID GIRL, YOU CAN DO THIS AND I
DID.
>> Reporter: AT TIMES IT WAS A
STRUGGLE FOR THE 53-YEAR-OLD.
>> THE WHOLE NEW ENVIRONMENT
FROM WHAT SHE WAS USED TO BACK
IN THE DAY.
>> Reporter: KAREN MANAGED TO
EARN HER DEGREE IN SOCIOLOGY
GRADUATING LAST WEEK.
♪
>> Reporter: AND IN THE PROCESS
LEAVING SOME INSPIRING FOOTSTEPS
HER DAUGHTER IS FOLLOWING IN AS
SHE CROSSES THE STAGE WITH HER
DIPLOMA THIS MOTHER'S DAY
WEEKEND.
♪
>> I'M SO PROUD OF YOU.
>> Reporter: MARCI GONZALEZ, ABC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> THE PERFECT STORY.
WE THANK MARCI FOR THAT.
"GMA" AND "THIS WEEK" IN THE
MORNING.
I'LL SEE YOU BACK TOMORROW
NIGHT.
HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND.
GOOD NIGHT.
I'LL SEE YOU BACK TOMORROW
NIGHT.
HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> TONIGHT ON ABC 7 NEWS AT
6:00, EVACUEE UATIONS ORDERED
NEAR A CONSTRUCTION SITE THAT
BURNED FOR SECOND TIME IN A
YEAR.
>> CENTRAL VALLEY POLICE
OFFICERS KILLED IN LINE OF DUTY.
>>> AND CALIFORNIA SCHOOL HIT BY
AN EXPLOSIVE ILLNESS OUTBREAK.
WHAT OFFICIALS BELIEVE IS THE
CAUSE.
ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS RIGHT
NOW.
>>> EAST BAY RESIDENTS FORCED
OUT OF THEIR HOME FIRST FOR A
CONSTRUCTION FIRE AND NOW
BECAUSE THAT ENORMOUS CRANE
THERE COULD COME CRASHING DOWN.
THE FIRE STARTED AROUND 5:00
THIS MORNING AT AN EMMERYVILLE
CONSTRUCTION SITE THAT HAS NOW
BURNED TWICE IN A YEAR.
WE ARE LIVE WHERE THE FIRE IS
STILL SMOLDERING TONIGHT.
>> YEAH FIRE CREWS ARE STILL
BUSY HERE DUECING HOT SPOTS,
WE'VE SEEN SMOKE RISING FROM
THIS FIRE SCENE ALL DAY LONG.
THE BIG WORRY RIGHT NOW THIS
CONSTRUCTION CRANE IN DANGER OF
FALLING AFTER BASICALLY MELTING
COUNSEL IN THE FIRE.
DOWN IN THE FIRE.
THIS FIRE IS LABELLED AS
SUSPICIOUS BURNED IN THE SECOND
TIME IN THE SAME SPOT.
>> SCARY MOTHER'S DAY WEEKEND.
>> MAYBES WOKE UP TO FLAMES
LIGHTING UP THE SKY DESTROYING A
MILLION-DOLLAR COMPLEX UNDER
CONSTRUCTION THE SAME PROJECT
THAT WENT UP IN JULY.
>> THAT'S THE SECOND TIME IT
BURNED DOWN.
>> CONSTRUCTION WORKER IN TEARS
SEEING THE SITE HE WORKED TURNED
TO RUBBLE.
>> UNBELIEVABLE, FEELS LIKE
SOMEBODY'S AGAINST US.
>> FIREFIGHTERS ATTACKING FROM
ALL SIDES WITH WATER.