YOU GO.
>> THANK YOU FOR YOUR TIME.
SEE YOU BACK HERE AT 6 OF OKAY.
>>> TONIGHT, PRESIDENT TRUMP
VERSUS THE NFL.
ACROSS THE COUNTRY, THE BIGGEST
PLAYS HAPPENING BEFORE THE GAME.
A SHOW OF SOLIDARITY AND
DEFIANCE AGAINST THE PRESIDENT.
PLAYERS TAKING A KNEE, LOCKING
ARMS DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
SOME TEAMS EVEN STAYING OFF THE
FIELD.
TOM BRADY, ONE OF FOOTBALL'S
BIGGEST STARS, WITH HIS HAND
ER HIS
>> I HATE YOU!
>> FANS ON BOTH SIDES SCREAMING
OVER THE ISSUE.
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP UNLEASHES AN
ENDLESS STREAM OF TWEETS ON GAME
DAY.
>>> ALSO BREAKING, THE DEADLY
CHURCH SHOOTING.
THE GUNMAN WEARING A MASK,
OPENING FIRE.
AND THE CHURCH MEMBER WHO
CONFRONTED HIM.
>>> SHOW OF FORCE.
AMERICAN BOMBERS FLYING THE
CLOSEST TO NORTH KOREA IN NEARLY
TWO DECADES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP CALLING KIM
JONG-UN "LITTLE ROCKET MAN" AS
NORTH KOREAN LEADERS SAY
TARGETING THE U.S. MAINLAND IS
MORE INEVITABLE.
>>> AND, DANGEROUS TURN?
THE CRIPPLED DAM IN PUERTO RICO.
THOUSANDS RUSHING TO GET TO
HIGHER GROUND.
AND HURRICANE MARIA'S NEW PATH.
THE NEW WATCH JUST ISSUED FOR
THE EAST COAST.
>>> AND GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US ON THIS
SUNDAY.
I'M TOM LLAMAS.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH THE
UNESCAPABLE HEAD-ON COLLISION OF
POLITICS AND SPORTS.LARS RESPON
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S ATTACK ON
THOSE WHO KNEEL IN PROTEST
DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
SIMILAR ACTS OF DEFIANCE SEEN
BEFORE EACH GAME.
PLAYERS PEACEFULLY TAKING A
KNEE, LOCKING ARMS, SOME WITH
FISTS RAISED IN THE AIR.
THE PITTSBURGH STEELERS AMONG
THE TEAMS CHOOSING NOT TO TAKE
THE FIELD DURING THE ANTHEM.
TRUMP SAYING PLAYERS WHO PROTEST
SHOULD BE FIRED OR SUSPENDED.
THE NFL COMMISSIONER, OWNERS,
COACHES AND PLAYERS SENDING A
UNITED MESSAGE.
AND TONIGHT, NEW COMMENTS FROM
THE PRESIDENT.
HERE'S MARY BRUCE.
>> Reporter: ON THIS FOOTBALL
SUNDAY --
♪ OH SAY CAN YOU SEE
>> Reporter: THE NFL IS SENDING
A MESSAGE TO PRESIDENT TRUMP.
FROM DETROIT TO BUFFALO, AND ALL
THE WAY TO LONDON, AS THE ANTHEM
PLAYS, THE CHORUS OF OPPOSITION
FROM THE FIELD IS GROWING.
PLAYERS AND COACHES KNEELING
TOGETHER.
ARMS LINKED, FISTS RAISED IN
SOLIDARITY.
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM AT FORBES
FIELD ENDING WITH THIS MOMENT.
THE PATRIOTS' TOM BRADY,
SHOULDER TO SHOULDER WITH HIS
TEAMMATES.
IN CHICAGO, ALL BUT ONE OF THE
STEELERS DECLINED TO TAKE THE
FIELD.
THE LONE PLAYER WHO STOOD,
ALEJANDRO VILLANUEVA, A U.S.
ARMY VETERAN.
AND IN NASHVILLE, THE TITANS AND
THE SEAHAWKS SITTING OUT THE
ANTHEM TOGETHER.
IT STARTED WITH THIS JAB, AND
CRUDE LANGUAGE, FROM THE
PRESIDENT ON FRIDAY.
TAKING ON FOOTBALL PLAYERS LIKE
COLIN KAEPERNICK, WHO KNEEL
DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM TO
PROTEST RACIAL AND SOCIAL
INJUSTICE.
>> WOULDN'T YOU LOVE TO SEE
SOMEBODY DISRESPECTS OUR FLAG,
ONE OF THE NFL OWNERS TO SAY,
"GET THAT SON OF A [ BLEEP ] OFF
THE FIELD RIGHT NOW, OUT.
HE'S FIRED.
HE'S FIRED!
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, HE'S
DOUBLING DOWN.
>> I THINK THE OWNERSHIP SHOULD
DO SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
I THINK IT'S VERY, VERY
DISRESPECTFUL TO OUR FLAG.
>> Reporter: AND INSISTS IT HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH RACE.
>> THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
RACE OR ANYTHING ELSE.
IT HAS TO DO WITH RESPECT FOR
OUR COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: ON TWITTER, THE
PRESIDENT SAYING IF NFL FANS
REFUSED TO GO TO GAMES UNTIL
PLAYERS STOP DISRESPECTING OUR
FLAG AND COUNTRY, YOU WILL SEE !
BUT THE NFL IS BACKING ITS
PLAYERS.
IN AN UNUSUALLY STRONG REBUKE,
THE COMMISSIONER SAYS, "DIVISIVE
COMMENTS LIKE THESE DEMONSTRATE
AN UNFORTUNATE LACK OF RESPECT
FOR THE NFL, OUR GREAT GAME AND
ALL OF OUR PLAYERS."
PEOPLE  PRESIDENO  TWHT NKD  IW
TOGETHER.
AND THAT INCLUDES BLACKS AND
WHITES AND EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: NOW, 66% OF
AMERICANS SAY HE IS DOING MORE
TO DIVIDE THE COUNTRY THAN UNITE
IT.
>> HE'S NOW USING SPORTS AS THE
PLATFORM TO TRY TO DIVIDE US.
>> Reporter: AND IT'S NOT JU
FOOTBALL.
TRUMP IS TAKING ON BASKETBALL
TOO, AFTER NBA CHAMPION STEPH
CURRY SAID HE DIDN'T WANT TO
VISIT THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> I DON'T WANT TO GO.
THAT'S REALLY IT.
>> Reporter: TRUMP THEN BEAT HIM
TO IT, DISINVITING HIM.
TWEETING, "GOING TO THE WHITE
HOUSE IS CONSIDERED A GREAT
HONOR FOR A CHAMPIONSHIP TEAM.
STEPH CURRY IS HESITATING,
THEREFORE INVITATION IS
WITHDRAWN!"
LEBRON JAMES' FIRST RESPONSE?
"YOU BUM.
CURRY ALREADY SAID HE ISN'T
GOING.
GOING TO THE WHITE HOUSE WAS A
GREAT HONOR UNTIL YOU SHOWED
UP."
>> MARY, FROM OUTSIDE
FEDEXFIELD, AND PRESIDENT TRUMP
WEIGHING IN AGAIN TONIGHT.
CLEARLY WATCHING SOME OF THE
GAMES TODAY?
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT SAID
HE DID WATCH SOME OF TODAY'S
GAMES, BUT HE SAID HE SAW
TREMENDOUS SOLIDARITY FOR OUR
COUNTRY AND OUR FLAG.
ON TWITTER, HE ADDED STANDING
WITH LOCKED ARMS IS GOOD.
KNEELING IS NOT ACCEPTABLE.
AND TOM, DESPITE THE PRESIDENT'S
RECENT COMMENTS, HE INSISTS HE'S
NOT URGING HIS SUPPORTERS TO
BOYCOTT THE NFL.
TOM?
>> SENDING A MIXED MESSAGE.
MARY, THANK YOU.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S OUTBURSTS
SPREADING BEYOND FOOTBALL AND
BASKETBALL.
OAKLAND A's ROOKIE BRUCE
MAXWELL, BECOMING THE FIRST
MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL PLAYER
TAKING A KNEE DURING THE ANTHEM.
OUTRAGE IS BUILDING OVER THE
PRESIDENT'S HEATED COMMENTS.
HERE'S RYAN SMITH.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, GROWING
BACKLASH ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
>> I HATE YOU!
>> Reporter: FANS IN
PHILADELPHIA CLASH OVER THE
CONTROVERSY IGNITED BY PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
THE NFL UNITING.
>> I GUESS WE'RE ALL A SON OF A
[ BLEEP ].
>> Reporter: FORMER HEAD COACH
REX RYAN CAMPAIGNED FOR TRUMP,
BUT HAD HARSH WORDS TODAY.
>> I'M PISSED OFF, I'LL BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
BECAUSE I SUPPORTED
DONALD TRUMP.
CALLING OUR PLAYERS S.O.B.s AND
ALL THAT KIND OF STUFF.
THAT'S NOT THE MEN THAT I KNOW.
THE MEN THAT I KNOW IN THE
LOCKER ROOM I'M PROUD OF.
>> Reporter: HALL OF FAME
QUARTERBACK TERRY BRADSHAW
DISAGREES WITH THE PROTEST, BUT
STANDS BEHIND THE PROTESTERS'
RIGHT TO DO IT.
>> IF OUR COUNTRY STANDS FOR
ANYTHING, FOLKS, WHAT, IT'S
FREEDOM.
PEOPLE DIED FOR THAT FREEDOM.
I'M NOT SURE IF OUR PRESIDENT
UNDERSTANDS THOSE RIGHTS.
>> Reporter: OWNERS FROM SIX
TEAMS TAKING THE FIELD DURING
THE ANTHEM IN SUPPORT OF THEIR
PLAYERS.
PATRIOTS OWNER BOB KRAFT IS A
WELL KNOWN FRIEND OF TRUMP, EVEN
FLYING ON AIR FORCE ONE,
DONATING $1 MILLION TO HIS
INAUGURAL COMMITTEE.
BUT TODAY SAYING HE'S "DEEPLY
DISAPPOINTED BY THE TONE OF THE
COMMENTS" AND "THERE IS NO
GREATER UNIFIER IN THIS COUNTRY
THAN SPORTS.
UNFORTUNATELY, NOTHING IS MORE
DIVISIVE THAN POLITICS."
WE SPOKE TO FANS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY AND THAT DIVIDE IS
CLEAR.
>> I STAND FOR THOSE WHO STAND
FOR US.
>> YOU GUYS MAKE A LOT OF MONEY,
AND THEY SHOULD STAND DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> I VOTED FOR PRESIDENT TRUMP,
BUT THERE ARE OTHER ISSUES HE
SHOULD BE MORECEON C WEDRN IT
>> WE AGREE WITH STANDING UP FOR
THE FLAG.
>> Reporter: THE TAKE A KNEE
HASHTAG TWEETED ROUGHLY 2
MILLION TIMES.
>> TONIGHT I'M TAKING A KNEE FOR
AMERICA.
>> Reporter: SINGER
STEVIE WONDER AND HIS SON
KNEELING AT THE GLOBAL CITIZENS
CONCERT LAST NIGHT.
OAKLAND A's BASEBALL PLAYER
BRUCE MAXWELL SHOWING HIS
SUPPORT.
AND TONIGHT, THE NFL WILL PLAY
THIS AD IN PRIMETIME SHOWING HOW
FOOTBALL CAN UNIFY.
>> WE MAY HAVE OUR DIFFERENCES,
BUT RECOGNIZE THERE'S MORE THAT
UNITES US.
>> RYAN JOINS US FROM OUTSIDE
METLIFE STADIUM.
I KNOW YOU'RE TALKING TO YOUR
SOURCES IN THE NFL.
ARE THEY SAYING THIS IS ONLY THE
BEGINNING OF THE PROTESTS?
>> Reporter: EMOTIONS WERE
RUNNING HIGH AMONG MANY PLAYERS,
AND FANS WERE GENERALLY
SUPPORTIVE OF THE PROTESTS ON
SUNDAY.
THAT MEANS THERE COULD BE MORE
PROTESTS TO COME.
>> RYAN, THANK YOU.
>>> SOME BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
TENNESSEE.
A DEADLY CHURCH SHOOTING THERE.
AT LEAST ONE KILLED, SEVERAL
WOUNDED.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE GUNMAN
WEARING A MASK, ARRIVED AT THE
CHURCH AND OPENED FIRE.
A CHURCH MEMBER STANDING UP TO
THE GUNMAN.
ADRIENNE BANKERT IS IN
TENNESSEE.
>> Reporter: THIS SMALL
TENNESSEE CHURCH, RIPPED APART
BY A GUNMAN ON A DEADLY SHOOTING
RAMPAGE.
>> THE CHURCH OF CHRIST PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN SHOT AT THAT LOCATION.
>> Reporter: THE FIRST CALLS
CAME IN AT 11:15 A.M. AS THE
SERVICE AT BURNETTE CHAPEL
CHURCH OF CHRIST NEAR NASHVILLE
LET OUT.
>> THIS IS A LEVEL ONE MASS
CASUALTY INCIDENT.
RGUNMAN KILLED ONE IN THE PARKG
LOT, THEN MADE HIS WAY TO THE
PULPIT.
>> THE GUY CAME FROM THE RIGHT
SIDE OF THE CHURCH, AND HE WAS
JUST SHOOTING.
HE WAS JUST SHOOTING, HE CAME
RIGHT TO THE MIDDLE AND SHOT
MORE.
>> Reporter: MINERVA ROSA'S
DRESS BLOODY FROM HELPING THE
PASTOR, ONE OF SEVEN HURT ALONG
WITH 68-YEAR-OLD LINDA BUSH.
>> SHE WAS PRETENDING TO BE DEAD
SO HE WOULDN'T SHOOT HER AGAIN.
>> Reporter: AFTER SEVERAL
MINUTES OF HORROR, ROBERT INGLE,
A CHURCH USHER, CONFRONTING THE
SHOOTER.
>> HE TACKLED HIM, HE WAS HURT
IN HIS HEAD, AND WITHOUT HIM I
THINK IT COULD HAVE BEEN WORSE.
>> Reporter: THE GUNMAN, NOW
IDENTIFIED BY POLICE AS
25-YEAR-OLD EMANUAL SAMSON, SHOT
DURING THE STRUGGLE.
POLICE SAY THAT HEROIC USHER
SAVED LIVES.
>> THE CHURCH USHER IS AN
EXTRAORDINARILY BRAVE
INDIVIDUAL.
>> Reporter: TOM, POLICE ARE
STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT THE
SHOOTER'S MOTIVES.
HE'S A FORMER MEMBER OF THE
CHURCH, AND THE U.S. ATTORNEY'S
OFFICE IS OPENING UP A CIVIL
RIGHTS INVESTIGATION INTO THE
SHOOTING.
>> ADRIENNE, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT UP, THE U.S. WITH A
SHOW OF FORCE, SENDING A MESSAGE
TO NORTH KOREA.
AMERICAN BOMBERS FLYING NEAR THE
NORTH KOREAN COAST.
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP AND THE
REGIME TRADE NEW INSULTS.
THE PRESIDENT CALLING KIM
JONG-UN LITTLE ROCKET MAN.
NORTH KOREA WARNING THAT AN
ATTACK ON THE U.S. IS BECOMING
MORE INEVITABLE.
HERE'S BOB WOODRUFF.
>> Reporter: AMERICAN
B-1 BOMBERS AND F-15 FIGHTER
JETS TOOK OFF IN THE NIGHT,
FLYING FARTHER NORTH OF THE DMZ
THAN ANY TIME IN NEARLY TWO
DECADES.
WHILE IN PYONGYANG THIS WEEKEND,
THOUSANDS MARCHED THROUGH THE
STREETS DURING A RALLY AGAINST
THE U.S.
THE SHOW OF FORCE FROM BOTH
NATIONS COMES LEY OF
INSULTS REACHES AN ALARMING
LEVE TL.HE VOL
PRESIDENT TRUMP TWEETED
SATURDAY, "JUST HEARD FOREIGN
MINISTER OF NORTH KOREA SPEAK AT
U.N.
IF HE ECHOES THOUGHTS OF LITTLE
ROCKET MAN THEY WON'T BE AROUND"
HIS TWEET COMES AFTER THE NORTH
KOREAN FOREIGN MINISTER SLAMMED
THE PRESIDENT AT THE UNITED
NATIONS, CALLING HIM "A MENTALLY
DERANGED PERSON" WHO "COMMITTED
AN IRREVERSIBLE MISTAKE."
DAYS EARLIER, PRESIDENT TRUMP IN
THE SAME VENUE WITH THAT
WARNING.
>> IF IT IS FORCED TO DEFEND
ITSELF OR ITS ALLIES, WE WILL
HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO TOTALLY
DESTROY NORTH KOREA.
>> Reporter: NORTH KOREA THEN
THREATENED TO TEST A HYDROGEN
BOMB ABOVE THE PACIFIC OCEAN,
SOMETHING THEY HAVE NEVER DONE
BEFORE.
>> EVERYTHING HE HAS SAID HE
WOULD DO.
I WILL TEST A HYDROGEN BOMB, I
WILL SEND AN ICBM TEST.
HE'S DONE.
SO WHY WOULDN'T HE TEST A
HYDROGEN BOMB OVER THE PACIFIC?
>> I THINK THE LIKELIHOOD IS
THERE THAT HE WILL TEST A BOMB
AT SOME POINT.
>> AND BOB JOINS US LIVE.
YOU'VE BEEN COVERING NORTH KOREA
FOR MORE THAN A DECADE, YOU WERE
JUST ON THE NORTH KOREAN/CHINA
BORDER.
AND YOU TOLD ME SOMETHING YOU'VE
NEVER SEEN BEFORE?
>> ON THE CHINESE SIDE, THE
TENSION IS GROWING.
PROBABLY WITH MORE MISSILE
LAUNCHES AND NUCLEAR TESTS.
BUT BOTTOM LINE, THEY HAVE NO
IDEA WHAT KIM JONG-UN WILL DO,
HE'S UNPREDI CLEABOMPARE
>>> AND THE BREAKING HEADLINE
ABOUT JARED KUSHNER.
ABC NEWS HAS CONFIRMED HE USED
PRIVATE E-MAIL FOR WHITE HOUSE
BUSINESS.
THE ACCOUNT REPORTEDLY SET UP
AFTER THE ELECTION, BUT BEFORE
THE INAUGURATION.
HIS ATTORNEY TELLS ABC NEWS
FEWER THAN 100 E-MAILS WERE
SENT, AND ALL HAVE BEEN
PRESERVED.
>>> LET'S TURN NOW TO PUERTO
RICO AND THE STUNNING
DEVASTATION BROUGHT BY HURRICANE
MARIA.
AUTHORITIES BEGINNING TO GET A
FIRSTHAND LOOK AT THE
DESTRUCTION.
FAMILIES CUT OFF WNOH ITEROW P
,
AT LEAST TEN KILLED.
THE IMMINENT THREAT AT THIS
HOUR, A DAM IN DANGER OF
FAILING.
THOUSANDS RUSHING TO HIGHER
GROUND.
HERE'S EVA PILGRIM.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, A DIRE
SITUATION.
OFFICIALS WARNING THIS DAM IN
PUERTO RICO COULD FAIL AT ANY
MOMENT.
>> WE'RE ENCOURAGING FOLKS TO
LEAVE.
IT'S GOING TO BE DIFFICULT TO
COME BACK AND GET THEM.
>> Reporter: AERIAL FOOTAGE
SHOWING THE SPILLWAY OVERFLOWING
AND RIPPING UP EVERYTHING IN ITS
PATH.
NOW THE DAM ITSELF, MORE THAN
THREE FOOTBALL FIELDS WIDE,
CRACKED AND THREATENING TO
COLLAPSE.
RESCUERS SAY GETTING TO THOSE IN
NEED IS DIFFICULT.
>> MOST OF THESE SEARCHERS WE'RE
DOING, WE'RE DOING IT BOOTS ON
THE GROUND.
WE'RE WALKING TO IT.
>> Reporter: ACROSS PUERTO RICO,
OFFICIALS NOW DESCRIBING
CONDITIONS AS "APOCALYPTIC."
FOR FIVE DAYS NOW, MILLIONS CUT
OFF FROM THE REST OF THE WORLD
WITHOUT WATER, FUEL, OR POWER.
>> I KNOW WE'RE NOT GOING TO GET
TO EVERYBODY IN TIME.
>> Reporter: THE LINE FOR JUST
$20 OF GAS STRETCHING FOR
BLOCKS.
>> EIGHT HOURS WAITING FOR GAS.
>> Reporter: AS DESPERATION
MOUNTS, AN ARGUMENT ERUPTS
MOMENTS AFTER THIS GAS STATION
SHUTS DOWN.
AFTER A THREE-HOUR WAIT,
BERTHA MELENDEZ IS EMPTY-HANDED.
>> I'M VERY MAD BECAUSE THIS IS
AN EMERGENCY.
>> Reporter: FACING MONTHS
WITHOUT POWER, MARIA IS NOW
BEING CALLED THE BIGGEST
CATASTROPHE THE ISLAND HAS EVER
SEEN.
AUTHORITIES WATCHING TO SEE HOW
MUCH WATER PUSHES INTO THIS
COLLAPSED SPILLWAY.
TONIGHT, THAT EVACUATION IS
STILL IN PLACE.
TOM?
>> EVA, THANK YOU.
>>> AND HURRICANE MARIA TONIGHT
CLOSING IN ON THE EAST COAST.
BUT WILL IT HIT THE MAINLAND?
ROB MARCIANO JUST BACK FROM
PUERTO RICO.
ROB, WE GOT TO KEEP A CLOSE EYE
ON MARIA.
>> WE DO.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S A CATEGORY 2
STORM.
400 MILES SOUTHEAST OF CAPE
HATTERAS.
105-MILE-AN-HOUR WINDS.
A CATEGORY STORM BY NORTH
CAROLINA WEDNESDAY.
IT WILL BE CLOSE ENOUGH TO HAVE
DIRECT IMPACTS.
TROPICAL STORM WATCHES POSTED
FOR EASTERN PARTS OF NORTH
CAROLINA.
COLD FRONT WILL KICK IT OUT.
92 DEGREES FOR FIVE DAYS IN A
ROW IN CHICAGO.HA THIS LATE IN E
YEAR.
BY THURSDAY, THE COLD FRONT
SQUEEZES THE WARM AIR OUT AND
MARE YA AS WELL.
THAT WILL KICK MARIA TO SEA.
>>> AND THE REPUBLICAN HEALTH
CARE BILL IN CRITICAL CONDITION.
TWO GOP SENATORS ALREADY SAYING
THEY WILL VOTE NO ON THE BILL TO
REPEAL AND REPLACE OBAMA CARE.
TED CRUZ AND SUSAN COLLINS
SIGNALING THEY WON'T VOTE FOR IT
EITHER.
JUST ONE MORE NO VOTE MEANS THE
BILL COULD FAIL.
MITCH McCONNELL SAYS HE STILL
WANTS A VOTE THIS WEEK.
>>> STILL AHEAD, THE COFFEE
RECALL.
CONTAMINATED.  MAY BE
>>> PLUS, THE AIR SHOW
CATASTROPHE CAPTURED ON VIDEO.
THOUSANDS WATCHING IN HORROR.
>>> PLUS, THE MYSTERIOUS AND
DANGEROUS CLASH BETWEEN A DRONE
AND A MILITARY CHOPPER.
THE DRAMATIC NEW DETAILS, JUST
COMING IN.
We cut the price of trades to
give investors even more value.
And at $4.95, you can trade
with a clear advantage.
Fidelity, where smarter
investors will always be.
>>> BACK NOW WITH A COLLISION
OVER THE SKIES AT THE U.N.
GENERAL ASSEMBLY.
THE INCIDENT INVOLVING A DRONE
AND A MILITARY HELICOPTER.
RAISING NEW QUESTIONS TONIGHT.
HERE'S ERIELLE RESHEF.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE PUSH
TO FIND THE PILOT WHO SLAMMED A
DRONE INTO THIS BLACK HAWK
HELICOPTER.
THE CRASH, THE FIRST BETWEEN A
DRONE AND A MILITARY AIRCRAFT.
IT HAPPENED JUST 500 FEET ABOVE
A NEW YORK NEIGHBORHOOD.
THE FAA SAYS IT'S ILLEGAL TO FLY
PRIVATE DRONES THAT HIGH.
THE 82nd AIRBORNE PILOT MANAGED
TO LAND THE BLACK HAWK SAFELY AT
A NEW JERSEY AIRPORT.
THE CHOPPER, TASKED WITH
PATROLLING THE UNITED NATIONS
GENERAL SEMBLY, TEMPORARILY
GROUNDED BECAUSE OF DAMAGE TO
THE BLADES AND WINDOW.
THIS FRAGMENT OF THE DRONE, THE
ONLY CLUE ABOUT WHO MAY HAVE
BEEN FLYING IT.
>> SOONER OR LATER WE ARE GOING
TO LOSE AN AIRPLANE TO A DRONE
DUE TO A COLLISION.
>> Reporter: LAW ENFORCEMENT
INCREASINGLY DEALING WITH THESE
HIGH-FLYING HAZARDS.
>> WE JUST HAD A NEAR MIDAIR
COLLISION WITH A DRONE.
>> Reporter: THIS SUMMER, A
DRONE CAME WITHIN 100 FEET OF A
STATE POLICE AIRCRAFT IN ACHUSE.
ANOTHER INCHED DANGEROUSLY CLOSE
TO A POLICE CHOPPER IN NORTH
CAROLINA.
>> IT COULD HAVE BEEN A
CATASTROPHIC EVENT.
>> Reporter: TOM, NONE OF THE
PARATROOPERS INSIDE THE BLACK
HAWK WERE INJURED.
THE 82nd AIRBORNE DIVISION SAYS
ITS PILOT HAD NO WARNING A DRONE
WAS NEARBY.
TOM?
>> ERIELLE, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE NEW
HEADLINE JUST COMING IN.
BRAND NEW DETAILS ON THE
PRESIDENT'S TRAVEL BAN.
THE NEW PROCLAMATION FROM THE
BAN.E HOUSE TONIGHT.
WHITE HOUS
NIGHT.
♪
[ Laughs ]
Rodney.
Bowling. Classic.
Can I help you?
It's me. Jamie.
I'm not good with names.
Celeste!
I trained you.
We share a locker.
-Moose man!
-Yo.
s o
Name Your Price Tools.
I trained you.
We share a locker.
He gets two?
I literally coined the phrase,
"We give you coverage options
based on your budget."
-That's me.
-Jamie!
-Yeah.
-You're back from Italy.
[ Both smooch ]
Ciao bella.
>>> TIME NOW FOR OUR "INDEX."
BREAKING NEWS, PRESIDENT TRUMP
REVEALING HIS NEW TRAVEL BAN.
THE CURRENT BAN EXPIRING TODAY.
THE PRESIDENT ISSUING A NEW
ORDER, IMPOSING TRAVEL
RESTRICTIONS ON CHAD, IRAN,
LIBYA, NORTH KOREA, SYRIA,
VENEZUELA AND YEMEN.
>>> NOW TO THE AIR SHOW HORROR
OVERSEAS.
LEANTILITANG A L AOO FP
MID-PERFORMANCE FAILING TO GET
ENOUGH ALTITUDE AND PLUNGING
DOWN INTO THE SEA.
IT HAPPENED SOUTH OF ROME.
OFFICIALS SAYING THAT PILOT WAS
KILLED.OLWING A
COFFEE RECALL.
THE FDA SAYING WATCH OUT FOR
NITRO BREW MADE BY THE DEATH
WISH COFFEE COMPANY.
THIS IS NOT A JOKE.
THE 11-OUNCE CANS MAY CONTAIN
BOTULISM, A POTENTIALLY FATAL
FOOD POISONING.
MAKERS OF THE COFFEE, WHICH HAS
ABOUT FOUR TO FIVE TIMES THE
CAFFEINE OF A REGULAR CUP, SAY
THROW IT AWAY OR RETURN IT FOR A
REFUND.
THEY SAY THEY ARE HALTING
PRODUCTION UNTIL THEY ADJUST
THEIR MANUFACTURING PROCESS.
>>> AND UP NEXT, WHEN WE COME
BACK, THE INVICTUS GAMES CLOSE
UP.
ONE COMPETITOR WHO REFUSED TO
GIVE UP.
THE AMAZING COMEBACK.
STAY WITH US.
d constipation,
and you're overwhelmed
by everything you've tried--
all those laxatives,
daily probiotics,
endless fiber--
it could be wearing on you.
Tell your doctor
what you've tried,
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults
with IBS
with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help relieve
your belly pain
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.e NZESS
to children less than six
and it should not be given
to children
six to less than eighteen.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS
if you have a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop
unusual or severe
stomach pain,
especially with
bloody or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe,
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor
right away.
Other side effects
include gas,
stomach-area pain
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
you get time for more life.
This family wanted to
keep the game going.
SON: Hey mom, one more game?
TECH: With Safelite, you get a
text when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
MOM: Sure.
Bring it!
TECH: I'm Micah with Safelite.
MOM: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care!
FAMILY: Bye!
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis?
How do you chase what you love
Do what I did.
Ask your doctor about HUMIRA.
It's proven to help relieve pain
and protect joints
from further irreversible damage
in many adults.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to block
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes to RA symptoms.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 20 years.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
d nervousyst proems,   rioualle,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
Ready for a new chapter?
Talk to your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA at work.
when you switch to Progressive.
Winds stirring.
Too treacherous for a selfie.
[ Camera shutter clicks ]
Sure, I've taken discounts
to new heights
with safe driver
and paperless billing.
But the prize at the top
is worth every last breath.
Here we go.
[ Grunts ]
Got 'em.
Ahh.
Wait a minute.
Whole wheat waffles?
[ Crying ] Why!
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, INVICTUS IS
LATIN FOR UNCONQUERED.
AND TONIGHT, IT'S ALSO THE VERY
DEFINITION OF THE WORD COMEBACK.
HERE'S MARCI GONZALEZ.
>> Reporter: A DECADE AFTER HIS
VEHICLE STRUCK AN IED IN IRAQ
KILLING THE SOLDIER NEXT TO HIM
AND LEAVING HIM WITH A SPINAL
CORD INJURY,
COLONEL DANIEL DUDEK, TAKING ON
THIS CHALLENGE, ON THE TRACK AND
IN THE POOL.
IT'S MORE THAN AN HONOR.
IT'S PART OF HIS HEALING.
>> DISTRACTION IS THE BEST
MEDICINE.
SO, SPORT IS THE BEST
DISTRACTION.
>> Reporter: HE IS ONE OF THE
550 INJURED MILITARY VETERAN
ATHLETES FROM 17 COUNTRIES
COMPETING IN THIS YEAR'S
INVICTUS GAMES IN TORONTO.
NOW IN HIS 26th YEAR OF MILITARY
SERVICE, HE IS STILL ON ACTIVE
DUTY.
AS HE FIGHTS TO TAKE HOME A
MEDAL FOR TEAM USA.
>> I'M GONNA BEAT MY TIMES, I'M
GONNA DO WHAT I CAN TO WIN.
>> Reporter: AND IN THE CROWDS,
THE CREATOR OF THE INVICTUS
GAMES, PRINCE HARRY.
>> HE IS A WARRIOR, I FEEL LIKE
HE IS ONE OF US.
>> Reporter: FIRST LADY
MELANIA TRUMP ALSO THERE.
BUT FOR DUDEK, THE FOCUS IS ON
THE INSPIRATION THIS COMPETITION
CAN SPARK FOR WOUNDED WARRIORS.
HEROES, JUST LIKE HIM.
>> THINGS LIKE THIS HOPEFULLY
CAN PUT A SPOTLIGHT ON SOMETHING
THAT I LD EOANE E TOI  LNTOVE.WA
>> Reporter: MARCI GONZALES, ABC
NEWS.
>> THANKS TO MARCY AND THE
ORGANIZERS OF THE INVICTUS
GAMES, AND ALL THE INCREDIBLE
ATHLETES.
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
I'M TOM LLAMAS IN NEW YORK.
"GMA" FIRST THING IN THE
MORNING.
DAVID MUIR WILL BE RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
"GMA" FIRST THING IN THE
MORNING.
DAVID MU
>>> TONIGHT ON ABC 7 NEWS AT
6:00, DRAWING A CROWD TO A
CANNES WOULD EVENT.
A RIGHT-WING COMMENTATORS
APPEARANCE PROVES COSTLY FOR
CAMPUS POLICE.
>>> TAKING A STANCE BY KNEELING
DOWN.
THE CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT
GAINING STRENGTH AFTER THE
PRESIDENT'S CONTROVERSIAL
COMMENTS AND ACLAMATION
FROM THE PRESIDENT TONIGHT
EXTENDS TRAVEL RESTRICTIONS.
ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
>>> LIVE, WHERE YOU LIVE, THIS
IS ABC 7 NEWS.
>>> A PEACEFUL APPEARANCE, BUT A
BIG PRICE TAG.
TODAY CONSERVATIVE PROVOCATEUR
SHOWED UP AT A CANCELED EVENT
WHERE HE DREW A FEW SUPPORTERS
AND A LOT OF POLICE.
GOOD EVENING.
I'M ERIC THOMAS.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
MILO YIANNOPOULOUS WAS IN AND
OUT WITH LITTLE TO NO
RESISTANCE.
BUT AS TIFFANY WILSON TELLS US,
THAT'S NOT WHAT HE'S SAYING.
SHE JOINS US LIVE FROM BERKELEY.
>> Reporter: WE SAW INTERESTING
INCONSISTENCIES BETWEEN WHAT WE
SAW HERE IN THE FIELD AND THE
STATEMENT THAT MILO
YIANNOPOULOUS RELEASED.
HE SAYS THAT PROTESTERS STORMED
THE BARRICADES AND THAT HE HAD
TO BE RUSHED OUT OF UC
BERKELEY'S CAMPUS.
WE WERE RIGHT THERE AND WE DID
NOT SEE ANYONE GOING OVER THE
BARRICA
BARRICADES.
IN FACT, IT WOULD HAVE BEEN VERY
DIFFICULT TO DO SO BECAUSE THERE
WERE POLICE OFFICERS EVERY FEW
FEET ALONG THE PERIMETER.
ALSO UC BERKELEY OFFICIALS SAY
THEY DON'TWHY
LEFT WHEN HE DID, BUT IT WAS HIS
CHOICE.
HIS UNSANCTIONED AND UNSPONSORED
APPEARANCE ON UC BERKELEY'S
CAMPUS CREATED HOURS OF
DISRUPTION AND DISCORD.
AND IT COST THE UNIVERSITY AT
LEAST $800,000 IN SECURITY.
YIANNOPOULOS SAW IT DIFFERENTLY.
>> I GOT TO