>> BYE-BYE.
>>> TONIGHT, THE HORROR SEEN
AROUND THE WORLD.
THE IMAGES ARE DISTURBING.
THE DEADLY CHEMICAL ATTACK
UNLEASHED IN SYRIA.
WE ARE STAYING AWAY FROM THE
MOST GRUESOME MOMENTS.
FAMILIES, CHILDREN, AMONG THE
VICTIMS.
GASPING FOR AIR TO SURVIVE.
AND THE MOMENT ANOTHER EXPLOSION
HITS.
OUR TEAM MAKING CONTACT WITH A
DOCTOR ON THE GROUND.
>>> ALSO BREAKING, PRESIDENT
TRUMP AND HIS CLAIM THAT
PRESIDENT OBAMA WIRETAPPED TRUMP
TOWER BEFORE THE ELECTION.
NOW, THE NEW QUESTION TONIGHT
INVOLVING PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER,
SUSAN RICE.
DID SHE ASK FOR NAMES?
DID SHE UNMASK THEM?
MEMBERS OF THE TRUMP TEAM CAUGHT
UP IN SURVEILLANCE BY THE U.S.
WHAT SHE IS SAYING TONIGHT.
>>> THE ABC NEWS INVESTIGATION.
FORMER TRUMP CAMPAIGN ADVISER
CARTER PAGE.
WERE RUSSIAN SPIES ACTIVELY
TRYING TO RECRUIT HIM TO WORK
FOR THEM?
BRIAN ROSS FINDS HIM TODAY.
>> DID YOU GIVE THEM DOCUMENTS?
DID YOU RECEIVE DOCUMENTS FROM
THEM?
>>> AND, TWO SEPARATE MANHUNTS.
THE OFFICER KILLED SHOWING UP TO
WORK.
AND IN ATLANTA, THE FEMALE
LAWYER TARGETED AND KILLED
DURING RUSH HOUR.
NEW REPORTING TONIGHT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US
ON A TUESDAY NIGHT.
WE'RE GOING TO BEGIN TONIGHT
WITH THE IMAGES THAT HAVE
STUNNED THE WORLD.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE THAT AFTER
SIX YEARS OF WAR IN SYRIA, THERE
COULD BE SOMETHING EVEN WORSE
THAN WHAT MANY HAVE ALREADY
SEEN.
TONIGHT, OUR TEAM HAS TAKEN
GREAT CARE TO POUR THROUGH THE
IMAGES FIRST, BUT WE WARN YOU,
THEY'RE STILL DIFFICULT TO SEE.
A CHEMICAL ATTACK.
SO MANY FAMILIES AND CHILDREN
AMONG THE VICTIMS.
SURVIVORS BEING SPRAYED OFF,
AFTER WAR PLANES DROPPED WHAT
APPEARS TO BE A TOXIC GAS.
THE WHITE HOUSE RESPONDING.
HERE'S JONATHAN KARL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, OUTRAGE
OVER THESE SCENES OF HORROR AND
SUFFERING IN SYRIA.
AN APPARENT WAR CRIME, A
SUSPECTED SARIN GAS ATTACK BY
THE GOVERNMENT KILLING DOZENS
AND SICKENING MANY MORE, YOUNG
CHILDREN AMONG THE VICTIMS.
RESCUE WORKERS DESPERATELY WORK
TO WASH THE CHEMICAL FROM THE
VICTIMS.
CHILDREN CLINGING TO LIFE,
STRUGGLING TO BREATHE.
>> THE GAS ATTACKS ARE
CONTINUING EVERY DAY AND NO ONE
IS DOING ANYTHING TO STOP THIS
GAS ATTACK.
>> Reporter: THIS ATTACK
FOLLOWING TWO CHLORINE GAS
ATTACKS OVER THE PAST WEEK.
WHILE THIS LOCAL ACTIVIST
REPORTED FROM ONE OF THOSE
HOSPITALS, IT WAS HIT WITH
ANOTHER AIRSTRIKE.
THE WHITE HOUSE CALLED THE
ATTACK "REPREHENSIBLE" AND SAID
IT "CANNOT BE IGNORED BY THE
CIVILIZED WORLD."
BUT THE STATEMENT ALSO TOOK AIM
AT PRESIDENT OBAMA.
"THESE HEINOUS ACTIONS BY THE
BASHAR AL-ASSAD REGIME ARE A
CONSEQUENCE OF THE PAST
ADMINISTRATION'S WEAKNESS AND
IRRESOLUTION."
THAT'S A REFERENCE TO PRESIDENT
OBAMA'S FAILURE TO PUNISH SYRIA
FOR CROSSING THE SO-CALLED RED
LINE WHEN IT USED CHEMICAL
WEAPONS IN 2013.
PRESIDENT OBAMA IN FACT BOASTED
THAT HE HAD WORKED OUT AN
AGREEMENT WITH RUSSIA AND SYRIA
TO GET RID OF ASSAD'S CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
>> ASSAD GAVE UP HIS CHEMICAL
THAT'S NOT SPECULATION ON OUR
PART.
>> Reporter: TRAGICALLY, THAT
WAS NOT TRUE.
AT LEAST SOME OF THE WEAPONS
REMAINED.
THE BIG QUESTION RIGHT NOW IS
WHETHER PRESIDENT TRUMP WILL
HOLD ASSAD ACCOUNTABLE FOR USING
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
HE DIDN'T TALK ABOUT IT TODAY
BUT HE DID SAY THIS IN A SPEECH
ON THE ECONOMY.
>> I'M NOT, AND I DON'T WANT TO
BE, THE PRESIDENT OF THE WORLD.
I'M THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES, AND FROM NOW ON, IT'S
GOING TO BE AMERICA FIRST.
>> Reporter: SECRETARY OF STATE
REX TILLERSON IGNORED QUESTIONS
ON THE ATTACK.
>> MR. SECRETARY, ANY COMMENT ON
THE CHEMICAL ATTACK IN SYRIA?
>> BASHAR AL ASSAD SHOULD STILL
BE PRESIDENT OF SYRIA?
>> Reporter: BUT JUST LAST WEEK
TILLERSON SIGNALED A SIGNIFICANT
CHANGE IN LONGTIME U.S. POLICY
THAT BASHAR AL-ASSAD MUST GO.
>> I THINK THE STATUS IN THE
LONGER TERM STATUS OF PRESIDENT
ASSAD WILL BE DECIDED BY THE
SYRIAN PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THESE
SYRIAN PEOPLE AREN'T DETERMINING
THE STATUS OF ASSAD, THEY ARE
TRYING TO SURVIVE HIS BRUTALITY.
>> AND JON WITH US LIVE TONIGHT
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
SECRETARY TILLERSON DID NOT TAKE
QUESTIONS ON THIS TODAY, BUT HE
APPEARS TO HAVE TAKEN TO HARSHER
LINE IN A STATEMENT TODAY THAN
JUST LAST WEEK?
>> Reporter: A MUCH HARSHER
LINE.
A WRITTEN STATEMENT WHERE HE
CONDEMNED ASSAD.
REFERRING TO HIS BRUTAL,
UNABASHED BARBARISM.
AND HIS FUNDAMENTAL DISREGARD
FOR HUMAN DECENCY.
AND CALLED OUT RUSSIA AND IRAN,
SAYING THEY BEAR GREAT MORAL
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE ATTACKS.
BUT IT'S UNCLEAR WHAT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION WILL DO ABOUT IT
AND WHETHER THEY NOW WANT ASSAD
TO GO.
>> JON, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN TO THE OTHER MAJOR
HEADLINE INVOLVING THE WHITE
HOUSE, AFTER PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CLAIM THAT PRESIDENT OBAMA
WIRETAPPED TRUMP TOWER.
SUSAN RICE ANSWERING QUESTIONS
TONIGHT.
DID SHE ASK THAT MEMBERS OF THE
TRUMP TEAM WERE UNMASKED AFTER
BEING SWEPT UP IN SURVEILLANCE
ON FOREIGN THREATS?
HERE'S CECILIA VEGA.
>> Reporter: IT WAS EXACTLY ONE
MONTH AGO THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
ACCUSED PRESIDENT OBAMA OF
WIRETAPPING HIM IN TRUMP TOWER.
AND TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT'S
CONSERVATIVE ALLIES SAY OBAMA'S
FORMER NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER
SUSAN RICE REVEALED THE
IDENTITIES OF TRUMP ASSOCIATES
SWEPT UP IN SURVEILLANCE.
FROM RICE TODAY, A FIRM DENIAL.
>> THIS IS NOT ANYTHING
POLITICAL HAS BEEN ALLEGED.
THE ALLEGATION IS THAT SOMEHOW
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS
UTILIZED INTELLIGENCE FOR
POLITICAL PURPOSES.
THAT IS ABSOLUTELY FALSE.
>> Reporter: SOURCES TELL ABC
NEWS THAT AS THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY INVESTIGATED RUSSIA'S
ELECTION MEDDLING, IN SOME
CASES, TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND
TRANSITION OFFICIALS WERE PICKED
UP IN SURVEILLANCE.
RICE REQUESTING THEIR
IDENTITIES.
TODAY RICE SAID SHE DID INDEED
ASK TO KNOW NAMES.
A REQUEST KNOWN AS UNMASKING,
DONE IN CASES WHERE U.S.
SECURITY IS AT RISK.
AMERICAN IDENTITIES THAT WOULD
OTHERWISE BE ANONYMOUS ARE
REVEALED TO THOSE WITH SECURITY
CLEARANCE, LIKE RICE.
>> IN ORDER TO UNDERSTAND THE
IMPORTANCE OF THE REPORT, AND
ASSESS ITS SIGNIFICANCE, IT WAS
NECESSARY TO FIND OUT, OR
REQUEST THE INFORMATION AS TO
WHO THAT U.S. OFFICIAL WAS.
>> Reporter: RICE WOULDN'T SAY
WHETHER ANY OF THOSE NAMES WERE
TRUMP ASSOCIATES AND SHE
VEHEMENTLY DENIED THAT SHE
LEAKED ANY NAMES.
>> I LEAKED NOTHING TO NOBODY
AND NEVER HAVE AND NEVER WOULD.
>> Reporter: AND SAYS THE
UNMASKING WAS A KEY PART OF HER
JOB.
>> WE CAN'T BE PASSIVE CONSUMERS
OF THIS INFORMATION AND NOT --
AND DO OUR JOBS EFFECTIVELY TO
PROTECT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
IMAGINE IF WE SAW SOMETHING OF
GRAVE SIGNIFICANCE THAT INVOLVED
RUSSIA, OR CHINA, OR ANYBODY
ELSE, INTERFERING IN OUR
POLITICAL PROCESS AND WE NEEDED
TO UNDERSTAND THE SIGNIFICANCE
OF THAT.
FOR US NOT TO TRY TO UNDERSTAND
IT WOULD BE DERELICTION OF DUTY.
>> Reporter: REPUBLICANS, NOT
BUYING IT.
SENATOR RAND PAUL TWEETING,
"SMOKING GUN FOUND."
SAYING --
>> SO NOW WE KNOW THAT SOMEONE
IN THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION WAS
EAVESDROPPING AND SPECIFICALLY
SEARCHING A DATABANK LOOKING FOR
THE TRUMP PEOPLE.
>> NO.
NO.
>> THAT'S A BIG DEAL.
>> Reporter: RICE MAINTAINS
THERE WAS NOTHING ILLEGAL, NO
SMOKING GUN, AND NO WIRETAPPING
OF TRUMP TOWER.
>> THERE WAS NO SUCH COLLECTION
OR SURVEILLANCE ON TRUMP TOWER
OR TRUMP INDIVIDUALS AND IT IS
VERY IMPORTANT TO UNDERSTAND,
AND BY THAT I MEAN DIRECTED BY
THE WHITE HOUSE OR TARGETED AT
TRUMP INDIVIDUALS.
>> LET'S GET TO CECILIA VEGA,
AND SOME REPUBLICANS ARE CALLING
FOR RICE TO TESTIFY.
WHERE DOES THE WHITE HOUSE
STAND?
>> Reporter: THEY'RE NOT
WEIGHING IN ON THIS ONE JUST
YET.
THEY DO, THOUGH, CALL THE
REPORTS ABOUT UNMASKING
TROUBLING, BUT THE CALLS GROWING
LOUDER.
THE REPUBLICANS JUST SENT A
LETTER TO THE SENATE AND HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEES
DEMANDING THAT RICE BE CALLED
UPON TO TESTIFY.
>> CECILIA, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO AN ABC NEWS
INVESTIGATION, AND IT INVOLVES
FORMER TRUMP CAMPAIGN ADVISER
CARTER PAGE.
AND THIS QUESTION -- DID RUSSIAN
SPIES TRY TO RECRUIT HIM TO WORK
FOR THEM?
TONIGHT, THE EVIDENCE, AND HOW
HE ANSWERS WHEN BRIAN ROSS
TRACKED HIM DOWN TODAY.
>> Reporter: TWO YEARS BEFORE
THIS NEW YORK BUSINESSMAN,
CARTER PAGE, BECAME A FOREIGN
POLICY ADVISER TO CANDIDATE
DONALD TRUMP, RUSSIAN SPIES
TRIED TO RECRUIT HIM AS AN
INTELLIGENCE SOURCE.
FBI DOCUMENTS SHOW THEY OFFERED
PAGE, IDENTIFIED AS MALE NUMBER
1, "FAVORS" AND "BUSINESS
OPPORTUNITIES" IN RUSSIA IN
EXCHANGE FOR INFORMATION.
"HE FLIES TO MOSCOW MORE OFTEN
THAN I DO," ONE RUSSIAN SPY TOLD
ANOTHER ABOUT PAGE.
"IT'S OBVIOUS THAT HE WANTS TO
EARN LOTS OF MONEY."
"YOU PROMISE A FAVOR FOR A
FAVOR."
THE SPIES, POSING AS RUSSIAN
TRADE OFFICIALS, SAID PAGE
PROVIDED THEM WITH DOCUMENTS ON
THE U.S. ECONOMY.
TODAY PAGE TOLD ABC NEWS THAT
ANY DOCUMENTS HE PASSED TO THE
RUSSIANS WERE OF LITTLE
CONSEQUENCE.
>> ANY INFORMATION I WOULD GIVE
IS, IS, AGAIN, IMMATERIAL.
AND ALL PUBLIC INFORMATION.
>> Reporter: DID YOU FEEL LIKE
YOU WERE WORKING FOR THEM AS AN
INTELLIGENCE SOURCE?
>> OF COURSE NOT, OF COURSE NOT.
>> Reporter: THAT'S WHAT THEY
CALL YOU.
>> IT'S RIDICULOUS.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S RIDICULOUS
ABOUT IT?
>> EVERYTHING.
MAKING IT UP AGAIN.
NOTHING.
GOOD TO SEE YOU.
>> Reporter: RUSSIA'S INTEREST
IN PAGE CONTINUED DURING THE
CAMPAIGN.
LAST JULY, THE LITTLE-KNOWN
BUSINESSMAN WAS INVITED TO
DELIVER A PRESTIGIOUS SPEECH AT
A MOSCOW UNIVERSITY WHERE HE
DENOUNCED THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION.
BUT PAGE HAS SAID ALLEGATIONS HE
SERVED AS A GO-BETWEEN FOR THE
KREMLIN AND THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
OR MET WITH SENIOR RUSSIAN
OFFICIALS ARE FALSE.
>> COMPLETELY MADE UP AND --
>> Reporter: NEVER HAPPENED?
>> ABSOLUTELY NEVER HAPPENED.
YEAH.
>> Reporter: BUT SINCE THAT
INTERVIEW, PAGE HAS ACKNOWLEDGED
HE DID MEET WITH THE RUSSIAN
AMBASSADOR AT THE REPUBLICAN
CONVENTION IN CLEVELAND.
WHITE HOUSE AIDES SAY PAGE WAS
NEVER A MAJOR PLAYER IN THE
CAMPAIGN.
AND THE RUSSIAN SPIES WHO TRIED
TO RECRUIT HIM ARE NOW BACK IN
MOSCOW.
>> BRIAN, DURING THE CAMPAIGN,
AMERICAN INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS
BECAME CONCERNED THAT PAGE WAS
ADVISING DONALD TRUMP?
>> THAT'S RIGHT, WHEN HE SHOWED
UP IN MOSCOW TO GIVE THE SPEECH
LAST JULY, IT ONLY ADDED TO
THEIR CONCERNS ABOUT THE
POSSIBLE RUSSIAN CONNECTION.
>> BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> MEANTIME ON CAPITOL HILL,
THE NEW EFFORT TO REPEAL AND
REPLACE OBAMACARE, TAKE TWO.
PRESIDENT TRUMP REPORTEDLY
HOPING FOR A VOTE NOW BY THE END
OF THE WEEK.
INTENSE MEETINGS TAKING PLACE
WITH SOME CONSERVATIVE
REPUBLICANS WHO STOPPED THE DEAL
LAST TIME.
BUT COULD PRE-EXISTING CONDITION
COVERAGE BE GOING AWAY IN THIS
NEW REPLACEMENT?
HERE'S MARY BRUCE.
>> Reporter: ON CAPITOL HILL
TODAY, VICE PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE
STEPPING IN TO BRING HEALTH CARE
REFORM BACK FROM THE DEAD.
IS HEALTHCARE GOING TO GET DONE
THIS WEEK?
WHAT MAKES THIS TIME ANY
DIFFERENT?
THE WHITE HOUSE IS NOW TRYING TO
STRIKE A DEAL WITH THE FREEDOM
CAUCUS, THOSE ULTRA-CONSERVATIVE
MEMBERS WHO KILLED THE FIRST
BILL.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ATTACKING THEM
EVER SINCE.
BUT NOW, EAGER FOR A WIN, THE
WHITE HOUSE SEEMS TO BE PUTTING
ON THE TABLE SOMETHING THE
PRESIDENT VOWED NOT TO TOUCH.
>> WHEN YOU REPLACE IT, ARE YOU
GOING TO MAKE SURE THAT PEOPLE
WITH PRECONDITIONS ARE STILL
COVERED?
>> YES.
BECAUSE IT HAPPENS TO BE ONE OF
THE STRONGEST ASSETS.
>> Reporter: TODAY, THE WHITE
HOUSE IS CONSIDERING EFFECTIVELY
DOING AWAY WITH THAT PROVISION.
PEOPLE WITH PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS COULD SEE THEIR
HEALTH CARE COSTS SKYROCKET.
ALSO ON THE CHOPPING BLOCK, THE
REQUIREMENT THAT INSURANCE
COMPANIES COVER ESSENTIAL
BENEFITS LIKE WELLNESS VISITS,
MENTAL HEALTH TREATMENT,
MATERNITY CARE AND EVEN
AMBULANCES.
NOW, INDIVIDUAL STATES COULD OPT
OUT.
SO, IS HEALTHCARE REFORM BACK
ON?
>> YES, IT IS.
>> Reporter: REPUBLICANS KNOW
THE CLOCK IS TICKING.
WITH MEMBERS ABOUT TO HEAD HOME
FOR TWO WEEKS, THEY COULD BE
FACING MORE OF THIS.
>> IF YOU YELL ONE MORE TIME
LIKE THAT, I'M GOING TO ASK
YOU --
[ BOOING ]
>> Reporter: STILL, TONIGHT, NO
AGREEMENT.
>> IT'S PREMATURE TO SAY WHERE
WE ARE OR WHAT WE'RE ON, BECAUSE
WE'RE AT THAT CONCEPTUAL STAGE
RIGHT NOW.
>> MARY, ARE MODERATE
REPUBLICANS GOING TO BE ONBOARD
THIS TIME?
>> Reporter: THE REPUBLICANS ARE
FACING THE SAME BALANCING ACT
THAT DERAILED THEM THE FIRST
TIME.
ANY CONCESSIONS TO CONSERVATIVES
RISK ALIENATING THE MODERATES.
THE VICE PRESIDENT IS BACK HERE
ON CAPITOL HILL TONIGHT MEETING
WITH REPUBLICAN LEADERS.
THEY'RE EAGER TO GET THIS DONE.
>> MARY, THANK YOU.
>>> ALSO THIS EVENING, IVANKA
TRUMP ANSWERING CRITICISM ABOUT
HER INVOLVEMENT WITH HER
FATHER'S ADMINISTRATION.
TAKING ON AN OFFICIAL ROLE AT
THE WHITE HOUSE AS AN ASSISTANT
TO THE PRESIDENT.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH CBS NEWS,
ASKED WHETHER SHE'S COMPLICIT
WITH HIS POLICIES, HERE'S WHAT
SHE SAID.
>> IF BEING COMPLICIT IS WANTING
TO, IS WANTING TO BE A FORCE FOR
GOOD, AND TO MAKE A POSITIVE
IMPACT, THEN I'M COMPLICIT.
>> IVANKA TRUMP WITH CBS.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, EXTREME
WEATHER ON THE WAY FOR MUCH OF
THE EAST.
FROM THE GULF UP THROUGH THE
OHIO VALLEY.
54 MILLION AMERICANS IN THE PATH
OF SEVERE STORMS.
POSSIBLE TORNADOES.
THE LATEST, IN DAYS OF DAMAGING
STORMS WE'VE BEEN COVERING.
THIS TORNADO WHIPPING UP 100
MILES AN HOUR, RIPPING OFF THE
SIDE OF A VIRGINIA BEACH HOME.
AFTERWARD, YOU CAN SEE THE OWNER
ON THE LEFT OPENING THE DOOR,
CREEPING TOWARD WHERE THERE USED
TO BE A BEDROOM WALL.
AND ROB MARCIANO, THIS IS GOING
TO BE ALL THE WAY UP THE COAST.
RIGHT INTO THE OHIO VALLEY.
>> Reporter: AND SEVERAL DAYS OF
IT.
A SNOWSTORM IN DENVER.
NOW IN THE PLAINS.
AND SEVERE WEATHER ALREADY
POPPING.
IN OKLAHOMA, A SEVERE WEATHER
WATCH THERE, WITH THE STORMS
FIRING.
DAMAGING HAIL AND WIND.
AND IT'S GOING TO EXPAND, BY
TOMORROW MORNING, TWO BANDS
ACROSS ALABAMA, MISSISSIPPI, THE
SOUTHEAST.
AND ANOTHER ROUND OF SEVERE
WEATHER LATE TOMORROW.
THE BULL'S EYE WILL BE IN
GEORGIA AND ALABAMA, AND THE
THREAT STRETCHES ALL THE WAY UP
INTO OHIO.
TOMORROW WILL BE A VERY, VERY
ACTIVE DAY.
>> ROB, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS A MASSIVE MANHUNT
IN TEXAS FOR THE KILLER OF A LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICER.
AUTHORITIES SAY THIS BLACK SUV
PULLED UP TO THE COURTHOUSE, AND
OPENED FIRE ON AN OFFICER.
AND REPORTS THAT LAST WEEK,
CLINT GREENWOOD TOLD CO-WORKERS
HE FELT THREATENED BY SOMEONE
HE HAD ONCE INVESTIGATED IN A
CORRUPTION CASE.
THE REWARD STANDS AT 6$5,000.
>>> THERE'S STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT."
NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN THE KILLING
OF A LAWYER IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
THE SUSPECT SEEN ON SURVEILLANCE
RUNNING FROM THE SCENE.
POLICE WITH NEW INFORMATION
TONIGHT COMING IN.
>>> ALSO, THE TEENAGER ATTACKED
BY A SHARK ON THE AMERICAN
COAST.
FIGHTING IT OFF, TO STAY ALIVE.
>>> AND THEN TONIGHT, THE SMALL
PLANE SLAMMING INTO THE SIDE OF
A MOUNTAIN.
THE DELTA 767 THAT HEARD THEIR
CALLS FOR HELP.
YOU'LL SEE WHAT HAPPENED NEXT.
may not always be clear.
But at T. Rowe Price,
we can help guide your
retirement savings.
So wherever your
retirement journey
takes you,
we can help you
reach your goals.
Call us
or your advisor
T. Rowe Price.
Invest With Confidence.
...it shouldn't be
Whateverfleas and ticks. home...
No, no no no no...
Seresto® kills and
repels fleas and ticks
for 8 continuous months -
for effective protection
in an easy-to-use,
non-greasy collar.
8-month Seresto®. From Bayer.
So find a Venus Smooth that
contours to curves,
The smoother the skin, the more
comfortable you are in it.
flexes for comfort,
and has a disposable
made for you.
Skin smoothing Venus razors.
Don't let dust and allergens
and life's beautiful moments.
Flonase Allergy Relief
delivers more complete relief.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause all your symptoms,
including nasal congestion
and itchy, watery eyes.
Flonase is an
allergy nasal spray
that works even
beyond the nose.
So you can enjoy every
beautiful moment to the fullest.
Flonase.
6>1 Changes everything.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, NEW TROUBLE
FOR FOX NEWS.
A NEW LAWSUIT, THIS TIME
CLAIMING RACIAL DISCRIMINATION.
AND IT COMES AFTER ALLEGATIONS
OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT.
TONIGHT, THERE'S NEW FALLOUT ON
THAT FRONT AS WELL.
A GROWING NUMBER OF ADVERTISERS
FLEEING BILL O'REILLY'S SHOW.
HERE'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> Reporter: A BURGEONING
BOYCOTT OF FOX NEWS TONIGHT AS
MORE THAN 15 COMPANIES PLAN TO
PULL ADS FROM THE NETWORK'S
TOP-RATED SHOW, "THE O'REILLY
FACTOR," IN THE WAKE OF REPORTS
BILL O'REILLY AND FOX NEWS PAID
FIVE WOMEN A TOTAL OF ALMOST
$13 MILLION IN SETTLEMENTS
DATING BACK 15 YEARS.
JUST YESTERDAY, RADIO HOST
DR. WENDY WALSH SAID SHE TOO WAS
SEXUALLY HARASSED BY O'REILLY.
>> HE TOLD ME I WAS A BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN.
HE ASKED ME TO GO TO HIS HOTEL
ROOM.
AND THEN HE BECAME HOSTILE TO ME
WHEN I SAID NO AND I WAS SOON
AFTER DISCONTINUED FROM HIS
SHOW.
>> Reporter: WALSH SAYS SHE IS
NOT ASKING FOR MONEY.
BUT MONEY IS WHAT O'REILLY SAYS
IS WHAT MAKES HIM A TARGET.
IN A STATEMENT POSTED ON HIS
WEBSITE OVER THE WEEKEND,
O'REILLY SAYS HE HAS TO PUT TO
REST ANY CONTROVERSIES TO SPARE
HIS CHILDREN.
TONIGHT, FOX NEWS IS RESPONDING,
SAYING WE VALUE OUR PARTNERS,
AND ARE WORKING WITH THEM TO
ADDRESS THEIR CURRENT CONCERNS
ABOUT "THE O'REILLY FACTOR."
>> LINSEY, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
LAWYER TARGETED AND KILLED
DURING RUSH HOUR.
YOU'LL SEE THE SUSPECT ON
SURVEILLANCE.
AND THE HEADLINE LATE TODAY.
>>> AND THE SMALL PLANE SLAMMING
INTO THE MOUNTAIN.
THE DELTA 767 THAT HEARD THE
CALLS FOR HELP.
>>> AND THE TEENAGE GIRL
FIGHTING OFF A SHARK ATTACK ON
THE AMERICAN COAST.
HER STORY, WHEN WE COME BACK.
s .
I didn't think there was
anything else to talk about.
But then I realized there was.
So, I finally broke the
silence with my doctor
about what I was experiencing.
He said HUMIRA is
for people like me
who have tried
other medications
but still experience
the symptoms
of moderate to severe
Crohn's disease.
In clinical studies, the
majority of patients on HUMIRA
saw significant
symptom relief.
And many achieved remission.
HUMIRA can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma,
have happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor if
you've been to areas
where certain fungal
infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections,
or have flu-like
symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
If you're still just
managing your symptoms,
talk with your
gastroenterologist about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA,
remission is possible.
and I smoked while
(Amanda) My I was pregnant.
This is the view I had
of my baby in the NICU.
My tip is,
speak into the opening so
your baby can hear you better.
(Announcer) You can quit.
For free help,
call 1-800-QUIT-NOW.
Hey Scout, what's with the
itchys and scratchys?
It's these fleas and ticks.
OW!
I'm getting bit like crazy.
Got any ideas for me?
Well, not all products
work the same.
That's why my owner
gives me K9 Advantix II.
It kills fleas,
ticks and mosquitoes.
Mosquitoes too?
Yep kills all three
through contact --
no biting required.
Wish my owner knew about
K9 Advantix II. Ow!
Well...could be worse.
Ooh. Glorious.
Protect against the bites
that can spread disease.
K9 Advantix II. Wise choice.
[ Rock music playing ]
Have fun
with your replaced windows.
Run away!
[ Grunts ]
Leave him! Leave him!
[ Music continues ]
Brick and mortar,
what?!
[ Music continues ]
[ Tires screech ]
[ Laughs ]
[ Doorbell rings ]
When you bundle home and auto
insurance with Progressive,
you get more
than a big discount.
That's what you get
for bundling home and auto!
Jamie!
You get sneaky-good coverage.
Thanks.
We're gonna live forever!
You get sneaky-good coverage.
Thanks.
Bburning of diabetic nerve pain
these feet...
jumped into city life
as a kid...
...and kept my town moving.
But I couldn't bear my diabetic
nerve pain any longer.
So I talked to my doctor
and he prescribed LYRICA.
LYRICA may cause serious
allergic reactions
or suicidal thoughts
or actions.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have these,
new or worsening depression,
or unusual changes in mood
or behavior.
Or swelling, trouble breathing,
rash, hives, blisters, muscle
pain with fever,
tired feeling or blurry vision.
Common side effects are
dizziness, sleepiness,
weight gain and swelling
of hands, legs, and feet.
Don't drink alcohol while
taking LYRICA.
Don't drive or use machinery
until you know how LYRICA
affects you.
Those who have had a drug or
alcohol problem
may be more likely
to misuse LYRICA.
Now I have less diabetic
nerve pain.
Ask your doctor about
LYRICA.
>>> TO THE "INDEX" TONIGHT.
NEW DEVELOPMENTS AFTER A
SHOOTING DURING RUSH HOUR IN
ATLANTA.
A CORPORATE LAWYER FOR UPS,
TARGETED IN THE CROSSWALK.
LATE TODAY, POLICE ARRESTING THE
SUSPECT, SPOTTED ON
SURVEILLANCE.
INVESTIGATORS BELIEVE SHE WAS
TARGETED.
THEY HAVE NOT SAID WHY.
>>> THE SEARCH AND RESCUE IN
WASHINGTON STATE.
A SMALL PLANE CRASHING INTO THE
SIDE OF A MOUNTAIN IN OLYMPIC
NATIONAL PARK.
THE INSTRUCTOR AND STUDENT
SENDING A DISTRESS CALL.
THEY WERE HEARD BY A DELTA 767
FLYING BY.
THE CREW RELAYING DETAILS TO AIR
TRAFFIC CONTROL.
THEN AIRLIFTED TO SAFETY.
THEY ARE EXPECTED TO BE OKAY.
>>> TO THE SHARK ATTACK IN
FLORIDA.
17-YEAR-OLD CAITLYN TAYLOR
BITTEN ON THE LEG WHILE SWIMMING
OFF DESTIN, FLORIDA.
SHE PUNCHED TO FIGHT OFF THE
SHARK.
HER MOTHER SAYS CAITLYN SUFFERED
CUTS TO HER HAND, JAW AND LEGS,
REQUIRING MORE THAN 120
STITCHES.
SHE'S GOING TO BE OKAY.
>>> NEW CONCERNS ABOUT INTERNET
PRIVACY IN THE HISTORY OF WHAT
YOU LOOK FOR ON YOUR COMPUTER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SIGNING A LAW
ALLOWING INTERNET PROVIDERS TO
SELL YOUR BROWSING HISTORY AND
PERSONAL DATA TO ADVERTISERS.
THE NEW LAW MAKES IT EASIER FOR
COMPANIES SUCH AS COMCAST, AT&T
AND VERIZON TO TRACK YOUR ONLINE
INFORMATION.
IT OVERTURNS AN FCC PRIVACY
REGULATION THAT WAS SET TO TAKE
EFFECT LATER THIS YEAR.
REPUBLICANS HAVE SAID THAT
MEASURE WAS EXCESSIVE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, "AMERICA
STRONG."
THE LITTLE BOY WITH BIG-LEAGUE
DREAMS.
YOU HAVE TO SEE WHAT HAPPENS,
AFTER THE BREAK.
So let me get this straight.
You're a rabbit?
Im Vern, the Orange Money
retirement rabbit, from Voya.
Riiight. And that means...?
I'm the money you save for
retirement.
I help you get organized so your
money could multiply. See?
Got it. Who's he?
He's green money for spending
today.
You know, paying bills, maybe a
little online shopping...
Makes it easy to tell you apart.
That, and I am better looking.
I heard that.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement,
it's time to get Voya.
(Vfirst ingredient?g food's
Corn?
Wheat?
In new Purina ONE True Instinct
Grain Free with Beef,
Real beef is number one.
No corn, wheat or soy.
Support your dog's whole body
health with Purina ONE.
(de♪p breath)
(phone ringing)
They'll call back.
No one knows your Ford better
than Ford and Ford Service.
Right now, during
The Big Tire Event,
get a $140 rebate by mail,
on four select tires.
♪
nitrites or artificial Ham has
preservatives.tes,
Now it's good for us all.
Like those who like.
Sweet
Those who prefer heat.
SFX - a breath of air
And those who just love meat.
Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
Sweet!
What bad back?Gels work so fast
you'll ask
What pulled hammy?
Advil Liqui - Gels make pain a
distant memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
your date with
destiny has arrived.
Let's do this!
New Cinnamon Frosted
Flakes are finally here.
Sweet cinnamon and the
frosted crunch you love.
Well?
Tastes like victory T.
Tastes like victory.
They're great!
Yet up 90% fall short in getting
key nutrients from food alone.
Let's do more.
Add One A Day 50+
a complete multi-vitamin
with 100% daily value
of more than 15
key nutrients.
One A Day 50+.
♪
I love you, basement
guest bathroom.
Your privacy makes you my
number 1 place...
...to go number 2.
I love you, but
sometimes you stink.
♪
New Febreze Air Effects with
OdorClear technology cleans...
...away odors
like never before.
Because the things you love
the most can stink.
And try Febreze Small Spaces to
clean away odors for up...
...to 30 days.
Breathe Happy with New Febreze.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
"AMERICA STRONG."
THE DEVOTED MOM, THE DETERMINED
BOY, AND THE COACH WHO HEARD
THEM.
IT'S A FIELD OF DREAMS FOR ONE
BOY WHO WISHES HE WAS OUT THERE.
8-YEAR-OLD DANNY JONES OF FT.
WORTH, TEXAS, WHO LOVES
BASEBALL.
HE WAS BORN WITHOUT A
FULLY-FUNCTIONING HEART, RELYING
ON JUST HALF OF IT.
HE'S HAD SEVEN SURGERIES, AND IS
STILL WAITING FOR A NEW ONE.
THE BACKPACK HAS LIFE-SAVING
MEDICATION TO KEEP HIS HEART
GOING.
HIS MOTHER WAS DETERMINED TO GET
HIM ON THE FIELD.
>> I ASKED SOME FRIENDS ON
FACEBOOK, DOES ANYBODY HAVE ANY
OLD UNIFORMS.
THAT'S WHAT STARTED THIS.
>> Reporter: THEY HAD MORE THAN
UNIFORMS.
ONE LITTLE LEAGUE COACH HAD A
SPOT ON THE TEAM.
>> I DIDN'T HESITATE.
I SAID, I'LL TAKE HIM.
>> Reporter: EVEN IF HE COULDN'T
PLAY, HE WAS GOING TO BE ON THE
TEAM.
BUT THEN, LOOK, DANNY, UP AT THE
PLATE, DURING PRACTICE.
HIS BACKPACK ON.
HIS BAT READY.
>> HE COMES TO THE FIRST
PRACTICE.
HEY, WHERE DO YOU WANT ME,
COACH?
>> Reporter: AND WITH THAT
WINNING ATTITUDE, HE EARNED A
SPOT.
>> HE SAID, I'VE BEEN WAITING
FOR THIS MY ENTIRE LIFE.
>> Reporter: HE WASN'T THE ONLY
ONE EXCITED.
FINALLY, DANNY'S CHANCE.
>> HE TAUGHT US WAY MORE THAN WE
COULD HAVE EVER IMAGINED.
>> DANNY MADE IT HOME.
THANKS FOR WATCHING ON A TUESDAY
NIGHT.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> A BULLET RIDDLED CAR, COPS
WITH GUNS AND A DEADLY SHOOTING.
ALL HAPPENING IN NAPA.
>>> THEIR TRANSITIONAL HOUSING
BURNED, THEIR SHELTER CLOSES
TOMORROW.
NOW THEY HAVE JUST ONE LAST
PLACE TO TURN FOR HELP.
>>> FREEDOM COMES WITH A $35
MILLION PRICE TAG AND A MURDER
SUSPECT IS WILLING TO PAY FOR IT
IN A STORY YOU'LL ONLY SEE ON
N
ABC7 NEWS.
>>> IN A NONCAPITAL CASE, THE
CONSTITUTION DEMANDS A
REASONABLE BAIL.
>> REASONABLE APPARENTLY COMES
WITH $35 MILLION AND A SUSPECT
IN THIS CASE IS COMING UP WITH
DOUBLE THAT AMOUNT SO SHE CAN
WALK FREE.
>> THIS IS A STORY YOU'LL SEE
ONLY ON ABC7 NEWS, WE HAVE BEEN
TRACKING IT FOR ALMOST A YEAR
NOW.
>> IT WAS LAST APRIL WHEN THIS
MAN KEITH GREEN DISAPPEARED FROM
MILLBRAE.
HIS GIRLFRIEND TIFFANY LI WAS
ONE OF THOSE ARRESTED IN
CONNECTION WITH HIS MURDER AND
SHE'S DUE TO GET OUT OF JAIL IN
THE NEXT WEEK.
HER BAIL IS THE HIGHEST IN
MEMORY, AND SHE'S POSTING EXCISE
THAT AMOUNT AS REQUIRED BY LAW.
>> IN A STORY YOU ONLY SEE ON 7.
VICK?
>> THE LAWYER FOR TIFFANY LEE
WAS TOLD THIS IS THE EIGHTH
HIGHEST BAIL EVER MADE IN THE
COUNTRY IN STATE COURT.
HERE'S HOW SAN MATEO DISTRICT
ATTORNEY STEVE WINESTAT FEELS
ABOUT LI MAKING THAT BAIL.
>> THE RICH DO GET TO BUY THEIR
WAY OUT IN THIS CIRCUMSTANCE,
AND THAT'S BOTHERSOME.
>> Reporter: THE HILLSBORO WOMAN
ACCUSED OF KILLING KEITH GREEN,
HER HUSBAND AND FATHER OF HER
TWO YOUNG CHILDREN.
INSTEAD OF POSTING CASH, THE
EQUITY IN THE PROPERTY HAS TO BE
$70 MILLION, DOUBLE THE $35
MIIO