THAT PLANE?
>> I'LL NOW WAITING FOR THE
VIDEO FROM THE PASSENGERS TAKEN
>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS, THE
AS WE COME ON THE AIR IN THE
WEST.
THE U.S. BRACING FOR A
HURRICANE.
MANDATORY EVACUATIONS.
HURRICANE WARNINGS IN EFFECT
RIGHT NOW.
STATES OF EMERGENCY ACROSS
SEVERAL L SEVERAL STATES.
NATE DEADLY TAKING AIM AT THE
GULF TONIGHT.
THE STORM MOVING RIGHT UP
THROUGH THE NORTHEAST.
ALSO, BREAKING FROM LAS VEGAS
TONIGHT.
WHAT POLICE HAVE JUST REVEALED
ABOUT THE SECURITY GUARD WHO
APPROACHED THAT DOOR.
WHAT LED HIM THERE IN THE FIRST
PLACE AND WHAT WAS WRITTEN ON
THE GUNMAN'S NOTE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SUDDENLY
SUMMONING REPORTERS TELLING THEM
THEY'RE WITNESSING THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM.
OUR REPORTER ASKS THE WHITE
HOUSE TONIGHT -- WHAT IS HE
TALKING ABOUT?
>>> A FAMOUS DALLAS COWBOYS STAR
AND HIS SON.
TONIGHT, A CAMPUS FRATERNITY
ACCUSED OF HAZING HIM DESCRIBED
AS A FIGHT CLUB.
>>> IN NEW YORK CITY,
AUTHORITIES SAY IT WAS AN
ALLEGED TERROR PLOT.
POLICE SAY THE PLANS FOR TIMES
SQUARE AND THE NEW YORK CITY
SUBWAY.
>>> AND KEITH URBAN.
THE MOMENT THAT MOVED SO MANY,
AS WE HONOR THE FACES.
GOOD EVENING AND IT IS GREAT TO
HAVE YOU WITH US ON A FRIDAY
NIGHT.
WE ARE A HURRICANE WEARY NATION
AND YET TONIGHT ANOTHER POWERFUL
STORM HEADED FOR THE U.S.
AT THIS HOUR NATE IS SPEEDING UP
AND GAINING STRENGTH.
RIGHT NOW HEADING INTO THE WARM
WATERS OF THE GULF.
STATES OF EMERGENCY ACROSS THE
GULF.
THE SYSTEM DEADLY BEFORE
ARRIVING.
22 LIVES LOST.
PREPARATIONS UNDER WAY AT THIS
HOUR AND THERE ARE NOW SOME
MANDATORY EVACUATIONS UNDER WAY.
LET'S GET TO GINGER ZEE WITH US
TONIGHT BECAUSE THIS WILL NOT
ONLY HIT THE GULF BUT WILL
TRAVEL THROUGH THE COUNTRY.
>> UP THROUGH THE NORTHEAST.
WE HAVE GOT TO WATCH FOR FLASH
FLOODING ALL THE WAY THROUGH
PENNSYLVANIA.
LET ME TAKE YOU STRAIGHT TO THE
MAP BECAUSE THE PENINSULA IS
SHOWING THE STORM EAST.
FLYING AT 21 MILES PER HOUR.
TO THE NORTH, NORTHWEST.
HURRICANE WARNING IN PLACEOR F
NEW ORLEANS, GULF PORT, BILOXI
MOBILE, TROPICAL WARNINGS
EXTENDING TO INLAND THERE.
THE BRUNT WILL BE FELT SATURDAY
NIGHT THROUGH SUNDAY MORNING.
THAT'S WHEN IT IS GOING TO MAKE
LANDFALL AND SPEEDS UP THROUGH
THE OHIO VALLEY INTO THE
NORTHEAST AND OUT BY TUESDAY.
BUT BEFORE THAT, THE IMPACT
STORM SURGE, FOUR TO SIX FEET.
ANYWHERE IN RED, THE BAY, GULF
SHORES UP TO EIGHT FEET AND TEN
INCHES OF RAIN.
ALONG THE GULF COAST.
>> TRACKING IT INTO THE WEEKEND.
THANK YOU.
IN THE CROSSHAIRS OF THIS STORM
NEW ORLEANS AND THE LOW LYING
CITIES ALONG THE GULF DANGEROUS
FLOODING AND STORM SURGE IS
LIKELY AND THIS QUESTION
TONIGHT.
ARE THE PUMPS READY IN NEW
ORLEANS?
ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI IS THERE.
>> Reporter: ACROSS THE GULF
TONIGHT, THIS IS THE STATE OF
EMERGENCY AND THEY'RE RACING TO
GET READY FOR THIS STORM.
>> WE'RE GOING TO FLOOD.
I KNOW WE'RE GOING TO FLOOD.
THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
OTHERWISE I WOULD STILL BE AT
THE OFFICE RIGHT NOW.
>> IN NEW ORLEANS A DOZEN OF THE
CITY'S DRAINAGE PUMPS AREN'T
WORKING.
THAT THEY NEED TO KEEP THE CITY
DRY.
TEAMS ARE CLEARING DRAINS AND
PARTS OF JEFFERSON PARISHES,
NEW ORLEANS AND ST. BERNARD,
MORE THAN 1,000 FAMILIES FORCED
TO LEAVE THEIR HOMES.
>> ONE OF THE GREATEST THREATS
TO THIS STORM IS NOT NECESSARILY
INTERIOR RAIN, BUT STORM SURGE.
>> Reporter: BILLY ROST IS
LEAVING TONIGHT.
HE'S MOVED EVERYTHING OFF THE
GROUND.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT THE SURGE
IS GOING TO DO.
IF YOU DON'T PICK IT UP YOU LOSE
IT.
THIS IS LIKE A GAMBLE.
>> Reporter: THREE FEET OF STORM
SURGE AND HE'S FINE.
SIX FEET, HE LOSES EVERYTHING.
HE'S EXPECTING FIVE.
>> YOU CAN ONLY DO SO MUCH.
YOU CAN'T RUN FROM WATER, BABY.
>> Reporter: THE STORM HAS
ALREADY KILLED.
AT LEAST 11 DEAD IN NICARAGUA,
AND EIGHT IN COSTA RICA.
DOZENS MORE MISSING AFTER
MUDSLIDES WASHED AWAY HOMES
>> AND STEVE JOINS US LIVE
TONIGHT.
STEVE, YOU WERE TELLING US THOSE
PUMPS CAN PULL OUT AN INCH OF
RAIN IN AN HOUR?
>> Reporter: YES.
BUT THAT'S JUST DURING THE FIRST
HOUR.
AFTER THAT, THE ABILITY OF A
PUMPING STATION DROPS TO ABOUT
HALF AN INCH AN HOUR ASSUMING
ALL THE PUMPS ARE WORKING WHICH
WOULD SURPRISE JUST ABOUT
EVERYONE IN THE CITY.
WHAT THAT MEANS IS THAT IF
SEVERAL INCHES OF RAIN FALL OVER
NEW ORLEANS ALL AT ONCE, THIS
CITY WILL STILL FLOOD EVEN WITH
ALL OF THE PUMPS WORKING
PROPERLY.
>> WE ARE THINKING ABOUT THAT
CITY AND EVERY CITY ALONG THE
GULF.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE MOVE ON TO OTHER
HEADLINES AT THIS HOUR AND FROM
LAS VEGAS NEW DEVELOPMENTS.
WHAT DREW THAT HOTEL SECURITY
GUARD TO THE HOTEL ROOM IN THE
FIRST PLACE AND EVEN THOUGH HE
WAS SHOT THROUGH THE DOOR WAS HE
THE ONE WHO STOPPED MORE
BLOODSHED?
MATT GUTMAN FROM LAS VEGAS
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: FIVE DAYS AFTER THE
WORST MASS SHOOTING IN AMERICAN
HISTORY, LAS VEGAS POLICE
ACKNOWLEDGING THEY STILL DON'T
KNOW WHAT DROVE STEPHEN PADDOCK
TO OPEN FIRE ON THAT HELPLESS
CROWD.
>> I GET IT.
WE ALL WANT ANSWERS.
WE HAVE LOOKED AT EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT WE ARE
LEARNING THAT HERO SECURITY
GUARD JESUS CAMPOS MAY HAVE
PREVENTED FURTHER BLOODSHED.
POLICE SAY PADDOCK HAD BEEN
SHOOTING WHEN CAMPOS ARRIVED ON
THE 32nd FLOOR RESPONDING TO A
DOOR ALARM.
>> WE BELIEVE HE WAS SHOOTING
INTO THE CROWD, AND THEN THE
SECURITY GUARD WAS SHOT DURING
THAT EVENT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT WE ARE
LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE FRANTIC
EFFORTS TO SAVE THE VICTIMS.
48-YEAR-OLD DOUG CARTER WAS
ATTENDING THE CONCERT WITH HIS
WIFE AND SON.
BUT THEY BECAME SEPARATED IN THE
CHAOS.
YOU SEE DOUG HERE DAZED AND
STAGGERING, A BULLET IN HIS ARM.
THE MAN TAKING THIS VIDEO RAY
PAGE TAKES HIM TO A MAKE-SHIFT
TRIAGE CENTER.
>> STAND RIGHT HERE.
HE'S IN SHOCK.
>> Reporter: IN THE DARK YOU
HEAR HIM MUMBLE ABOUT HIS GUT.
>> I GOT MY GUT HURTS THOUGH.
>> Reporter: WHEN THE PEOPLE
HELPING HIM PULL UP HIS SHIRT
THAT LIGHT ILLUMINATES ANOTHER
BULLET HOLE IN HIS CHEST.
>> I DO GOT ONE?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: POLICE OFFICERS
COMFORTING HIM, KEEPING HIM
CALM.
RAY PAGE THEN GOES TO GET HIS
TRUCK.
>> I'M GOING TO TRY TO FIND A
MEDIC.
I'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>> Reporter: WHEN HE RETURNS
VICTIMS PILING INTO HIS PICKUP.
RAY PAGE DELIVERING DOUG AND THE
OTHERS TO SAFETY.
AND IT WOULD BE 14 AGONIZING
HOURS UNTIL DOUG WAS REUNITED
WITH HIS FAMILY.
DID YOU KNOW HE WAS HIT?
>> I HAD NO IDEA UNTIL 12:00 THE
NEXT DAY WHEN WE FOUND HIM IN
THE HOSPITAL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT HIS SON IS
THANKFUL TO THE HEROES WHO SAVED
HIS DAD.
>> JUST AMAZING THERE WAS
SOMEBODY THERE TO HELP MY DAD
AND HE WAS -- I THOUGHT HE WAS
ON THE STREET SOMEWHERE.
I HAD NO IDEA.
>> MATT POLICE ARE CALLING THAT
SECURITY GUARD A TRUE HERO.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
POLICE ARE SAYING AS THAT GUARD
NEARED THE DOOR IT DIVERTED HIS
ATTENTION FROM THE CROWD TO THE
HALLWAY.
HE BEGAN FIRING WILDLY INTO IT
INJURING THAT SECURITY GUARD.
SOMEHOW THAT GUARD MANAGED TO
GET AWAY AND ALERT AUTHORITIES.
HE'S BEING HAILED AS A HERO AS
THE CITY CONTINUES TO MOURN.
THERE HAVE BEEN THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE HERE AT THIS MEMORIAL
SITE ALL DAY DAVID.
>> ALSO TONIGHT, WHAT WAS
WRITTEN ON A NOTE FOUND IN THE
GUNMAN'S HOTEL ROOM AS WE
LEARNED HOW MUCH THE GUNMAN MADE
IN THE DAYS BEFORE THE ATTACK
AND THE MILLIONS HE MADE IN JUST
ONE YEAR.
HERE'S BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: SHE JUST RETURNED
TO THE US FROM THE PHILIPPINES
TWO DAYS AGO, BUT TONIGHT
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES HAVE PUT A
CLOSE WATCH ON MARILOU DANLEY TO
MAKE SURE SHE DOESN'T TRY TO
LEAVE THE COUNTRY AS THEY
STRUGGLE TO FIND THE MOTIVE
BEHIND HER BOYFRIEND'S CRIME.
>> WE HAVE NO CREDIBLE
INFORMATION TO REPORT TO YOU AS
TO MOTIVATION.
>> Reporter: FBI AGENTS AND
POLICE SAY THEY ARE SKEPTICAL OF
DANLEY'S CLAIMS THAT SHE KNEW
NOTHING ABOUT THE PLANS OF HER
LONGTIME BOYFRIEND
STEPHEN PADDOCK.
BUT A FAMILY FRIEND WHO VISITED
THEM IN NEVADA SAY THAT COULD
WELL BE TRUE, THAT SHE WAS
SUBSERVIENT TO HIM.
>> IT'S NOT WHAT I SAW AS A
LOVING, CARING RELATIONSHIP.
>> Reporter: ADAM LEFEVRE TOLD
AN AUSTRALIAN TV STATION HE
SPENT A WEEK WITH THE COUPLE IN
NEVADA IN 2015, STAYING WITH
THEM IN A LUXURY CASINO SUITE,
AND LATER AT HIS HOME, WHERE
PADDOCK SHOWED OFF WHAT HE
CALLED HIS GUN ROOM.
>> HE WAS VERY STRICT AND VERY
FIRM ON THE FACT THAT IT IS A
RIGHT, IT IS A CAPACITY, AND IT
IS THE FREEDOM OF EVERY AMERICAN
RESIDENT AND PERSON TO
PARTICIPATE, TO OWN A GUN AND
USE IT AS SEEN FIT WHEN NEED BE.
AND THAT LAW SHOULD NEVER BE
CHANGED.
>> Reporter: LATE TODAY
AUTHORITIES CONFIRMED REPORTS
THE SHOOTER LEFT BEHIND SOME
KIND OF A NOTE, WHICH
AUTHORITIES SAY CONTAINED A
SERIES OF CRYPTIC NUMBERS, BUT
WAS NOT A SUICIDE NOTE.
OFFICIALS ARE TRACKING EVERY
ASPECT OF HIS LIFE, BACK TO HIGH
SCHOOL IN LOS ANGELES AND
EARLIER, AND HIS RECENT
PRESCRIPTIONS FOR VALIUM.
>> WE ARE LOOKING AT EVERY
ASPECT FROM BIRTH TO DEATH OF
THIS SUSPECT IN THIS CASE.
>> Reporter: IN THE FINAL DAYS
BEFORE THE SHOOTING, OFFICIALS
TELL ABC NEWS HE WAS IN THE
COMPANY OF PROSTITUTES AND WENT
GAMBLING IN THE MANDALAY BAY
CASINO, WINNING BIG JACKPOTS ON
BOTH FRIDAY AND SATURDAY NIGHTS.
>>> BRIAN YOU WERE SAYING
STEPHEN PADDOCK CALLED HIMSELF A
PROFESSIONAL GAMBLER.
AND YOU'RE LEARNING HOW MUCH HE
MADE IN ONE YEAR ALONE?
>> IN THE YEAR 2015 HE REPORTED
INCOME OF $5 MILLION.
>> AND NO MOTIVE?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
>> BRIAN, THANKS.
I HOPE EVERYONE WILL JOIN US FOR
AN ABC NEWS "20/20" DOCUMENTARY
PRESENTATION ON THE LAS VEGAS
MASSACRE, HEARTBREAK AND HEROES.
WE HAVE NEW REPORTING TONIGHT AT
10:00 EASTERN/9:00 CENTRAL.
>>> IN THE MEANTIME, NEXT TO THE
WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT PRESIDENT
TRUMP RAISING NEW QUESTIONS
AFTER WHAT HE SAID DURING A
PHOTO-OP SUMMONING REPORTERS
TELLING THEM THIS WAS THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM.
CECELIA VEGA ASKING THE WHITE
HOUSE WHAT DID HE MEAN.
>> Reporter: IN THE STATE DINING
ROOM, THIS IS THE IMAGE
PRESIDENT TRUMP SUMMONED
REPORTERS TO SEE -- THE
PRESIDENT SMILING, SURROUNDED BY
HIS TOP MILITARY LEADERS AND
THEIR SPOUSES.
THEN CAME THE UNSOLICITED,
CRYPTIC COMMENT.
>> DO YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT THIS
REPRESENTS?
>> TELL US, SIR.
>> MAYBE IT'S THE CALM BEFORE
THE STORM.
>> WHAT'S THE STORM?
>> COULD BE THE CALM -- THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM.
>> WHAT STORM, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> WE HAVE THE WORLD'S GREAT
MILITARY PEOPLE.
I WILL TELL YOU THAT.
THANK YOU ALL FOR COMING.
THANK YOU.
>> WHAT STORM MR. PRESIDENT?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: AND TODAY IN THE
OVAL OFFICE, WE TRIED AGAIN.
>> MR. PRESIDENT, WHAT DID YOU
MEAN BY "CALM BEFORE THE STORM"?
YESTERDAY WHAT DID YOU MEAN BY
THAT?
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: AFTER A WINK, AND A
PAUSE --
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: THE COMMENT
ESPECIALLY OMINOUS AS THE UNITEO
ST
WORDS WITH NORTH KOREA, AND THE
PRESIDENT IS ON THE VERGE OF
DECERTIFYING THE NUCLEAR DEAL
WITH IRAN.
>> WAS HE REFERRING TO MILITARY
ACTION WHEN HE SAID CALM BEFORE
THE STORM?
>> WE'RE NEVER GOING TO SAY IN
ADVANCE WHAT THE PRESIDENT IS
GOING TO DO.
>> HOW SERIOUSLY SHOULD THE
AMERICAN PUBLIC OR AMERICAN
ADVERSARIES FOR THAT MATTER TAKE
THESE COMMENTS?
IS HE SERIOUS?
>> I THINK YOU CAN TAKE THE
PRESIDENT PROTECTING THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE ALWAYS EXTREMELY
SERIOUS AND IF HE FEELS THAT
ACTION IS NECESSARY, HE'LL TAKE
IT.
>> CECELIA VEGA PRESSING THE
WHITE HOUSE TODAY.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE ALSO KNOW
THE ADMINISTRATION IS MOVING
FORWARD TODAY ON A ROLLBACK OF
AN OBAMACARE MANDATE REQUIRING
EMPLOYEE COVERAGE OF BIRTH
CONTROL, 55 MILLION WOMEN HAVE
ACCESS TO WITHOUT A COPAYMENT
AND NOW SOME EXCEPTIONS?
>> Reporter: EMPLOYERS WILL NO
LONGER OFFER THESE INSURANCE
PLANS THAT COVER BIRTH CONTROL.
IF THEY CLAIM IT VIOLATES
MORAL CONVICTIONS OR
RELIGIOUS BELIEFS IT TAKES
EFFECT IMMEDIATELY.
DEMOCRATS ARE CALLING THIS A NEW
LOW AND REPUBLICANS ARE CHEERING
THIS AS THE PRESIDENT MAKING
GOOD ON A CAMPAIGN PROMISE.
>> TO PUERTO RICO.
NEW NUMBERS FROM FEMA.
MORE THAN TWO WEEKS AFTER THE
STORM JUST 10% OF THE ISLAND HAS
ELECTRICITY BACK AND MORE THAN
HALF HAS DRINKABLE WATER.
PRESIDENT TRUMP MARKING HISPANIC
HERITAGE MONTH TODAY STRESSING
THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT'S COMMITMENT
AND PRONOUNCING PUERTO RICO THIS
WAY.
>> WE ARE ALSO PRAYING FOR THE
PEOPLE OF PUERTO RICO.
WE LOVE PUERTO RICO.
PUERTO RICO.
>> WE LOVE YOU.
>> AND WE ALSO LOVE PUERTO RICO.
>> THE PRESIDENT AT THE WHITE
HOUSE TODAY.
TO A POLICE INVOLVED SHOOTING
DEATH IN CHARLOTTE.
AUTHORITIES SAY A TRAGIC
MISUNDERSTANDING THAT LEFT ONE
MAN DEAD.
HERE'S PIERRE THOMAS TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT NEWLY
RELEASED VIDEO FROM A FATAL
POLICE SHOOTING IN CHARLOTTE
REVEALING HOW LIFE AND DEATH
SITUATIONS PLAY OUT IN SECONDS.
EARLY LAST MONTH POLICE RESPOND
AFTER RECEIVING A 911 CALL FROM
A SPANISH SPEAKING MAN WHO
CLAIMS HE WANTS TO TURN HIMSELF
IN, TELLING THE 911 DISPATCHER I
CALLED YOU TO COME FOR ME.
HE ACKNOWLEDGES HE HAS A GUN BUT
SAYS IT'S EMPTY.
WITH WORD OF A
FIREARM, OFFICERS DON'T TAKE HIS
WORD BUT THE GUN WON'T BE
LOADED.
THEY MOVE IN GUNS DRAWN.
>> DROP THE GUN.
>> Reporter: THEN LESS THAN A
MINUTE ENDS THE LIFE OF RUBIN
GALINDO.
HE STEPS OUT, HIS HANDS IN THE
AIR.
POLICE SEE A GUN.
[ SHOTS FIRED ]
THE GUN WAS IN FACT EMPTY.
FAMILY MEMBERS CONCERNED THAT
THE OFFICERS ACTED TOO QUICKLY.
POLICE CHIEF IS STANDING BY HIS
MEN AND UP TO A PROSECUTOR
INVESTIGATING THE CASE.
DAVID.
>> FROM THE PENTAGON, A FOURTH
U.S. SPECIAL OPERATIONS SOLDIER
HAS DIED AND HIS IDENTITY NOT
REVEALED BUT THE FACES OF THE
THREE OTHERS WHO DIED THERE.
STAFF SERGEANT BRIAN BLATT FROM
WASHINGTON STATE, STAFF SERGEANT
JEREMIAH JOHNSON FROM OHIO AND
STAFF SERGEANT DUSTIN WRIGHT
FROM GEORGIA.
THEY WERE AMBUSHED WHILE ON A
JOINT PATROL.
BY EXTREMISTS.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD THIS FRIDAY.
THE ALLEGED TERROR PLOT IN NEW
YORK CITY.
THE DETAILS REVEALED TONIGHT.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE PLAN FOR THE
ATTACKS IN TIMES SQUARE AND THE
NEW YORK CITY SUBWAY.
THE FBI SEIZING BOMB-MAKING
MATERIALS.
MORE AFTER THE BREAK.
>>> A FAMOUS DALLAS COWBOYS STAR
AND HIS SON IN THE NEWS.
THE CAMPUS FRATERNITY ACCUSED OF
HAZING HIM.
A BAT TO THE STOMACH IN A
CULTURE DESCRIBED AS A FIGHT
CLUB.
>>> AND KEITH URBAN AND THE
MOMENT THAT MOVED SO MANY AS WE
HONOR THE FACES.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
of multi.
♪
That's why there's Trintellix,
a prescription medication
for depression.
Trintellix may help you take
a step forward
in improving your depression.
Tell your healthcare
professional right away
if your depression worsens,
or you have unusual changes
in mood,
behavior or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in children,
teens and young adults.
Do not take with MAOIs.
Tell your healthcare
professional about
your medications, including
migraine, psychiatric
and depression medications,
to avoid a potentially
life-threatening condition.
Increased risk of bleeding or
bruising may occur,
especially if taken with NSAID
pain relievers,
aspirin or blood thinners.
Manic episodes or
vision problems
may occur in some people.
May cause low sodium levels.
The most common side effects
were nausea,
constipation and vomiting.
TRINTELLIX had no significant
impact on weight
in clinical trials.
Ask your healthcare
professional about TRINTELLIX.
Rethink your allergy pills.
Flonase Sensimist Allergy Relief
helps block 6 key
inflammatory
substances
with a
gentle mist.
Most allergy
pills
only block
one.
And 6 is greater
than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
♪
Traders -- They're always
looking for advantages.
The smart ones look
to Fidelity to find them.
We give you research
and data-visualization tools
to help identify
potential opportunities.
So, you can do it this way...
or get everything you need to
help capture investment ideas
and make smarter trading
decisions with Fidelity
for just $4.95
per online U.S. equity trade.
Fidelity.
Open an account today.
♪
I AM TOTALLY BLIND.
AND NON-24 CAN THROW MY
DAYS AND NIGHTS OUT OF SYNC,
KEEPING ME FROM THE
THINGS I LOVE TO DO.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR,
AND CALL
844-214-2424.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE
ALLEGATIONS OF BRUTAL HAZING AT
THE UNIVERSITY OF OKLAHOMA.
THE SON OF A FORMER DALLAS
COWBOY STAR SUING A FRATERNITY
CLAIMING A PLEDGE RITUAL LEFT
HIM WITH BRAIN INJURIES AND
MEMORY LOSS.
HERE'S DAVID WRIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE SON OF
A DALLAS COWBOYS LEGEND IS SUING
A UNIVERSITY OF OKLAHOMA
FRATERNITY OVER AN ALLEGED
HAZING RITUAL THAT HE SAYS LEFT
HIM WITH PERMANENT BRAIN DAMAGE.
FORMER COWBOY TIGHT END
JAY NOVACEK'S SON BLAKE IS SUING
OKLAHOMA'S CHAPTER OF BETA THETA
PI, ACCUSING THE FRATERNITY OF
VIOLENT HAZING RITUALS.
HIS LAWYER PROVIDED PHOTOS OF
WHAT HE SAYS WAS A "FIGHT CLUB,"
JUST LIKE THE MOVIE, THAT HE
SAYS LEFT NOVACECK WITH A BROKEN
NOSE.
NOVACEK IS SUING OVER ANOTHER
ALLEGED INCIDENT.
>> HE WAS BEATEN WITH A BASEBALL
BAT AND KNOCKED UNCONSCIOUS.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS THE
INCIDENT LED TO TRAUMATIC BRAIN
INJURY AND SEVERE MEMORY LOSS.
THE LAWSUIT SAYS THAT INCIDENT
TOOK PLACE ON OCTOBER 11, 2015,
BUT THE FRATERNITY SAYS NOVACEK
WAS NOT EVEN IN OKLAHOMA THAT
DAY, CITING THIS INSTAGRAM PHOTO
POSTED FROM THE DALLAS COWBOY'S
GAME.
NOVACEK'S LAWYER SAYS HIS CLIENT
CANNOT BE SURE OF THE EXACT DATE
BECAUSE OF THE MEMORY LOSS.
SO THEY'RE AMENDING THE LAWSUIT.
THE FRATERNITY SAYS IT DOES NOT
CONDONE HAZING, AND CALLS THESE
ALLEGATIONS FALSE AND
INFLAMMATORY, DAVID.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, BREAKING
NEWS COMING IN ON THE MAN BEHIND
SO MANY MOVIES OF OUR TIME.
HE APOLOGIZED YESTERDAY AND
WHAT'S HAPPENED TONIGHT.
>>> ALSO, THE ALLEGED TERROR
PLOT INVOLVING NEW YORK CITY
TARGETING TIMES SQUARE AND THE
SUBWAY.
WHAT AUTHORITIES ARE NOW
REVEALING.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
THE
SUBWAY.
WHAT AUTHORITIES ARE NOW
REVEALING.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
CDs, baseball cards.
Your old magic set?
(Sigh)
And this wrestling ticket.
Which you still owe me for.
Seriously? $25?
I didn't even want to go.
Ahh, your diary!
"Mom says it is
totally natural..."
$25 is nothing.
(Alert beep)
Abracadabra, bro.
Settle up with your friends
on October 17th
with the Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
Settle up with your friends
on October 17th
When it comes to strong bones,
are you on the right path?
We have postmenopausal
osteoporosis...
..and a high risk for fracture,
so with our doctors...
...we chose Prolia®...
...to help make our bones
stronger.
Only Prolia® helps strengthen
bones...
...by stopping cells that damage
them...
...with 1 shot every 6 months.
Do not take Prolia® if you have
low blood calcium, are pregnant,
are allergic to it, or take
XGEVA®.
Serious allergic reactions, like
low blood pressure; trouble
breathing;
throat tightness; face, lip or
tongue swelling...
...rash, itching or hives have
happened.
Tell your doctor about dental
problems, as severe jaw bone...
...problems may happen or new or
unusual pain in your hip groin,
or thigh,
as unusual thigh bone fractures
have occurred.
peak to your doctor before
stopping Prolia®,
as spine and other bone
fractures have occurred.
Prolia® can cause serious side
effects, like low blood calcium;
serious infections, which could
need hospitalization;
...skin problems; and severe
bone, joint, or muscle pain.
If your bones aren't getting
stronger...
...isn't it time for a new
direction?
Why wait? Ask your doctor about
Prolia®.
eight hundred dollars whenlmost
we switched our auto and
home insurance.
Liberty did what?
Yeah, they saved us a ton,
which gave us a little wiggle
room in our budget.
Wish our insurance did that.
Then we could get a real
babysitter instead of
your brother.
Hey, welcome back.
This guy... right?
Yes.
Ellen.
That's my robe.
You could save seven hundred
eighty two dollars
when Liberty stands with you.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
I even accept I have a higher
risk of stroke due to AFib,
I accept I take easier trails
than I used to.
a type of irregular heartbeat
not caused
by a heart valve problem.
But no matter what path I take,
I go for my best.
So if there's something better
than warfarin,
I'll go for that too. ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS reduced the risk of
stroke better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS unless
your doctor tells you to,
as stopping increases your risk
of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and in
rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS, you may
bruise more easily...
...and it may take longer than
usual for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care for
sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase your
bleeding risk
if you take certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about all
planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor about ELIQUIS.
>>> TO THE "INDEX" TONIGHT AND
THE DANGEROUS CHASE THROUGH THE
STREETS OF MIAMI.
A SUSPECTED BANK ROBBER TRYING
TO OUTRUN POLICE.
FOR 40 MINUTES.
CARJACKING TWO DRIVERS AT
GUNPOINT.
POLICE SAY HE WAS STILL ARMED
WHEN HE JUMPED INTO A RIVER.
THE SUSPECT SHOT AND KILLED BY
OFFICERS.
HE THREATENED TO SHOOT AND
REFUSED TO SURRENDER.
>> THE TERROR PLOT REVEALED HERE
IN NEW YORK CITY.
AUTHORITIES ARRESTING THREE
SUSPECTS BEHIND AN ALLEGED ISIS
INSPIRED PLAN TO DETONATE BOMBS
AND TAKING
PICTURES OF THEIR POSSIBLE
TARGETS.
PROSECUTORS SAY THE SUSPECTS
MARKED UP A MAP OF THE SUBWAY
SYSTEM AND THE FBI SAID THE
SUSPECTS WERE FROM CANADA,
PAKISTAN AND THE PHILIPPINES.
>>> HARVEY WEINSTEIN WILL BE
SUSPENDED FROM THE COMPANY THAT
BEARS HIS NAME PENDING AN
INVESTIGATION INTO CLAIMS OF
SEXUAL HARASSMENT.
ALLEGATIONS MADE BY ASHLEY JUDD.
WEINSTEIN APOLOGIZING FOR HIS
ACTIONS YESTERDAY.
>>> THE MOMENT THAT MOVED SO
MANY.
KEITH URBAN AND WHAT HE DID AS
WE REMEMBER TONIGHT.
Whenstuff happens. d...
Shut down cold symptoms fast
with Maximum
Strength Alka Seltzer
Plus Liquid Gels.
Only have a sore throat?
Get long-lasting
relief for up to 6 hours
with New Alka Seltzer
Plus Sore Throat Relief.
DEPEND SILHOUETTE
ACTIVE FIT BRIEFS,
FEATURE A THIN DESIGN
FOR COMPLETE COMFORT.
THEY SAY "MOVE IT OR LOSE IT" -
AND AT MY AGE, I'M
MOVING MORE THAN EVER.
BECAUSE GETTING
OLDER IS INEVITABLE.
BUT FEELING OLDER?
THAT'S SOMETHING I CONTROL.
GET A FREE SAMPLE
AT DEPEND.COM.
What twisted ankle?ask
THAT'S SOMETHING I CONTROL.
What muscle strain?
Advil makes pain a distant
memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
Remember that accident I got in
with the pole, and I
had to make a claim
and all that?
Is that whole thing
still dragging on?
No, I took some pics
with the app and...
filed a claim, but...
You know how they send you
money to cover repairs and...
They took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid
right away, but...
at the very end of
it all, my agent...
Wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy.
But if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience
for any reason,
they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim Satisfaction
Guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, SINGER
KEITH URBAN AT A VIGIL IN
NASHVILLE FOR THE VICTIMS IN LAS
VEGAS.
HE TALKED ABOUT A QUESTION FROM
HIS 9-YEAR-OLD AND PERFORMED A
SONG.
TONIGHT WE REMEMBER 58 NAMES, 58
FACES LOST.
>> MY 9-YEAR-OLD AS I WAS
DRIVING HER TO SCHOOL SAID TO
ME, DAD, YOU SEEM QUIET.
I SAID, YEAH.
I'M REALLY -- A LOT OF PEOPLE
KILLED LAST NIGHT.
AND SHE SAID DID YOU KNOW ANY OF
THEM?
AND I SAID, NOT THAT I KNOW OF.
AND THEN SHE SAID, WELL, THEN
WHY ARE YOU SO SAD?
I SAID, WELL, FIRST OF ALL,
THESE WERE INNOCENT PEOPLE.
♪ WHEN YOU'RE WEARY
♪ FEELIN' SMALL
♪ WHEN TEARS ARE IN YOUR EYES
♪ I WILL DRY THEM ALL
♪ I'M ON YOUR SIDE
♪ OH WHEN THE TIMES GET ROUGH
♪ AND PRECIOUS CAN BE FOUND
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY MEOWN
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN
♪ LIKE A BRIDGE OVER TROUBLED
WATER ♪
♪ I WILL LAY ME DOWN
>> THANK YOU FOR WATCHING ON
ANOTHER DIFFICULT WEEK.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER TONIGHT ON
"20/20".
I'M DAVID MUIR.
GOOD NIGHT.
.
>>> UP AND AWAY, THEN BACK FOR
MORE.
LIVE WITH THE BEST OF THE BLUE
ANGELS SO FAR AND WHAT THERE'S
TO LOOK FORWARD TO WITH FLEET
WEEK THERE WEEKEND.
>> IT'S DEFINITELY A STIGMA
ATTACHED TO MENTALLY HEALTH
ISSUES.
>> TONIGHT YOU'LL MEET TEENAGERS
WORKING TO END THE STIGMA OF
MENTALLY ILLNESS.
>>> AND WE ARE WITH THE WARRIORS
IN CHINA.
WHERE STEPH CURRY ISN'T THE ONLY
STAR.
WHAT MAKE THIS MAN WITH GLASSES
SUCH A BIG
>>> ONE ICON NEXT TO ANOTHER,
THE GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE AND THE
BL ANGELS, IT IS FLEET WEEK
AND THE BEST IS YET TO TODAY.
I'M DAN ASHLEY.
>> I'M CHRISTIAN SZE.
YOU CANNOT MISS THE SOUNDS OF
THE JETS FLYING OVER THE BAY,
GETTING A GLIMPSE TAKE MORE
EFFORT.
>> ABC 7 NEWS REPORTER LIVE WITH
MORE.
CORNELL.
>> Reporter: YEAH, LOTS OF
VIEWING SPOTS ALL OVER THE CITY
BUT I THINK WE HAD THE BEST SEAT
IN THE HOUSE.
THE WEATHER WAS PERFECT FOR THE
SHOW.
TODAY WAS A BIT OF A WARM-UP.
THEY'LL BE BACK IN THE AIR
SATURDAY AND SUNDAY AFTERNOON.
THE NAVY'S BLUE ANGELS ROARED
ACROSS THE SFROES WATER FRONT.
THE JAW-JANING PRECISION, AR
BASK FLYING.
>> I LOVE THE BLUE ANGELS, I
THINK THEY ARE SMART.
>> Reporter: BRAYTON TOOK THE
DAY OFF TO SEE THE WEEK SHOW.
>> I LEFT A MESSAGE ON THE
SCHOOL ANSWERING MACHINE SAYING
HE HAS A BAD CASE OF WANTING TO
SEE THE BLUE ANGELS HERE WE ARE.
>> Reporter: EARLIER THIS AIR
FORCE-16 CAPABLE OF FLYING
BUZZED THE WATER FRONT.
>>