IN RUBBLE
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS.
A MASSIVE TORNADO, MORE THAN A
MILE WIDE, TEARS THROUGH
OKLAHOMA ON LIVE TV.
>> JUST SAW A POWER FLASH IN THE
SKY.
THIS IS A LARGE, VIOLENT
TORNADO.
>> AN ENTIRE TOWN IN RUINS.
FIRES BREAKING OUT.
A SCHOOL SUFFERS A DIRECT HIT.
>> HOPEFULLY WE DIDN'T LOSE ANY
LIVES HERE.
>> AS NEIGHBORS DIG THROUGH
DEBRIS BY HAND TO TRY TO HELP
THEIR NEIGHBORS.
>> THE DAMAGE IS OVERWHELMING.
IT IS MIND-BLOWING.
>> AND TONIGHT AN OUTBREAK OF
MORE THAN 50 TWISTERS HAS TAKEN
LIVES AND FLATTENED HOMES.
55 MILLION AMERICANS STILL IN
THE STORM ZONE TONIGHT.
OUR EXTREME WEATHER TEAM RIGHT
THERE IN THE HEART OF TORNADO
ALLEY, WITH THE VERY LATEST ON
"WORLD NEWS."
>>> GOOD EVENING ON THIS MONDAY
NIGHT.
AS WE COME ON THE AIR, WE ARE IN
THE MIDDLE OF A BREAKING STORY.
A MASSIVE TORNADO DESCENDING
THROUGH THE HEARD LAND LIKE A
WRECKING BALL.
HOUSES GROUND TO SPLINTERS.
AS THOSE FIRES ERUPED.
WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING AT THERE,
HOURS AGO, WAS THE SCHOOL
GYMNASIUM.
AND THERE'S THIS NEW PHOTO, A
LITTLE GIRL PULLED ALIVE FROM
THE RUBBLE OF HER ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA,
PASSED ALONG A HUMAN CHAIN TO
SAFETY.
AND THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE
THE MOMENT OF THE CRISIS.
THIS IS IN THE DAY.
SUDDENLY SKIES ARE DARK AS
MIDNIGHT AS THE STORM MOVERS IN.
LISTEN.
[ CRACKLING, WIND BLOWING ]
>> AS OF RIGHT NOW, 37 ARE
REPORTED DEAD.
AT LEAST 100 INJURED OR BEING
FREETED IN HOSPITALS.
NATIONAL GUARD DESCENDING AND
EMERGENCY MEDICAL TEAMS RACING
INTO TOWN.
OUR EXTREME WEATHER TEAM IS IN
OKLAHOMA.
AND ABC'S GINGER ZEE LEADS US
OFF.
>> IT'S TURNING INTO A
DESTRUCTIVE TORNADO AND IT'S
GETTING BIGGER.
>> Reporter: THIS AFTERNOON, A
LOCAL TELEVISION HELICOPTER
CATCHING THE PICTURES, CATCHING
THIS TORNADO, RANKED A
PRELIMINARY EF-4 HELP YOU CAN
SEE THE FLASHES OF THE POWER
LINES AND TRANSFORMERS BEING
RIPPED APART.
>> THERE'S A HUGE FLASH RIGHT
THERE.
IT'S JUST RIPPING UP EVERYTHING
IN ITS PATH.
>> Reporter: FROM THE GROUND,
DARKNESS OVERWHELMING MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
YOU CAN SEE THE COLOSSAL TORNADO
BEARING DOWN ON ON THE STREET.
UNBELIEVABLE DESTRUCTION.
ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOOD, GONE.
HOUSES AND CARS PILED ON TOP OF
EACH OTHER.
IN SOME PARTS, EVERYTHING
LEVELED.
CARS TOSSED.
PEOPLE DIGGING AND CRAWLING
THROUGH RUBBLE.
>> STARTED HEADING IN.
WE WERE PULLING WALLS OFF OF
PEOPLE.
THERE WERE PEOPLE CRAWLING OUT
FROM EVERYWHERE AND ANYWHERE.
BASICALLY JUST A WAR ZONE.
>> Reporter: BUILDINGS CRUSHED
BY THE DESTRUCTIVE TORNADO THAT
WREAKED HAVOC FOR ALMOST AN
HOUR.
AND HERE, SCHOOL BUSES STILL
LINED UP OUTSIDE THIS SCHOOL.
BUT THE GYM, TORN APART.
>> IT JUST TORE THROUGH IT LIKE
A TRUCK RUN RIGHT THROUGH THE
CENTER OF IT.
>> AND SADLY, THEY FOUND A MAN
AND THEN A WOMAN AND A SMALL
BABY.
>> OH.
>> Reporter: OUR AFFILIATE SPOKE
TO SIXTH GRADER BRADY WHO WAS
INSIDE BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL WHEN THE STORM HIT.
>> UM, WELL, I WAS IN MY
BUILDING.
WE WERE TOLD TO GET IN OUR
TORNADO PRECAUTION SYSTEM.
BUT THEN THEY MOVED US TO THE
BOYS AND GIRLS BATHROOM.
SOME KIDS WERE NOT FOLLOWING
DIRECTIONS OF STAYING AWAY FROM
UNDER THE, UH, SINKS AND STUFF.
AND THEY GOT UNDER THERE AND
SOME OF THE BLOCKS COLLAPSED ON
THEM.
IT WAS JUST DEBRIS.
THERE WAS JUST CARS BEAT UP.
MY MOM WAS FLIPPING OUT.
THAT WAS HER CAR.
>> ARE YOU DOING ALL RIGHT, BUD?
I KNOW THIS IS PRETTY WILD TO
TAKE IN ALL AT ONE TIME.
HAVE YOU HAD A CHANCE TO TALK TO
YOUR MOM?
>> YEAH, SHE WAS ON TOP OF ME.
SHE WAS ABLE TO BE WITH ME.
>> Reporter: GINGER ZEE, ABC
NEWS, MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
>> AND FROM GINGER TO ABC'S
VETERAN JOURNALIST MIKE BECHER.
HE'S IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA AS WELL.
YOU KNOW HIM FROM HIS REPORTING
FROM THE DANGEROUS ZONES IN
AFGHANISTAN.
HE REPORTS IN TO US NOW.
>> DIANE AS THE SUN SETS OVER
THIS MASSIVE SCENE OF
DESTRUCTION IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA,
THE FOCUS OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD
I'M IN HAS SHIFTED FROM
BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY SCHOOL,
WHICH WAS HIT BY THE TORNADO, TO
THE NEIGHBORHOOD, AS THEY SEARCH
UNDER PILES OF WOOD AND BRICK
AND STONE THAT USED TO BE
HOUSES, LOOKING FOR, EITHER
SURVIVORS, OR FOR THE DEAD.
THE GOOD NEWS NOW IS THAT
STUDENTS IN THE SCHOOL AND
ADULTS ASSOCIATED WITH THE
SCHOOL, TELL US THAT NO CHILDREN
DIED.
THAT TORNADO PASSED RIGHT OVER
THAT SCHOOL.
WE WERE LESS THAN A MILE FROM IT
WHEN IT HIT THE SCHOOL, AND YOU
COULD SEE THE EXPLOSION AND THE
DEBRIS WHEN IT HIT THAT LARGE
STONE STRUCTURE.
BUT A LITTLE 7-YEAR-OLD GIRL
PULLED ME ASIDE AND SAID, I WAS
IN THAT SCHOOL.
AND OUR TEACHER GRABBED ME, AND
THE REST OF THE STUDENTS, AND
SAID, WE'RE GOING TO THE SAFE
ROOM, AND WE ALL GOT THERE, AND
WE WERE QUIET.
AND THE TORNADO CAME, AND IT
PASSED.
AND WE WALKED OUT, AND WE WERE
ALL ALIVE.
THAT WAS HER QUOTE.
SHE WAS TAKING IT IN STRIDE
BECAUSE SHE WAS SITTING IN FRONT
OF WHAT USED TO BE HER HOME,
WHICH NO LONGER EXISTED.
SO THIS SEARCH AND RESCUE IN
THIS IMMENSE OF A DISASTER WILL
TAKE DAYS BEFORE THERE'S A FINAL
TOLL OF THE DEAD, AND ALL OF THE
LIVING ARE ACCOUNTED FOR.
DIANE?
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH, MIKE
BOETTCHER REPORTED IN FOR US
TONIGHT FROM MOORE.
>> AND WE ARE HEARING REPORTS OF
VICTIMS BEING RUSHED TO NEARBY
HOSPITALS.
MOMENTS AGO I SPOKE TO A
HOSPITAL 12 MILES FROM MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, WHERE THE INJURED ARE
BEING CARED FOR RIGHT NOW.
BROOK, THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
TALKING WITH US TONIGHT.
GIVE ME A SENSE, HOW MANY
PATIENTS DO YOU HAVE PER MINUTE
STILL COMING IN?
>> WE'RE RECEIVING PATIENTS
LITERALLY, MINUTE BY MINUTE.
AT LAST CHECK, WE RECEIVED A
TOTAL OF 37 PATIENTS.
THEY RANGE, WE HAVE TEN IN
CRITICAL CONDITION RIGHT NOW.
12 IN SERIOUS.
AND 15 ARE LISTED IN FAIR OR
GOOD CONDITION AT THE MOMENT.
>> WHAT KIND OF INJURIES ARE YOU
SEEING?
>> WE'RE SEEING EVERYTHING FROM
JUST MINOR LACERATIONS TO SEVERE
HEAD INJURIES AND ABDOMINAL
WOUNDS.
MOST LIKELY FROM PUNCTURES FROM
FLYING DEBRIS.
>> WE'VE HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT
THOSE CHILDREN IN THE TWO
SCHOOLS, WHO WERE INSIDE.
ANY OF YOUR CHILDREN FROM THOSE
SCHOOLS, AND WHAT ABOUT THEIR
CONDITION?
>> WE RECEIVED A TOTAL OF FIVE
CHILDREN OF THOSE 37.
I KNOW THAT TWO OF THE 37 WERE
FROM THAT SCHOOL.
>> AND IS IT POSSIBLE, WITH
PRIVACY, TO GIVE US ANY SENSE OF
THEIR CONDITION?
>> WELL, THANKFULLY NONE OF THE
FIVE CHILDREN THAT WE HAVE RIGHT
NOW ARE LISTED IN CRITICAL.
ONE IN SERIOUS AND THE OTHERS
ARE FAIR OR GOOD.
SO THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
>> THAT'S REALLY GREAT NEWS.
HOW MANY MORE PATIENTS CAN YOU
RECEIVE?
HOW MUCH ARE YOU EQUIPPED TO
>> WELL, WE DO RUN THE BUSIEST
ER IN THE STATE, SO WE ARE
ACCUSTOMED TO HIGH VOLUME.
MAYBE NOT TO THE EMOTIONAL
EXTENT OF THIS TRAGEDY, BUT WITH
ONLY TEN CRITICAL AT THE MOMENT,
WE'RE CAPABLE OF HANDLING
ANYMORE.
>> GIVE ME A SENSE OF WHAT
YOU'RE HEARING AROUND TOWN.
ARE THERE AMBULANCES GOING OUT
ALL OVER TOWN, OR ARE YOU STILL
LOOKING FOR REINFORCEMENTS?
>> WHAT WE'VE HEARD IS THAT THE
ROADS ARE STILL IMPASSABLE IN
THAT AREA, SO IT'S TAKING A
SIGNIFICANT AMOUNT OF TIME TO
GET OUT OF THE AREA AND TO OUR
HOSPITAL.
THE AMBULANCES ARE SHOWING UP,
INSTEAD OF JUST ONE PATIENT AT A
TIME, THEY'RE BRINGING THREE AND
FOUR PATIENTS AT A TIME.
MANY PEOPLE ARE JUST ARRIVING BY
PRIVATE VEHICLE AS WELL.
>> AGAIN, WE THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR PHONING INTO US.
WE KNOW IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG
NIGHT.
>> CERTAINLY DIANE.
>> WE WISH ALL OF YOU THE BEST
AS YOU DO YOUR BEST FOR
EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> THANK YOU.
>> AND OF COURSE WE'VE ALSO BEEN
HEARING EYEWITNESS DESCRIPTIONS,
VIVID ONES, OF THE UTTER
DESTRUCTION ON THE GROUND.
EARLIER, MELISSA NEWTON SPOKE
ABOUT THE DEVASTATION SHE SAW
WHEN SHE LOOKED OUTSIDE HER
DOOR.
>> I LOOKED TO THE WEST AND I
SEE IT.
HAIL THE SIZE OF GOLF BALLS
POUNDING MY CAR AT THE TIME.
GOT HOME FAST AS POSSIBLE, GOT
OUR DOGS, AND GOT INTO THE
SHELTER, ABOUT FIVE MINUTES
LATER, WE WERE HIT.
OUR NEIGHBORHOOD IS COVERED IN
DEBRIS.
SHINGLES AND PIECES OF SHEET
ROOT AND WOOD IN OUR YARD AND
ALL ACROSS OUR NEIGHBORHOOD.
SOME HOMES COMPLETELY GONE.
IT'S DEVASTATING.
THERE ARE TWO BY FOURS GOING
THROUGH PEOPLE'S ROOFS LIKE
PROJECTILE OBJECTS.
HEARING THE STORM GOING OVER MY
HOUSE, WHICH ROARING, WHIRLING
SOUND, IT WAS SO LOUD.
OUR DOGS WERE DOWN ON THE GROUND
JUST SHAKING, BLESS THEIR
HEARTS.
IT WAS A FRIGHTENING EXPERIENCE.
THANK GOD WE HAD A SHELTER.
>> AND SO MANY HAD SHELTERS.
NOW, I WANT TO CHECK BACK IN
WITH ABC'S METEOROLOGIST JINKER
ZEE FOR A MOMENT.
SHE'S ON THE GROUND IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
GINGER, IN THESE MOMENTS, WHAT
ARE YOU SEEING RIGHT NOW?
>> Reporter: WELL, WE SET UP
RIGHT AWAY, AT BRIARWOOD
ELEMENTARY, ONE OF THE SCHOOLS
HARDEST HIT.
WE MET ONE WOMAN LOOKING FOR HER
NIECE.
SHE STILL HADN'T FOUND HER.
SHE KNEW SHE WAS OKAY, BUT STILL
HADN'T BEEN RE-UNITED.
WE'RE SEEING A LOT OF THOSE
TYPES OF STORIES.
ALSO AT THIS POINT I'M SEEING
THE WARREN THEATER, NOW WE'RE
SEEING SOME OF THE WALLS UP, BUT
JUST PEOPLE WALKING THE STREETS.
REFUGEES WITH SUITCASES OF ALL
TWHA HAVE LEFT, WHAT THEY'VE
BEEN ABLE TO GET BEFORE THE SUN
SETS HERE IN MOORE.
>> ARE YOU STILL SEEING PEOPLE
DIGGING THROUGH THEIR HOMES?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THE WATER IS SPOUTING OUT OF THE
PLUMING AND THEY'RE STILL
DIGGING THROUGH TRYING TO FIND
THINGS BEFORE THE SUN SETS.
ONE WOMAN TOLD US, WE JUST WANT
TO FIND OUR OWN THINGS BEFORE
SOMEBODY ELSE DOES.
>> AND INITIALLY, WE SAW ALL
THOSE FIRES BURNING, HAVE THEY
GONE OUT?
>> WE STILL SEE SOME PLUMES OF
SMOKE.
I SAW A COUPLE BEFORE ME MOVED
TO A DIFFERENT AREA.
SO I DON'T THINK THAT'S OVER
WITH YET.
THE SMELL OF GAS IS PERMEATING
STILL.
IT'S ALMOST SICKENING WHEN
YOU'RE STANDING THERE.
>> AND OF COURSE SO DANGEROUS.
THANK YOU, GINGER AND I KNOW
YOU'RE STANDING BY FOR THE REST
OF THE BROADCAST.
I WANT TO TURN TO ABC'S SAM
CHAMPION 26 MILES AWAY FROM LAKE
THUNDERBIRD, OKLAHOMA.
TELL US MORE ABOUT THIS MASSIVE
TORNADO.
>> Reporter: DIANE, I GOT TO
TELL YOU, THIS IS AN INCREDIBLE
SIGHT.
THIS IS THE THIRD DAY THAT
VIOLENT STORMS HAVE BEEN IN THIS
AREA.
AND THE THIRD DAY SEEMED TO HAVE
DROPPED THE WORST TORNADO OF
THEM ALL.
WE'LL HAVE PICTURES FROM STORM
CHASER VIDEOS.
THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE HAS
THIS STORM RIGHT NOW ON A
PRELIMINARY CATEGORY HERE AS AN
EF-4, THIS IS RARIFIED TERRITORY
FOR TORNADOES.
THERE ARE SOME REPORTS IT WAS ON
THE GROUND FOR 40 MINUTES,
COVERING 12 MILES IN THAT TIME.
THERE ARE SOME REPORTS THAT SAY
ON THE GROUND, THIS TORNADO WAS
ABOUT TWO MILES WIDE.
AND WE WON'T KNOW UNTIL WE CAN
GET IN AND LOOK AT THE DEBRIS
FIELD THERE.
YOU CAN SEE THE TORNADO FILLING
THE SKY.
ANOTHER AMAZING THING ABOUT THIS
TORNADO IS ON THE RADAR, WHEN IT
FIRST POPPED OUT IN NEWCASTLE,
BY THE WAY, THIS IS BEING CALLED
THE NEWCASTLE-MOORE TORNADO, BUT
WHEN IT DROPPED DOWN, IT WAS
JUST A FINGER OF A TORNADO,
BARELY A FUNNEL CLOUD.
WITHIN AN HOUR, IT WAS A MONSTER
STORM DEVELOPING JUST ABOUT AS
QUICKLY AS ALL THE DETAILS HAVE
TOLD US THE JOPLIN STORM
DEVELOPED.
THIS STORM HAS BEEN COVERED WITH
STORM CHASERS AND LOCAL
TELEVISION FROM START TO FINISH.
RUBBLE.'RE LOOKING A THE
THE UNBELIEVABLE DEBRIS FIELD.
YOU HEARD GINGER IN THE FIELD
WALKING AROUND THERE AND WE
HEARD REPORTS THAT SOME OF THE
FOUNDATIONS WERE COMPLETELY
CLEARED.
THAT PUTS IT DEFINITELY IN THAT
EF-4 AND MAYBE EVEN HIGHER
CATEGORY, THE STORM THAT'S
CAPABLE OF TAKING A FOUNDATION
AND CLEARING IT OF DEBRIS, AS
THE STORM LEAVES THE AREA.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE IT'S BEEN SWEPT
ALREADY BY A BIG TRACTOR.
BUT IT HASN'T BEEN YET.
IT WAS JUST THE STORM THAT DID
THAT DAMAGE.
AND IN OTHER AREAS, BUILDINGS
JUST SHATTERED.
THEN YOU LOOK AT MAJOR
CONSTRUCTION.
YOU SEE MAJOR CEMENT
CONSTRUCTION ALSO BEING DAMAGED.
THIS IS VERY UNUSUAL AND THE
SIGNATURE OF A VERY LARGE AND
VERY POWERFUL TORNADO.
FOLKS HAVE BEEN DIGGING THROUGH
THE DEBRIS AND LIFTING UP THESE
HEAVY PIECES OF DEBRIS, WHETHER
IT'S WALL BOARD OR SIDING OR
ROOFING, TWISTED METAL, TRYING
TO FIND ANYONE WHO MIGHT STILL
BE IN THE RUBBLE.
ALL OF THIS IS GOING ON, BECAUSE
THIS IS STILL A VERY LARGE AREA.
FROM THE SKY, YOU CAN SEE IT'S
HOUSE AFTER HOUSE AFTER HOUSE IN
NEIGHBORHOODS.
THIS IS A GROWING NEIGHBORHOOD
THAT'S JUST SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA
CITY.
VERY LARGE AREA OF HOMES, VERY
LARGE RESIDENTIAL AREA, WITH
LOTS OF HOMES.
AND IT'S HOMES, BUSINESSES,
HOSPITALS, ALL JUST TAKEN OUT BY
THIS ONE STORM.
SOMETHING THAT I GOT TO TELL
YOU, I HAVEN'T REALLY SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS.
AND I DON'T LIKE TO COMPARE
STORMS TOO MUCH.
BUT SOMETIMES YOU LOOK AT THE
DAMAGE AND YOU SEE IT AND IT
REMINDS YOU OF ANOTHER STORM AND
THIS STORM IS REMINDING US A LOT
OF JOPLIN AND THAT'S NOT A GOOD
THING.
>> THANK YOU AGAIN, SAM.
JUST REMINDS US HOW IMPORTANT
THE WARNING SYSTEM IS AGAIN.
THERE WERE 20 OR 30 MINUTES FOR
EVERYONE TO GET TO SOME KIND OF
SHELTER.
STILL AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS," WE
HAVE MORE STORIES FROM THE STORM
ZONE, INCLUDING THE INCREDIBLE
ONE OF A FATHER AND SON
RE-UNITED TONIGHT.
MINE WAS EARNED
IN DJIBOUTI, AFRICA. 2004.
VIETNAM IN 1972.
[ All ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]
USAA AUTO INSURANCE
IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN
FROM GENERATION TO GENERATION.
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE MILITARY MEMBERS,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY,
GET AN AUTO INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA. WE KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS TO SERVE.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT Aleve
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HIM,
HE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HIM ALL DAY
AS HE GOES BACK
TO TAKING TYLENOL.
THAT WAS OKAY, BUT AFTER LUNCH
MY KNEE STARTED TO HURT AGAIN,
AND NOW I GOTTA TAKE MORE PILLS.
♪
YUP ANOTHER PILL STOP.
CAN I GET MY Aleve BACK YET?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY Aleve.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS MAY, BUY Aleve
AND HELP THOSE IN NEED.
MOMMY'S HAVING
A FRENCH FRY.
YES SHE IS, YES SHE IS.
[ bop ]
[ Male Announcer ]
COULD'VE HAD A V8.
100% VEGETABLE JUICE,
WITH THREE OF YOUR DAILY
VEGETABLE SERVINGS
IN EVERY LITTLE BOTTLE.
SEE, I KNEW TESTOSTERONE
COULD AFFECT SEX DRIVE,
BUT NOT ENERGY
OR EVEN MY MOOD.
THAT'S WHEN I TALKED
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD TESTS...
SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.
THAT'S IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.
[ Male Announcer ]
TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T
HAVE ANDROGEL 1.62%
TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED
TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY
INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.
WOMEN AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WITH APPLICATION SITES.
DISCONTINUE ANDROGEL
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED SIGNS
OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,
WHICH MAY INCLUDE
CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE,
POSSIBLY DUE
TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER
OR WHO HAVE OR MIGHT HAVE
PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING,
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
WORSENING OF
AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,
POSSIBLE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER,
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING
OF ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY,
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS,
PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP,
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS,
ESPECIALLY INSULIN,
CORTICOSTEROIDS, OR MEDICINES
TO DECREASE BLOOD CLOTTING.
IN A CLINICAL STUDY, OVER 80%
OF TREATED MEN HAD THEIR
T LEVELS RESTORED TO NORMAL.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.
CHANGE YOUR NUMBER. TURN IT UP.
ANDROGEL 1.62%.
♪
>> THEY ARE STUNNING PICTURES
AND STUNNING STORIES FROM THE
FAMILIES ON THE GROUND THERE IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
AND ONE A FATHER, HIS SON
GABRIEL WAS IN SCHOOL, RODE OUT
THE STORM INSIDE ONE OF THE
SCHOOLS THAT TOOK A DIRECT HIT.
AND HOURS AGO FATHER AND SON
WERE REUNITED, HERE'S THEIR
STORY IN THEIR OWN WORDS.
>> THIS IS GABRIEL AND RYAN
WHEELER.
HE'S MY SON.
AND 30 MINUTES AGO YOU DIDN'T
KNOW WHERE HE WAS?
>> DID NOT KNOW WHERE HE WAS.
I JUST RUSHED HOME, WE JUST GOT
REUNITED, BUT HE'S OKAY.
HE WAS DIRECTLY IN THE TORNADO.
HIS TEACHER WAS RIGHT NEXT TO
HIM.
MISS SIMON HAD THE KIDS IN ONE
HALLWAY, AND SHE SAID THAT IT
SOUNDED LIKE A TRAIN COMING.
SO SHE SAID THAT THEY HAD TO
MOVE, SO THEY WENT INTO AN
INTERIOR CLOSET.
THERE WAS ONLY SIX KIDS.
THEY GOT DOWN.
THEY WERE TELLING STORIES AND
APPARENTLY THEY GOT INTO
POSITION, AND THE TEACHER HELD
THEIR HEADS, AND BRICKS AND
EVERYTHING WERE FALLING ALL OVER
THE KIDS.
SHE GOT HER ARM INJURED.
ONE OF THE BOYS GOT A BIG GASH
IN HIS HEAD BUT HE'S OKAY.
AND HE WAS THE LAST ONE TO BE
REUNITED WITH A FAMILY MEMBER,
SO WE'VE GOT HIM.
SHE SAID HE WAS HELPING PEOPLE,
PULLING STUFF OFF OF KIDS.
WE'RE JUST GLAD THAT HE'S SAFE.
I WAS ON THE HIGHWAY, WE WERE
GETTING SLAMMED WITH HAIL AND
RAIN AGAIN.
AND ALL I WAS THINKING ABOUT WAS
MY SON.
ALL THE REPORTS WERE SAYING THAT
BRIARWOOD WAS GOING.
SO THAT'S ALL -- IT DIDN'T
MATTER.
>> I FELT THEM AND IT WAS
RAINING ON ME AND ALL THAT.
>> CAN YOU TELL ME, IN THAT
CLOSET, WHAT WAS YOUR TEACHER
TELLING YOU AS SHE PUT HER HANDS
OVER YOUR HEAD AND HELD YOU
CLOSE?
>> SHE SAID IT WAS JUST OKAY.
>> FOR ONE FAMILY, SUCH GREAT
NEWS TONIGHT.
>>> AND COMING UP NEXT HERE,
OTHER FAMILIES SENDING A MESSAGE
TO THE WORLD FROM THE STORM
ZONE, HOW ONE WOMAN COMFORTED A
LOT OF SMALL CHILDREN AS THE
TORNADO WAS BEARING DOWN.
male A.
IT'S THE MOST POWERFUL THING
ON THE PLANET.
LOVE HOLDS US IN THE BEGINNING.
COMFORTS US AS WE GROW OLD.
LOVE IS THE REASON YOU CARE.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
IN YOUR LIFE...
THAT MAKE LIFE WORTH LIVING.
♪
♪ SWEET LOVE OF MINE
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
IT'S BEEN THAT WAY
SINCE THE DAY YOU MET.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
IT COULD BE A QUESTION
OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL
FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE
READY ANYTIME
THE MOMENT'S
RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE
MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY
TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME
CIALIS IS THE
ONLY DAILY
ED TABLET
APPROVED TO
TREAT ED AND
SYMPTOMS OF BPH
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN 4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC
REACTIONS SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
[ Female Announcer ]
OFF! Deep Woods Dry Repellent.
THE PROTECTION
OF OFF! Deep Woods
WITH A FORMULA THAT FEELS DRY
NOT GREASY.
OFF! Deep Woods Dry.
Keeps Bugs OFF!
SC Johnson.
WITH THERMACARE HEATWRAPS.
THE ONLY WRAP WITH PATENTED
HEAT CELLS THAT PENETRATE DEEP
TO RELAX, SOOTHE,
AND UNLOCK TIGHT MUSCLES.
AND NOW, INTRODUCING
REUSABLE THERMACARE COLD WRAPS.
PAIN RELIEF
WITHOUT THE SHOCK OF ICE.
♪
>> MORE FACES FROM THE STORM.
AND TONIGHT WE ARE HEARING FROM
ONE WOMAN WHO'S A RESIDENT OF
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
SHE WORKS AT A DAYCARE CENTER,
AND WHEN THE STORM HIT, IT WAS
UP TO HER TO KEEP SMALL CHILDREN
CALM AND SAFE, AND HERE'S WHAT
SHE TOLD US.
>> WE KNEW THE STORMS WERE
COMING.
WE HAD THE NEWS ON AND WE HAD
THE RADIO ON, AND MY PHONE
STARTED GOING OFF, LETTING US
KNOW THERE WAS AN ALERT.
THE RADIO AND TVs WENT OFF AND
THE SIREN.
WE LINE OUR KIDS UP, STRAIGHT
INTO THE INNER MOST BATHROOM AND
PUT MATS ON TOP OF ALL OF US,
HUDDLED TOGETHER UNTIL IT WAS
OVER.
YOU SING AND YOU READ TO MAKE
THEM NOT CRY OR BE SCARED OR
UPSET ABOUT WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
I DIDN'T KNOW WHAT STREET WAS
TURNING ON TO WALK TO MY HOUSE.
HOUSES EVERYWHERE JUST
FLATTENED.
YOU SEE PEOPLE JUST SITTING
AROUND WITH THEIR STUFF THAT'S
DESTROYED.
I FEEL HORRIBLE FOR EVERYBODY
THAT THEIR HOUSES ARE GONE.
AND I WAS AT WORK, SO I DON'T
EVEN KNOW WHAT REALLY HAPPENED.
I KNOW WALKING AROUND AND SEEING
EVERYBODY, IT'S PRETTY TOUGH.
AND I'M REALLY SCARED TO SEE
WHAT MY HOUSE LOOKS LIKE.
>> QUITE A TEACHER, QUITE A
WOMAN.
>>> AND COMING UP, WE HAVE THE
VERY LATEST ON THIS BREAKING
STORY.
NEW TORNADO WARNINGS RIGHT NOW,
AND FINAL THOUGHTS FROM THE
STORM ZONE.
YEARS AGO, MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
TO TAKE A CENTRUM SILVER
MULTIVITAMIN EVERY DAY.
I TOLD HIM, SURE.
CAN'T HURT, RIGHT?
AND NOW TODAY,
I SEE THIS IN THE NEWS.
ONCE AGAIN, CENTRUM SILVER
WAS CHOSEN BY RESEARCHERS
FOR ANOTHER LANDMARK STUDY.
THIS TIME LOOKING AT EYE HEALTH.
MY DOCTOR!
HE KNOWS HIS STUFF.
[ Male Announcer ] CENTRUM.
THE MOST STUDIED.
THE MOST RECOMMENDED.
AND THE MOST PREFERRED
MULTIVITAMIN BRAND.
THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
MORE...
STEP!
[ Mom ] MY LITTLE GIRL...SHE
LOVES TO HELP OUT ON BIG JOBS.
GOOD THING THERE'S
BOUNTY SELECT-A-SIZE.
IT'S THE SMALLER POWERFUL SHEET
THAT ACTS LIKE A BIG SHEET.
LOOK! ONE SELECT-A-SIZE SHEET
OF BOUNTY
IS 50% MORE ABSORBENT
THAN A FULL SIZE SHEET
OF THE LEADING ORDINARY BRAND.
♪
I GOT IT!
[ Mom ] USE LESS WITH THE SMALL
BUT POWERFUL PICKER UPPER.
BOUNTY SELECT-A-SIZE.
AND TRY BOUNTY NAPKINS.
THAT'S NOT MUCH, YOU THINK.
EXCEPT IT'S 2% EVERY YEAR.
GO TO E-TRADE AND FIND OUT
HOW MUCH OUR ADVICE
AND GUIDANCE COSTS.
SPOILER ALERT: IT'S LOW.
IT'S GUIDANCE ON YOUR TERMS,
NOT OURS.
E-TRADE. LESS FOR US.
MORE FOR YOU.
I WORKED A PATROL UNIT FOR 17
YEARS IN THE CITY OF BALTIMORE.
WHEN I FIRST STARTED
EXPERIENCING THE PAIN,
IT'S HARD TO DESCRIBE
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A NUMBNESS
BUT YET YOU HAVE THE PAIN
LIKE THOUSANDS OF NEEDLES
STICKING IN YOUR FOOT.
IT WAS PROGRESSIVELY
GETTING WORSE,
AND AT THAT POINT,
I KNEW I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
WHEN I WENT BACK
TO MY HEALTH CARE PROFESSIONAL,
THAT'S WHEN SHE SUGGESTED
THE LYRICA.
ONCE I STARTED
TAKING THE LYRICA,
THE PAIN STARTED SUBSIDING.
[ Male Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYE SIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN, AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS, AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO'VE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
TO HEAR MORE OF TERRY'S STORY,
VISIT LYRICA.COM.
>>> A DEVASTATING SCENE IN
OKLAHOMA.
BREAKING NEWS, DEDETAILS ON
THE MASSIVE PATH OF
DESTRUCTION.
>> ALSO A BUSY AFTERNOON FOR
FIREFIGHTERS ACROSS THE BAY
AREA.
WE'LL SHOW YOU WHERE THIS
SIX-ALARM FIRE BURNED HOMES
THIS AFTERNOON.
>> TWO REASONS TO SAY YAHOO
TODAY.
AT YAHOO.
BIG MOVES INSPIRED BY THE
YOUTH MOVEMENT NOW UNDERWAY.
>> AND THE BAY AREA UNIVERSITY
WITH A LOFTY GOAL TO RESHAPE
THE FUTURE OF HUMANITY.
>> THIS IS TERRIBLE, GUYS.
ABSOLUTELY TERRIBLE THIS,
TORNADO IS MASSIVE.
>> IT IS MASSIVE.
TONIGHT WIDE SPREAD
DEVASTATION IN OKLAHOMA AFTER
A MONSTER TORNADO TOUCHES
DMOUN A POPULATED SUBURB ARE
RIPPING THROUGH SCHOOLS AND
HOMES JUST SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA
CITY.
WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING THIS
STORY ALL DAY LONG.
GOOD EVENING, I'M DAN ASHLEY.
>> THE STATE MEDICAL EXAMINER
SAYS THE DEATH TOLL HAS NOW
RISEN TO 51.
THE NUMBER IS EXPECTED TO
CLIMB.
WE HAVE SOME IMAGES TO SHOW
YOU.
EMERGENCY RESPONDERS ARE IN
SEARCH AND RESCUE MODE
SEARCHING FOR ANY TRAPPED
SURVIVORS.
AMONG THE DEAD AT LEAST SEVEN
CHILDREN FROM AN ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL HIT HARD BY THE STORM.
100 PEOPLE, IN FACT 65 OF THEM,
CHILDREN, BEING TREATSED AT
SEVERAL HOSPITALS IN THE
OKLAHOMA CITY AREA.
MANY OF THEM SUFFERED MAJOR
INJURIES.
FIVE OF THE CHILDREN BROUGHT
FROM A LOCAL ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
THE HEAVIEST DAMAGE IS IN THE
COMMUNITY OF MOORE ON THE
SOUTHEASTERN EDGE OF OKLAHOMA
CITY, NOT FAR FROM DOWNTOWN.
WE HAVE REMARKABLE VIDEO JUST
MOMENTS BEFORE IT TOUCHED DOWN.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE IMPACT
FROM THE TORNADO APPEARS TO BE
MORE SEVERE THAN THE ONE IN
1999 WHAT DEVASTATED THE
UNIVERSITY, KILLING 36 PEOPLE.
THE PRESIDENT...