WARRIORS.
>> YES.
>> THEY'LL GET REGISTRATION.
>> HOW FUN IS THAT.
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT OUT OF CONTROL, HOW TO
STOP THE WILDFIRE NOW
THREATENING ONE OF AMERICA'S
GREAT NATIONAL PARKS, TRIPLING
IN SIZE, BURNING IN THREE
DIRECTIONS TONIGHT.
THOUSANDS OF FAMILIES IN ITS
PATH.
WE'RE LIVE AT YOSEMITE.
>> BREAKING NEWS, THE STUNNING
NUMBERS ON SYRIA, HOW MANY
PEOPLE MIGHT HAVE BEEN ATTACKED
WITH CHEMICAL WEAPONS AND WHAT
THE FBI DIRECTOR IS TELLING ABC
NEWS ABOUT AMERICANS IN SYRIA.
ARE THEY A NEW THREAT TO OUR
HOMELAND.
>>> TEXT MESSAGES, THE TEENAGER
ABDUCTED AND RESCUED FROM THE
WOODS REVEALING WHAT WAS IN
THOSE MESSAGES AND LETTERS SHE
EXCHANGED WITH HER KIDNAPPER.
>>> AND VANISHED.
WATCH THESE TREES TONIGHT
DISAPPEAR BEFORE OUR EYES.
THE MASSIVE SINK HOLE CAUGHT ON
TAPE IN ONE AMERICAN COMMUNITY,
WHAT CAUSED IT, AND THIS EVENING
WHERE IT COULD HAPPEN NEXT.
>> GOOD EVENING.
DIANE IS OFF ON THIS THURSDAY
NIGHT.
WE DO BEGIN WITH AN AMERICAN
TREASURE THREATENED BY THAT
FIERCE AND GROWING WILDFIRE
TONIGHT.
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK AND THAT
FIRE INCHING CLOSER BY THE
MINUTE.
THIS IS THE SCENE ON THE GROUND
THIS EVENING.
THE ANCIENT SEQUOIAS, FIRE
TRUCKS RUSHING THROUGH VALLEYS
OF FIRE.
AND JUST LISTEN TONIGHT.
THE SOUND OF THAT WILDFIRE
RAGING OUT OF CONTROL, HUNDREDS
OF FIREFIGHTERS NOW DEPLOYED.
NEW EVACUATIONS UNDER WAY.
THAT FIRE ONE OF AT LEAST 50
BURNING IN THE WEST TONIGHT
IN THE COUNTY WHERE YOSEMITE IS
JUST DECLARING A STATE OF
EMERGENCY.
ABC'S NEAL KARLINSKY IS ON THE
FRONT LINES FOR US AND HE LEADS
US OFF TONIGHT.
GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING FROM
THE SOUTH SIDE OF AN ANGRY FIRE
TONIGHT.
THESE ARE NOT CLOUDS BEHIND ME.
THIS IS SMOKE.
THIS GIVES YOU A SENSE OF THE
SIZE AND THE SOAP OF THIS BLAZE
AS THESE PLUMES CONTINUE TO
INTENSIFY AND GET DARKER AND DIE
DOWN AGAIN AS THIS FIRE IS
FOUGHT MAINLY FROM THE AIR.
AT THE YOSEMITE ROSE BED AND
BREAKFAST BUILT FOR THE
THOUSANDS WHO FLOCK TO ITS
UNTOUCHED BEAUTY EACH YEAR,
THEY'RE MAKING THEIR LAST STAND.
THE FIRE IS COMING OVER THE HILL
STRAIGHT AT THEM AND THE OWNER
IN HIS BULLDOZER TO HELP OUT IS
MAKING PLANS WITH THE FIRE TEAM.
>> GIVE ME THE SIGNAL AND I CAN
MAKE LAPS AROUND THE HOUSE
WITHOUT A PROBLEM.
>> Reporter: JUST DOWN THE ROAD
THIS MAN HAS ANOTHER FIRE TEAM
AT HIS HOUSE, STARING DOWN AN
INTENSE AERIAL FIRE FIGHT TO
STOP THE FLAMES BEFORE THEY BURN
THROUGH HIS PROPERTY.
>> ARE YOU STICKING HERE
THROUGHOUT?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SLEL TER SHELTER IN PLACE,
PROTECT WHAT I CAN AS LONG AS I
CAN.
>> Reporter: THE WIND HAS CAUSED
RAPIDLY CHANGING CONDITIONS AS
WE FOUND OUT FIRST HAND.
IT SHOT UP AGAIN, THE FLAMES
DID.
WHILE SHOOTING THIS MATERIAL IN
THE FIRE ZONE -- WHOA!
A CHUNK OF FLAMING TREE BIG
ENOUGH TO SERIOUSLY HURT SOMEONE
FELL NEAR OUR CAR.
IT'S UNUSUALLY BAD RIGHT NOW
EVEN THOUGH THE WILDFIRE NUMBERS
ARE DOWN NATIONWIDE.
THEY'RE WAY UP IN CALIFORNIA
WHERE THERE HAVE BEEN NEARLY 40
PERCENT MORE FIRES THAN LAST
YEAR.
HUNDREDS MORE CAUSED BY
LIGHTNING WITHIN JUST DAYS.
WE FOUND HOMEOWNERS PACKED UP,
READY TO LEAVE IF THEY HAVE TO.
>> IF WE LOSE IT ALL, WE HAVE A
GREAT INSURANCE POLICY, SO.
>> HOPEFULLY IT WON'T COME TO
THAT.
>> WE'LL START ALL OVER AGAIN.
>> Reporter: THE FIRE IS NOT
THREATENING ANY MORE HOMES RIGHT
NOW BUT IT IS CONTINUING TO
GROW.
IT HAS TRIPLED IN SIZE SINCE
YESTERDAY.
THEY'VE GOT A REAL FIGHT ON
THEIR HANDS.
>> THAT DARK SMOKE BEHIND YOU,
NEAL.
THANKS TO YOU.
I WANT TO BRING IN ABC'S
METEOROLOGIST GINGER ZEE WHO IS
TRACKING THIS FIRE FOR US.
YOU WERE TELLING ME THE FIRE IS
CLOSE TO YOSEMITE AND THE PARK
IS NOT IN THE CLEAR YET.
>> NOT AT ALL.
THEY HAVE THAT DRY FOALAGE.
IT'S ALL OF THE WEST.
50 LARGE WILDFIRES IN NINE
STATES OUT WEST DEALING WITH
THIS.
LIGHTNING AS NEAL MENTIONED A
HUGE ISSUE.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE RED FLAG
WARNINGS FOR SO MANY PLACES.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU WHO HAS THIS.
SEE THAT LOW PRESSURE SYSTEM.
THAT'S PART OF THE ISSUE.
KICKING OFF THUNDERSTORMS, GUSTY
WINDS AND IN JUST THE LAST 24
HOURS OVER 4,400 LIGHTNING
STRIKES STARTING 45 NEW FIRES
JUST IN CALIFORNIA.
>> GINGER, THANKS TO YOU AS
ALWAYS.
>>> WE TURN OVERSEAS TO SYRIA
AND THE STUNNING NUMBERS TONIGHT
WE HEARD FROM THE STATE
DEPARTMENT, POTENTIALLY MORE
THAN 1,000 VICTIMS IN THE LATEST
POSSIBLE CHEMICAL ATTACKS, THE
WORLD STILL STUDYING THOSE
DISTURBING IMAGES, THE VICTIMS,
INCLUDING WOMEN AND CHILDREN OF
THIS NEWEST ATTACK.
THIS EVENING THAT DISTURBING
HEADLINE FROM WASHINGTON ABOUT
WHAT WE COULD BE LOOKING AT NOW.
U.N. WEAPONS INSPECTORS ARE ON
THE GROUND FACING HUGE HURDLES
TRYING TO DETERMINE IF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS WERE, IN FACT, ACCUSED.
ABC'S CHIEF GLOBAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT MARTHA RADDATZ IS
IN THE REGION FOR US TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: IT'S A TERRIBLE AND
URGENT TASK.
TONIGHT THE U.S. AND U.N. RACING
TO FIND OUT WHETHER CHEMICAL
WEAPONS KILLED THESE MEN, WOMEN
AND CHILDREN AND JUST HOW MANY
DIED.
TODAY A SHOCKING NEW NUMBER FROM
OPPOSITION GROUPS REVEALED IN
WASHINGTON.
>> THE MOST RECENT ESTIMATES
WE'VE SEEN RANGE FROM 1,000 TO
1800 WHICH IS OBVIOUSLY A BROAD
RANGE.
>> Reporter: THE ASSAD REGIME
SAYS THE CLAIMS THAT IT CARRIED
OUT A CHEMICAL ATTACK ARE
BASELESS.
BUT THE WORLD IS REACTING
SWIFTLY AND FORCEFULLY.
AS U.N. INVESTIGATORS BEG FOR
ACCESS TO THE SITE, THE EVIDENCE
MAY BE QUICKLY DISSIPATING.
DAVID, TONIGHT PRESIDENT OBAMA
HAS DIRECTED THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY TO DO EVERYTHING
POSSIBLE TO FIND ADDITIONAL
INFORMATION ABOUT THIS SUSPECTED
ATTACK, BUT WE DON'T KNOW WHAT
THE U.S. RESPONSE WOULD BE.
DAVID?
>> MARTHA RADDATZ WITH US AGAIN
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>>> ALSO NEW WORD THIS EVENING
ON AMERICANS NOW BELIEVED TO
HAVE JOINED THE FIGHT ON THE
GROUND IN SYRIA POTENTIALLY
HELPING TERRORIST GROUPS THERE.
COULD THOSE AMERICANS, IN FACT,
POSE A THREAT TO OUR HOMELAND.
OUR SENIOR JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT
PIERRE THOMAS SAT DOWN WITH FBI
DIRECTOR ROBERT MULLER TODAY.
>> WE KNOW MULLER IS ABOUT TO
STEP DOWN AFTER 12 YEARS.
THIS WAS REALLY SOMETHING TODAY
IN YOUR INTERVIEW EXPRESSING
REAL CONCERN ABOUT AMERICANS ON
THE GROUND IN SYRIA?
>> REPORTER: THE FBI DIRECTOR IS
CONCERNED ABOUT RADICALS WHO
HAVE GONE TO FIGHT INCLUDING
MEMBERS OF AL QAEDA, AND HE SAID
THERE IS INTELLIGENCE AMERICANS
MAY HAVE JOINED THEM.
>> YOU ARE CONCERNED ABOUT WHAT
THEY -- NUMBER ONE, THE
ASSOCIATIONS THEY WILL MAKE AND
SECONDLY, THE EXPERTISE THEY
WILL DEVELOP AND WHETHER OR NOT
THEY WILL UTILIZE THAT EXPERTISE
TO UNDERTAKE AN ATTACK IN THE
HOMELAND.
SO, YES, WE ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
THAT.
>> AS HE GETS READY TO LEAVE HIS
POST, PIERRE, YOU ASKED WHAT
STILL KEEPS HIM UP AT NIGHT AND
WHAT DID HE TELL YOU?
>> Reporter: HE WAS BLUNT AS
ALWAYS.
HE WORRIES ABOUT TERRORISTS
TAKING ON A PLANE WITH A BOMB OR
USING BIOLOGICAL OR CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
HE SAID THOSE THREATS ARE VERY,
VERY REAL.
>> PIERRE THOMAS WITH US FROM
OUR WASHINGTON BUREAU, THANK
YOU.
>>> FROM SYRIA TO THE BREAKING
IMAGES FROM EGYPT TONIGHT WHERE
AFTER MORE THAN TWO YEARS BEHIND
BARS, FORMER PRESIDENT HOSNI
MUBARAK WAS LET OUT OF PRISON,
TAKEN AWAY IN A HELICOPTER.
A DRAMATIC CHANGE OF FORTUNE
FROM OUR TIME THERE DURING THE
REVOLUTION THAT BROUGHT HIM
DOWN.
OUR ABC NEWS TEAM WAS ON THE
GROUND IN CAIRO AS THEY PUSHED
HIM FROM POWER.
WE ALL REMEMBER THAT MOMENT IN
THE
SQUARE AS SUPPORTERS WITH WHIPS
RODE IN ON CAMEL AND HORSE BACK
TARGETING THE PROTESTORS.
NOT LONG AFTER, THIS IMAGE,
AROUND THE WORLD OF MUBARAK
DISGRACED IN A CAGE IN A
COURTROOM.
TONIGHT THE EYES OF EGYPT AND
THE WORLD WERE ON THAT
HELICOPTER, MUBARAK BEING
WHISKED AWAY TO A MILITARY
HOSPITAL.
THE MAN ELECTED TO REPLACE HIM,
MOHAMMED MORSI, IN PRISON
INSTEAD.
>>> BACK AT HOME TO AN AMERICAN
WHO SHARED SECRETS BEFORE EDWARD
SNOWDEN AND THE NSA.
BRADLEY MANNING WAS THE ARMY
PRIVATE WHO LEAKED THE TOP
SECRET DOCUMENTS, JUST SENTENCED
TO 35 YEARS BEHIND BARS THIS
WEEK, TONIGHT REVEALING HE WANTS
TO LIVE BEHIND BARS AS A WOMAN.
THE AMERICAN MILITARY RESPONDING
TO THAT REQUEST.
HERE'S ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT JIM AVILA NOW.
>> Reporter: BRADLEY MANNING HAD
ONE MORE SECRET TO TELL, THE
SMALL STATURED MAN IN THE ARMY
GREENS IS ACTUALLY A WOMAN
INSIDE.
THOSE PICTURES OF HIM CROSS
DRESSING SHOWN AT TRIAL WERE
REAL AND NOT A DEFENSE TACTIC.
IN A LETTER RELEASED TODAY,
MANNING WROTE, "AS I TRANSITION
INTO THIS NEXT PHASE OF MY LIFE,
I WANT EVERYONE TO KNOW THE REAL
ME.
I AM CHELSEA MANNING.
I AM A FEMALE."
MANNING WANTS TO BE CALLED "SHE"
AND BEGIN THE TRANSFORMATION
IMMEDIATELY.
"GIVEN THE WAY THAT I FEEL AND
HAVE FELT SINCE CHILDHOOD, I
WANT TO BEGIN HORMONE THERAPY AS
SOON AS POSSIBLE."
THAT MAY BE DIFFICULT BECAUSE AT
FORT LEAVENWORTH WHERE HE'S TO
SERVE A 35-YEAR SENTENCE FOR
RELEASING 700,000 DOCUMENTS TO
WIKILEAKS, THE MILITARY DOES NOT
OFFER THAT TYPE OF TREATMENT BUT
MANNING'S ATTORNEY VOWS TO
FIGHT.
>> I'M GOING TO CHANGE THAT.
>> Reporter: THE ATTORNEYS FIRST
DEMONSTRATED THEIR CLIENT'S
FEELING ABOUT BEING A WOMAN
DURING THE PRE-TRIAL HEARINGS.
MANNING CALLED HIMSELF BRIE YAN
NA BACK THEN.
TODAY THE SIGNATURE READS
CHELSEA.
JIM AVILA, ABC NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> NEXT TO CALIFORNIA TONIGHT
AND THE TEENAGER KIDNAPPED AND
RESCUED FROM THE WOODS, HANNAH
ANDERSON.
WE HAD LEARNED ABOUT THE DOZEN
TEXT MESSAGES SENT BACK AND
FORTH WITH THE KIDNAPPER IN THE
HOURS BEFORE IT UNFOLDED.
TONIGHT SHE REVEALS IN HER OWN
WORDS WHAT THOSE TEXT MESSAGES
WERE ABOUT AND THE LETTER SHE
EXCHANGED WITH THE ALLEGED
KIDNAPPER, TOO.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: SHE WAS KIDNAPPED,
HER MOTHER AND BROTHER TORTURED
AND KILLED.
NOW A LITTLE MORE THAN A WEEK
AFTER HER RESCUE, 16-YEAR-OLD
HANNAH ANDERSON SEEN BY SO MANY
AS A VICTIM, FEELS THE NEED TO
DEFEND HERSELF.
IN AN INTERVIEW BROADCAST ON NBC
NEWS, SHE EXPLAINED WHY SHE HAD
WRITTEN LETTERS TO JIM DiMAGGIO
HER 40-YEAR-OLD ABDUCTOR WHO SHE
HAD ALWAYS KNOWN AS UNCLE JIM.
>> THE LETTERS WERE FROM A YEAR
AGO WHEN ME AND MY MOM WEREN'T
GETTING ALONG VERY WELL.
ME AND HIM TALKED ABOUT HOW TO
DEAL WITH IT.
HE HELPED ME THROUGH IT.
>> Reporter: AS FOR THE 13 PHONE
EXCHANGES WITH DiMAGGIO THE DAY
OF HER ABDUCTION, SHE SAYS THEY
WEREN'T PHONE CALLS BUT TEXT
MESSAGES BECAUSE HE WAS PICKING
HER UP FROM CHEERLEADING CAMP
AND DIDN'T KNOW WHERE TO FIND
HER.
AS THE COMMUNITY COMES TOGETHER
TO RAISE MONEY FOR THE FUNERAL
OF HER MOW AND 8-YEAR-OLD
BROTHER, HANNAH EXPRESSES
GRATITUDE FOR THE AMBER ALERT
THAT SHE SAYS SAVED HER.
>> I DIDN'T REALLY KNOW WHAT IT
WAS BUT I KNOW IT HELPED PEOPLE
FIND ME.
WITH EVERYONE'S SUPPORT IT CAN
HELP A LOT.
>> Reporter: HER HOPE NOW, THAT
PEOPLE WON'T SEE HER AS A VICTIM
BUT AS A SURVIVOR INSTEAD.
LINSEY DAVIS, ABC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>>> TO BOSTON TONIGHT, NEW
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE CASE OF THE
FORMER FOOTBALL STAR CHARGED
WITH MURDER IN MASSACHUSETTS.
FORMER NEW ENGLAND PATRIOT AARON
HERNANDEZ DIDN'T SPEAK BUT
MOUTHED THE WORDS "I LOVE YOU"
TO HIS MOTHER IN COURT TODAY.
HE WAS INDICTED BY A GRAND JURY
FOR SHOOTING HIS FRIEND.
PROSECUTORS SAY HE ORCHESTRATED
THAT KILLING.
HE'S BEING HELD WITHOUT BAIL AND
REMAINS IN SOLITARY CONFINEMENT.
>>> TO A CASE PLAYING OUT IN SAN
DIEGO TONIGHT INVOLVING THE
EMBATTLED MAYOR THERE.
ALL WEEK PROTESTORS PUTTING
PRESSURE ON THE MAYOR TO RESIGN
AFTER THE SEXUAL HARASSMENT
SCANDAL, THAT 1-800 NUMBER SET
UP FOR ALLEGED VICTIMS.
ONE PROTESTER TAKING TO THE AIR
WRITING, "SURRENDER BOB," ACROSS
THE SKY.
TONIGHT A NEW IMAGE GIVING US A
CLUE ABOUT WHAT THE DISGRACED
MAYOR MAY BE PLANNING NEXT.
ABC'S RYAN OWENS ON THE CASE
AGAIN TONIGHT.
>> MAYOR FILNER, ARE YOU GOING
TO RESIGN?
>> Reporter: IF THIS VIDEO IS
ANY INDICATION, IT MAY FINALLY
BE OVER.
SAN DIEGO MAYOR BOB FILNER
LOADING BOXES INTO HIS SUV
OUTSIDE CITY HALL LAST NIGHT.
>> GOOD TO SEE YOU GUYS.
>> Reporter: AFFILIATE KGTV HAS
LEARNED MAYOR FILNER IS PREPARED
TO RESIGN TOMORROW IF THE CITY
COUNCIL SIGNS OFF ON A DEAL
HASHED OUT OVER THREE DAYS OF
MEDIATION.
THE 70-YEAR-OLD IS ACCUSED OF
SEXUALLY HARASSING 18 WOMEN.
>> THERE WAS A HAND THAT WENT TO
MY BACK, TO MY BUTTOCK AND I WAS
SHOCKED.
>> Reporter: THE DETAILS OF THE
SETTLEMENT ARE CONFIDENTIAL BUT
MANY DON'T WANT TAXPAYERS TO PAY
FILNER ANOTHER CENT.
>> HIS PARTING GIFT SHOULD BE
GOOD RIDDANCE INSTEAD OF A
HANDOUT.
>> Reporter: ESPECIALLY
ACCORDING TO HIS CRITICS BECAUSE
HE'S BECOME SUCH A PUNCH LINE.
♪ MAYBE IT'S TIME YOU LEFT
>> Reporter: IN FACT, SOME
VOTERS WANT HIM RECALLED BEFORE
HE CAN QUIT.
THEY SAY RESIGNATION IS TOO EASY
FOR A MAN WHO HAS EMBARRASSED
AMERICA'S 8th LARGEST CITY.
RYAN OWENS, ABC NEWS, SAN DIEGO.
>>> NOW TO THE BREAKING HEADLINE
WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING ALL DAY
FROM WALL STREET.
REAL CONCERN TODAY WHEN
COMPUTERS SUDDENLY FROZE, STOCKS
HALTED, NO ONE KNEW WHAT WAS
HAPPENING AT THE NASDAQ AS
AMERICANS AND THEIR 401(k)s,
THEIR RETIREMENTS, WERE FOR A
TIME FROZEN FOR THREE HOURS.
I WANT TO BRING IN OUR CHIEF
BUSINESS AND ECONOMICS
CORRESPONDENT REBECCA JARVIS.
YOU WERE WITH US ALL AFTERNOON.
YOU WERE TELLING ME THIS IS
UNPRECEDENTED.
>> THIS IS SOMETHING WE'VE NEVER
SEEN BEFORE IN COMPANIES MOST
PEOPLE OWN IN THEIR RETIREMENT
SAVINGS -- APPLE, GOOGLE,
MICROSOFT, FACEBOOK.
ALL OF THESE COMPANIES CEASED TO
TRADE FOR THREE HOURS TODAY.
MUCH OF THAT TIME WAS SPENT
TRYING TO DETERMINE JUST WHY
THAT WAS.
VERY LITTLE INFORMATION COMING
OUT.
THEY'VE TRACED IT TO A TECHNICAL
PROBLEM AT THE NASDAQ BUT STILL
WE DON'T KNOW WHY THAT HAPPENED.
>> WE KNOW THERE WAS A FEAR THAT
THIS WAS A POTENTIAL TERROR
THREAT, A POSSIBLE HACKER.
THE FBI DIRECTOR TOLD ABC NEWS
THIS IS THE KIND OF THING THAT
KEEPS HIM UP AT NIGHT.
>> THIS IS WHY THE PRESIDENT WAS
NOTIFIED.
THE S.E.C., THE TREASURY ALL
WATCHING THIS SITUATION TO
DETERMINE EXACTLY WHERE IT GOES.
THERE IS A VERY REAL CYBER
THREAT AND IF IT IMPACTS OUR
MARKETS IT COULD IMPACT PEOPLE'S
LIVES.
>> WE SHOULD MENTION WHEN IT WAS
ALL OVER THE NASDAQ CLOSED UP 38
POINTS TODAY.
THE DOW WAS UP 66 POINTS.
NO MONEY WAS LOST BUT SOME REAL
NERVES WERE TESTED ON WALL
STREET THIS AFTERNOON.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS" THIS
THURSDAY NIGHT.
LOOK AT THESE TREES THIS
EVENING.
THIS IS NO SCI-FI THRILLER, THIS
IS THE REAL THING IN AN AMERICAN
TOWN, A MASSIVE SINK HOLE.
WHAT CAUSED IT.
WHY SCIENTISTS SAY IT CAN HAPPEN
AGAIN AND WHERE.
>>> BREAKING, A HUSBAND
OVERBOARD, LOST AT SEA, JUST
FOUND, SURVIVED 18 HOURS, NO
LIFE VEST, HOW DID HE DO IT?
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS IS CLAIRA.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT ALEVE
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HER,
SHE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HER ALL DAY
TO SEE HOW IT GOES.
[ Claira ] AFTER THE DELIVERIES,
I WAS OKAY.
NOW THE CIABATTA IS DONE
AND THE PAIN IS STARTING AGAIN.
MORE PILLS? SERIOUSLY?
SERIOUSLY.
[ GROANS ]
ALL THESE STOPS TO TAKE
MORE PILLS CAN BE A PAIN.
CAN I GET MY ALEVE BACK?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY ALEVE.
[ Male Announcer ] LOOK FOR THE
EASY-OPEN RED ARTHRITIS CAP.
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY ALEVE.
I DBEFORE I DOSEARCH
ANY PROJECTS ON MY HOME.
I LOVE MY CONTRACTOR,
AND I AM SO THANKFUL
TO ANGIE'S LIST
FOR BRINGING US TOGETHER.
FIND OUT WHY
MORE THAN TWO MILLION MEMBERS
COUNT ON ANGIE'S LIST.
ANGIE'S LIST --
REVIEWS YOU CAN TRUST.
[ Male Announcer ] EVER WONDER
WHY NO OTHER MOUTHWASH
FEELS LIKE LISTERINE®?
BECAUSE NO OTHER MOUTHWASH
WORKS LIKE LISTERINE®.
IN YOUR MOUTH,
BACTERIA FORMS IN LAYERS.
LISTERINE® PENETRATES
THESE LAYERS
DEEPER THAN OTHER MOUTHWASHES,
KILLING BACTERIA ALL THE WAY
DOWN TO THE BOTTOM LAYER.
SO FOR A CLEANER,
HEALTHIER MOUTH,
GO WITH THE MOUTHWASH
DENTISTS RECOMMEND
MORE THAN ALL OTHERS COMBINED.
#1 DENTIST RECOMMENDED
LISTERINE®...
POWER TO YOUR MOUTH™.
#1 DENTIST RECOMMENDED
LISTERINE®...
THIS MAN IS ABOUT TO BE
THE MILLIONTH CUSTOMER.
WOULD YOU MIND IF
I GO AHEAD OF YOU?
INSTEAD WE HAD SOMEONE
GO AHEAD OF HIM
AND WIN FIFTY THOUSAND DOLLARS.
CONGRATULATIONS YOU ARE
OUR ONE MILLIONTH CUSTOMER.
NOBODY LIKES TO MISS OUT.
THAT'S WHY ALLY TREATS ALL
THEIR CUSTOMERS THE SAME.
WHETHER YOU'RE THE
FIRST OR THE MILLIONTH.
IF YOUR BANK DOESN'T THINK
YOU'RE SPECIAL ANYMORE,
YOU NEED AN ALLY.
ALLY BANK.
YOUR MONEY NEEDS AN ALLY.
♪
NOW YOU CAN GIVE YOURSELF
A KICK IN THE REAR!
V8 V-FUSION PLUS ENERGY.
NATURAL ENERGY FROM GREEN TEA
PLUS FRUITS AND VEGGIES.
NEED A LITTLE KICK?
OOH!
COULD'VE HAD A V8.
IN THE JUICE AISLE.
>>> IT'S REALLY BEEN SOMETHING.
WE'VE SEEN A NUMBER OF THOSE
STUNNING SINK HOLES THIS YEAR
BUT NOTHING LIKE THIS.
TONIGHT A REMARKABLE SCENE IN
LOUISIANA CAUGHT ON CAMERA,
EVERYTHING VANISHING IN 30
SECONDS BUT WHAT CAUSED IT AND
COULD IT HAPPEN NEAR YOU.
HERE'S ABC'S MATT GUTMAN
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THIS IS NOT AN
OPTICAL ILLUSION.
A STAND OF TREES SEEMLY MELTING
INTO THIS SWAMP IN LOUISIANA IS
BEING SWALLOWED INTO A MASSIVE
SINK HOLE, SUCKING EVERYTHING
DOWN WITH IT.
WATCH THOSE TREES AGAIN DIPPING
SLOWLY AT FIRST AND THEN QUICKLY
VANISHING INTO THE HOLE.
SCIENTISTS SAY IT'S MORE THAN A
FOOTBALL FIELD DEEP.
IT'S NEAR AN OLD SALT MINE.
WORKERS WERE USING WATER TO
DISSOLVE AND PUMP OUT THE SALT
DEEP UNDERGROUND AND EVENTUALLY
PUMPED OUT ENOUGH TO MAKE THE
GROUND GIVE WAY.
NOW THE EARTH SLOWLY MOVES INTO
THE CAVERN CAUSING GROWING SINK
HOLES ABOVE.
>> IT'S GOING TO CONTINUE TO
GROW UNTIL IT FINDS A POINT
WHERE IT CAN SUPPORT ITSELF.
>> Reporter: THE SINK HOLE
APPEARED A YEAR AGO.
150 HOUSEHOLDS WERE EVACUATED
AND THE STATE IS SUING THE
COMPANY THAT MINED THE SALT.
SINK HOLES ARE COMMON AND OFTEN
OCCUR NATURALLY.
THIS ONE IN DOWNTOWN GUATEMALA
CITY BORE A HOLE BIG ENOUGH TO
SWALLOW THE STATUE OF LIBERTY.
THEY RIDDLED THE STATE OF
FLORIDA BECAUSE MOST OF THE
STATE SITS ON POUROUS LIMESTONE.
>> IT BURNS THROUGH THE ROCK.
WE'RE TALKING HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF YEARS.
>> Reporter: THIS SINK HOLE NEAR
ORLANDO GULPED DOWN PART OF A
RESORT, FORCING DOZENS TO
EVACUATE.
ANOTHER ONE IN FLORIDA EARLIER
THIS YEAR TURNED DEADLY, KILLING
JEFF BUSH AS HE LAY SLEEPING IN
BED.
PERHAPS THERE IS NO GREATER
VISUAL OF A SINK HOLE'S
DESTRUCTIVE POWER THAN THIS.
MATT GUTMAN, ABC NEWS,
LOUISIANA.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, BREAKING
TONIGHT, AN AMAZING TALE OF
SURVIVAL, A HUSBAND WHO SURVIVED
18 HOURS, TOSSED OVERBOARD, NO
LIFE JACKET.
WHERE THIS HAPPENED WHEN WE COME
BACK.
>>> AND A POP STAR WHO SURPRISED
AN ENTIRE FLIGHT.
HE DIDN'T SAY, "THIS IS YOUR
CAPTAIN SPEAKING."
HE SANG INSTEAD, WHEN WE COME
BACK.
INSTEAD, WHEN WE COME
IT WAS VERY
PAINFUL
SITUATION.
THE RASH WAS ON MY RIGHT HIP,
GOING ALL THE WAY DOWN MY LEG.
I'M VERY ATHLETIC AND
I SWIM IN THE OCEAN.
SHINGLES FORCED ME
OUT OF THE WATER.
THE DOCTOR ASKED ME
"DID YOU HAVE CHICKENPOX
WHEN YOU WERE A CHILD?"
THE PAIN LEVEL WAS SO HIGH,
IT BECAME UNBEARABLE.
AT HUMANA, OUR MEDICARE AGENTS
SIT DOWN WITH YOU AND ASK.
BEING ACTIVE.
AND BEING WITH THIS GUY.
[ Male Announcer ]
GETTING TO KNOW YOU
IS HOW WE HELP YOU CHOOSE
THE HUMANA MEDICARE PLAN
THAT WORKS BEST FOR YOU.
MI FAMILIA.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
WE WANT TO HELP YOU ACHIEVE
YOUR BEST HEALTH,
SO YOU CAN KEEP DOING
THE THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT TO YOU.
TAKING CARE
OF OUR CUSTOMERS.
TAKING CARE OF HER.
AND THE NEXT THING ON OUR LIST
IS BUNGEE JUMPING.
[ Male Announcer ]
HELPING YOU --
NOW THAT'S WHAT'S IMPORTANT
TO US.
[ CRASHING ]
[ Male Announcer ] WHEN YOUR
FAVORITE FOOD STARTS A FIGHT,
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
AND GOES TO WORK IN SECONDS.
♪ TUM, TUM TUM TUM TUMS!
STARTS WITH FRESHLY-MADE PASTA,
AND 100% REAL CHEDDAR CHEESE.
BUT WHAT MAKES STOUFFER'S
MAC N' CHEESE BEST OF ALL.
THAT MOMENT
YOU ENJOY IT AT HOME.
STOUFFER'S. MADE WITH CARE
FOR YOU OR YOUR FAMILY.
SHE'AND YOU LOVE HER FOR IT.IDE.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A
QUESTION OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME
THE MOMENT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS
THE ONLY DAILY ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED
AND SYMPTOMS OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL YOUR MEDICAL
CONDITIONS AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN 4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC
REACTIONS SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
>> OUR "INSTANT INDEX" TONIGHT
STARTS WITH AN AMAZING SURVIVAL
TALE.
AT 10:00:A.M. A MAN SET OUT ON A
SOLO FISHING TRIP IN THE GULF OF
MEXICO.
THREE HOURS LATER HE TEXTED HIS
WIFE THIS PICTURE BUT THAT WAS
LAST SHE HEARD FROM HIM.
BY 8:30 AT NIGHT SHE CALLED THE
POLICE.
RESCUE CREWS SEARCHED BY AIR AND
SEA.
AT 4:00 IN THE MORNING THEY
FOUND HIM ALIVE FLOATING WITHOUT
A LIFE VEST, TREADING WATER, 18
HOURS LATER FOUND, AND A WIFE
RELIEVED TONIGHT.
>>> SOMETHING MILLIONS OF
AMERICAN FAMILIES WHO WELCOME A
PUPPY INTO THEIR HOME CAN RELATE
TO.
PRESIDENT OBAMA REVEALING
SOMETHING ABOUT THE NEWEST
ADDITION TO THEIR FAMILY TODAY,
THEIR PUPPY, SUNNY.
>> NOT COMPLETELY POTTY TRAINED.
>> SAYING TO THE FOLKS THERE
HE'S NOT COMPLETELY POTTY
TRAINED.
GIVEN THAT INFORMATION TONIGHT,
THERE IS NO WORD ON WHETHER
SUNNY HAS BEEN ALLOWED INTO THE
OVAL OFFICE TONIGHT.
WE'LL KEEP YOU POSTED.
>>> SOME PASSENGERS ON BOARD A
SOUTHWEST FLIGHT FROM PHOENIX TO
LOS ANGELES GOT QUITE A
SURPRISE.
LOOK WHO SHOWED UP AND SANG A
TUNE.
♪
>> POP STAR GAVIN DeGRAW IN AN
IMPROMPTU SERENADE, PART OF
SOUTHWEST'S NEW PROGRAM,
SURPRISING
PASSENGERS AT 35,000 FEET WITH A
CONCERT, A NEW PROGRAM THEY
STARTED, SOMETHING THEY DO WHEN
THEY HAVE STARS ON BOARD THE
PLANE.
>>> GAVIN DeGRAW ISN'T THE ONLY
ONE SINGING THIS WEEK.
I'M BACK TONIGHT AFTER SITTING
DOWN WITH SUPERSTAR ALICIA KEYS,
AND TOMORROW NIGHT YOU'LL SEE
THE AMAZING PROJECT SHE'S
WORKING ON RIGHT NOW AND YOU'LL
HEAR THE SONG SHE CHOSE TO SING
TO ME.
SHE'S SINGING IT RIGHT HERE.
AND WHY SHE CHOSE THAT SONG.
IF YOU HAVE ANY GUESSES, SEND ME
A LITTLE TWEET, OUR PERSON OF
THE WEEK TOMORROW NIGHT.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, A FATHER
AND SON WE ALL KNOW WELL HERE,
PUT TO THE TEST TONIGHT AND WHAT
THEY DID WRONG THAT SO MANY OF
US DO ON THOSE TRIPS WITH THE
CHILDREN AND GRANDCHILDREN.
WHEN WE COME BACK, HOW TO GET
THAT CASH BACK.
STIFFNESS...
ACCOMPLISHING EVEN LITTLE THINGS
CAN BECOME MAJOR VICTORIES.
I'M PHIL MICKELSON, PRO GOLFER.
WHEN I WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS,
MY RHEUMATOLOGIST
PRESCRIBED ENBREL
FOR MY PAIN AND STIFFNESS,
AND TO HELP STOP JOINT DAMAGE.
[ Male Announcer ]
ENBREL MAY LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS
INCLUDING INFECTIONS,
TUBERCULOSIS,
LYMPHOMA, OTHER CANCERS,
NERVOUS SYSTEM
AND BLOOD DISORDERS,
AND ALLERGIC REACTIONS
HAVE OCCURRED.
BEFORE STARTING ENBREL,
YOUR DOCTOR SHOULD TEST YOU
FOR TUBERCULOSIS
AND DISCUSS WHETHER
YOU'VE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL INFECTIONS
ARE COMMON.
YOU SHOULD NOT START ENBREL
IF YOU HAVE AN INFECTION
LIKE THE FLU.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU'RE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,
HAVE CUTS OR SORES,
HAVE HAD HEPATITIS B,
HAVE BEEN TREATED
FOR HEART FAILURE,
OR IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS PERSISTENT FEVER,
BRUISING, BLEEDING,
OR PALENESS.
SINCE ENBREL HELPED RELIEVE
MY JOINT PAIN,
IT'S THE LITTLE THINGS
THAT MEAN THE MOST.
ASK YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST
IF ENBREL IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
[ Doctor ] ENBREL,
THE NUMBER ONE BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
PRESCRIBED BY RHEUMATOLOGISTS.
ICAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEVING HEARTBURN,GIC MEDICINE
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES
24-HOUR HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL
PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
ALWAYS GO THE EXTRA MILE.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE,
I DID MY RESEARCH.
MY DOCTOR AND I
WENT WITH AXIRON,
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
>> FINALLY TONIGHT IF YOU ARE
HEADING OUT WITH THE CHILDREN,
THE GRANDCHILDREN IN THESE FINAL
WEEKS OF SUMMER, SOME TIPS TO
SAVE REAL MONEY.
NICK WATT WITH REAL MISTAKES
WE'VE ALL MADE BEFORE.
>> Reporter: MY LITTLE BOY MILO
AND I ARE SPENDING THE DAY AT
THE WORLD FAMOUS FISHERMEN'S
WHARF.
>> WHAT ELSE DO YOU WANT TO BUY?
>> Reporter: WE'RE MAKING SOME
CLASSIC TOURIST MISTAKES,
SPENDING TOO MUCH AND NOT SEEING
THE REAL SAN FRANCISCO.
I NEED A KNIGHT IN SHINING
ARMOR, AND HERE HE IS.
>> THE TRAP IS GETTING STUCK AND
NOT KNOWING WHERE TO GO AND
FOLLOWING THE CROWDS THAT DON'T
KNOW WHERE THEY'RE GOING.
>> Reporter: JOHN'S RULE NUMBER
ONE TO AVOID THAT FATE.
>> ASK YOURSELF THAT QUESTION,
WHAT'S TWO STREETS OVER.
>> Reporter: SURE ENOUGH, A
SECRET PASSAGE WAY TO A REAL
FISHERMAN'S WHARF.
LATER WE JUMPED A CABLE CAR TWO
STREETS OVER FROM THE MAIN
TOURIST LINE, NO CROWDS.
THEY EVEN LET MILO RING THE
BELL.
ONTO RULE NUMBER TWO.
>> LEAVE THE TOURIST ATTRACTION
AND FOLLOW THE LOCALS TO LUNCH.
>> Reporter: IS IT REALLY
CHEAPER?
WE BOUGHT TWO BOTTLES OF WATER
AT THE WHARF.
>> HOW MUCH IS THAT?
>> $4.89.
>> Reporter: THEN FOLLOWED THE
LOCALS TO LUNCH.
THE WATER HERE IS ONLY A DOLLAR
A BOTTLE.
>> I THOUGHT I WAS BEING SMART
GOING INLAND TO BUY SOUVENIRS.
>> WE BOUGHT TWO CABLE CARS
TODAY.
THE ONE AT FISHERMAN'S WHARF WAS
$9 AND THIS ONE WAS $2.99, BUT
TO BE FAIR, THE WHEEL DID JUST
FALL OFF OF IT.
>> Reporter: RULE NUMBER THREE,
A SURPRISING ONE, THE TIME WE
WASTED, THE TIME WE SPENT JUST
GETTING THERE, JUST PLAIN NOT
WORTH IT.
SOMETIMES IT'S OKAY TO WALLOW IN
THE TOURIST HOT SPOT JUST FOR
>>> A SAN FRANCISCO STATE OF
EMERGENCY OVER THE RIM NEAR
NEAR YOSEMITE WHAT. 84 SQUARE
MILES OF FLAMES AND SMOKE ARE
SENDING THERE.
>> A TWO WEEK SWEEP OF
HOMELESS SEX OWE GRERNDZ.
>> AND A FIGHT TO SAVE ONE OF
THE STATE'S BIGGEST COMMUNITY
COLLEGE WILL BE WAGED IN THE
COURT.
>> ABC 7 NEWS I TEAM LOOKED
INTO THE DEATH OF A HILY
REGARDED MEMBER OF THE SAN
FRANCISCO POLICE BRASS.
>> IN FIRE IS SO LARGE THAT IS
WHAT WE'RE SEEING NOW.
>> HUGE FLAMES ROARING OUTSIDE
OF YOSEMITE TONIGHT.
FIREFIGHTERS HAVE BEEN UNABLE
TO TAME THEM.
>> THIS IS A TERRIFYING FIRE.
THE GOVERNOR DECLARED A LOCAL
STATE OF EMERGENCY BECAUSE OF
THE RIM FIRE.
SO DID THE CITY WHICH OPERATES
A CAMP AND GETS WATER AND
POWER FROM THE HETCH HETCHY
RESERVOIR THERE.
THE FIRE IS SPROU SHAEDING UP
AND DOWN THE CANYON.
AND TOURED THE COMMUNITY OF
PINE MOUNTAIN LAKE.
HIGHWAY 120 INTO YOSEMITE IS
STILL CLOSED.
>> THE WINDS HAVE PICKED UP
HAD AFTERNOON.
BUT TODAY, THE DAY BEGAN WITH
A RED FLAG WARNING LIFTED
ENABLING FIREFIGHTERS TO
MAKEUP GROUND LOST AFTER THE
FIRE TRIPLED IN ACREAGE.
THIS FIRE EXPLODED OUT OF
CONTROL WHEN JUST THE WIND
BANNED THE FLAMES.
>> THIS IS A VERY COMPLEX
FIRE.
JUST UNIQUE FIRE BEHAVIOR.
>> BUT AT TACK CONTINUES TO
PLAY A KEY ROLE POUNDING THE
FIRE WITH RETARDANT AND WATER
ONE OF THE MAIN WAYS TO FIGHT
THE FIRE BECAUSE MUCH IS NOT
ACCESSIBLE.
FOLKS