FACT THAT HE WENT BACK TO
COLLEGE THE NEXT DAY.
THAT THEY WENT ON WITH LIFE.
AND THAT ALMOST MAKES YOU THINK
THAT THEY WERE PLANNING
SOMETHING ELSE, THIS THEY WERE
JUST GOING TO GO BACK TO THEIR
REGULAR LIFE.
THEY WEREN'T GOING TO RUN.
THEY WEREN'T GOING TO RUN AWAY.
THEY WOULD PERHAPS TRY THIS KIND
OF THING AGAIN.
WE GO BACK HERE TO THE SNIPER IN
2002, AND HOW TERRIFYING THAT
WAS IN WASHINGTON, D.C.
WHEN THAT SNIPER WAS PICKING OFF
PEOPLE AND PART OF THAT TERROR
IS, YOUR LIFE JUST KIND OF WENT
ON EVERY DAY, YOU DIDN'T KNOW
WHAT THESE PEOPLE WERE DOING,
YOU HAD NO IDEA WHO WAS AFTER
YOU AND IT'S -- THAT'S REALLY
THE EVERY THE ANYTHING OF
TERROR.
IF YOU REALLY HAVE NO IDEA AND
NOBODY MADE ANY CLAIMS IN
MONDAY'S BOMBING, SO, THAT
TERROR REALLY, REALLY -- THE
NEIGHBORHOOD THAT YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT, IMAGINE WHAT THAT
NEIGHBORHOOD HAS BEEN THROUGH
TODAY.
IMAGINE WHAT THIS CITY HAS BEEN
THROUGH IN THIS WEEK.
ONE WEEK AGO, THOSE TERRIBLE,
TERRIBLE BOMBINGS.
I WAS TALKING TO A YOUNG WOMAN
EARLIER IN THE WEEK WHO HAD A
FRIEND WHO WAS BADLY INJURED IN
THAT BOMBING AND THIS MORNING,
I'M CALLING HER AND TELLING HER,
WELL, WAIT A MINUTE, THE SUSPECT
WENT TO A HIGH SCHOOL,
APPARENTLY RIGHT NEAR YOU.
SO, ALL OF THESE EVENTS
HAPPENING SO FAST AND SO HEART
BREAKING.
WE CAN ONLY HOPE WE GET
RESOLUTION TONIGHT.
>> ALL RIGHT, MARTHA.
AND FOR ANYONE WHO HAPPENED TO
MISS THE MOMENT THAT WE GOT THAT
PHONE CALL FROM GEORGE, WHO GAVE
US, FIRST WORD, OF HOW THEY
APPEARED TO HAVE FOUND THIS
SUSPECT, I WANT TO REPLAY IT,
BECAUSE HIS FRIEND, DAVE
HANNEBURY, FROM TWO DOORS DOWN,
WAS IN HIS HOUSE BEING
INTERVIEWED ABOUT WHAT HAPPENED.
HE TOLD US ABOUT HOW HIS FRIENDS
BOAT AND HERE WE ARE WITH THIS .
HERE HE IS AGAIN.
GEORGE PIZZUTO.
>> BUT WHAT HAPPENED WAS, AFTER
THEY LIFTED THE BAN, MY
NEIGHBORHOOD, DAVID
NEIGHBOR, HE WENT OUTSIDE TO GET
SOME FRESH AIR AND HE HAD HIS
24-FOOT BOAT ON A TRAILER WITH A
WINTER COVER, A SHRINK WRAP
COVER OVER IT.
HE NOTICED SOMETHING WAS OFF.
SO, HE GOT A LADDER AND PUT IT
UP AGAINST THE SIDE AND HE HAS A
ZIP COVER.
HE LIFTED UP THE ZIP COVER AND
HE -- AND AS HE WENT UP TO THE
LADDER, HE NOTICED BLOOD AND
THEN HE THOUGHT HE SAW WHAT
LOOKED LIKE A BODY LAYING IN THE
BOAT.
SO, HE GOT OUT OF THE BOAT FAST
AND CALLED THE POLICE AND THAT'S
WHEN -- THAT'S WHEN EVERYONE
ASCENDED, DESCENDED, WHATEVER
YOU WANT TO SAY, ON FRANKLIN
STREET AND RUSHED THEM RIGHT
OVER TO -- THEY'RE IN OUR HOUSE
BEING INTERVIEWED.
WHAT'S BEEN GOING ON OVER THERE
IS, THERE WERE A NUMBER OF SHOTS
FIRED AND WHAT APPEARED TO BE
SOME EXPLOSIVE DEVICES, WHETHER
THEY THREW THEM IN THE BOAT OR
THEY WERE THROWN OUT OF THE
BOAT, I DON'T KNOW, BUT THEY
HAVEN'T POSITIVELY IDENTIFIED
THE PERSON, I'M PRETTY SURE
THAT'S WHO IT IS, BUT THEY DON'T
WANT TO GO -- THEY HAVEN'T GONE
IN YET BECAUSE THEY DON'T KNOW
IF HE IS WIRED FOR EXPLOSIVES.
>> YES, THAT'S BEEN A CONCERN
ALL ONG.
THIS IS A STAGGERINGRY
YOU'RE TELLING US.
>> SO, ANYW, WHAT'S GOING ON
T NOW  THEY'RE -- THEY
JUST SHUT THE POWER OFF TO THE
HOUSE, I DON'T KNOW WHY, BUT AIR
ALL STILL HERE.
EVERYONE IS STILL HERE.
>> BUT TO GO BACK OVER IT ONCE
MORE, SIR, SO, YOUR FRIEND, IT'S
DAVE HANNEBURY, SYOU SAY?
>> YEAH, HE'S THE ONE THAT OWNS
THE HOUSE.
AND, LIKE I SAY, HE JUST
HAPPENED TO NOTICE, IT DIDN'T
LOOK RIGHT AND HE LOOKED INSIDE
AND THAT'S WHERE HE SAW THE
BLOOD AND THE BODY AND THAT'S --
THEY BELIEVE THAT THAT'S THE
PERSON NOW.
>> AND AGAIN --
>> I DON'T KNOW, THEY DON'T KNOW
HOW, YOU KNOW, THERE'S NO OTHER
INFORMATION.
RIGHT NOW THEY'RE STILL HERE.
>> HE WENT OUT IN HIS YARD AFTER
HE WAS GIVEN PERMISSION TO EXIT,
SO, THIS WAS VERY RECENTLY THIS
EVENING.
>> YES, WE'VE BEEN IN ALL DAY
AND THEY SAID, YOU KNOW, YOU
CAN -- WE'RE LIFTING THE BAN,
BUT WE SUGGEST YOU DON'T GO TOO
FAR AND HE JUST WENT OUT TO HIS
YARD AND RIGHT IN HIS YARD,
RIGHT OUTSIDE HIS BACK DOOR IS
HIS BOAT AND LIKE I SAID, I TOLD
YOU THE REST OF THE STORY.
>> WHAT CAN YOU TELL ME ABOUT
YOUR FRIEND?
>> THEY'RE JUST WAITING.
>> YES.
TELL ME ABOUT YOUR FRIEND DAVE.
WE'RE ALL IMAGINING WHAT HE IS
LIKE.
>> WELL, RIGHT NOW HE'S -- HE'S
PRETTY MUCH IN SHOCK.
HE'S ONLY TALKING TO WHOEVER HE
HAS.
COMMISSIONER DAVIS HAS BEEN IN
HERE.
A LOT OF THE S.W.A.T. TEAM, THE
BOSTON POLICE, THE WATERTOWN
POLICE, THEY'VE ALL BEEN IN MY
HOUSE HERE INTERVIEWING HIM AND
HE'S JUST TOTALLY DISTRAUGHT.
AND HIS WIFE, WHO IS SUFFERING
SOME MAJOR MEDICAL PROBLEMS, IS,
YOU KNOW, ALL HER --
EVERYTHING -- THEY JUST RUSHED
THEM OUT OF THE HOUSE AND SHE
COULDN'T -- THEY COULDN'T TAKE
ANYTHING WITH THEM.
>> AND AS WE SAID EARLIER, THE
VULNERABILITY OF THAT COUPLE IN
THAT HOUSE, THE BOAT SO CLOSE,
THE SUSPECT SO CLOSE.
AND AGAIN, I'M TOLD IT WAS A
24-FOOT BOAT, BY THE WAY, IN THE
BACK, BUT THERE IT WAS, THE
VULNERABILITY, SO CLOSE TO THEIR
HOUSE, TO CLOSE TO THEIR LIVES
TONIGHT.
I WANT TO BRING IN ROBIN DUMA,
WHO IS ALSO AN EYEW, LIVES
NEI HEARD POLICE TALKING IN
THE BACKYARD, ROBIN?
WHAT DID YOU HEAR?
>> YES, AS MY NEIGHBOR SAID,
WHEN THEY TOLD US WE COULD GO
OUT, QUITE A FEW PEOPLE DID
THAT, BUT WITHIN MINUTES, THE
POLICE REALLY DESCENDED ON THE
NEIGHBORHOOD AND WE HAD QUITE A
FEW OF THEM IN OUR BACKYARD AND
WE HEARD THEM SAYING THAT HE WAS
POKING HOLES THROUGH THE
PLASTIC, THAT SHRINK WRAP, ON
THE BOAT.
AND LOOKED LIKE HE WAS TRYING
TO, YOU KNOW, ASSESS WHAT WAS
GOING ON, SEE WHAT WAS GOING ON
AROUND HIM.
>> SO, LET ME UNDERSTAND.
THE POLICE WERE TRYING TO POKE
HOLES OR THE SUSPECT WAS INSIDE?
>> THE SUSPECT.
HE WAS IN THE BOAT, POKING HOMES
TO TRY TO SEE OUT.
>> THIS IS WHAT YOU HEARD POLICE
SAY?
>> YES.
>> WHICH WOULD INDICATE AND WE
HAD NOT HEARD THIS BEFORE, THAT
HE MIGHT HAVE STILL BEEN ALIVE
WHEN THEY CAME UP.
AND WE KNOW THERE WAS THAT
EXCHANGE OF GUN FIRE.
ANYTHING ELSE YOU SAW OR HEARD
ABOUT THAT MOMENT?
>> NO, REALLY, IT WAS JUST
OVERHEARING THEM.
WE TRIED TO HEAR WHAT THE POLICE
RADIOS ARE SAYING, BUT IT'S A
LITTLE BIT DIFFICULT.
THERE WAS QUITE A BIT OF GUN
FIRE, WHICH ACTUALLY HAPPENED
BEFORE WE OVERHEARD THE POLICE
OFFICERS TALKING.
YOU KNOW, THE -- THERE WAS JUST
A RUSH DOWN THE STREET OF ALL
THE VEHICLES AND JUST NOW THEY
ACTUALLY BROUGHT AN AMBULANCE
DOWN THE STREET AND AN ENORMOUS
BLACK SPECIAL UNIT TRUCK.
BUT INITIALLY, THEY ALL CAME
RUSHING DOWN THE STREET AND THEN
THERE WAS QUITE A BIT OF GUN
FIRE.
THEN THERE WAS REALLY NOTHING.
WE HEARD THE POLICE OFFICERS
SPEAKING AND THEN A LITTLE
WHILE -- WELL, QUITE AWHILE
LATER, THERE WERE SEVERAL
EXPLOSIONS AND THEN SOME MORE
GUN FIRE.
AND NOW, REALLY, FOR THE LAST
LITTLE WHILE, NOT MUCH SEEMS TO
BE GOING ON.
THE HELICOPTERS HAVE LEFT.
BUT THESE LARGER, WELL, ONE
AMBULANCE AND A LARGER BIG BLACK
TRUCK JUST CAME DOWN THE STREET.
>> WELL, AGAIN, SUCH VIVID
DETAIL THAT YOU ARE ALL GIVING
US FROM PHONING IN AND WE THANK
YOU.
BUT LET ME GO THROUGH THAT
AGAIN.
YOU SAID THERE WAS GUN FIRE,
THEN SOMETHING SOUNDED EXPLOSIVE
AND THEN GUN FIRE AGAIN?
>> INITIALLY THERE WAS A LOT OF
GUN FIRE, SO, WE WERE TOLD, GO
OUTSIDE, QUITE A FEW PEOPLE DID.
I WOULD SAY ABOUT FOUR MINUTES
LATER, THE POLICE CAME RUSHING
DOWN THE STREET.
THEN THERE WAS QUITE A BIT OF
GUN FIRE RIGHT WHEN THEY ALL
ARRIVED.
THEN, REALLY NOT MUCH OF
ANYTHING FOR AWHILE.
WE THEN OVERHEARD THE POLICE
OFFICERS IN OUR BACKYARD TALKING
ABOUT THIS POKING HOLES THROUGH
THE PLASTIC.
AND THEN I WOULD SAY A GOOD 45
MINUTES, HOUR LATER, THERE WAS
MORE GUN FIRE AND WHAT SOUNDED
LIKE THREE SMALL EXPLOSIONS, I
MEAN, WE'RE ABOUT FOUR HOUSES
AWAY, THAT'S WHAT IT SOUNDED
LIKE TO ME.
AND NOW THERE'S REALLY -- I
HAVEN'T HEARD ANY EXPLOSIONS OR
GUN FIRE OR ANYTHING LIKE THAT
FOR, I'D SAY ABOUT ANOTHER 45
MINUTES, HOUR AT THIS INT.
>> WELL, AGAIN, IT RAISES THE
QUESTION, IF THERE WAS ANY
EXPLOSIVE AROUND THAT POLICE
WERE TRYING TO DETONATE.
WE OBVIOUSLY WILL HAVE THIS
CLARIFIED AS TIME GOES ON.
THERE WAS FEAR ENOUGH IN YOUR
HOUSE.
WHEN ALL OF THIS STARTS
HAPPENING, HOW AFRAID WERE YOU?
>> IT WAS -- IT ACTUALLY STARTED
LAST NIGHT AT ABOUT 1:45 A.M.,
THERE WERE -- IT'S A VERY QUIET
NEIGHBORHOOD AND THE HELICOPTERS
CAME OVER AND I THOUGHT, OKAY,
FINE, THERE'S A HELICOPTER, BUT
IT WAS OBVIOUSLY SOMETHING MUCH
MORE THAN THAT.
WHEN I WENT TO THE WINDOW, I
COULD SEE OFFICERS MOVING
THROUGH THE NEIGHBORHOOD WITH
FLASHLIGHTS.
IT WAS VERY, VERY UNNERVING.
AND I REALLY DIDN'T FALL ASLEEP
AFTER THAT.
WE'VE ALL ACTUALLY BEEN UP SINCE
THAT TIME AND OVER THE COURSE OF
THE DAY TODAY IT KIND OF WANED.
THERE WERE TIMES WHEN IT FELT
MORE STRESSFUL AND OTHER TIMES
WHEN PEOPLE SEEMED TO BACK OFF A
BIT.
THIS HAS HEIGHTENED THE STRESS
AND, YOU KNOW, BUT IT IS -- IT
IS -- IT'S KIND OF JUST A
WEARING, STRESSFUL EXPERIENCE.
THE NEIGHBORHOOD HAS A LOT OF
BARNS, OLD OUTBUILDINGS,
GARAGES, SHEDS AND SUCH AND I
HAVE TO ADMIT, EVEN WHEN I HEARD
THE POLICE SAYING THEY FELT
CONFIDENT THEY'VE DONE A
THOROUGH SEARCH, I HAD
QUESTIONS, JUST BECAUSE I KNOW
THE NATURE OF THE NEIGHBORHOOD
AND ALL THESE OUT BUILDINGS AND
WONDERED, REALLY, IF THEY HAD
MANAGED TO GO INTO THE NOOKS AND
CRANNIES.
>> I THINK THERE WILL BE A LOT
OF PEOPLE ASKING QUESTIONS JUST
LIKE THAT TOMORROW.
AND ONE OF THOSE INDELIBLE
DETAILS ABOUT THE HUMANITY
INVOLVED IN WHAT HAS BEEN
HAPPENING IS, YOU SAY THE
NEIGHBORS HAD JUST BROUGHT HOME
A FOUR-DAY OLD INFANT?
>> YES, MY NEXT DOOR NEIGHBORS
HAVE A NEWBORN, HE CAME HOME ON
ZSH I KIND OF LOST TRACK OF
TIME, IT WAS EITHER WEDNESDAY OR
THURSDAY.
HE'S JUST NEW TO THE WORLD AND,
SO, YOU KNOW, I HAVE NO DOUBT --
WE'VE BEEN TEXTING BACK AND
FORTH, I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM THEM
FOR THE LAST FEW HOURS, BUT YOU
KNOW, I'M JUST IMAGINING IT'S A
PRETTY STRESSFUL SITUATION TO
HAVE A BABY AND TO HAVE ALL OF
THIS GOING ON, YOU KNOW, JUST
OUTSIDE.
>> AND YOU HAVE HEARD ABOUT THE
HANNEBURYS?
ANY THOUGHTS ABOUT THEM TONIGHT?
>> NO, I MEAN, I MEAN -- WE ALL
KNOW -- I MEAN, I HAVE TO ADMIT,
I DON'T KNOW THAT I KNOW ALL MY
NEIGHBORS LAST NAMES, WE ALL
KNOW EACH OTHER BY FIRST NAME.
IT'S A VERY CLOSE KNIT
NEIGHBORHOOD.
THERE ARE FOLKS WHO HAVE BEEN
HERE, AS THEY HAVE, FOR A VERY
LONG TIME AND I'VE BEEN HERE FOR
ABOUT 11 YEARS, WE ALL KNOW EACH
OTHER VERY WELL.
AND --
>> DAVE IS HIS FIRST NAME.
>> YEAH, YEAH, I KNOW THE FAMILY
AND I KNOW -- I MEAN, MY
14-YEAR-OLD SAID, OH, MY GOSH,
YOU KNOW, IT'S THAT BOAT.
AND, YOU KNOW, AND I HAD EVEN
SAID EARLIER TODAY, NOT ABOUT
THAT BOAT, BUT WE LIVE RIGHT
NEAR THE CHARLES RIVER AND THERE
IS A YACHT CLUB THAT HAS ALL THE
BOATS SHRINK WRAPPED AND I SAID,
THINKING OUT LOUD THIS MORNING,
I SAID, DO YOU THINK THEY'VE
GONE THROUGH ALL THOSE BOATS?
THERE ARE 50 OR 60 OF THEM.
IF I WAS RUNNING AWAY, I'D THINK
TO GO IN THAT DIRECTION AND HIDE
THERE.
SO, IT'S KIND OF, YOU KNOW,
INTERESTING THAT THAT'S WHERE HE
WAS, NOT AT THE YACHT CLUB, BUT
JUST DOWN THE STREET.
>> WELL, AGAIN, WE KNOW THERE IS
THE FOG OF INFORMATION RIGHT NOW
BUT YOU DID THINK THAT YOU
OVERHEARD POLICE IN THE BACKYARD
TALKING ABOUT THE SUSPECT,
PERHAPS, TRYING TO LOOK OUT OF
THIS COVERING THAT WAS ON THAT
BOAT AND WE WILL TRY TO VERIFY
THAT THROUGHOUT THIS EVENING.
I ALSO READ A QUOTE FROM YOU,
YOU SAID, I'VE NEVER FELT SAFER
IN MY LIFE.
EVERY OFFICER IN THE UNIVERSE.
>> AS YOU MIGHT IMAGINE, MY
PARENTS, YOU KNOW, FRIENDS,
EVERYONE IN THE WORLD IS TEXTING
AND CALLING, EVEN PEOPLE I
HAVEN'T HEARD FROM IN YEARS, AND
I DID SAY, KIDDINGLY, YOU KNOW,
HOW COULD YOU NOT FEEL SAFE, OUR
HOUSE IS ABSOLUTELY SURROUNDED
BY EVERY LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICER
IN THE UNIVERSE, SO, I WAS -- IT
WAS A LITTLE TONGUE IN CHEEK.
I THINK I'LL FEEL A LOT BETTER
ONCE WE KNOW, YOU KNOW, THIS IS
OVER.
>> ROBIN, STAY IN TOUCH WITH IT.
CALL BACK IN.
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> AND A NUMBER OF YOU HAVE BEEN
ASKING ONLINE ABOUT SOMETHING
ALL DAY, THE OLDER BROTHER, THE
DECEASED BROTHER, HAD A WIFE OR
AT LEAST A GIRLFRIEND, WE'RE NOT
SURE IF THEY WERE MARRIED, BUT
THEY HAVE A 3-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER,
AS WELL.
AND A NUMBER OF YOU HAVE BEEN
ASKING, WHERE IS SHE?
DO THEY HAVE HER IN CUSTODY
TONIGHT?
BRIAN ROSS, IF YOU CAN HEAR ME
NOW, DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING ABOUT
THAT?
IS THERE ANY CHANCE THAT THE
OLDER BROTHER'S WIFE IS IN
CUSTODY NOW, DO WE KNOW
ANYTHING?
SOUNDS AS IF BRIAN IS DEBRIEFING
SOMEBODY ON SCENE THERE, I'LL GO
TO PIERRE THOMAS WITH THE SAME
QUESTION?
HE IS DOING THE SAME THING.
YOU ARE GETTING AN EYEWITNESS ON
REPORTING AT WORK, THE ABC NEWS
FORCE.
THIS IS WHAT WE DO, SEEKING OUT
EVERY SINGLE PIECE OF
INFORMATION.
SO, WE'RE DOING IT WITH YOU, YOU
ARE PART OF OUR NEWS ROOM, IN A
SENSE HERE ONLINE.
AND WE HAVE SOMEONE ELSE ON THE
TELEPHONE?
IRENE SANTORO.
IRENE, HELLO, IT'S DIANE.
TELL ME WHAT YOU SAW.
>> HELLO, DIANE.
YES, WELL, WE'VE BEEN HERE ON
FRANKLIN STREET, WELL, ALL DAY,
AND WE'VE BEEN HEARING
EVERYTHING ALL NIGHT, AS WELL.
WITH HALL CONTINUERS AND LIGHTS,
ET SET THAT HERE.
BUT PRESENTLY, WE HAVE ABOUT,
OH, MAYBE ABOUT 70 POLICE
VEHICLES LINING OF WASHBURN
STREET.
THAT'S PERPENDICULAR TO FRANKLIN
STREET, WHICH IS RIGHT IN FRONT
OF OUR HOUSE.
AND IT'S SOMETHING THAT, IT'S A
LITTLE IRONIC, BECAUSE AS SOON
AS THE GOVERNOR LIFTED THE BAN
THAT WE COULD LEAVE OUR HOME IS
WHEN ALL OF A SUDDEN, IT SEEMS
HELL BROKE LOOSE.
I GUESS THERE'S A FEW LOUD WORDS
HERE, LOUD VOICES AND THEN I
STARTED TO SEE POLICE RUSH DOWN
WITH GUNS, WITH RIFLES, TOWARD
THE CURVE OF FRANKLIN STREET.
SO, A FEW POLICEMEN AND THEN
CAME BECAME IN DROVES, EVERYBODY
WAS COMING.
THE VEHICLES WERE PARKING ALONG
ANY WHICH WAY ON THE SIDEWALK.
LIKE SOMETHING THAT YOU'D SEE ON
TELEVISION OR A MOVIE.
MY HEART STARTED TO PALPITATE
HERE AND I'M STILL PALPITATING.
AND SHORTLY AFTER THAT, THEN THE
S.W.A.T. TEAM CAME.
THERE ARE ABOUT TEN INDIVIDUALS
THAT CAME ALL IN THEIR DARK
UNIFORMS HERE WITH RIFLES, ET
CETERA.
WALKING, RUNNING DOWN TO THE
CORNER OF FRANKLIN, AS WELL.
>> ALL RIGHT.
IRENE, I'M GOING TO STOP YOU FOR
A MINUTE BECAUSE WE HAVE A
FLASH.
WE HAVE SOME BREAKING NEWS RIGHT
NOW, WANT EVERYBODY TO SIT UP
AND PAY ATTENTION.
WE HAVE PIERRE THOMAS.
PIERRE, WHAT DID YOU LEARN?
>> Reporter: WE HAVE THREE
FEDERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT SOURCES
TELLING US THAT THE SUSPECT IS
IN CUSTODY.
CONDITION UNKNOWN.
CONDITION UNKNOWN, DIANE, BUT
OUR GUIDANCE IS THAT THE SUSPECT
IS IN CUSTODY.
>> IN CUSTODY.
AND AGAIN, IT SEEMED
INCONCEIVABLE AFTER ALL THESE
REPORTS OF THAT GUN FIRE AND THE
WAY HE WAS SURROUNDED, PIERRE?
>> Reporter: AGAIN, WE ARE
UNCLEAR ON WHAT EXACTLY HIS
CONDITION IS, DIANE.
I'M TRYING TO GET SOME CLARITY
ON THAT, BUT THE GUIDANCE WE
HAVE, A SUSPECT IS IN CUSTODY
AND WE SHOULD BE GETTING FURTHER
INFORMATION FROM THE BOSTON AND
LOCAL AUTHORITIES VERY SOON.
>> AND AGAIN, WE HAD HEARD THAT
THE HANNEBURYS, SAW THE BOAT,
SAW BLOOD IN IT, WHICH INDICATED
HE MIGHT HAVE BEEN INJURED,
MAYBE IN SERIOUS CONDITION IN
THAT BOAT, BUT BRIAN ROSS, ARE
YOU HEARING THE SAME THING?
>> Reporter: I AM, DIANE.
I JUST TALKED TO WITH THE STATE
REPRESENTATIVE FROM THIS AREA.
HE CONFIRMED THAT THAT WAS THE
SUSPECT NUMBER TWO IN THE BOAT.
THAT HE, IN FACT, FIRED OFF A
NUMBER OF ROUNDS AT POLICE.
THEY DID NOT RETURN FIRE.
AND THAT THEY SENT IN ROBOTS TO
LOOK AT HIM AND A SPECIAL
MACHINE THAT COULD TIP THE BOAT
AND TIP IT OVER.
SO, HE HAS CONFIRMED TO ABC NEWS
THAT IT IS SUSPECT NUMBER TWO IN
THE BOAT AND THAT HE WAS
BLEEDING AND THEY PLANNED TO
JUST LET HIM BLEED OUT OR WAIT
UNTIL HE WAS IN THEY WHEN THEY
COULDN'T RESPOND BECAUSE THEY
WEREN'T SURE IF HE HAD A SUICIDE
VEST ON.
THAT'S FROM STATE REPRESENTATIVE
JOHN LONG.
>> AGAIN, HE SAYS TO YOU THAT
THE SUSPECT FIRED AT THEM?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
THE SUSPECT FIRED AT THEM.
THEY WERE UNDER INSTRUCTIONS NOT
TO RETURN FIRE.
HE FIRED OFF AT THEM AND THAT
THE EXPLOSIONS THAT WERE HEARD
MIGHT HAVE BEEN STUN GRENADES.
>> AH, WE DID HEAR THAT REPORT
OF SOME EXPLOSION.W, TELL ME AB
BOAT AGAIN AND THE PURPOSE OF
THAT?
>> Reporter: THEY HAVE SEVERAL
ROBOTS THEY SENT DOWN, SOME TO
TAKE A LOOK INSIDE THE BOAT, BUT
THERE WAS ANOTHER MACHINE,
ACCORDING TO REPRESENTATIVE
LONG, THAT COULD ACTUALLY TIP
THE BOAT, TIP HIM OUT OF THE
BOAT.
>> I WANT TO BRING IN DICK
CLARK, BECAUSEHIIS STUNNING
NEWS, DICK.
THEY APPARENTLY WERE STANDING
THERE, HE WAS FIRING ON THEM AND
THEY SOME HOW COULD TIP THE BOAT
TO TRY TO DISABLE AT LEAST HIS
ABILITY TO SUCCEED IN FIRING AT
THEM?
>> WELL, IF THEY HAVE A ROBOT
THAT'S LARGE ENOUGH AND
CERTAINLY, THEY EXIST, AND THEY
HAVE ARMS THAT GO UP TO
MANIPULATE BOMBS, THEY COULD
HAVE USED ARMS TO RIP THE SHRINK
WRAP AND THEN TO PULL ALONG ONE
SIDE OF THE BOAT, HAVE HIM FALL
OUT.
AND THAT MAY BE WHAT HAPPENED.
>> AGAIN, WE HEARD THIS REPORT
FROM AN EYEWITNESS AND IT WAS SO
EARLY AND WE WERE ALL TRYING TO
BE EXTREMELY CAREFUL, THAT THE
POLICE HAD BEEN OVERHEARD SAYING
THAT THEY HAD SEEN HIM SNEAKING
A LOOK OUT FROM UNDER THAT COVER
ON THE BOAT.
THIS SEEMS TO GIVE NEW VALIDITY
TO THAT, BRIAN.
>> Reporter: WELL, INDEED, AND
REPRESENTATIVE LONG SAYS, YOU
KNOW, IT'S OVER.
THERE'S NOT A QUESTION NOW.
WHEN HE CAME TO SPEAK WITH ME,
HE SAID IT'S JUST A QUESTION OF
MAKING SURE THAT HE IS
INCAPACITATED SO THAT IF HE HAS
A SUICIDE VEST, HE COULD NOT
DETONATE IT AND HARM ANY OF THE
OFFICERS.
>> AND, AGAIN --
>> Reporter: HE ALSO TOLD ME,
DIANE, HE MENTIONED THAT THE
GOVERNOR IS ALREADY HERE AT THE
COMMAND CENTER AND WE SHOULD SEE
HIM SHORTLY.
>> ALL RIGHT, PIERRE?
>> Reporter: DIANE, I CAN NOW
TALK ABOUT AN EARLIER
CONVERSATION THAT I COULD NOT
DISCLOSE.
AT ONE POINT, A LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIAL HERE IN WASHINGTON WAS
LISTENING TO THE POLICE SCANNER
TRAFFIC AND THERE WAS A MOMENT
WHEN THE SUSPECT WAS NOT MOVING
AND THEN APPARENTLY SAT UP IN
THE BOAT.
AND THAT WAS, YOU KNOW, A
CRITICAL MOMENT WHEN IT BECAME
CLEAR TO LAW ENFORCEMENT THAT
THE SUSPECT WAS, IN FACT, ALIVE.
AND SO IT'S REMARKABLE, AFTER
ALL OF THIS, THAT IS SUSPECT WAS
ALIVE AT THIS POINT.
AGAIN, WE DO NOT KNOW HIS
CONDITION AT PRESENT.
>> THIS IS BEYOND ANY DRAMA THAT
CAN BE WRITTEN, PIERRE.
AND, AGAIN, WHEN WE HEAR THAT HE
IS IN CUSTODY, WHAT DOES THAT
MEAN?
>> Reporter: THAT MEANS THAT LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS HAVE TAKEN
HIM.
HE IS IN POLICE CUSTODY, DIANE.
>> IT COULD MEAN HOSPITAL, IT
COULD MEAN --
>> Reporter: WELL, WE KNOW THAT
THEY SENT EMERGENCY PERSONNEL,
MEDICAL PERSONNEL TO THE SCENE,
WHICH WOULD BE TYPICAL IN A
SITUATION LIKE THIS, NOT ONLY
FOR THE SUSPECT, BUT ALSO FOR
POTENTIAL INJURIES TO POLICE, AS
WELL.
>> ALL RIGHT, I WANT TO GO BACK
TO BRIAN ROSS, BECAUSE, BRIAN,
ON THE SCENE, DO THEY NOW
BELIEVE, AND I KNOW YOU DO NOT
KNOW HIS CONDITION YET, COULD BE
A SPECTRUM OF THINGS, BUT HAS
ANYBODY SUGGESTED TO YOU THAT
THEY BELIEVE THEY MAY BE ABLE TO
GET SOME INFORMATION FROM HIM
ABOUT HOW MANY INVOLVED, WHAT
ELSE MIGHT HAVE BEEN PLANNED?
>> Reporter: CERTAINLY IF HE'S
TAKEN ALIVE, THEN THAT SETS HIM
UP FOR A TRIAL ON CHARGES, MOST
LIKELY, OF PREMEDITATED MURDER
UNDER FEDERAL LAW, AS I
UNDERSTAND IT, THAT WOULD BE THE
PLAN, TO TRY HIM UNDER FEDERAL
TERRORISM CHARGES, NOT STATE
MURDER CHARGES.
BUT THAT DOES OPEN THE
POSSIBILITY THAT HE WOULD BE
ABLE TO BE QUESTIONED AND REVEAL
WHETHER IT WAS JUST HE AND HIS
BROTHER OR IF THERE WAS A LARGER
ORGANIZATION HE WAS PART OF.
THAT WOULD BE VERY, VERY
IMPORTANT TO STOP HIM, BUT IT'S
ALSO IMPORTANT TO KNOW WHETHER
HE REPRESENTED SOMETHING THAT
WAS DEEPER AND MORE TROUBLING.
>> I WANT TO TELL EVERYBODY
ABOUT A TWEET FROM MAYOR TOM
MENINO OF BOSTON.
HE TWEETED OUT, "WE GOT HIM."
"WE GOT HIM."
AND BRIAN, WHEN YOU SAY THAT
THEY ARE BRINGING HIM IN UNDER
FEDERAL TERRORISM CHARGES, WHAT
IS THE DISTINCTION YOU'RE MAKING
THERE?
>> Reporter: AS I UNDERSTAND IT,
THE PLAN WAS TO CHARGE HIM WITH
FEDERAL TERRORISM CHARGES AS
OPPOSED TO STATE MURDER CHARGES.
NOW, ONE DISTINCTION IS THAT IN
MASSACHUSETTS, THERE IS NO DEATH
PENALTY.
UNDER FEDERAL TERRORISM CHARGES,
THERE COULD BE.
BUT THAT WAS MY UNDERSTANDING
THAT THIS WAS A CASE, BEING
HANDLED BY THE FBI, BY THE
FEDERAL GOTT, AND THE
JURISDICTION WOULD BE WITH THE
U.S. ATTORNEY HERE IN
MASSACHUSETTS.
>> I WANT TO BRING BACK IN EVAN
GOODMAN, WHO HAS BEEN SUCH A
GREAT REPORTER, CITIZEN REPORTER
FOR US TONIGHT.
EVAN, YOU ARE RIGHT THERE, CLOSE
TO THE SCENE AND YOU HEARD A
CHEER GO UP?
>> HI, DIANE, YES.
SO, BASICALLY, A COUPLE OF US
WERE OUTSIDE AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
WE HEARD A PRETTY SIZABLE CHEER
DOWN THE ROAD, SO
CLOSE, AND WE WALKED OUT TO THE
FRONT AND WE INTERCEPTED A
POLICE OFFICER AND, YOU KNOW, WE
ASKED IF HE WAS ALIVE OR NOT AND
THEY SAID, HE'S IN CUSTODY, HE'S
ALIVE AND, YOU KNOW, WE'RE GOING
TO PROSECUTE HIM AND BRING TIME
THE JUSTICE.
>> SO, NO INDICATION THAT HE WAS
IN SUCH GRAVE CONDITION THEY HAD
A DOUBT IF HE'D SURVIVE?
>> WELL, I BELIEVE SO -- I'M
LOOKING OUTSIDE RIGHT NOW AND I
SAW A COUPLE OF AMBULANCES GO
BY, I'M ASSUMING THEY'RE FOR THE
SUSPECT.
I DON'T KNOW WHO ELSE WAS
INJURED, YOU KNOW, IF ANYBODY
ELSE WAS INJURED.
BUT YOU KNOW, I DO BELIEVE HE
WAS BLEEDING OUT PRETTY BADLY.
YOU KNOW, JUDGING FROM HIS
WOUNDS EARLIER ON TODAY AND
PROBABLY FROM THE FIRE FIGHT
THAT WENT ON.
BUT I DO BELIEVE HE IS ALIVE   D
AND, YOU KNOW, WE ARE GOING TO
GET SOME ANSWERS, WHICH IS
PROBABLY THE MOST COMFORTING
FEELING, YOU KNOW, THROUGH ALL
THIS.
>> AND FOR ALL OF THOSE WHO ARE
INJURED AND IN THE HOSPITAL AND,
OF COURSE, FOR THE FAMILIES OF
THOSE WHO DIED AND WHO HAVE BEEN
SO SERIOUSLY INJURED, I KNOW, AT
THIS POINT, ANSWERS ARE
SOMETHING THAT MATTERS, VITALLY
TO THEM.
AND, AGAIN, WE -- YOU ARE RIGHT
THAT HE MUST HAVE BEEN BLEEDING
ENOUGH, THAT DAVE, WHO WENT BACK
TO LOOK AT HIS BOAT, SAW IT
PRETTY QUICKLY.
>> YEAH, ABSOLUTELY, DIANE.
AND LET ME JUST GIVE YOU GUYS A
QUICK, WHAT'S GOING ON IN FRONT
OF ME, BASIC LICK.
Y
RESIDENTS ARE ON THE STREET
RIGHT NOW, I'M LESS THAN A BLOCK
AWAY.
THERE ARE FLIFR POLICE OFFICERS
WALKING UP, PEOPLE ARE
CONGRATULATING THEM, GIVING THEM
PATS ON THE BACK AND, YOU KNOW,
ASKING QUESTIONS, SO, IT'S MORE
OF A LESS TENSE SCENARIO RIGHT
NOW AND PEOPLE ARE OUTSIDE AND
WALKING AROUND, SO, IT SEEMS
LIKE IT'S A LITTLE BIT MORE
LENIENT, YOU KNOW, AS IT WAS
EARLIER IN THE DAY.
>> YES END AND, AGAIN, WE WERE
TOLD EARLIER THAT THE GUN FIRE
SEEMS TO BEEN COMING FROM INSIDE
THE BOAT OUT AT POLICE, THAT
POLICE APPARENTLY HAD MOVED IN,
THEY HAD SOME DEVICE, A ROBOTIC
DEVICE THAT COULD BE TIPPING THE
BOAT.
THEY WERE CONCERNED ABOUT A
SUICIDE VEST AND, DICK CLARK,
HOW WOULD THEY HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
DETERMINE, ULTIMATELY, IF HE HAD
ONE ON OR NOT IF THEY COULDN'T
APPROACH THE BOAT?
>> WELL, I THINK THEY PROBABLY
DID APPROACH THE BOAT WITH THE
ROBOT.
AND THE ROBOT PROBABLY HAD A
CAMERA IN IT AND THEY WERE
PROBABLY ABLE TO TELL THAT WAY
THAT THERE WAS NO -- THERE WAS
NO SUICIDE BELT.
>> I WANT TO PLAY THE SOUND.
APPARENTLY NOW WE HAVE AUDIO OF
THE POLICE SCANNER AND YOU CAN
HEAR, "WE GOT HIM.
LISTEN."
>> SUSPECT'S IN CUSTODY, BUT
NOBODY INSIDE THE PERIMETER.
PUT THAT OUT ON CHANNEL ONE.
>> SUSPECT IN CUSTODY.
AND ONLINE, OK, NOT JUST AMONG
POLICE, NOT JUST AMONG THE
PEOPLE OF BOSTON, BUT ALL ACROSS
THIS COUNTRY, PEOPLE ARE SAYING,
HE'S IN CUSTODY, WE NEED
ANSWERS, AND SOMEONE SAID,
"VICTORY, WE ARE STRONG."
LET'S GO BACK TO LINSEY DAVIS,
ON THE SCENE THERE IN WATERTOWN
TONIGHT.
LINSEY?
>> Reporter: DIANE, IF YOU GUYS
CAN SEE THAT AMBULANCE GOING
DOWN THE STREET, WE BELIEVE THAT
THE SUSPECT WAS INSIDE THAT
AMBULANCE.
YOU CAN HEAR PEOPLE CHEERING.
PEOPLE APPLAUDING.
THESE SAME RESIDENTS, MANY OF
THEM -- YOU CAN SEE PEOPLE
HUGGING RIGHT HERE.
VERY JUBILANT ON THE SCENE.
MANY OF THESE SAME PEOPLE WERE
STANDING ON THE CORNER WHEN THE
POLICE WENT IN AND THEY WERE
CHEERING THEN AND YELLING.
MOMENTS AGO, WE HEARD THEM SAY,
"WE GOT HIM" AND THEY WERE
CHEERING AGAIN.
ONE LITTLE BOY SAID TO HIS DAD,
"IT IS OVER?"
AND HE SAID, "YEAH, SON, IT'S
OVER."
AND THEY HUGGED.
PEOPLE ARE VERY EXCITED.
CERTAINLY, AS YOU CAN IMAGINE,
VERY RELIEVED.
>> AND MORE FROM THE MAYOR OF
BOSTON.
"I HAVE NEVER LOVED THIS CITY
AND ITS PEOPLE MORE THAN I DO
TODAY.
NOTHING CAN DEFEAT THE HEART OF
THIS CITY, NOTHING."
AND HIS EARLIER TWEET, "WE GOT
HIM."
CANNOT HELP BUT ECHO IN THE MIND
OF EVERYBODY WHEN SOMEONE SAID
THAT ABOUT SADDAM HUSSEIN AND
OBAMA, AS WEL0
BAM OSAMA, AS WELL.
POLICE SAY THEY HAVE HIM IN
CUSTODY.
I WANT TO SEE IF YOU HAVE
ANYTHING FROM THE SOURCES THAT
HAVE BEEN CALLING YOU ALL NIGHT.
>> Reporter: DIANE, WE CAN
CONFIRM THAT THE SUSPECT IS
ALIVE.
HE'S IN THAT AMBULANCE.
ONE OF OUR OFFICIALS GOT A TEXT
FROM THE SCENE SAYING SUSPECT IS
ALIVE IN THE AMBULANCE.
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S GO TO JON
KARL AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
JON, WHAT ARE YOU HEARING THERE
AND WHAT ARE THEY SAYING ABOUT
WHAT HAPPENS NEXT, IMMEDIATELY
IN THE NEXT HOURS?
>> Reporter: WELL, DIANE,
DEPENDING ON THE CONDITION OF
THE SUSPECT, THE NEXT THING YOU
CAN EXPECT TO HAPPEN WILL BE THE
ACTIVATION OF THE PRESIDENT'S
HIGH VALUE INTERROGATION GROUP.
THIS IS A GROUP MADE UP OF THE
CIA, THE DIA AND THE FBI.
THIS WAS SET UP BY PRESIDENT
OBAMA IN 2009 AFTER THEY DID
AWAY WITH THE CIA'S
INTERROGATION PROGRAM AND IT IS
DESIGNED FOR EXACTLY THIS
SITUATION.
TO GO IN AND TO INTERROGATE
SUSPECTED TERRORISTS IMMEDIATELY
AFTER THEIR APPREHENSION.
I HAVE BEEN TOLD PRIOR TO THIS
THAT THIS GROUP WAS ON STAND-BY
AND READY TO GO.
THAT'S THE NEXT THING WE'RE
LOOKING FOR.
TRYING TO GET INTELLIGENCE AND
INFORMATION OUT OF THIS
INDIVIDUAL BECAUSE THE BIG
QUESTION HERE, DIANE, THAT THE
ENTIRE INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY
HAS BEEN FOCUSED ON IS WHETHER
OR NOT THESE BROTHERS WERE
ACTING ALONE OR WHETHER OR NOT
THEY WERE PART OF A LARGER GROUP
AND THERE COULD BE OTHER
PLOTTERS OUT THERE.
>> AGAIN, MARTHA RADDATZ, WE
KNOW HIS OLDER BROTHER HAD GONE
BACK TO RUSSIA.
WE HAVE A KIND OF DARK AGE IN
THERE FOR A FEW MOMENTS WHEN HE
WAS BACK IN RUSSIA.
WE HAVE NO IDEA WHERE HE WENT.
>> Reporter: WE HAVE NO IDEA.
HE WAS THERE SIX MONTHS.
SO, THAT'S A PERIOD THEY'RE
REALLY GOING TO LOOK AT AND IF
THEY CAN INTERROGATE THIS
SUSPECT, THEY WILL DO THAT, THE
YOUNGER BROTHER.
THEY WILL ASK HIM WHATEVER THEY