>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, YOSEMITE BURNING.
AND THE NEW THREAT THIS EVENING.
THE FIERCE WINDS NOW FUELING THE
FIRE.
AS CREWS FIGHT TO PROTECT THE
ANCIENT SEQUOIAS.
THE HOMES ON THE PARK'S EDGE.
AND THE RESERVOIR WHERE SAN
FRANCISCO GETS ITS WATER.
THE STATE OF EMERGENCY IN EFFECT
TONIGHT.
>>> TOO LITTLE TOO LATE.
THE MESSAGE FROM THE U.S. TO
SYRIA THIS EVENING.
WILL THE WHITE HOUSE TAKE
ACTION, AFTER NEW AND GRUESOME
IMAGES?
ABC'S MARTHA RADDATZ, STANDING
BY.
>>> TAKING ON TRUMP.
THE STATE ATTORNEY GENERAL IS
SUING DONALD TRUMP TONIGHT,
AFTER SPENDING OVER 35 GRAND TO
ATTEND TRUMP UNIVERSITY.
WHAT DID THEY GET IN RETURN?
>>> AND THE LITTLE BOY AND HIS
BRAVERY.
CALLING 911.
>> SOMEONE'S TRYING TO BREAK
INTO MY HOUSE.
>> WHAT HE DOES, AND THAT
CALMING VOICE AT THE OTHER END.
>> YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING REAL GOOD.
DOING PERFECT.
YOUR MOM'S GOING TO BE SO PROUD
OF YOU.
>>> GOOD EVENING AND THANKS FOR
BEING HERE ON A SUNDAY NIGHT.
AND WE DO BEGIN WITH THE NEW
THREAT THIS EVENING.
THE FIERCE WINDS NOW FUELING THE
FIRE, BURNING IN YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK.
WINDS EXPECTED THROUGH THE
EVENING AND TONIGHT, NOT ONLY
ARE FIRE CREWS TRYING TO KEEP
THE FLAMES FROM REACHING
THOUSANDS OF HOMES, THEY ARE
BATTING TO PROTECT THOSE FAMOUS
GIANT SEQUOIAS, THE ANCIENT
TREASURES OF THE PARK.
THE FIRE HAS NOT REACHED THEM
YET, BUT SO MANY OTHER TREES THE
FIRE HAS REACHED.
133,000 ACRES, A HUGE PART OF
THE PARK, ALREADY CHARRED.
JUST LISTEN TO IT TONIGHT.
THE SOUND OF THE BONE DRY TIMBER
GOING UP IN FLAMES.
AND OUR TEAM, VISITING THAT
CRUCIAL RESERVOIR IN THE PARK,
WHERE SAN FRANCISCO GETS ITS
WATER SUPPLY.
CONTRIBUTING TO THAT STATE OF
EMERGENCY NOW IN CALIFORNIA.
AND TONIGHT, AS 47 FIRES BURN IN
NINE WESTERN STATES, THE BIGGEST
FIGHT IS RIGHT THERE AT YOSEMITE
AND THAT'S WHERE WE BEGIN WITH
ABC'S NEAL KARLINSKY AGAIN
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE FIGHT
INSIDE YOSEMITE IS HOT AND
INTENSE.
CREWS AREN'T JUST TRYING TO STOP
THE FIRE -- THEY'RE TRYING TO
PROTECT A GROVE OF THE PARK'S
FAMED SEQUOIAS -- THREE DOZEN IN
ALL.
THE HUGE TREES ARE AMONG THE
OLDEST LIVING THINGS ON EARTH,
AND TEAMS HAVE BEEN ASSIGNED
JUST TO THEM.
>> I'M FROM VIRGINIA, SO THE
FUEL TYPES HERE ARE DIFFERENT.
AND THIS IS DEFINITELY DRY, SO,
THIS IS SOME PRETTY EXTREME FIRE
BEHAVIOR THAT WE'RE ENCOUNTERING
HERE.
>> Reporter: MORE TEAMS ARE
INSIDE THE PARK TO PROTECT THE
AREA AROUND THE MASSIVE
HETCH HETCHY RESERVOIR.
WE SAW FIRST HAND, THE FIRE IS
CLOSE TO THE AREA THAT SUPPLIES
85% OF SAN FRANCISCO'S WATER.
CAUSE ENOUGH FOR THE GOVERNOR TO
DECLARE A STATE OF EMERGENCY AND
PUT PUBLIC UTILITY CREWS ON
ALERT TO MONITOR THE WATER'S
QUALITY.
>> IT'S STILL ACTIVELY BURNING
AS WE SPEAK.
IT HAS AFFECTED OUR WATER AND
POWER SYSTEM.
>> Reporter: ON THE ROAD OUTSIDE
THE PARK, CREWS ARE CUTTING DOWN
BURNED TREES THEY CALL "WIDOW
MAKERS," BECAUSE THEY FALL
WITHOUT WARNING.
FURTHER TO THE NORTH, THE NOW
FAMILIAR SIGHT -- MORE FAMILIES
DISPLACED, EVACUATING AS THE
FIRE BURNS THEIR WAY.
>> 15 MINUTES TO BE OUT OF OUR
HOUSE.
SO WE ONLY GOT OUR KIDS, OUR
ANIMALS AND A LITTLE BIT OF
PICTURES.
IT WAS HARD.
>> Reporter: ELSEWHERE, AIR
CHOKED WITH THICK SMOKE AND ASH
IS THE PROBLEM.
YOU CAN FEEL IT.
>> YEAH, IT'S PRETTY BAD.
IT'S PRETTY BAD.
I'M ALL CONGESTED.
YOU GET THE SINUS INFECTION AND
ALL THAT STUFF.
>> Reporter: THIS IS WHAT
FIREFIGHTERS ARE WORKING SO HARD
TO PROTECT.
THESE PICTURES WERE TAKEN INSIDE
YOSEMITE ON SATURDAY BY TOURISTS
HERE FROM THE UK, AMAZED THAT
THE FIRE IS NOWHERE TO BE SEEN
INSIDE -- FOR NOW.
WE'RE HERED A THE SIDE OF
YOSEMITE THAT HAS BEEN CLOSED
OFF AND IS NOW BEING PROTECTED
BY FIREFIGHTERS.
THIS FIRE REMAINS VERY INTENSE,
ONLY ABOUT 7% CONTAINED.
IT'S BURNING HOT, THEY'RE HAVING
A VERY HARD TIME GETTING AHOLD
OF THIS ONE, DAVID.
>> ALL RIGHT, NEAL KARLINSKY
LEADING US OFF.
NEAL, OUR THANKS TO YOU.
I WANT TO BRING IN ABC
METEOROLOGIST GINGER ZEE.
AND AS WE'VE BEEN SAYING HERE,
THE MAJOR THREAT TONIGHT, THE
WINDS.
>> RIGHT.
AND THAT IS GOING TO SUBSIDE
ONLY A LITTLE AS WE GET INTO THE
START OF THE WORK WEEK.
I HAVE TO SHOW YOU, DAVID,
THE REAL PROBLEM IS GOING TO BE
THE HEAT AND, OF COURSE, THE DRY
CONDITIONS.
IT'S GOING TO BE EVEN HOTTER AND
DRIER AS WE START THIS WEEK IN
THAT PART OF CALIFORNIA.
>> ALSO, THE FLOODING AND THE
HEAT YOU'RE WATCHING AS WE TURN
TO ANOTHER WEEK.
>> RIGHT.
HUGE HEADLINES COMING OUT.
AND WE'VE GOT FLASH FLOODING
THAT'S HAPPENING RIGHT NOW IN
THE SOUTHWEST.
YOU CAN SEE, SOME PICTURES,
FRESH IN FROM NEAR NEEDLES,
CALIFORNIA, WHERE U.S. 95 MEETS
HIGHWAY 40, I-40, IT HAD TO SHUT
DOWN IN BOTH WAYS BECAUSE OF ALL
THAT RAIN.
GREATER THAN A HALF INCH IN JUST
15 MINUTES.
I HAVE TO SHOW YOU, IT'S NOT
OVER.
AND THIS IS A TWO-DAY EVENT
HERE.
REALLY MOSTLY TONIGHT INTO EARLY
TOMORROW, YOU COULD GET TWO-PLUS
INCHES VERY QUICKLY.
AND QUICKLY DAVID, I HAVE TO
TELL YOU, HEAT IN THE MIDWEST,
IT IS RECORD-BREAKING.
MINNEAPOLIS TODAY HIT 96.
THEY WILL STAY IN THE 90s.
LEGITIMATE HEAT WAVE FOR
CHICAGO, ST. LOUIS AND KANSAS
CITY.
>> ALL RIGHT, TRACKING IT ALL.
GINGER ZEE TONIGHT.
GINGER, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE CRISIS IN SYRIA
THIS EVENING, AND TO A MESSAGE
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE, INTENDED
FOR THE PRESIDENT OF SYRIA.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYING THERE IS
VERY LITTLE DOUBT THAT IT WAS
THE SYRIAN REGIME THAT USED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS AGAINST ITS OWN
PEOPLE IN RECENT DAYS.
AND TONIGHT, MORE OF THOSE NEW
IMAGES OF THE AFTERMATH.
BELIEVED TO BE THE SINGLE
DEADLIEST ATTACK SO FAR THERE IN
SYRIA.
SYRIA SAYS IT WILL ALLOW
INSPECTORS.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYING THAT TIME
HAS PASSED.
AND SO TONIGHT HERE, WE ASK,
WILL AMERICA ACT?
WHAT ARE THE OPTIONS?
AND IF SO, HOW SOON?
ABC'S CHIEF GLOBAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT, MARTHA RADDATZ,
REPORTING IN FROM THE REGION
AGAIN TONIGHT.
MARTHA?
>> Reporter: DAVID, IT APPEARS
TONIGHT THAT THE U.S. IS CLOSER
TO TAKING MILITARY ACTION IN
SYRIA THAN EVER BEFORE, WITH
STRONG WORDS FROM U.S. OFFICIALS
TODAY AND WARSHIPS AT THE READY.
NAVY DESTROYERS AND SUBMARINES
NOW IN THE MEDITERRANEAN SEA
COULD LAUNCH CRUISE MISSILES
INTO SYRIA WHENEVER ORDERED,
TARGETING SYRIAN REGIME COMMAND
AND CONTROL HEADQUARTERS,
AIRFIELDS OR AIRCRAFT THAT MIGHT
BE USED TO CARRY CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
ANOTHER OPTION -- U.S. FIGHTER
JETS LAUNCHING WEAPONS FROM
OUTSIDE SYRIAN AIR SPACE.
>> THE SYRIANS HAVE CREATED THIS
SANCTUARY, WHERE THERE ARE
SURFACE TO AIR MISSILES.
>> Reporter: IMAGES OF THE
SUSPECTED CHEMICAL ATTACK HAVE
OUTRAGED THE WORLD.
MEN, WOMEN AND CHILDREN KILLED
IN THE MOST HORRIFIC WAY.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAYS HE WILL NOT
INTERVENE UNTIL THE ATTACK IS
VERIFIED, BUT ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS ARE TONIGHT SAYING
THERE IS A STRONG SUSPICION THAT
THE ASSAD REGIME LAUNCHED THE
ATTACK, ADDING THAT THE REBELS
DO NOT EVEN HAVE THE KIND OF
ROCKETS IN WHICH THE CHEMICALS
WERE BELIEVED TO BE DELIVERED.
TODAY, SYRIA SAID IT WOULD ALLOW
U.N. INSPECTORS TO VISIT THE
SITE, BUT AMERICAN OFFICIALS SAY
IT'S TOO LITTLE, TOO LATE, AND
THE EVIDENCE THEY WOULD PRESENT
IS LIKELY CORRUPTED.
SO, HOW SOON COULD THIS HAPPEN?
U.S. OFFICIALS TELL ABC NEWS, A
RESPONSE MUST BE TIMELY, DONE
SOON ENOUGH TO PREVENT ANOTHER
CHEMICAL ATTACK.
"WE ARE NOT TALKING ABOUT
MONTHS."
>> I THINK THE BEST THAT WE
COULD HOPE FOR IS TO DETER MR.
ASSAD FROM USING CHEMICALS
AGAINST HIS PEOPLE AGAIN.
AND WORST CASE, DRAG US INTO A
LARGER MIDDLE EAST CONFLICT.
>> Reporter: DAVID, THE
ADMINISTRATION HAS ALSO MADE
VERY CLEAR THEY DO NOT WANT TO
TAKE ANY KIND OF ACTION ALONE.
SO, THERE HAVE BEEN URGENT
MEETINGS WITH ALLIES HERE IN THE
REGION AND ELSEWHERE.
DAVID?
>> MARTHA RADDATZ WITH US AGAIN
TONIGHT.
MARTHA, OUR THANKS TO YOU.
>>> AND NOW TO EGYPT THIS
EVENING, WHERE IT'S BEEN HARD TO
KEEP TRACK OF WHICH LEADERS ARE
JAILED, WHICH ONES HAVE BEEN SET
FREE.
TONIGHT, THE FIRST GLIMPSE OF
FORMER EGYPTIAN PRESIDENT HOSNI
MUBARAK SINCE HE WAS RELEASED
LAST WEEK.
MUBARAK ARRIVING BY HELICOPTER
FOR A COURT APPEARANCE THIS
SUNDAY.
THIS IS NOW HIS RETRIAL FOR THE
KILLING OF PROTESTERS DURING THE
ARAB SPRING.
INSIDE, HE SAT IN A WHEELCHAIR
IN THE DEFENDANT'S CAGE, WEARING
DARK SUNGLASSES THERE.
LAST WEEK, WE SHOWED YOU MUBARAK
BEING FREED AFTER THE CURRENT
PRESIDENT, MOHAMED MORSI, WAS
JAILED INSTEAD.
>>> TO ANOTHER CASE OVERSEAS
INVOLVING AMERICAN COLLEGE
STUDENT AMANDA KNOX, WHO NOW
SAYS SHE WILL NOT BE ATTENDING
THE SECOND TRIAL IN HER CASE IN
ITALY.
HER LAWYERS HAVE CONFIRMED THAT
SHE WILL NOT GOT BACK FOR THE
PROCEEDINGS.
KNOX IS BEING TRIED AGAIN FOR
THE MURDER OF HER ROOMMATE BACK
IN 2007.
SHE SPENT FOUR YEARS IN PRISON
FOR THAT CRIME BEFORE HE
CONVICTION WAS OVERTURNED.
HER LAWYERS WILL REPRESENT HER
AT THE RETRIAL, WHICH BEGINS
NEXT MONTH.
>>> AND TO AUSTRALIA TONIGHT,
WHERE THERE IS A SEARCH UNDER
WAY THIS EVENING FOR A VICTIM
AFTER A VERY RARE ATTACK THERE.
A YOUNG MAN VANISHING AFTER
BEING ATTACKED BY A CROCODILE IN
AN AREA WHERE THE ONCE
ENDANGERED CROCODILE POPULATION
IS NOW FLOURISHING.
AND IT ALL PLAYED OUT AS
ONLOOKERS WATCHED HORRIFIED BY
WHAT THEY SAW.
HERE'S ABC'S JEFFREY KOFMAN.
>> Reporter: LOOK.
TAKE PICTURES.
BUT STAY OUT OF THE WATER.
THAT IS THE VERY CLEAR ADVICE
FOR TOURISTS IN THIS
CROCODILE-INFESTED CORNER OF
AUSTRALIA.
24-YEAR-OLD SHAWN COLE WAS AT A
WIRTH DATE PARTY IN A REMOTE
JUNGLE LODGE WHEN HE AND A PAL
DECIDED TO IGNORE THE COUNCIL
AND SWIM IN THIS NOTORIOUS
RIVER.
AS HIS HORRIFIED FRIENDS LOOKED
ON, IT WAS OVER IN AN INSTANT.
A 16-FOOT CROCK SNAPPED HIS JAWS
AND THE YOUNG PARTY-GOER
DISAPPEARED.
>> ONE OF THE GUARDS THAT WORK
HERE SAID, LOOK, I THINK
SOMEONE'S BEEN TAKEN BY A CROCK.
I WENT, ARE YOU JOKING?
>> Reporter: THERE ARE THOUSANDS
AND THOUSANDS IN THIS RIVER.
POLICE AND WILDLIFE OFFICERS
RUSHED TO THE SCENE, SEARCHING
THROUGH THE NIGHT FOR SOME SIGN
OF THE VICTIM.
BY DAYBREAK, THEY KILLED THREE
GIANT CROCKS, BUT FOUND NOTHING.
JEFFREY KOFMAN, ABC NEWS,
LONDON.
>> JEFFREY, THANK YOU.
>>> AND BACK HERE AT HOME
TONIGHT, AND TO A BREAK IN THE
CASE IN TEXAS, AFTER A
REMARKABLE 911 CALL.
A BRAVE BOY AS HIS HOME WAS
BEING ROBBED, CALLING FOR HELP.
AND THE CALMING VOICE AT THE
OTHER END OF THE LINE.
HERE TONIGHT, ABC'S GIO BENITEZ.
>> Reporter: LISTEN CLOSELY AS
12-YEAR-OLD DEION MURDOCH DIALS
911, ALONE IN HIS TEXAS HOME.
>> 911.
WHERE IS THE EMERGENCY?
HELLO?
>> SOMEONE IS TRYING TO BREAK
INTO MY HOUSE.
THEY JUST BROKE THE WINDOW,
MA'AM.
>> THEY JUST BROKE THE WINDOW?
WHAT ROOM ARE YOU IN?
>> I'M IN MY MOTHER'S ROOM RIGHT
NOW.
PLEASE HURRY.
>> IS YOUR HOUSE -- I AM.
STAY ON THE PHONE WITH ME.
>> Reporter: THE DISPATCHER
TELLS LITTLE DEION TO GO INTO
THE CLOSET, DOING HER BEST TO
REASSURE HIM ALONG THE WAY.
AS POLICE SAY THESE TWO YOUNG
MEN BREAK INTO THE HOUSE.
>> I'M GOING TO HAVE TO WHISPER
NOW BECAUSE I THINK THEY'RE
COMING IN.
PLEASE HURRY.
>> THEY ARE, THEY ARE.
>> THEY'RE IN THERE.
>> THEY'RE INSIDE THE ROOM NOW.
>> Reporter: THEN, CHILLING
SILENCE FOR A FULL MINUTE.
>> YOU THERE?
DEION?
OKAY, JUST STAY THERE.
THE OFFICERS, I THINK THEY'RE
GOING TO CATCH THE GUY, OKAY?
>> Reporter: WHEN POLICE
ARRIVED, THEY SAID THEY SAW THE
TWO MEN RUNNING FROM THE HOME.
THE DISPATCHER KEEPING THE CHILD
ON THE LINE, WITH A LOVING TONE.
>> SO, IS THE POLICE OFFICER
OUTSIDE THE HOUSE?
>> YEAH.
BUT STAY INSIDE THE CLOSET.
BECAUSE THEY'RE TRYING TO FIND
THE BAD GUYS, OKAY?
YOU'RE DOING GOOD.
YOU'RE DOING REAL GOOD.
DOING PERFECT.
YOUR MOM'S GOING TO BE SO PROUD
OF YOU.
>> THIS IS ACTUALLY THE ONLY
THING I COULD THINK OF.
>> WELL, YOU THOUGHT WELL.
YOU THOUGHT WELL.
YOU'RE A VERY, VERY SMART YOUNG
MAN.
YOU DID A GOOD THING.
>> Reporter: AMAZING.
AND DURING THE BREAK-IN, DEION'S
MOM SAYS SHE WAS AT THE HOUSING
AUTHORITY, LOOKING FOR A NEW
HOME.
BECAUSE OF THE BOY'S QUICK
THINKING AND THAT CALM
DISPATCHER, DAVID, THE SUSPECTS
ARE NOW BEHIND BARS.
>> LOVE HOW SHE SAID THE MOM
WOULD BE PROUD.
SO MANY PROUD OF THE DISPATCHER,
TOO.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
>> THANK,S, GIO.
>>> TO WASHINGTON TONIGHT, THE
HISTORIC CIVIL RIGHTS MARCH, 50
YEARS AGO, IS BEING REMEMBERED.
A QUARTER OF A MILLION PEOPLE
FLOODING THE CITY IN 1963,
MARCHING FOR THEIR RIGHTS.
THIS WEEKEND, TENS OF THOUSANDS
RETURNING TO REMEMBER MARTIN
LUTHER KING DELIVERING HIS "I
HAVE A DREAM" SPEECH.
TONIGHT HERE, WE HEAR FROM
ANOTHER MAN WHO SPOKE THAT DAY,
THAT KNEW KING AND WHO KNEW
PRESIDENT JFK, A PRESIDENT
WORRIED ABOUT WHAT WOULD PLAY
OUT THAT DAY.
ABC'S BYRON PITTS IS IN
WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: THE YEAR, 1963.
WHEN A 34-YEAR-OLD NEGRO
PREACHER HAD THE AUDACITY TO
DREAM ALOUD.
>> WE ARE DETERMINED TO BE FREE
IN '63.
>> Reporter: DETERMINED,
PERHAPS, BUT NOT FULLY
OPTIMISTIC.
ORGANIZERS HOPED FOR 100,000.
A QUARTER MILLION SHOWED UP.
>> DR. MARTIN LUTHER KING.
>> Reporter: AND ON AUGUST 28th,
1963, NOT A SOUL HAD A CLUE HOW
IT MIGHT TURN OUT.
EDITH LEE PAINE WAS 12.
SHE TRAVELED BY BUS NINE HOURS
WITH HER MOTHER TO BE THERE ON
THE MALL.
WHAT DID YOU THINK OF DR. KING?
>> I HELD ONTO EVERY WORD THAT
HE SAID, JUST LIKE EVERYONE ELSE
THAT WAS HERE.
>> Reporter: PEOPLE WATCHED LIVE
ON TELEVISION FROM AROUND THE
WORLD.
BOTH DRAWN BY WHAT MIGHT HAPPEN
AT THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL.
AND STILL REELING FROM WHAT DID
ON THE STREETS OF BIRMINGHAM
WEEKS EARLIER.
CONGRESSMAN JOHN LEWIS, BACK
THEN, THE NEWLY APPOINTED
CHAIRMAN OF THE STUDENT
NONVIOLENT COORDINATING
COMMITTEE, WAS ALREADY THERE.
>> WHEN WE MET WITH PRESIDENT
KENNEDY, HE WAS SO AFRAID OF
VIOLENCE.
>> HOW LONG CAN WE BE PATIENT?
>> Reporter: LIKE KING, LEWIS
WAS ONE OF THE MARCH ORGANIZERS
AND SPEAKERS.
>> WE WANT TO BE FREE NOW.
>> Reporter: AT WHAT POINT, DID
YOU RECOGNIZE IT AS AN HISTORIC
MOMENT?
>> I STEPPED TO THE PODIUM.
I SAW HUNDREDS AND HUNDREDS OF
YOUNG PEOPLE.
I SAID TO MYSELF, THIS IS IT.
>> Reporter: AND YOU WERE STILL
A KID.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE BEEN SITTING ON
A LUNCH COUNTER STOOL AND
SOMEONE WALK UP AND SPIT ON YOU,
POUR HOT WATER, HOT COFFEE ON
YOU, YOU SAY YOU'RE COMMITTED TO
NONVIOLENCE, YOU HAVE TO GROW
UP.
>> Reporter: OLD SOUL, AS THEY
SAY.
>> I WAS AN OLD SOUL.
>> Reporter: OLD SOULS PUSHING
FOR A NEW AMERICA.
>> I HAVE A DREAM.
>> Reporter: IT WAS NOT LEFT TO
ONE MAN, THE FINAL SPEAKER OF
THE DAY.
>> MY FOUR LITTLE CHILDREN WILL
ONE DAY LIVE IN A NATION WHERE
THEY WILL NOT BE JUDGED BY THE
COLOR OF THEIR SKIN BUT BY THE
CONTENT OF THEIR CHARACTER.
I HAVE A DREAM TODAY.
>> Reporter: AND IT'S A DREAM
THAT STILL LIVES ON, 50 YEARS
LATER.
YOU STILL COME HERE OFTEN?
>> OH, YES.
TO REFLECT.
TO REMEMBER.
>> Reporter: REMEMBERING HIS OLD
FRIEND AND THE DAY THAT BOTH
MADE HISTORY AND CHANGED IT.
>> OUR THANKS TO BYRON TONIGHT.
AND ABC NEWS WILL CARRY
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S SPEECH,
MARKING THE ANNIVERSARY, LIVE
FROM THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL,
WEDNESDAY AFTERNOON HERE.
>>> AND A PASSING TO NOTE
TONIGHT, A STAR OF STAGE, SCREEN
AND TV HAS DIED.
JULIE HARRIS PLAYED A
12-YEAR-OLD IN "THE MEMBER OF
THE WEDDING" AND WON FIVE TONY
AWARDS FOR HER ACTING ON
BROADWAY.
IN HOLLYWOOD, SHE STARRED AS THE
ROMANTIC LEAD AGAINST HEARTTHROB
JAMES DEAN IN "EAST OF EDEN" AND
PLAYED THE FREE SPIRIT ED LILIME
CLEMENTS ON THE PRIMETIME SOAP
"KNOTS LANDING."
JULIE HARRIS WAS 87 YEARS OLD.
>>> AND AN IMAGE TO PASS ALONG
TONIGHT OF AMERICA'S NEWEST
TREASURE.
IN FACT, AFTER A CAREFUL
EXAMINATION THIS SUNDAY, THE
BABY GIANT PANDA BORN AT
WASHINGTON'S NATIONAL ZOO
FRIDAY.
AND TODAY, THE ALL IMPORTANT
CHECKUP.
ZOO KEEPERS SAY THEY FOUND THE
CUB TO BE HEALTHY AND VIBRANT,
BUT THEY WON'T KNOW IF IT'S A
BOY OR A GIRL FOR ANOTHER TWO OR
THREE WEEKS.
SO STAY TUNED.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS" THIS
SUNDAY NIGHT.
WOULD YOU SPEND UP TO $35,000 TO
ATTEND TRUMP UNIVERSITY?
SOME STUDENTS DID.
AND TONIGHT, THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL NOW TAKING ON TRUMP.
>>> AND LATER HERE TONIGHT, THE
HUSBAND REMEMBERING HIS WIFE.
WRITING A SONG ABOUT HIS LOVE OF
75 YEARS, IT WON A CONTEST.
THEY PUT IT TO MUSIC.
AND YOU'LL SEE HIM AS HE HEARS
IT FOR THE FIRST TIME.
♪ OH SWEET LORRAINE
♪ I WISH WE COULD DO ALL
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS IS THE AGE OF KNOWING
WHAT YOU'RE MADE OF.
WHY LET ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION
GET IN YOUR WAY?
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT VIAGRA.
ASK IF YOUR HEART
IS HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE VIAGRA IF YOU TAKE
NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN;
IT MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE DROP
IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
HEADACHE, FLUSHING,
UPSET STOMACH,
AND ABNORMAL VISION.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION
LASTING MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
STOP TAKING VIAGRA AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY,
IF YOU EXPERIENCE
A SUDDEN DECREASE OR LOSS
IN VISION OR HEARING.
THIS IS THE AGE
OF TAKING ACTION.
VIAGRA.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR.
I TOOK MY SON FISHING
EVERY YEAR.
WE HAD A GREAT SPOT,
NOT EASY TO FIND, BUT WORTH IT.
BUT WITH COPD
MAKING IT HARD TO BREATHE,
I THOUGHT
THOSE DAYS MIGHT BE OVER.
SO MY DOCTOR
PRESCRIBED SYMBICORT.
IT HELPS SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE
MY LUNG FUNCTION
STARTING WITHIN FIVE MINUTES.
SYMBICORT DOESN'T REPLACE
A RESCUE INHALER
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS.
WITH SYMBICORT,
TODAY I'M BREATHING BETTER.
AND THAT MEANS...FISH ON!
SYMBICORT IS FOR COPD
INCLUDING CHRONIC BRONCHITIS
AND EMPHYSEMA.
IT SHOULD NOT BE TAKEN
MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
SYMBICORT MAY INCREASE YOUR RISK
OF LUNG INFECTIONS,
OSTEOPOROSIS,
AND SOME EYE PROBLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HEART CONDITION
OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING IT.
WITH COPD, I THOUGHT
I'D MISS OUR FAMILY TRADITION.
NOW SYMBICORT SIGNIFICANTLY
IMPROVES MY LUNG FUNCTION,
STARTING WITHIN 5 MINUTES.
AND THAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE
IN MY BREATHING.
TODAY, WE'RE READY
FOR WHATEVER SWIMS OUR WAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT SYMBICORT.
I GOT MY FIRST
PRESCRIPTION FREE.
CALL OR CLICK
TO LEARN MORE.
[ Male Announcer ] IF YOU CAN'T
AFFORD YOUR MEDICATION,
ASTRAZENECA
MAY BE ABLE TO HELP.
YOU KNOW, FROM OUR 4,000
TELEVISION COMMERCIALS.
YEP, THERE I AM WITH FLO.
HOO-HOO! WATCH IT!
[Chuckles] ANYHOO, 3 MILLION
PEOPLE SWITCHED TO ME LAST YEAR,
SAVING AN AVERAGE
OF $475.
[Sigh] IT FEELS GOOD
TO HELP PEOPLE SAVE...
WITH GREAT DISCOUNTS LIKE
SAFE DRIVER, MULTICAR,
AND MULTIPOLICY.
SO CALL ME TODAY.
YOU'LL BE GLAD YOU DID.
CANNONBOX!
[SPLASH!]
DIARRHEA, GAS, BLOATING?
YES!
ONE Phillips' Colon Health
PROBIOTIC CAP EACH DAY
HELPS DEFEND
AGAINST THESE DIGESTIVE ISSUES
WITH THREE STRAINS
OF GOOD BACTERIA.
LIVE THE REGULAR LIFE.
Phillips'.
>>> NOW TO A BRAND NEW LAWSUIT
TONIGHT, TAKING ON TRUMP, AMS OF
STUDENTS SPENT UP TO $35,000 TO
ATTEND TRUMP UNIVERSITY.
TONIGHT, THE STATE ATTORNEY
GENERAL NOW SUING DONALD TRUMP.
HERE'S ABC'S LINZIE JANIS.
♪
♪ MONEY MONEY MONEY
>> Reporter: ON "THE
APPRENTICE," BILLIONAIRE REAL
ESTATE MOGUL DONALD TRUMP OFFERS
ONE LUCKY CONTESTANT THE
OPPORTUNITY TO LEARN FROM HIM.
>> NOT GOING TO GET ALONG WITH
PEOPLE, YOU MAY BE SUCCESSFUL,
BUT IT'S GOING TO BE A LOT
HARDER.
>> Reporter: BUT IT'S NOT THE
FIRST TIME HE'S OFFERED TO TEACH
THE SECRETS OF HIS SUCCESS.
>> WE TEACH SUCCESS.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT.
SUCCESS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, HE'S BEING
SUED BY NEW YORK'S ATTORNEY
GENERAL, WHO SAYS HE WAS MAKING
FALSE PROMISES TO THOUSANDS OF
STUDENTS WHO TOOK HIS INVESTMENT
COURSES.
A LAWSUIT FILED LATE SATURDAY
ALLEGES TRUMP OPERATED HIS
SCHOOL WITHOUT A LICENSE FOR SIX
YEARS.
RECRUITING 5,000 PEOPLE THROUGH
AN ELABORATE BAIT AND SWITCH.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE
PROFESSORS THAT ARE ABSOLUTELY
TERRIFIC.
>> Reporter: PROMISING THEM THE
CHANCE TO BECOME RICH, ONLY IF
THEY SPENT UP TO $35,000 ON HIS
EXCLUSIVE CLASSES AND MENTORING
PROGRAMS.
>> THEY WERE FLEECED.
THEY WERE TAKEN.
THEY WERE CONVINCED BY VERY
PERSUASIVE MOTIVATIONAL SPEAKERS
AND BY VIDEOS OF TRUMP.
THEY DIFFERENT GET ANY SECRETS.
THEY DIDN'T GET ANY MENTORSHIP.
THEY DIDN'T GET ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: RESPONDING OVER THE
WEEKEND, TRUMP TWEETED,
"LIGHTWEIGHT NEW YORK STATE
ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC
SCHNEIDERMAN IS TRYING TO EXTORT
ME WITH A CIVIL LAWSUIT."
AND DIRECTING HIS FOLLOWERS TO A
WEBSITE LAUNCHED FRIDAY,
CLAIMING 98% OF FORMER STUDENTS
WERE SATISFIED WITH THEIR
COURSES.
THE TRUMP SCHOOL DID DROP THE
TERM UNIVERSITY AS REQUESTED BY
THE STATE IN 2010, BUT TRUMP AND
OTHER DEFENDANTS, INCLUDING THE
FORMER PRESIDENT OF THE SCHOOL,
ARE BEING SUED FOR $40 MILLION
IN RESTATION PLUS POTENTIALLY
TENS OF MILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN
PENALTIES.
DAVID?
>> MORE TO COME.
LINZIE JANIS, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, AFTER THE BATMAN
BACKLASH, THE NEW HEADLINE
TONIGHT.
WE KNEW IT WAS BEN AFFLECK
PLAYING BATMAN AND WE KNEW HENRY
KAVL WOULD BE PLAYING SUPERMAN.
TONIGHT, THE NEW ROLE REVEALED.
MY NAME IS LEE KAUFMAN.
MARRIED TO MORTY KAUFMAN.
[ Lee ]
NOW THAT I'M GETTING OLDER
SOME THINGS ARE HARDER TO DO.
THIS IS NOT
A SAFE THING TO DO.
BE CAREFUL BABE.
THERE SHOULD BE SOME WAY
TO MAKE IT EASIER
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
LET'S OPEN IT UP
AND SEE WHAT'S COOKIN'.
OH I LIKE THAT.
LOOK AT THIS
IT'S GOT A HANDLE ON IT.
I DON'T HAVE TO CLIMB UP.
THIS YELLOW PART UP HERE REALLY
CATCHES A LOT OF THE DUST.
DID YOU NOTICE
HOW CLEAN IT LOOKS?
MORTY ARE YOU LISTENING?
MORTY?
[ Morty ]
I'M LISTENING!
I WANT YOU TO KNOW
MORTY ARE YOU LISTENING?
MORTY?
TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS
TO MAKE THE CALL.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE,
MY DOCTOR AND I
WENT WITH AXIRON,
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT THE
ONLY UNDERARM LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
[ Male Announcer ]
STAYING WARM AND DRY
HAS NEVER BEEN OUR PRIORITY.
♪
CATERING TO
THE CONVENIENTLY LOCATED
HAS NEVER BEEN OUR PRIORITY.
OUR PRIORITY IS, WAS
AND ALWAYS WILL BE
SERVING YOU,
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
WE GET TO SEE EVERYONE
IN AMERICA ALMOST EVERY DAY.
AND WE'VE NOTICED THAT YOU'RE
SENDING AND RECEIVING
MORE PACKAGES THAN EVER.
SO WE WANTED TO GIVE YOU
A MORE RELIABLE WAY
TO SHIP THEM.
WITH IMPROVED PRIORITY MAIL
FLAT RATE.
DON'T JUST TAKE OUR WORD
FOR IT --
NOW WE'LL PROVE IT
EVERY STEP OF THE WAY
WITH TRACKING
UP TO ELEVEN SCANS,
SPECIFIED DELIVERY DATES,
AND FREE INSURANCE UP TO $50
ALL FOR THE SAME LOW RATE.
WE'LL NEVER STOP DELIVERING
FOR EVERY PERSON
IN THIS COUNTRY.
[ Woman ] WE ARE THE
UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.
[ Man ] WE ARE THE
[ Woman #2 ] WE ARE THE
UNITED STATES POSTAL SERVICE.
[ Male Announcer ] WE ARE THE
AND OUR PRIORITY IS YOU.
GO TO USPS.COM®
AND TRY IT TODAY.
>>> OUR "INSTANT INDEX" ON A
SUNDAY FRIGHNIGHT.
IN THE UPCOMING "MAN OF STEEL"
SEQUEL, BEN AFFLECK'S CASTING
HAS SET OFF A BACKLASH.
THE CASTING OF BRYAN CRANSTON AS
THE EVIL LEX LIEU THOR.
CRANSTON REPORTEDLY SIGNING ON.
>>> VIDEO TRENDING TONIGHT.
BUT THESE ARE NO SPECIAL
EFFECTS.
TIAL WAVE OF FOG TONIGHT TO SHOW
YOU.
SLOWLY ROLLING DOWN OVER A
MOUNTAIN ROAD IN NEWFOUNDLAND.
PEOPLE WERE SIMPLY MESMERIZED.
>>> AND LOOK AT THIS TONIGHT.
A LITTLE GIRL AND THE GORILLA
WHO WAS ENTERTAINING HER.
RUNNING BACK AND FORTH, THE BABY
GORILLA, TESTING THE LITTLE
GIRL'S SPEED.
AND THEN SO ENAMORED WITH HIS
NEW FRIEND, HE PUCKERED UP,
HOPING FOR A KISS AND LOOK.
SHE GIVES HIM ONE BACK.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, THE HUSBAND WHO JUST
LOST HIS LOVE OF 75 YEARS,
HEARING THE SONG HE WROTE FOR
HER, PUT TO MUSIC.
SHE'S ALWAYS HAD A PLAYFUL SIDE.
AND YOU LOVE HER FOR IT.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A
QUESTION OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME
THE MOMENT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS
THE ONLY DAILY ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED
AND SYMPTOMS OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL YOUR MEDICAL
CONDITIONS AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN 4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC
REACTIONS SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
IT'S HARD TO DESCRIBE,
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A NUMBNESS,
BUT YET YOU HAVE THE PAIN
LIKE THOUSANDS OF NEEDLES
STICKING IN YOUR FOOT.
IT WAS PROGRESSIVELY
GETTING WORSE,
AND AT THAT POINT
I KNEW I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
ONCE I STARTED TAKING THE LYRICA
THE PAIN STARTED SUBSIDING.
[ Male Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYESIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO HAVE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE, A LOVE
SONG.
THE BITTERSWEET LYRICS ABOUT A
WOMAN NAMED LORRAINE,
WRITTEN BY THE HUSBAND WHO JUST
LOST HIS LOVE OF 75 YEARS.
BUT HE NEVER KNEW THE SONG WOULD
BE PUT TO MUSIC.
HERE'S ABC'S SUSAN SAULNY.
>> Reporter: THE YEAR WAS 1938.
FRED REMEMBERS FIRST SEEING THE
LOVE OF HIS LIFE AT AN A&W ROOT
BEER STAND.
SHE WAS A CAR HOP.
THE WAITRESS DELIVERING THE
FOOD.
>> SHE WAS JUST THE PRETTIEST
GIRL I EVER SAW.
>> Reporter: THEY WERE MARRIED
FOR 73 YEARS.
JUST THIS APRIL, HE LOST
LORRAINE.
SHE WAS 91.
NOT LONG AFTER, HE BEGAN WRITING
A SONG ABOUT HER.
>> AFTER SHE PASSED AWAY, I JUST
WAS SITTING IN THE FRONT ROOM
ONE EVENING BY MYSELF AND IT
JUST COME RIGHT TO ME ALMOST.
>> Reporter: WITH HIS SONG
WRITTEN, FRED THEN RAEPDS IN THE
NEWSPAPER OF A CONTEST, LOOKING
FOR THE BEST SONG, AND THE
WINNER WOULD HAVE THAT SONG
PRODUCED.
SO MANY SENT IN VIDEOS OF
THEMSELVES SINGING, BUT FRED
JUST SENT HIS WORDS.
>> INSTEAD OF A VIDEO, WE
RECEIVED A VERY LARGE MANILA
ENVELOPE.
THE LETTER WAS JUST SO
HEARTWARMING AND WE SAID, FRED,
I SAID, WE'RE GOING TO RECORD
YOUR SONG.
>> Reporter: WHEN IT WAS DONE,
THEY INVITED HIM TO LISTEN TO IT
FOR THE FIRST TIME.
THEY GAVE FRED THE HEADPHONES.
>> TELL ME WHEN YOU'RE READY.
♪
>> Reporter: MISSING HIS LOVE,
TONIGHT, FRED WITH A SONG TO
REMEMBER THAT FACE HE FIRST SAW
75 YEARS AGO.
♪ SWEET LORRAINE
>> Reporter: SUSAN SAULNY, ABC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
♪ I WISH WE COULD DO ALL THE
GOOD TIMES OVER AGAIN ♪
>> YOU CAN HEAR THE WHOLE SONG
AT iTUNES.
"GMA" IN THE MORNING AND DIANE
SAWYER RIGHT BACK HERE TONIGMOR
NIGHT.
SWEET LORRAINE.
THAT ONE'S FOR YOU.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NEXT ON ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:00,
A LOOK AT WHAT'S KEEPING
FIREFIGHTERS FROM GAINING
CONTROL OVER A DESTRUCTIVE
WILDFIRE AT YOSEMITE.
>>> TWO CHILDREN ARE SHOT AND
RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL.
>>> AND A LOOK AT THE
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO THAT POLICE
IN THE SOUTH BAY HOPE CAN HELP
THEM CATCH A KILLER.
ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
>>> LIVE FROM THE KGO TV
BROADCAST CENTER, THIS IS ABC 7
NEWS.
>>> A BATTLE FOR TERRAIN
CONTINUES IN TUOLUMNE COUNTY AS
THE WILDFIRE RAGES FOR ITS
EIGHTH DAY.
I'M AMA DAETZ.
THE FIRE IS JUST 7% CONTAINED
RIGHT NOW.
IT'S BURNED THROUGH NEARLY
134,000 ACRES.
IT HAS DESTROYED FOUR HOMES AND
A DOZEN OTHER STRUCTURES.
IT'S NEARLY PUT SAN FRANCISCO'S
WATER AND ELECTRICITY SUPPLIES
IN DANGER.
MORE THAN 2800 FIREFIGHTERS ARE
HAVING A HARD TIME GETTING
CONTROL OF THE FIRE BECAUSE OF
ROUGH TERRAIN AND TALL TREES
WHICH CATCH FIRE FAR ABOVE THEIR
REACH.
THE WEATHER IS MAKING THEIR
EFFORT MORE DIFFICULT.
LEIGH GLASER SHOWS US WHY.
>> IT WAS REALLY A HOT DAY OUT
THERE ON THE FIRE LINES AND A
GUSTY WINDS, REPORTED GUSTS TO
35 MILES PER HOUR IN THE HIGHER
TERRAIN THERE.
WE'RE GIVING YOU A GOOD SENSE OF
THAT PLUME OF SMOKE THAT'S BEING
CREATED BY THESE FIRES.
AND IT'S MOVING AS FAR NORTH AS
SOUTH LAKE TAHOE.
THEY'RE REPORTING VERY POOR AIR
QUALITY.
CURRENT READINGS, TEMPERATURES
IN THE UPPER 80s.
HOT OUT THERE.
HUMIDITY AT ONLY 17%.
VERY DRY.
THOSE WINDS SOUTHWEST GUST TO
30-PLUS MILES PER HOUR.
TOMORROW NOT A LOT OF RELIEF
HERE.
90.
THOSE WINDS WILL PICK UP AS
WELL.
THERE IS A CHANCE OF SOME DRY
LIGHTNING AS WE HEAD INTO
TUESDAY NIT