OUR NEXT NEWSCAST IS COMING UP
IN HALF AN HOUR AT 6:00.
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, TERROR IN BROAD
DAYLIGHT.
A DEADLY ATTACK IN THE STREETS
OF LONDON.
THE BIZARRE, ON-CAMERA
CONFESSION.
>> YOU PEOPLE WILL NEVER BE
SAFE.
>> AND CONCERN TONIGHT ABOUT A
NEW TACTIC ON THE TERROR FRONT.
>>> AN ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE FROM
OKLAHOMA.
CELLPHONE VIDEO FROM INSIDE AN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN THE FURY OF
THE MONSTER TORNADO.
>> OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> A BRAVE HERO TEACHER.
SHE TELLS DAVID MUIR HOW THEY
ALL MADE IT OUT.
>>> SPRING SPIKE.
GAS PRICES SOARING JUST IN TIME
FOR MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND, AND
HOW WHERE YOU PARK COULD SAVE
YOU MONEY.
>>> AND RACE TO THE TOP OF MOUNT
EVEREST.
TWO MEN IN THEIR 80S, IN A
CUT-THROAT RIVALRY.
HOW ARE THEY DOING IT, AND WHO
WILL MAKE IT TO THE SUMMIT
FIRST?
>>> GOOD EVENING.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH THAT
TERROR IN BROAD DAYLIGHT,
RAISING QUESTIONS ABOUT A NEW
KIND OF TERROR ATTACK.
TWO MEN, WITH A NUMBER OF BRUTAL
WEAPONS IN LONDON, ATTACKED
ANOTHER MAN, REPORTED TO BE A
SOLDIER.
WE WARN YOU, THE IMAGES OF THE
AFTERMATH ARE STRONG, AND ALL OF
THIS APPARENTLY DELIBERATE
THEATER BY THE ATTACKER.
TONIGHT, OFFICIALS IN THE UNITED
STATES AND THE UNITED KINGDOM
ARE STUDYING THE MEANING OF THIS
TAPE.
AND ABC'S LAMA HASAN IS THERE AT
THE SCENE OF THE ATTACK.
LAMA?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
WE'RE STANDING RIGHT IN FRONT OF
WHERE THIS BRUTAL ATTACK TOOK
PLACE.
RIGHT HERE BEHIND ME, JUST A
HUNDRED YARDS FROM THE MILITARY
BARRACKS.
A BARBARIC ATTACK IN BROAD
DAYLIGHT.
THE VICTIM REPORTED TO BE A
BRITISH SOLDIER.
EYEWITNESSES SAY HE WAS WALKING
ON THE SIDEWALK OUTSIDE HIS
BARRACKS WHEN HE IS HIT BY A
CAR.
THEN TWO MEN JUMP OUT AND BEGIN
ATTACKING HIM WITH KNIVES,
HACKING HIM TO DEATH.
>> THERE WAS TWO PEOPLE LEANING
OVER.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE TRYING TO
RESUSCITATE HIM.
THERE WAS A BLOKE AGAINST THE
WALL.
THEN ANOTHER BLOKE CAME ALONG
AND TOLD ME THEY WERE ACTUALLY
STABBING HIM.
>> I SAW THE GUY WITH, LIKE AN
AXE IN ONE HAND AND LIKE A GUN
IN ANOTHER HAND.
AND THEN HE WAS LITERALLY
WALKING AROUND KIND OF TALKING
TO PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: THEN THE GUNMAN
APPROACHED A PASSERBY WITH A
CAMERA.
>> I APOLOGIZE THAT WOMEN HAD TO
WITNESS THIS TODAY.
BUT IN OUR LAND OUR WOMEN HAVE
TO SEE THE SAME.
>> Reporter: LOOK CLOSELY, HIS
HANDS SOAKED IN BLOOD AS HE
GRIPS A BUTCHER'S KNIFE AND A
CLEAVER, SAYING THIS.
>> YOU PEOPLE WILL NEVER BE
SAFE.
REMOVE YOUR GOVERNMENT.
THEY DON'T CARE ABOUT YOU.
YOU THINK DAVID CAMERON IS GOING
TO GET CAUGHT IN THE STREET WHEN
WE START BUSTING OUR GUNS.
YOU THINK THE POLITICIANS ARE
GONNA DIE, NO IT'S GONNA BE YOU.
>> Reporter: POLICE ARRIVE AND
FIRE ON THE ATTACKERS HOLDING A
GUN.
>> TWO MEN WHO WE BELIEVE, FROM
EARLIER REPORTS, TO BE CARRYING
WEAPONS, WERE SHOT BY POLICE.
THEY HAVE BEEN TAKEN TO SEPARATE
LONDON HOSPITALS AND ARE
RECEIVING TREATMENT FOR THEIR
INJURIES.
>> Reporter: POLICE STREAMED OUT
ON THE STREETS, A NEARBY SCHOOL
ON LOCKDOWN.
AS BRITISH PRIME MINISTER
CAMERON CALLED THE ATTACK
SICKENING.
>> WE'RE URGENTLY SEEKING AND
THE POLICE ARE URGENTLY SEEKING
THE FULL FACTS ABOUT THIS CASE.
BUT THERE ARE STRONG INDICATIONS
IT IS A TERRORIST INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE RACE IS
ON TO LEARN EVERYTHING THERE IS
ABOUT THESE TWO ATTACKERS,
INCLUDING WHETHER OR NOT ONE OF
THEM IS OF AFRICAN ORIGIN WITH
TIES TO TERRORIST GROUPS, AND IF
SOLDIERS, INCLUDING 10,000 U.S.
SERVICE PERSONNEL SERVING HERE
IN THE UK, ARE NOW THE TARGETS.
>> ALL RIGHT, LAMA HASAN,
REPORTING IN TONIGHT, THANK YOU
SO MUCH.
>>> NOW WE TURN TO THE OTHER
TERROR INVESTIGATION RIGHT HERE
AT HOME -- THE BOSTON BOMBINGS.
THE TWO BROTHERS ALLEGEDLY
FORMING THEIR OWN TERROR CELL.
AND THE MAN WHO MAY HAVE HELD
CLUES TO WHO THEY WERE, TONIGHT
HAS BEEN SHOT BY THE FBI.
ABC'S SENIOR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT, PIERRE THOMAS,
HAS THOSE DETAILS.
>> Reporter: IBRAGIM TODASHEV, A
MIXED MARTIAL ARTS FIGHTER, WAS
FRIENDS WITH SUSPECTED MARATHON
BOMBER, TAMERLAN TSARNAEV.
THEY EVEN TRAINED AT THE SAME
GYM.
>> BACK WHEN THEY USED TO LIVE
IN BOSTON, RIGHT, THEY USED TO
HANG OUT.
NOT HANG OUT, HE KNEW HIM
BECAUSE HE WAS AN MMA FIGHTER.
THE OTHER GUY WAS A BOXER.
>> Reporter: THE FBI HAD BEEN
TALKING TO TODASHEV, A CHECHEN,
FOR WEEKS AFTER THEY DISCOVERED
HE HAD CALLED TAMERLAN IN THE
DAYS BEFORE THE BOMBING.
EARLY THIS MORNING, AUTHORITIES
WERE INTERVIEWING HIM WHEN
MATTERS TURNED VIOLENT.
LAW ENFORCEMENT SOURCES SAY HE
LUNGED AT AN FBI AGENT WITH A
KNIFE.
HE WAS SHOT AND KILLED.
IN A DRAMATIC TWIST, SOURCES
TELL ABC NEWS TODASHEV WAS ABOUT
TO SIGN A CONFESSION IN
CONNECTION WITH A 2011 TRIPLE
HOMICIDE IN THE BOSTON AREA.
THREE MEN HAD THEIR THROATS
SLASHED, MARIJUANA AND CASH
SPRINKLED OVER THEIR BODIES.
SINCE THE BOSTON BOMBING,
TAMERLAN AND HIS BROTHER
DZHOKHAR HAVE EMERGED AS KEY
SUSPECTS IN THOSE SLAYINGS.
THE VICTIMS WERE ASSOCIATES OF
TODASHEV AND TAMERLAN.
LAW ENFORCEMENT SOURCES SAY
THERE'S NO EVIDENCE TYING
TODASHEV TO THE BOMBINGS.
PIERRE THOMAS, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> NOW THE LATEST TONIGHT ON
THE BIG STORY WE'VE BEEN
COVERING THIS WEEK, THE DIRECT
HIT TWISTER OUTBREAK IN
OKLAHOMA.
TONIGHT AN ABC NEWS EXCLUSIVE,
CELLPHONE VIDEO OF WHAT HAPPENED
IN ONE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
BY THE WAY, PRESIDENT OBAMA WILL
VISIT OKLAHOMA THIS WEEKEND, AND
ABC'S DAVID MUIR LEADS OUR
COVERAGE ONCE AGAIN TONIGHT WITH
THAT EXCLUSIVE.
DAVID?
>> Reporter: DIANE, GOOD
EVENING, AND FOR THE FIRST TIME
TONIGHT WE HEAR AND SEE THE
MOMENT THAT TORNADO HIT ONE OF
THOSE TWO ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS.
IN THIS CASE, BRIARWOOD
ELEMENTARY.
THE NATIONAL WEATHER SERVICE
TELLING US WINDS WERE MORE THAN
200 MILES PER HOUR AT THAT
POINT.
AS YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE, AS THAT
TWISTER HOVERED OVER THE SCHOOL,
IT WAS PITCH BLACK, AND
TERRIFYING INSIDE.
THIS IS THE MOMENT THE MONSTROUS
TORNADO HIT BRIARWOOD
ELEMENTARY.
FOR THE FIRST TIME, WE SEE WHAT
STUDENTS SAW HUDDLED IN THAT
BATHROOM.
COMPLETE DARKNESS.
AND THIS IS WHAT THEY HEARD.
[ WIND AND SCREAMING ]
>> Reporter: AS THE PRESSURE
FROM THE TORNADO TOOK HOLD OF
THAT SCHOOL, THAT BATHROOM, FELT
THE AIR PUSHING DOWN.
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER.
IT'S ALMOST OVER!
>> Reporter: THEIR TEACHER
PROMISING IT WOULD END.
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER.
>> I HATE THIS!
>> Reporter: YOU HEAR ONE OF THE
STUDENTS TELL HER, I HATE THIS.
>> HONEY, IT'S OKAY.
IT'S ALMOST OVER.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN HEAR THE
TEACHER WITH THE WHISTLE, TRYING
TO CALM THE STUDENTS.
>> KEEP YOUR HEADS DOWN!
>> Reporter: CRYING, THEY LEAVE
THE BATHROOM.
>> WOW, OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD.
OH, MY GOD, MY HOUSE.
OH, MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD.
[ CRYING ]
>> Reporter: THEY WALK THE
HALLWAYS.
>> OH MY GOD!
OH, MY GOD!
>> Reporter: GIANT PIECES OF
DEBRIS.
YOU CAN HEAR THE STUDENTS
DISTRAUGHT.
THEN THEY WALK OUTSIDE.
ONCE OUTSIDE, THE TEACHER, NOW
WORRIED ABOUT TWO OTHER
STUDENTS.
HER SON SAM, A FIRST GRADER, HER
DAUGHTER MARIE IN FOURTH.
AND THEN IN FRONT OF HER, SAM
APPEARS.
>> IT'S OKAY, HONEY.
>> Reporter: THEN THE MOMENT DAD
ARRIVES.
>> SAM, THERE'S DADDY.
JOEY, JOEY!
>> Reporter: SHE TELLS HIM SHE
HASN'T FOUND THEIR DAUGHTER.
AND HE FINDS HER ALIVE.
>> JOEY!
>> Reporter: THE PARKING LOT,
ONCE FILLED WITH TEACHERS AND
PARENTS' CARS RIGHT THERE ON THE
RIGHT, EMPTY.
AND LATE TODAY, AUTHORITIES
ALLOWING US TO BRING HER BACK TO
THAT SCHOOL.
AS WE WALK TOWARD IT, THE FIRST
THING WE NOTICE, THE MANGLED
PLAYGROUND.
>> OH, THERE'S OUR PLAYGROUND.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE
PLAYGROUND HERE?
>> THIS IS THE PLAYGROUND.
>> Reporter: TEARS FROM THE
TEACHER WHO COULD NOT BELIEVE
WHAT SHE WAS SEEING.
THE FIRST GRADE CLASSROOM BACK
IN THE CORNER THERE, WHERE HER
SON'S TEACHER WAS LYING ON TOP
OF HIM AND THE OTHER CHILDREN,
TO KEEP THEM SAFE.
INCREDIBLE TO THINK HER SON
CRAWLED OUT OF THAT RUBBLE WITH
ALL THOSE FIRST GRADERS, AND
LOOK AT THIS, RIGHT HERE IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE SCHOOL, A CAR
LANDING FROM THE PARKING LOT.
JUST BEYOND THAT CAR, SHE TAKES
ME UNDERNEATH THE TWISTED METAL,
DOWN THE HALLWAYS, ALL THAT'S
LEFT OF THE SCHOOL.
AMONG THE ONLY WALL STANDING,
THAT BRICK WALL TO THE BATHROOM
WHERE HER CLASS WAS SAVED.
>> THIS IS WHERE WE WALKED DOWN,
AND I WAS RIGHT HERE.
>> Reporter: FEDERAL AUTHORITIES
WERE HERE TODAY TOURING THE
DAMAGE, AND AGAIN THE QUESTIONS
SURROUNDING THOSE SAFE ROOMS AND
WHY THERE WERE NOT ANY IN EITHER
OF THOSE TWO SCHOOLS.
WE LEARNED IT CAN COST UP TO
$300 A SQUARE FOOT, UP TO A
MILLION DOLLARS OR MORE TO BL
THE SAFE ROOMS, BUT A LOT OF
PARENTS BELIEVE YOU CAN'T PUT A
PRICE TAG ON SAFETY.
THAT CONVERSATION HAS BEGUN.
ONE MORE DISCOVERY I WANTED TO
SHOW YOU FROM INSIDE THAT
SCHOOL.
WE FOUND THIS TODAY.
HER STUDENTS HAD MADE THIS FOR
HER BECAUSE THEY WERE GOING ON
TO MIDDLE SCHOOL.
THEY HAD JUST THREE DAYS LEFT.
SHE SAID SHE'LL CHERISH THIS
PHOTO.
WE'LL GET IT BACK TO HER AFTER
THE BROADCAST.
>> SO MANY STORIES, BUT THAT WAS
TRULY STUNNING.
THANK YOU AND OUR THANKS TO HER
AS WELL.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> TONIGHT THERE ARE OTHER
PARTS OF THE COUNTRY UNDER THE
THREAT OF SEVERE WEATHER.
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE MAP WITH THE
NEW SYSTEM SWEEPING IN FROM THE
WEST.
FROM BOSTON TO D.C., AS FAR WEST
AS CLEVELAND, MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
TOLD TO BRACE FOR HIGH WINDS,
HAIL, AND EVEN THE POSSIBILITY
OF A TORNADO.
>>> NEXT NOW WE TURN TO
WASHINGTON AND THAT SCANDAL
ABOUT BASIC FAIRNESS AND THE
IRS.
TODAY LAWMAKERS CALLED THE HEAD
OF THE IRS DIVISION THAT DEALS
WITH TAX-EXEMPT GROUPS, LOIS
LERNER, BUT HERE IS WHAT SHE
SAID TODAY.
>> I HAVE NOT DONE ANYTHING
WRONG.
I HAVE NOT BROKEN ANY LAWS.
I HAVE NOT VIOLATED ANY IRS
RULES OR REGULATIONS, AND I HAVE
NOT PROVIDED FALSE INFORMATION
TO THIS OR ANY OTHER
CONGRESSIONAL COMMITTEE.
>> AND THAT WAS PRETTY MUCH IT
BECAUSE AFTER THAT, SHE INVOKED
HER FIFTH AMENDMENT RIGHT AND
REFUSED TO ANSWER ANY QUESTIONS.
>>> AND NEXT, A NEW REPORT
TONIGHT THAT IS LIKELY TO GIVE A
LOT OF AMERICANS A WAKE-UP CALL
JUST IN TIME FOR THE LONG
WEEKEND AHEAD.
MEMORIAL DAY SHAPING UP TO BE AS
BUSY AS EVER.
MORE THAN 31 MILLION AMERICANS
EXPECTED TO DRIVE MORE THAN 50
MILES TO GET AWAY, BETWEEN
TOMORROW AND MONDAY.
AND MANY WILL BE IN FOR A
SURPRISE, A DRAMATIC HIKE IN GAS
PRICES.
ABC'S CHIEF BUSINESS
CORRESPONDENT, REBECCA JARVIS,
BREAKS IT DOWN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE
NATIONAL AVERAGE FOR A GALLON OF
GAS IS $3.66.
WITH PRICES CLIMBING THE LAST 17
STRAIGHT DAYS.
DRIVERS IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
COUNTRY ARE ESPECIALLY HARD HIT.
MIDWEST PRICES ON AVERAGE HAVE
JUMPED A WHOPPING 66 CENTS THIS
MONTH.
IN MINNESOTA, PRICES HIT A
RECORD, $4.28 A GALLON THIS
WEEK.
VERSUS THE REST OF THE COUNTRY
WHERE PRICES ARE UP BETWEEN TWO
AND 12 CENTS.
THAT'S BECAUSE?
>> THAT'S BECAUSE OF THE
REFINERY OF WORK, IT'S ONGOING
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE COUNTRY,
AND IT WILL END SOON.
>> Reporter: BUT IN THE
MEANTIME, IT'S ADDING UP.
A MONTH AGO, A ROAD TRIP TO THE
GRAND CANYON FROM MINNEAPOLIS
WOULD HAVE COST $700, TODAY
ABOUT $900.
WHILE RECORD PRICES HAVE
PLATEAUED, EXPERTS SAY DRIVERS
ON THE COAST SHOULD BUCKLE UP.
AMERICANS PAY THE MOST AT THE
PUMP DURING SUMMER MONTHS.
TIPS FOR YOUR TRIP.
PARK IN THE SHADE.
LESS GAS EVAPORATION.
A COOLER CAR MEANS LESS AC.
PLUS FILL THE TANK ALL THE WAY
UP.
FILLING UP HALFWAY ONLY MEANS
YOU'LL BURN MORE GAS GOING TO
AND FROM THE STATION.
REBECCA JARVIS, ABC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>>> AND STILL AHEAD ON "WORLD
NEWS," LOOKING FORWARD TO THE
WEEKEND.
LOOK AT THIS POOL.
YOU CAN SEE THAT TEST FIGURE AT
THE BOTTOM OF THE POOL.
BUT HOW ABOUT NOW?
IT'S A SUMMER SAFETY ALERT
COMING UP.
PLEASE DO NOT MISS IT.
IT'S NEXT.
YEARS AGO, MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
TO TAKE A CENTRUM SILVER
MULTIVITAMIN EVERY DAY.
I TOLD HIM, SURE.
CAN'T HURT, RIGHT?
AND NOW TODAY,
I SEE THIS IN THE NEWS.
ONCE AGAIN, CENTRUM SILVER
WAS CHOSEN BY RESEARCHERS
FOR ANOTHER LANDMARK STUDY.
THIS TIME LOOKING AT EYE HEALTH.
MY DOCTOR!
HE KNOWS HIS STUFF.
[ Male Announcer ] CENTRUM.
THE MOST STUDIED.
THE MOST RECOMMENDED.
AND THE MOST PREFERRED
MULTIVITAMIN BRAND.
THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
AND THE MOST PREFERRED
MULTIVITAMIN BRAND.
no secondhand smoke in here...
...and no cigarette
advertising around here.
There's a reason we
know this is really bad...
...and this is really good.
There's a reason 2 in 3
people are surviving cancer.
And we cannot be
silent until it's 3 out of 3.
This shout-out is for
everything the American
Cancer Society has done
in the last 100 years.
Let's make noise
and finish the fight.
[ clang ]
MY HOUSE IS
WHERE PLANTS CAME TO DIE.
BUT, IT TURNS OUT
ALL I WAS MISSING
WAS MIRACLE-GRO POTTING MIX.
IT'S GOT WHAT A PLANT NEEDS
LIKE MIRACLE-GRO PLANT FOOD
THAT FEEDS THEM
FOR UP TO SIX MONTHS.
YOU GET BIGGER,
HEALTHIER PLANTS, GUARANTEED.
WHO'S GOT TWO GREEN THUMBS
THANKS TO MIRACLE-GRO?
AH, THIS GAL.
BOOM!
WITH THE RIGHT SOIL,
EVERYONE GROWS WITH MIRACLE-GRO.
AND YOU'LL DUMP
YOUR OLD DUSTER.
SWIFFER 360 DUSTER EXTENDER
CLEANS HIGH AND LOW,
WITH THICK ALL AROUND FIBERS
THAT ATTRACT AND LOCK
UP TO TWO TIMES MORE DUST
THAN A FEATHER DUSTER.
SWIFFER GIVES CLEANING
A WHOLE NEW MEANING.
THAN A FEATHER DUSTER.
AN INTENSE BURNING SENSATION
I WOKE UP WITH THIS HORRIBLE
RASH ON MY RIGHT SIDE.
LIKE SOMEBODY HAD
SET IT ON FIRE.
AND THE DOCTOR SAID, CINDIE,
YOU HAVE SHINGLES.
HE SAID, YOU HAD CHICKENPOX
WHEN YOU WERE A LITTLE GIRL...
I SAID, YES, I DID.
I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY EVER THINKS
THEY'RE GOING
TO GET SHINGLES.
BUT IT HAPPENED TO ME.
FOR MORE OF THE INSIDE STORY,
VISIT SHINGLESINFO.COM
>>> THIS WEEKEND IS COMING, TIME
TO GET THE BATHING SUITS OUT OF
THE BOTTOM DRAWER.
AND A REPORT TODAY FROM THE
CONSUMER PRODUCTS SAFETY
COMMISSION REMINDS US, ALL THE
WAYS WE CAN KEEP OUR CHILDREN
SAFE IN THE WATER.
ABC'S DAVID KERLEY TELLS US NOW
HOW TO PREVENT A TRAGEDY.
>> Reporter: WHAT YOU ARE ABOUT
TO SEE COULD SAVE YOUR CHILD'S
LIFE.
WATCH THE BOY WITH THE BLUE TOP,
HOW SILENTLY AND QUICKLY HE
FACES DROWNING.
AS HE MOVES TO DEEPER WATER,
SUDDENLY HE SLIPS AWAY.
LOOK AT IT AGAIN.
THAT FAST, UNDER WATER FOR TEN
SECONDS BEFORE BEING SAVED.
BUT SOME KIDS END UP AT THE
BOTTOM OF THE POOL AND CAN'T BE
SEEN.
LOOK AT THIS DUMMY IN CALM WATER
VERSUS WHEN THE WATER IS CHURNED
UP.
WHICH IS WHY TONIGHT WITH NEARLY
300 KIDS UNDER 5 DROWNING EACH
YEAR THE GOVERNMENT IS PLEADING
WITH PARENTS.
>> THIS IS PREVENTABLE.
IF YOU HAVE CHILDREN, MAKE SURE
THEY KNOW HOW TO SWIM.
IF YOU HAVE A POOL, MAKE SURE
THERE'S A FENCE AROUND IT.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN HALF OF
THOSE UNDER 5 DROWN IN THEIR
FAMILY POOL.
THESE RECOMMENDATIONS AND
WARNINGS ARE NOTHING NEW.
BUT UNFORTUNATELY THE NUMBER OF
CHILDREN DROWNING HAS REMAINED
STEADY.
CULLEN JONES NEARLY BECAME A
STATISTIC AT AGE 5.
>> I WAS UNDER WATER FOR ABOUT
30 SECONDS.
AND IT ONLY TAKES A CHILD ABOUT
20 SECONDS TO DROWN.
>> Reporter: JONES NOT ONLY
SURVIVED, HE LEARNED HOW TO
SWIM.
BOY, CAN HE SWIM.
HE BECAME AN OLYMPIC GOLD
MEDALIST IN 2008, AND IS NOW
TRYING TO TURN AROUND THOSE
DROWNING STATISTICS BY INSPIRING
AND TEACHING KIDS.
HIS ADVICE, THE CURE-ALL.
LEARN TO SWIM.
>> I URGE FAMILIES AND PARENTS
TO TAKE ONE SUMMER, PUT THE HAIR
IN BRAIDS, GO NATURAL FOR ONE
SUMMER, THAT'S IT, LEARN HOW TO
SWIM.
BECAUSE IT'S JUST LIKE RIDING A
BIKE, YOU NEVER FORGET HOW TO DO
IT.
>> Reporter: HE HASN'T
FORGOTTEN.
HE'S TRAINING FOR THE NEXT
OLYMPICS, HOPING SOME OF THESE
KIDS WILL FOLLOW HIS LEAD.
DAVID KERLEY, ABC NEWS,
BETHESDA, MARYLAND.
>>> AND STILL AHEAD HERE, TALK
ABOUT HOPE FOR EVERYONE.
TWO MEN IN THEIR 80s ARE RACING
EACH OTHER TO TOP OF MOUNT
EVEREST.
SEE IT NEXT.
I stepped on the machine, and it
showed me the pressure points on
my feet and exactly where I
needed more support.
I had tired, achy feet.
Until I got my number.
My Dr. Scholl's Custom Fit
Orthotics Number.
Now I'm a believer.
You'll be a believer, too.
Learn where to find your number
at DrScholls.com.
THAT YOUR MOUTH
IS UNDER ATTACK,
FROM FOOD PARTICLES
AND BACTERIA.
TRY FIXODENT.
IT HELPS CREATE
A FOOD SEAL DEFENSE
FOR A CLEAN MOUTH
AND KILLS BACTERIA
FOR FRESH BREATH.
♪
FIXODENT,
AND FORGET IT.
VIETNAM IN 1972.
[ All ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]
USAA AUTO INSURANCE
IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN
FROM GENERATION TO GENERATION.
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE MILITARY MEMBERS,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY,
GET AN AUTO INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA. WE KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS TO SERVE.
>>> TIME NOW FOR TONIGHT'S
INSTANT INDEX.
WE JUST SAW NUMBERS YOU MIGHT
WANT TO SEE.
IF YOU'RE PLANNING SUMMER
VACATION.
A SURVEY OUT TODAY FROM JULY'S
CONSUMER REPORTS, RATING THE
AIRLINES FOR THINGS LIKE COMFORT
AND CLEANLINESS.
NUMBER ONE, VIRGIN AMERICA, 89
OUT OF 100.
ON THE BOTTOM, SPIRIT AIRLINES,
50 OUT OF 100, BUT IT'S ON THE
BOTTOM OF PRICES AS WELL.
>>> AND A PHOTO OF A RACE TO THE
TOP OF MOUNT EVEREST.
HOW IS THIS POSSIBLE?
TWO MEN IN THEIR 80s ARE AT THIS
MOMENT DUELING TO SEE WHO WILL
SET A RECORD AT THE TOP.
ONE HAS A HEARING AID, THE
OTHER, FOUR HEART SURGERIES.
LETS REVIEW.
IT'S 29,000 FEET UP, AND NEARLY
200 MUCH YOUNGER PEOPLE HAVE
DIED TRYING.
HERE'S 80-YEAR-OLD YUICHIRO
MIURA EATING SUSHI ON HIS WAY
UP.
AND NEPAL RECORD HOLDER, M
MIMIN
MIN SHERCHAN, 81, IS CHASING
HIM.
MIURA EXPECTS TO REACH THE PEAK
TOMORROW.
THEY BOTH SAID THE SECRET IS
STAYING FIT THEIR WHOLE LIFE.
AND BOTTLED OXYGEN, GIVING THEM
AS MUCH LUNG POWER AS TEENAGERS.
>>> AND, FINALLY, OUR PLAYLIST,
SINGS TONIGHT WITH CAROLE KING,
WHO'S WOVEN A MUSICAL TAPESTRY,
ALL OF US SHARE.
TONIGHT THE 71-YEAR-OLD SINGER
SONGWRITER WILL BE HONORED AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
♪ AND I'LL BE THERE
♪ YES, I WILL
♪ YOU'VE GOT A FRIEND
>> YESTERDAY SHE GOT THE
GERSHWIN PRIZE FOR POPULAR SONG
AT THE LIBRARY OF CONGRESS, THE
FIRST WOMAN EVER TO RECEIVE IT,
SINGING THAT SONG SHE WROTE,
"YOU'VE GOT A FRIEND."
♪
>>> AND STILL AHEAD, WHAT IT IS
TO BE FROM OKLAHOMA.
JUST ASK TOBY KEITH, COMING UP.
ASK TOBY KEITH, COMING UP.
I HAVE LOW TESTOSTERONE.
THERE, I SAID IT.
SEE, I KNEW TESTOSTERONE
COULD AFFECT SEX DRIVE,
BUT NOT ENERGY
OR EVEN MY MOOD.
THAT'S WHEN I TALKED
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD TESTS...
SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.
THAT'S IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.
[ Male Announcer ]
TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T
HAVE ANDROGEL 1.62%
TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED
TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY
INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.
WOMEN AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WITH APPLICATION SITES.
DISCONTINUE ANDROGEL
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED SIGNS
OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,
WHICH MAY INCLUDE
CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE,
POSSIBLY DUE
TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER
OR WHO HAVE OR MIGHT HAVE
PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING,
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
WORSENING OF
AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,
POSSIBLE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER,
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING
OF ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY,
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS,
PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP,
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS,
ESPECIALLY INSULIN,
CORTICOSTEROIDS, OR MEDICINES
TO DECREASE BLOOD CLOTTING.
IN A CLINICAL STUDY, OVER 80%
OF TREATET  NORMAL.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.
CHANGE YOUR NUMBER. TURN IT UP.
ANDROGEL 1.62%.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.
CHANGE YOUR NUMBER. TURN IT UP.
I am an American
I'm a teacher.
I'm a firefighter.
I'm a carpenter.
I'm an accountant.
A mechanical engineer.
And I shop at Walmart.
Truth is, over sixty
percent of America
shops at Walmart
every month.
I find what I need,
at a great price.
And the money I save goes
to important things.
Braces for my daughter.
A little something for my
son's college fund.
When people look at me,
I hope they see someone
building a better life.
VO: Living better:
that's the real Walmart.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT Aleve
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HIM,
HE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HIM ALL DAY
AS HE GOES BACK
TO TAKING TYLENOL.
THAT WAS OKAY, BUT AFTER LUNCH
MY KNEE STARTED TO HURT AGAIN,
AND NOW I GOTTA TAKE MORE PILLS.
♪
YUP ANOTHER PILL STOP.
CAN I GET MY Aleve BACK YET?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY Aleve.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS MAY, BUY Aleve
AND HELP THOSE IN NEED.
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
>>> THIS WEEK WE WATCHED ABC'S
MIKE BOETTCHER, WALK THE STREETS
IN OKLAHOMA, HIS HOME STATE.
NOW HE'S GOING TO TELL US WHY
200-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS CANNOT
SHAKE SOMETHING HE LOVES --
THE SPIRIT OF THE PEOPLE AT
HOME.
>> Reporter: STANDING A HALF
MILE IN FRONT OF SUNDAY'S
VIOLENT STORM, WATCHING YET
ANOTHER TORNADO PLOW THROUGH RED
DIRT AND THE HOUSES BUILT ON IT,
I SILENTLY WONDERED "WHY DO I
LIVE HERE?"
THE ANSWER IS ROOTED IN DUST --
I'M AN OKIE.
THE O WORD WAS EQUIVALENT TO A
RACIAL SLUR DURING THE 1930s
DUST BOWL.
BUT OKIES, LIKE COUNTRY MUSIC
SUPERSTAR TOBY KEITH, A MOORE
NATIVE, WHO STILL LIVES HERE,
NOW DEFINE OKIE WITH WORDS LIKE
RESILIENT AND TOUGH.
>> JUST PERSISTENT, TENACIOUS
WILL TO SURVIVE AND CALL THIS
HOME.
THEY'RE GOING TO SAVE THEIR
POSSESSIONS.
THEY'RE GOING TO BOARD THEIR
HOUSE UP.
NOT BE A WHOLE BUNCH OF CRY
BABIES.
YOU KNOW WHAT I MEAN?
IT'S JUST NOT -- THESE PEOPLE
ARE JUST GOING TO BE TOUGH, GET
UP AND GET IT DONE.
>> UNBELIEVABLE!
>> Reporter: THAT RESILIENCY WAS
PROVED AFTER THE 1999 MOORE
TORNADO.
AND THE 1995 OKLAHOMA CITY
BOMBING.
EVEN NEWCOMERS LIKE NBA STAR
KEVIN DURANT TAKE PRIDE IN OKIE
RESILIENCE.
>> WE'LL COME TOGETHER AND
BOUNCE BACK FROM THIS.
YOU KNOW, IT'S TOUGH RIGHT NOW,
BUT THE SUN WILL SHINE SOON.
>> Reporter: A FEELING SHARED BY
SUPERSTARS AND ANONYMOUS VICTIMS
ALIKE.
>> WE'VE DONE IT ONCE ALREADY.
WE CAN DO IT AGAIN.
>> OKLAHOMANS ARE STRONG.
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: A PRIDE THAT A
MEMBER OF OKLAHOMA'S NEW
GENERATION PUT TO MUSIC.
♪ CAN YOU HEAR THIS SONG
♪ THE OKLAHOMA STRONG
>> Reporter: MIKE BOETTCHER, ABC
NEWS.
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
>>> AND WE THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
WATCHING.
WE'RE ALWAYS THERE FOR YOU AT
ABCNEWS.COM.
"NIGHTLINE," OF COURSE, WILL BE
HERE LATER, AND "WORLD NEWS"
WILL SEE YOU RIGHT BACK HERE
AGAIN TOMORROW NIGHT.
GOODNIGHT.
>>> WHY IS RICHMOND SO
RELUCTANT TO FILE SUIT?
>> TONIGHT A CAMPAIGN
CONTRIBUTION.
>> NEW TROUBLE FOR CALTRANS.
TURNS OUT THE NEW BAY BRIDGE
ISN'T THE ONLY ONE WHERE
BRITEL BOLTS ARE INSTALLED.
>> WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU
WHAT THE PATROL FOUND WHIT
WENT LOOKING FOR UNSAFE LIMOS
AND VAN AUTOS DOES THE STATE
OWE YOU MONEY?
MILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN
UNCLAIMED CASH FOR CALIFORNIA
CRIME VICTIMS.
>> A NEW ULTIMATUM TONIGHT
FROM RICHMOND TO CHEVRON.
SETTLE WUPT CITY OR LEAVE IT
UP TO A JUDGE TO DECIDE.
GOOD EVENING, I'M DAN ASHLEY.
>> RICHMOND CITY COUNCIL IS
PREPARED TO SUE ITS BIGGEST
NEIGHBOR IN F.NECESSARY BUT
LAST NIGHT THE COUNCIL VOTED
TO DELAY FILING THAT LAWSUIT.
THE STRI OF MONEY AND
POLITICS.
MARK?
>> CHEVRON KNOWS IT'S IN
TROUBLE AND NOW THE CITY ARE
TRYING TO REACH A SETTLEMENT.
>> AFTER THE FIRE, HUNDREDS OF
RESIDENTS LINED UP FOR
COMPENSATION FOR ILL AFFECTS
THEY SUFFERED AND CHEVRON SAID
THEY'D SETTLE THE CLAIMS BUT
MAYOR BELIEVES THE COMPANY
NEEDS PRODDING.
>> I PUT FORWARD A MOTION WE
HIRE THIS LAW FIRM THAT WOULD
BE POTENTIALLY FILING A CIVIL
LEGAL ACTION AGAINST CHEVRON
FOR DAMAGE AUTOS BUT LAST
NIGHT THE MOTION WAS DEFEATED.
THE CITY COUNCIL DECIDED TO
GIVE CHEVRON 30 DAYS TO REACH
AN AGREEMENT.
>> YOU GIVE ME $200,000 I
THINK I'M GOING TO BE BEHOLDEN
TO YOU.
>> THE CITY COUNCIL WOMAN
BECKELS VOTED WITH THE MAYOR
BUT TALKING ABOUT NATH R.NTA
BAITS WHO GOT 200,000S NDZ
SUPPORT FOR MOVING FORWARD.
A POLITICAL ORGANIZATION
ENTIRELY FUNDED BY CHEVRON.
CHEVRON GAVE MOVING FORWARD
$1.2 MILLION, MUCH SPENT IN
THE LAST WEEK SO 2012
CAMPAIGN.
>> THERE