>>
>>> TONIGHT, THE GROWING
>>> TONIGHT, SEVERAL BREAKING
STORIES AS WE COME ON THE AIR IN
THE WEST.
THE GROWING FIRESTORM.
PRESIDENT TRUMP VERSUS THE NFL.
GROWING BACKLASH TO THE
PRESIDENT'S ANGRY WORDS ABOUT
ATHLETES WHO PROTEST DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
>> GET THAT SON OF A [ BLEEP ]
OFF THE FIELD.
>> FROM PATRIOTS OWNER BOB
KRAFT, QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY TO
LeBRON JAMES, ON LIVE TV TODAY.
PLAYERS LOCKING ARMS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
TENSIONS BOILING OVER AMONG
FANS.
AND TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE IS
ASKED, WITH NORTH KOREA, WITH
HEALTH CARE, WITH THE EMERGENCY
IN PUERTO RICO, WHY THIS?
WHY NOW?
>>> ALL OF THIS AS THE GOVERNOR
OF PUERTO RICO SAYS THEY ARE
DEALING WITH A HUMANITARIAN
DISASTER, THAT THEY NEED HELP.
>>> ALSO BREAKING AT THIS HOUR,
CHAOS AND ARRESTS ON THE HILL.
PROTESTERS WORRIED ABOUT LOSING
THEIR HEALTH INSURANCE HAULED
OFF.
AND THE HEADLINE AS WE COME ON
THE AIR TONIGHT.
ONE REPUBLIC SENATOR WHO WAS ON
THE FENCE NOW ANNOUNCING HER
DECISION.
IS THE PLAN DEAD?
>>> AND SMOKE SUDDENLY FILLING
THE CABIN TODAY.
PASSENGERS MAKING A QUICK
ESCAPE.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A MONDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP, HIS WORDS ABOUT SOME
PLAYERS AND THE NFL, AND THE
BACKLASH, DIVIDING FANS.
AND LEADING TO PLAYERS AND TEAM
OWNERS, SOME OF WHOM SUPPORTED
THE PRESIDENT, TO NOW BREAK
RANKS WITH HIM ON THIS ISSUE.
TEAMS ACROSS THE COUNTRY THIS
WEEKEND SHOWING SOLIDARITY, SO
MANY LOCKED ARM IN ARM.
PATRIOTS QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY,
A FRIEND OF PRESIDENT TRUMP,
SPEAKING OUT TODAY, CALLING THE
PRESIDENT'S REMARKS DIVISIVE.
THE STEELERS PLAYER WHO STOOD
ALONE, HIS TEAM IN THE LOCKER
ROOM.
BUT A SHORT TIME AGO, NOW
APOLOGIZING, HE SAYS, FOR
INADVERTENTLY MAKING HIS TEAM
LOOK BAD.
AND AS I MENTIONED, THE WHITE
HOUSE WAS ASKED, WITH SO
MUCH AT STAKE ALREADY, WITH
NORTH KOREA, HEALTH CARE, WHY
DID THE PRESIDENT TARGET THIS?
ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, PRESIDENT
TRUMP DEFIANT AND UNAPOLOGETIC
ABOUT SPARKING A NATIONAL
>> WOULDN'T YOU LOVE TO SEE ONE
OF THESE NFL OWNERS, WHEN
SOMEBODY DISRESPECTS OUR FLAG,
TO SAY, GET THAT SON OF A
[ BLEEP ] OFF THE FIELD RIGHT
NOW, OUT.
HE'S FIRED.
>> Reporter: AN ADMINISTRATION
SOURCE TELLS ABC NEWS THE
PRESIDENT HAD EVERY INTENTION OF
MENTIONING THE NFL BEFORE A
PACKED HOUSE IN ALABAMA, BUT HE
ALSO WENT WAY BEYOND WHAT WAS
WRITTEN IN THAT SPEECH.
ATTACKING PLAYERS LIKE FORMER
SAN FRANCISCO 49ers QUARTERBACK
COLIN KAEPERNICK, WHO TOOK A
KNEE DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM,
A SILENT PROTEST AGAINST POLICE
BRUTALITY AND RACIAL INJUSTICE.
>> IF YOU SEE IT, EVEN IF IT'S
ONE PLAYER, LEAVE THE STADIUM.
>> Reporter: THE REACTION
INSTANT.
♪ O SAY CAN YOU SEE
>> Reporter: ON FOOTBALL FIELDS
AROUND THE COUNTRY, PLAYERS
UNITED IN PROTEST, MANY
KNEELING, OTHERS LINKING ARMS,
THEIR OWNERS AND COACHES JOINING
THEM, TOO.
FROM THE RAIDERS TO THE SAINTS,
PLAYERS SAT IN SILENCE.
IN NASHVILLE, EMPTY BENCHES.
BOTH TEAMS, THE TITANS AND
SEAHAWKS, STAYING THE LOCKER
ROOM WHEN THE ANTHEM PLAYED.
BUT THIS IMAGE OF STEELERS
LINEMAN ALEJANDRO VILLANUEVA
GOING VIRAL, TOO.
THE ARMY VET WHO SERVED THREE
TOURS IN AFGHANISTAN EMERGING
FROM THE TUNNEL TO PLACE HIS
HAND OVER HIS HEART, WHILE HIS
TEAMMATES STAYED BEHIND.
TONIGHT, HIS JERSEY SELLING MORE
THAN ANY OTHER PLAYER IN THE
NFL.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS, THIS IS NOT
ABOUT RACE.
THIS HAS NOTHING TO DO WITH
RACE OR ANYTHING ELSE.
THIS HAS TO DO WITH RESPECT FOR
OUR COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT, EVEN
SOME OF HIS OWN FRIENDS ARE
JOINING IN THE CHORUS OF
CRITICS.
PATRIOTS QUARTERBACK TOM BRADY
AMONG THOSE LINKING ARMS, AND
NOW, HE IS SPEAKING OUT.
>> I CERTAINLY DISAGREE WITH,
YOU KNOW, WHAT HE SAID, AND
THOUGHT IT WAS JUST DIVISIVE.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
CLOSE FRIEND, PATRIOTS OWNER BOB
KRAFT, SAYS HE IS DEEPLY
DISAPPOINTED WITH THE
PRESIDENT'S TONE.
AND FORMER NFL COACH REX RYAN, A
TRUMP SUPPORTER, SAYS HE'S
FURIOUS.
>> I'M PISSED OFF, I'LL BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
YOU KNOW, BECAUSE I SUPPORTED
DONALD TRUMP.
BUT I'M READING THESE COMMENTS
AND IT'S APPALLING TO ME.
>> Reporter: IT ALL COMES ON THE
HEELS OF THOSE PROTESTS IN
CHARLOTTESVILLE -- WHITE
SUPREMACISTS MCHARINWIG TH
THERE WERE "VERY FINE PEOPLE" ON
BOTH SIDES.
DOES THE PRESIDENT BELIEVE THAT
THERE ARE VERY FINE PEOPLE WHO
KNEELED YESTERDAY WATCHING THOSE
GAMES, OR ARE THEY ALL S.O.B.s?
>> I THINK YOU'RE TRYING TO
CONFLATE DIFFERENT THINGS HERE.
LOOK, WE CERTAINLY RESPECT THE
RIGHTS THAT PEOPLE HAVE, BUT I
THINK WE ALSO NEED TO FOCUS.
THIS IS ABOUT THE PRESIDENT
BEING FOR SOMETHING, THIS IS
ABOUT THE PRESIDENT BEING FOR
RESPECT IN OUR COUNTRY, THROUGH
SYMBOLS LIKE THE AMERICAN FLAG.
>> CECILIA VEGA WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
AND CECILIA, THE PRESIDENT
TWEETING ABOUT SPORTS, ABOUT 20
TIMES FROM OUR COUNT, SINCE
SATURDAY.
AND TODAY, THE WHITE HOUSE WAS
ASKED, YOU KNOW, WITH NORTH
KOREA, HEALTH CARE, THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS IN PUERTO
RICO, WHY DID THE PRESIDENT
CHOOSE TO DO THIS?
>> Reporter: WELL, DAVID, THE
WHITE HOUSE SAYS THE PRESIDENT
IS STANDING UP FOR PATRIOTISM,
PLAIN AND SIMPLE.
AND I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU,
SOURCES HERE ARE STANDING BEHIND
HIM, INSIDE THIS WEST WING.
THEY BELIEVE MOST AMERICANS WILL
SIDE WITH HIM ON THIS ONE.
DAVID, THE PRESIDENT IS TWEETING
RIGHT NOW, AGAIN, SAYING THAT
THERE HAS BEEN TREMENDOUS
BACKLASH AGAINST THE NFL.
>> WE'VE SEEN THE DIVISION AMONG
FANS AND SOME PLAYERS, AS WELL,
CECILIA.
YOU TOLD US ABOUT THE STEELERS
PLAYER, THE ARMY VET WHO CAME
OUT TO THE FIELD FOR THE ANTHEM.
THE REST OF HIS TEAM WAS INSIDE.
THE LOCKER ROOM.
TONIGHT, HE SEEMS TO BE
APOLOGIZING TO HIS TEAM FOR JUST
INADVERTENTLY MAKING THEM FEEL
BAD?
>> Reporter: YEAH, DAVID, HE'S
BASICALLY SAYING THIS WAS A
MIXUP.
HE DIDN'T MEAN TO BE SEPARATED
FROM HIS TEAM OUT THERE ON THE
FIELD.
HE IS APOLOGIZING TO THE
PLAYERS, TO THE COACH.
HE SAYS THAT HE ACTUALLY
SUPPORTS THE PROTESTERS WHO ARE
EXERCISING THEIR FIRST AMENDMENT
RIGHTS.
WE ARE ALSO HEARING FROM THAT
TEAM'S QUARTERBACK, DAVID,
HE'S SPEAKING OUT, TOO,
SAYING HE DIDN'T MEAN FOR THE
T AAMTEHEPEM APO IS NEVER A TI
TO PROTEST.
>> CECILIA VEGA LEADING US OFF
ON A MONDAY NIGHT.
CECILIA, THANK YOU.
>>> TODAY WAS SUPPOSED TO BE THE
DAY WHEN NBA PLAYERS WERE ASKED
ABOUT THE SEASON AHEAD.
IT'S MEDIA DAY.
INSTEAD, THEY WERE ASKED ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT.
AND AMONG THEM, LeBRON JAMES.
TONIGHT, WHAT HE SAID, AND NOW,
THE FANS IN THESE STADIUMS,
SUDDENLY AT ODDS WITH ONE
ANOTHER, TAKING SIDES.
ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN IN
GLENDALE TONIGHT, WHERE THE
COWBOYS PLAY THE CARDINALS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
BASKETBALL'S ICON, LeBRON JAMES,
KNEW THE QUESTIONS WOULD NOT BE
ABOUT THE SEASON AHEAD, BUT
ABOUT PRESIDENT TRUMP -- AND HE
WAS READY.
>> THE PEOPLE RUN THIS COUNTRY.
NOT ONE INDIVIDUAL AND DAMN SURE
NOT HIM.
>> Reporter: IT WAS LeBRON JAMES
WHO THIS WEEKEND SAID PRESIDENT
TRUMP IS "NOW USING SPORTS AS
THE PLATFORM TO TRY TO DIVIDE
US."
>> HE DOESN'T UNDERSTAND HOW
MANY KIDS, NO MATTER THEIR RACE,
LOOK UP TO THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
THAT'S WHAT MAKES ME MORE SICK
THAN ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: AND RESPONDING TO
THE PRESIDENT'S CRITICISM THAT
THOSE WHO KNEEL LACK RESPECT FOR
THE FLAG.
>> IT IS ABOUT EQUALITY AND
PEOPLE HAVING THE OPTION AND THE
FREEDOM TO SPEAK UPON THINGS
THAT THEY FEEL THAT'S NOT JUST.
>> Reporter: AND IN ADDITION TO
FOOTBALL AND BASKETBALL, TODAY,
THE PRESIDENT DRAWING IN NASCAR.
>> WE ASK YOU THAT PLEASE RISE
AND REMOVE YOUR HATS.
>> Reporter: AFTER THE PRESIDENT
TWEETED, "SO PROUD OF NASCAR AND
ITS SUPPORTERS AND FANS, THEY
WON'T PUT UP WITH DISRESPECTING
OUR COUNTRY OR OUR FLAG," NASCAR
ROYALTY, DALE EARNHARDT JR., NOT
BUYING IT, TWEETING A QUOTE BY
JOHN K. KENNEDY.
OTHER SPORTS ICONS WEIGHING IN,
LIKE HALL OF FAMER TERRY
BRADSHAW.
>> THIS IS AMERICA.
IF OUR COUNTRY STANDS FOR
ANYTHING, FOLKS, WHAT, IT'S
FREEDOM.
PEOPLE DIED FOR THAT FREEDOM.
I'M NOT SURE IF OUR PRESIDENT
UNDERSTANDS THOSE RIGHTS.
>> Reporter: THE TYPICAL
FRICTION BETWEEN PLAYERS, OWNERS
AND LEAGUE BRASS MELTING AWAY.
OWNERS LINKING ARMS WITH
PLAYERS.
BUT THE PRESIDENT'S WORDS AND
THE PROTESTS THAT FOLLOWED ARE
ALSO IGNITING NEW TENSIONS
BETWEEN FANS.
>> I HATE YOU!
>> BOO!
>> Reporter: NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOTS FANS BOOING THE TEAM
INCLUDING TOM BRADY, AS MEMBERS
LINKED ARMS.
AFTER MOST OF THE STEELERS
STAYED IN THE LOCKER ROOM DURING
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM, JIM HEENEY
BURNED A MOUND OF STEELERS GEAR.
>> I'M A LIFELONG STEELERS FAN.
NOT ANYMORE.
>> Reporter: DURING THE
CAMPAIGN, THE PRESIDENT MADE
THIS PREDICTION.
>> BUT I THINK THE THING THAT
WILL SURPRISE PEOPLE, I'LL BE A
UNIFIER.
I THINK I'LL BRING PEOPLE
TOGETHER.
AND THAT INCLUDES BLACKS AND
WHITES AND EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT, AS
FANS HEAD INTO THE STADIUM, NO
MATTER WHAT SIDE THEY ARE,
PEOPLE TELLING US THE
PRESIDENT'S MOST RECENT WORDS
ARE NOT DRAWING OPPOSING SIDES
ANY CLOSER.
>> I FEEL LIKE IT'S GOING TO
TURN INTO, LIKE, MORE LIKE WHITE
VERSUS BLACK.
>> MATT GUTMAN WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT FROM GLENDALE, OUTSIDE
THE CARDINALS/COWBOYS GAME.
THE NFL COMMISSIONER, OF COURSE,
WATCHING ALL OF THIS CLOSELY,
AND NOW RESPONDING TO THE
PROTESTS, MATT?
>> Reporter: AND RESPONDING
STRONGLY, DAVID.
WRITING, "THE WAY WE REACTED
THIS WEEKEND MADE ME PROUD."
NOW, ODDLY ENOUGH, IT TOOK A
CONTROVERSY OF THIS MAGNITUDE,
AFTER YEARS OF FRICTION, TO
FINALLY UNITE THE LEAGUE.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> WE ARE ALSO FOLLOWING
BREAKING NEWS RIGHT NOW FROM
CAPITOL HILL IN THE SENATE'S
LATEST EFFORT TO KILL OBAMACARE.
REPUBLICANS COULD ONLY AFFORD TO
LOSE ONE MORE VOTE, AND TONIGHT,
IT APPEARS THEY'VE LOST IT.
ALL OF THIS AS HUNDREDS OF
PROTESTERS WORRIED ABOUT LOSING
THEIR HEALTH INSURANCE PACKED
THE HALLWAYS OF THE CAPITOL.
THERE ARE MANY ARRESTS.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE ON SENATOR
COLLINS TONIGHT, WHO NOW SAYS
NO.
SO, IS THE EFFORT DEAD?
MARY'S BACK ON THE HILL.
>> Reporter: WITH PROTESTS
MOUNTING TONIGHT, THE REPUBLICAN
HEALTH CARE BILL APPEARS DOOMED
TO FAIL.
LATE WORD TONIGHT THAT MAINE
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS SAYS SHE
IS A NO, MAKING HER THE THIRD
SENATOR TO COME OUT AGAINST THE
BILL.
THE REPUBLICANS DO NOT HAVE THE
VOTES.
THE DRAMATIC MOVE COMES AFTER
OPPOSITION TO THE REPUBLICAN
G INTH CARE BILL CARROE
HILL.
>> NO CUTS FOR MEDICAID!
>> Reporter: ANGER AND
FRUSTRATION BOILING OVER.
TODAY'S HEARING HAD JUST BEGUN
WHEN THE CRIES RANG OUT.
>> IF YOU WANT A HEARING, YOU
BETTER SHUT UP.
>> Reporter: AND OUTSIDE, CHAOS.
>> MOVE AGAINST THE WALL!
RIGHT NOW!
MOVE AGAINST THE WALL!
>> Reporter: PROTESTER AFTER
PROTESTER HAULED OFF AND
ARRESTED, MANY IN WHEELCHAIRS.
THIS MAN PHYSICALLY DRAGGED OUT.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN LINING UP HERE
FOR HOURS.
CHECK THIS OUT.
THIS IS JUST THE BEGINNING.
IT GOES ON AS FAR AS YOU CAN
SEE.
PAM WILLIS CAME ALL THE WAY FROM
WYOMING.
SHE SAYS THIS BILL IS A MATTER
OF LIFE OR DEATH FOR HER
DAUGHTER.
WHAT'S THE MESSAGE THAT YOU WANT
LAWMAKERS TO HEAR FROM YOU AND
FROM EVERYBODY ELSE IN THIS
LINE?
>> BE HUMAN.
CARE.
CARE ABOUT INSURANCE FOR
EVERYONE, NOT JUST YOURSELVES OR
YOUR RELATIVES.
CARE ABOUT EVERYONE.
EVEN THE POOR.
>> Reporter: OPPONENTS OF THE
BILL, LIKE SENATORMcN OHCA, IN
HAVE CALLED FOR AN OPEN AND
BIPARTISAN PROCESS, BUT THIS IS
THE ONE AND ONLY PUBLIC HEARING
ON THE LATEST PLAN.
THE WITNESS LIST, MOSTLY
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS, NOT
AVERAGE AMERICANS.
>> IT'S A FRAUD.
IT'S A FAKE.
IT'S JUST A FACADE.
THEY DON'T WANT US TO TESTIFY.
THEY DON'T WANT US TO BE HERE.
>> Reporter: EARLIER TODAY, EVEN
THE PRESIDENT SEEMED TO
ACKNOWLEDGE DEFEAT.
>> WE HAVE 52 VOTES, SO, WE
CAN'T LOSE ANY VOTES.
I MEAN, PRACTICALLY.
SO, WE'RE GOING TO LOSE TWO OR
THREE VOTES AND THAT'S THE END
OF THAT.
>> BOTTOM LINE, MARY BRUCE LIVE
ON THE HILL, MARY, FIRST OF ALL,
DOES THIS APPEAR TO BE DEAD,
THIS EFFORT TONIGHT?
AND WE ALSO KNOW THEY'VE BEEN
TRYING TO DO THIS FOR SEVEN
YEARS, THE REPUBLICAN PARTY HAS.
THEY WANTED TO DO THIS WITH A
SIMPLE MAJORITY, NOW THAT WILL
NO LONGER BE AN OPTION?
>> Reporter: WELL, DAVID, RIGHT
NOW, THIS BILL IS GOING NOWHERE.
WHICH MEANS IF REPUBLICANS WANT
TO OVERHAUL OBAMACARE, THEY'RE
LIKELY GOING TO HAVE TO WORK
WITH DEMOCRATS.
THEY'RE NOW GOING TO NEED 60
VOTES, EVEN AFTER ALL THIS TIME,
REPUBLICANS STILL CAN'T AGREE ON
A PATH FORWARD.
THE DIVIDES WITHIN THE
REPUBLICAN PARTY SEEM SIMPLY TOO
DEEP RIGHT NOW FOR THEM TO
FULFILL THEIR SIGNATURE PROMISE
TO THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, MARY.
NOW IT BECOMES A TEST FOR BOTH
PARTIES MOVING FORWARD.
MARY, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO THE GROWING
EMERGENCY UNFOLDING IN PUERTO
RICO.
THE GOVERNOR OF PUERTO RICO NOW
BEGGING FOR HELP AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA, CALLING THIS A, QUOTE,
HUMANITARIAN DISASTER.
3.4 MILLION U.S. CITIZENS LIVE
THERE.
AND LOOK AT THIS SATELLITE IMAGE
OF THE ISLAND, LIT UP IN JULY.
AND NOW THIS IMAGE FROM THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT, JUST IN THE
DAYS NOW AFTER MARIA STRUCK.
MOST OF THE ISLAND IN DARKNESS.
ABC'S EVA PILGRIM TONIGHT TAKING
US FLYING OVER PUERTO RICO IN A
HELICOPTER, AND YOU WILL SEE
WHERE THE EYE OF THE HURRICANE
HIT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, NEW
PICTURES OF THE DEVASTATION IN
PUERTO RICO, AS THE ISLAND'S
RNGOVE
HELP, CALLING HURRICANE MARIA'S
DESTRUCTION A HUMANITARIAN
DISASTER FOR ITS 3.4 MILLION
U.S. CITIZENS.
WE ARE MANY DAYS REMOVED FROM
HURRICANE MAN SEE, THERE ARE STL
SEVERAL NEIGHBORHOODS THAT ARE
FLOODED.
HOME AFTER HOME RIPPED TO
SHREDS.
MUDSLIDES LEAVING HOMES
TEETERING ON THE EDGE.
THE GROUND THEY WERE BUILT ON
GONE.
ON THE GROUND, FEAR OF A
CATASTROPHIC FAILURE AT THE
GUAJATACA DAM.
8,000 RESIDENTS TOLD TO GET OUT
NOW.
>> THE CREW THAT'S BEHIND US,
THEY WALKED ABOUT TWO MILES TO
GAIN ACCESS TO A PERSON WHO WE
KNEW NEEDED HELP.
>> Reporter: A STRUGGLE FOR
BASIC NECESSITIES IN THE
SWELTERING HEAT.
WE MET JOSE VIDAL STANDING IN
THE SUN, TRYING TO GET A DAY'S
WORTH OF GENERATOR FUEL.
CUT OFF FROM FAMILY.
YOU HAVEN'T TALKED TO YOUR
FAMILY TO LET THEM KNOW YOU'RE
ACT YET?
>> NO, NO.
MY MOM, I HAVEN'T SPOKEN TO HER.
>> Reporter: WE LET HIM BORROW
OUR PHONE.
>> HEY, MA.
HOW YOU DOING?
I'M OKAY.
I'M ALL RIGHT.
DOING OKAY.
DOING THE BEST WE CAN.
>> Reporter: A MOMENT OF CONTACT
AMID ALL THIS ISOLATION.
>> IT'S BEEN SO POWERFUL TO
WATCH THOSE PHONE CALLS,
FAMILIES FINALLY CONNECTING,
EVEN DAYS AFTER MARIA.
EVA WITH US LIVE TONIGHT.
AND EVA, THERE'S BEEN SOME
PROGRESS INVOLVING COMMERCIAL
FLIGHTS IN AND OUT OF PUERTO
RICO?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
THE FAA SAYS THERE ARE ABOUT A
DOZEN FLIGHTS IN AND OUT OF SAN
JUAN EACH DAY, AND RISING.
BUT MARIA DESTROYED SOME
CRITICAL NAVIGATIONAL SYSTEMS.
THEY ARE HAVING TO USE CHAIN
SAWS TO GET TO ONE OF THE MAIN
RADAR SITES TO REPAIR IT.
DAVID?
>> EVA PILGRIM, THE WORK MONTHS
AND YEARS TO COME.
THANK YOU.
>>> AND NOW, A WEEK AFTER
HURRICANE MARIA FIRST HIT THOSE
CARIBBEAN ISLANDS, TROPICAL
STORM WARNINGS ARE UP ALONG
PARTS OF THE EAST COAST OF THE
U.S. TONIGHT.
MANDATORY EVACUATIONS FOR PARTS
OF NORTH CAROLINA AT THIS HOUR.
SO, LET'S GET TO CHIEF
METEOROLOGIST GINGER ZEE, STILL
TALKING ABOUT MARIA.
AND A REAL THREAT TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: AND ONLY MOVING
NORTH AT 7 MILES PER HOUR.
SO, IT'S GOING TO TAKE ITS TIME
HERE, BUT THE RIP CURRENTS AND
THE HIGH SURF COULD BE POSSIBLE
ALL THE WAY FROM FLORIDA TO
MASSACHUSETTS, DAVID.
BUT YOU KIND OF ZOOM IN, YOU CAN
SEE WHO MARIA IS GOING TO EFFECT
THE MOST.
THAT WOULD BE THE OUTER BANKS OF
NORTH CAROLINA, COASTAL NORTH
CAROLINA.
TWO TO FOUR FEET OF STORM SURGE.
GUSTS UP TO 60 MILES AN HOUR,
BEFORE THIS STORM FINALLY TURNS
INTO THE ATLANTIC THURSDAY AND
FRIDAY.
AND QUICKLY, THE OTHER BIG
HEADLINE EVERYONE IS TALKING
ABOUT, THAT INTENSE HEAT.
THAT RIDGE HAS BEEN BUILT IN.
MANY CITIES, CLEVELAND, DETROIT,
CHICAGO, HAVE SEEN FOUR, FIVE OR
SIX DAYS OF 90-PLUS.
THERE'S SOME RELIEF, LOOKS LIKE
GREEN ON THE MAP IS COMING.
>> THAT'S GOOD NEWS.
IN SOME CASES, SCHOOLS CLOSED.
>> Reporter: ABSOLUTELY.
>> ALL RIGHT, GINGER, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT, TO THAT NEW THREAT
FROM NORTH KOREA TONIGHT.
ITS TOP DIPLOMAT NOW SAYING THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S VERBAL ATTACKS
ARE A DECLARATION OF WAR, AND
THAT HIS COUNTRY NOW HAS THE
RIGHT TO RESPOND.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF GLOBAL
AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT MARTHA
RADDATZ TONIGHT.
T LLCAA ter: TONIGHT, NORTH
TRUMP A "DECLARATION OF WAR."
>> ROCKET MAN SHOULD'VE BEEN
HANDLED A LONG TIME AGO.
LITTLE ROCKET MAN.
WE'RE GOING TO DO IT, BECAUSE WE
REALLY HAVE NO CHOICE.
>> Reporter: AFTER THOSE WORDS,
A TWEET.
THE PRESIDENT THREATENING THE
LEADERS OF NORTH KOREA, SAYING
THAT IF THEY KEEP UP
PROVOCATIONS, THEY "WON'T BE
AROUND MUCH LONGER."
WHILE U.S. BOMBERS PUSHING
FURTHER OFF THE COAST OF NORTH
KOREA, THE FARTHEST NORTH
THEY'VE BEEN IN NEARLY TWO
DECADES.
NORTH KOREA NOW THREATENING TO
SHOOT THOSE BOMBERS DOWN.
AND AT THE WHITE HOUSE TODAY --
>> WE'VE NOT DECLARED WAR ON
NORTH KOREA, AND FRANKLY THE
SUGGESTION OF THAT IS ABSURD.
>> WOW.
A LOT GOING ON AND LET'S GET TO
MARTHA NOW.
SOME SOBERING WORDS FROM THE
PRESIDENT'S NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER TONIGHT, H.R. McMASTER,
JUST A SHORT TIME AGO.
>> Reporter: YEAH, JUST IN,
DAVID.
HE SAID, WHAT WE HOPE TO DO IS
TO AVOID WAR, BUT WE CANNOT
DISCOUNT THAT POSSIBILITY.
AS YOU SAID, SOBERING.
>> ALL RIGHT, MARTHA RADDATZ.
GOOD TO HAVE YOU HERE TONIGHT.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS MONDAY.
THE DEADLY CHURCH SHOOTING.
AUTHORITIES REVEALING MESSAGES
THE SUSPECT POSTED ONLINE BEFORE
OPENING FIRE.
>>> ALSO, THE PLANE AND THE
SCARE JUST TODAY.
SMOKE FILLING THE CABIN.
PASSENGERS RUSHING TO ESCAPE
THIS FLIGHT.
>>> WE HAVE NEWS TONIGHT ABOUT
ASPIRIN AND YOUR HEART AND THE
POSSIBLE RISK TO PATIENTS WHO
STOP TAKING THAT DAILY DOSE ON
THEIR OWN.
>>> AND THEN THE DEADLY CRASH.
THE MOTHER AND TWO CHILDREN
COLLIDING WITH A POLICE OFFICER
RESPONDING TO EMERGENCY CALL.
QUESTIONS TONIGHT ABOUT WHETHER
THE OFFICER SHOULD BE CHARGED.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
...there's something you
to smay be missing.
A key part of your wellness
that you may be...
...overlooking.
♪
It's your eyes.
That's why there's Ocuvite,
from Bausch + Lomb.
As you age your eyes can lose
vital nutrients.
Ocuvite helps replenish those
nutrients.
Ocuvite has Lutein, Zeaxanthin,
and Omega-3.
Nourish your eyes to help them
be their healthy best.
Ocuvite eye vitamins.
Be good to your eyes.
But he's got work to do.
with a sore back.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
CHURCH SHOOTING IN TENNESSEE.
THE SUSPECT BEHIND BARS.
AND AUTHORITIES NOW SAY HE HAD
BEEN TO THAT CHURCH BEFORE.
HERE'S STEVE OSUNSAMI.
>> Reporter: TENNESSEE POLICE
TONIGHT ARE HOLDING THE ACCUSED
MURDERER, 25-YEAR-OLD EMANUEL
SAMSON, WITHOUT BOND, AND SAY
MORE CHARGES ARE COMING.
>> THIS IS A LEVEL ONE MASS
CASUALTY INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: THEY WERE JUST
GETTING OUT OF SUNDAY SERVICES
AT THIS NASHVILLE CHURCH WHEN
POLICE SAY THE SUDANESE
IMMIGRANT PULLED INTO THE
PARKING LOT WITH THREE PISTOLS
AND A RIFLE.
WITNESSES SAY WHEN 39-YEAR-OLD
MELANIE CROW WALKED OUT, HE
GUNNED HER DOWN.
>> THERE'S NO UNDERSTANDING
EVIL.
THERE'S NO UNDERSTANDING HATE.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY SAMSON
HAD ATTENDED SERVICES AT THE
CHURCH BEFORE.
SIX OTHER PEOPLE, INCLUDING THE
PASTOR, WERE WOUNDED.
>> WE GOT A POSSIBLE SIX
VICTIMS.
THE SUSPECT IS DOWN.
>> Reporter: POLICE HAVE STOPPED
SHORT OF EXPLAINING A MOTIVE,
BUT THEIR REPORTS SAY SAMSON'S
FATHER THOUGHT HE WAS SUICIDAL
IN JULY.
SUNDAY'S SHOOTING WAS STOPPED BY
A CHURCH USHER WHO FOUGHT WITH
HIM.
CALEB ENGLE GOT A GUN FROM HIS
OWN CAR AND HELD HIM UNTIL
.EDPOEIVRR A
USHER SAVED LIVES.
AND THEY'RE CALLING HIM A HERO.
DAVID?
>> STEVE, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
THE MAJOR HEADLINE THIS EVENING
ABOUT ASPIRIN AND YOUR HEART.
>>> AND THEN, THE AIR SCARE
TODAY.
SMOKE SUDDENLY FILLING THE
CABIN.
PASSENGERS HAVING TO ESCAPE.
WE'LL BE BACK.
With my moderate to severe
Crohn's disease,...
...I was always searching for
ways to manage my symptoms.
Then I realized managing was
all I was doing.
When I finally told my doctor,
he said HUMIRA was for people
like me
who have tried other
medications,...
but still experience the
symptoms
of moderate to severe
Crohn's disease.
In clinical studies,
the majority of patients
on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom
relief...
...and many achieved remission.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections...
...including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,...
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,...
...and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested
for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,...
...hepatitis B, are prone to
infections,
...or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
If you're still just managing
your symptoms,
ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA, remission
is possible.
I tabut with my back paines,
I couldn't sleep
and get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
I CAN DO MORE TO LOWER MY A1C.
AND I CAN DO IT WITH
WHAT'S ALREADY WITHIN ME.
BECAUSE MY BODY CAN STILL O IIN
AND ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
ACTIVATES MY BODY TO RELEASE IT.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT COMES IN A ONCE-WEEKLY,
TRULY EASY-TO-USE PEN.
IT WORKS 24/7, AND YOU DON'T
HAVE TO SEE OR HANDLE A NEEDLE.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU HAVE A PERSONAL
OR FAMILY HISTORY OF
MEDULLARY THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU HAVE MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU'RE ALLERGIC
TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE A LUMP OR
SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
SEVERE STOMACH PAIN,
OR SYMPTOMS LIKE ITCHING,
RASH, OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE,
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY WORSEN
KIDNEY PROBLEMS.
I CHOOSE ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY
TO ACTIVATE MY WITHIN.
IF YOU NEED HELP LOWERING
YOUR A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR,
ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
ItThe power of Nexium
24HR protection
from frequent heartburn.
All day, and all night.
Now packed into
a pill so small,
We call it mini.
New ClearMinis from Nexium 24HR.
See Heartburn Differently.
>>> TO THE INDEX.
THE DEADLY POLICE CRASH IN NEW
MEXICO.
VIDEO SHOWING OFFICER JONATHAN
McDONALD SPEEDING TO AN
EMERGENCY CALL IN APRIL,
COLLIDING WITH A MOTHER AND HER
TWO CHILDREN IN THEIR SUV.
HER 6-YEAR-OLD SON DIED THE NEXT
DAY.
McDONALD DRIVING UP TO 80 MILES
PER HOUR.
THE D.A. DECIDING IF HE WILL
FACE CHARGES.
>>> THE PLANE SCARE MOMENTS
R EGTEAFNTINNDLA F G AIRLINES F
FROM VEGAS TAXIING DOWN THE
RUNWAY.
SMOKE FILLING THE CABIN.
PASSENGERS TOLD TO COVER THEIR
FACES.
THE AIRLINE NOW SAYS IT WAS A
MECHANICAL ISSUE.
>> TO ASPIRIN AND HEART DISEASE.
A NEW STUDY SHOWING PATIENTS WHO
TAKE A LOW DOSE ASPIRIN DAILY
FOR AT LEAST ONE YEAR WILL
INCREASE THEIR RISK OF HEART
DISEASE IF THEY STOP ON THEIR
OWN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR FIRST.
THE STUDY APPEARS IN THE JOURNAL
"CIRCULATION."
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
AMAZING FEAT TONIGHT.
THE YOUNG U.S. MARINE THAT JUST
MADE HISTORY.
SHE IS AMERICA STRONG.
♪
Your body was made for better
things than
rheumatoid arthritis.
Before you and your
rheumatologist move to another
treatment, ask if XELJANZ is
right for you.
XELJANZ is a small pill for
adults with
moderate to severe RA for whom
methotrexate did not work well.
XELJANZ can reduce joint pain
and swelling in as little as
two weeks, and help stop further
joint damage.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma and other
cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ if you have
on.
tiannTears in the stomach or
intestines, low blood cell
counts and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you were in
a region where fungal
infections are common and if you
have had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or are prone
to infections.
XELJANZ can reduce the symptoms
of RA,
even without methotrexate, and
is also available
in a once-daily pill.
Ask about XELJANZ XR.
Whstuff happens. old
Shut down cold
symptoms fast
with Maximum Strength
Alka Seltzer Plus
Liquid Gels.
♪
my doctor recommended I
switch laxatives.
Stimulant Laxatives
make your body go
by forcefully stimulating the
nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX is different.
It works with the
water in your body
to hydrate and soften.
Unblocking your
system naturally.
MiraLAX.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
AMERICA STRONG.
FOR THE FIRST TIME IN ITS
242-YEAR HISTORY, THE MARINE
CORPS WELCOMING ITS FIRST FEMALE
INFANTRY OFFICER.
THIS LIEUTENANT MADE HISTORY
TODAY, BECOMING THE FIRST FEMALE
INFANTRY OFFICER IN THE U.S.
MARINE CORPS.
>> NO, WE'RE GOING TO PUSH TO
THE FRONT.
GET YOUR GUN READY TO MOVE.
>> Reporter: THE MARINE CORPS
PUTTING OUT THESE IMAGES.
THAT INFANTRY OFFICER WOULD
RATHER US SKIP HER NAME, ASKING
THAT SHE SIMPLY SERVE WITH HER
FELLOW MARINES.
SHE COMPLETED A GRUELING 13-WEEK
INFANTRY OFFICER COURSE.
THE MARINES ARE TESTED
PHYSICALLY, MENTALLY, AS THEY
COVER MILES OFFER T ER THTERRAI
OBSTACLES.
CARRYING 80 POUNDS OF GEAR FOR
MORE THAN 14 MILES.
IT WAS LESS THAN TWO YEARS AGO,
THE DECISION WAS MADE TO OPEN
ALL COMBAT ROLES TO WOMEN.
THAT LIEUTENANT, THE FIRST
FEMALE TO SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETE
THIS COURSE.
AMERICA STRONG.
AND WE SALUTE HER TONIGHT.
THANKS FOR WATCHING HERE ON A
MONDAY NIGHT.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
UNTIL THEN, GOOD NIGHT.
.
>>> RHETORIC AND REACTION, SEE
WHOSE TALKING AND WHOSE TAKING
FEUD BETWEEN THE PRESIDENT AND
THE PROFESSIONAL
>>> THAT'S GOING TO CAUSE UC
BERKELEY A LOT.
HOW THE UNIVERSITY SAYS BY
PLAYING BY THE ORGANIZATION
SPEECH WEEK.
>>> LOOK WHO TOOK OVER TWITTER
TODAY.
>>> CRITICAL COMMENTS FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP CONTINUES TO
FUEL DIFFERENT TEAMS.
THE DALLAS COWBOYS AND THEIR
OWNER JERRY JONES LINKED
TOGETHER AND TOOK A KNEE JUST
BEFORE THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
I'M CHRISTINE.
>> AND I'M BDAN ASHLEY.
>> PLAYERS KNEELED AND LINKED
ARMS AND IN SOME CASES WERE NOT
ON THE FIELD WHILE THE ANSWER
ANTHEM PLAYED.
THIS WAS IN RESPONSE TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP CALLING THE
PLAYERS WHO PROTEST SOB'S DURING
THE RALLY IN ALABAMA.
AND REACTION HAS BEEN SWIFT FROM
NFL PLAYERS INCLUDING SAN
MATTEO'S OWN T>> IOM CERTAINLY
WHAT HE SAID AND THOUGHT IT WAS
DWOOIF.
>> NO NFL PLAYER COACH OR OWNER
HAS COME OUT IN AGREEMENT WITH
THE PRESIDENT WHO BELIEVES THE
PROTESTERS ARE DISRESPECTING THE
FLAG AND BY EXTENSION, THE
COUNTRY.
>> THE PRESIDENT'S LATEST TWEET
ON THE MATTER REEDS, TREMENDOUS
BACKLASH AGAINST THE NFL AND ITS
PLAYERS FOR DISRESPECT OF OUR
COUNTRY.
>> ALISA HAIRING TON BLINKS THE
LIVE COVERAGE IN ALAMEDA WHO
LOOKS AT SOME PEOPLE WHO ARE