ASSOCIATION.
>> CAN'T EAT HOT DOGS.
THANKS FOR JOINING
>>> TONIGHT, SEVERAL BREAKING
STORIES AS WE COME ON THE AIR.
FIRST, OUR TEAM TAKES YOU INSIDE
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S DECISION TO
STRIKE IN SYRIA.
59 TOMAHAWK MISSILES FIRED FROM
AMERICAN NAVY DESTROYERS,
HITTING SYRIAN MILITARY TARGETS.
WE HAVE NEW DETAILS FROM INSIDE
THE WAR ROOM.
>>> AND THE WARNING FROM RUSSIA
NOW, AND THEIR MESSAGE FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THE HEADLINE LATE TODAY.
SYRIAN PLANES ALREADY TAKING OFF
AGAIN FROM THAT AIRBASE THE U.S.
BOMBED.
>>> ALSO BREAKING TONIGHT, THE
DEADLY TERROR ATTACK.
A TRUCK BARRELING RIGHT INTO A
SHOPPING CENTER.
RUNNING DOWN VICTIMS.
THE GLOBAL BULLETIN.
THE PERSON OF INTEREST.
THE MANHUNT.
AND LATE WORD NOW OF AN ARREST.
WE'RE ON THE SCENE IN SWEDEN.
>>> THE NATIONWIDE MANHUNT HERE
AT HOME.
SCHOOLS SHUT DOWN.
A SUSPECT CONSIDERED "EXTREMELY
DANGEROUS."
POLICE SAY HE MADE THIS VIDEO
MAILING A MESSAGE TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
>>> AND THE PICTURES COMING IN
NOW.
THE FIRES BREAKING OUT ALONG
THIS HIGHWAY IN FLORIDA DURING
SPRING BREAK.
THOUSANDS OF ACRES ALREADY
>>> GOOD EVENING.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US
HERE ON A VERY BUSY FRIDAY
NIGHT.
WE'RE GETTING A MUCH CLEARER
PICTURE OF WHAT LED TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S ORDER TO TAKE MILITARY
ACTION AGAINST SYRIA.
LAST NIGHT, THE WORLD SAW THE
MISSILE STRIKE IN SYRIA, MORE
THAN 50 TOMAHAWK MISSILES FIRED.
IT CAME JUST TWO DAYS AFTER THE
HORRIFIC CHEMICAL ATTACK ON
FAMILIES, SO MANY CHILDREN AMONG
THE VICTIMS.
OFFICIALS SAY THEY HAVE PROOF
THE PLANE THAT DROPPED THAT
TOXIC GAS WAS A SYRIAN FIGHTER
JET THAT TOOK OFF FROM THIS
BASE.
AND NOW, WORD THAT SYRIAN PLANES
ARE TAKING OFF FROM THAT
AIRFIELD ALL OVER AGAIN.
HERE'S MARTHA RADDATZ, LEADING
US OFF.
>> Reporter: UNDER THE COVER OF
DARKNESS, DOZENS OF U.S.
TOMAHAWK CRUISE MISSILES FIRED
INTO SYRIA FROM TWO NAVY
WARSHIPS IN THE MEDITERRANEAN.
RAINING DOWN ON THE SHAYRAT
AIRBASE, WHERE THE SYRIAN PLANE
CARRYING THOSE CHEMICAL WEAPONS
HAD TAKEN OFF.
THE CRUISE MISSILES ALREADY
LAUNCHED AS THE PRESIDENT WAS
WRAPPING UP HIS FIRST DINNER
WITH THE CHINESE PRESIDENT AT
MAR-A-LAGO.
HOURS EARLIER, ABOARD AIR FORCE
ONE, PRESIDENT TRUMP HAD
SIGNALED TO THE WORLD THAT
MILITARY ACTION AGAINST SYRIA
WAS A STRONG POSSIBILITY.
>> I THINK WHAT HAPPENED IN
SYRIA IS A DISGRACE TO HUMANITY.
AND HE'S THERE, AND I GUESS HE'S
RUNNING THINGS.
SO SOMETHING SHOULD HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: SOON AFTER LANDING
IN FLORIDA, THE PRESIDENT WOULD
GIVE HIS COMMANDERS THE GREEN
LIGHT.
THE PENTAGON USING MILITARY
CHANNELS TO LET THE RUSSIANS
KNOW, THIS WAS NOT AN ATTACK ON
THEIR TROOPS AND AIRCRAFT IN
SYRIA.
SYRIAN TELEVISION SHOWING WHAT
IT SAID WAS THE U.S. ASSAULT IN
THE DISTANCE.
SYRIAN OFFICIALS CLAIMING AT
LEAST SEVEN WERE KILLED.
THE PENTAGON SAYS IT STRUCK ALL
59 OF ITS TARGETS.
DESTROYING AT LEAST 20 SYRIAN
AIRCRAFT, AIR DEFENSE SYSTEMS,
RADAR AND AMMUNITION SUPPLY
BUNKERS.
ONCE THOSE MISSILES FELL, THE
PRESIDENT HUDDLED WITH HIS
NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM TO ASSESS
THE DAMAGE.
THE RETALIATION COMING JUST 60
HOURS AFTER THE WORLD SAW THE
FIRST HORRIFIC IMAGES OF THAT
CHEMICAL ATTACK, IMAGES THAT
PUSHED THE PRESIDENT TO ACT.
>> TONIGHT, I ORDERED A TARGETED
MILITARY STRIKE ON THE AIRFIELD
IN SYRIA FROM WHERE THE CHEMICAL
ATTACK WAS LAUNCHED.
>> Reporter: THE PENTAGON
PROVIDING EVIDENCE IT SAYS SHOWS
ASSAD WAS BEHIND THE WAR CRIME.
THE FLIGHT PATH DATA OF THE
SYRIAN WARPLANE.
AND TONIGHT, THE U.S. MILITARY
LOOKING INTO WHETHER THE
RUSSIANS KNEW ABOUT THAT
CHEMICAL ATTACK OR ASSISTED IN
ANY WAY.
TODAY AT THE UNITED NATIONS,
AMBASSADOR NIKKI HALEY WARNED
THAT THE U.S. COULD STRIKE
AGAIN.
>> THE UNITED STATES TOOK A VERY
MEASURED STEP LAST NIGHT.
WE ARE PREPARED TO DO MORE.
>> SO LET'S BRING IN MARTHA,
LIVE IN WASHINGTON.
WE'RE LEARNING TONIGHT AS WE
COME ON THAT THE RUSSIANS HAVE
SUSPENDED THE HOTLINE THAT HAD
BEEN SET UP BETWEEN THE RUSSIANS
AND THE PENTAGON INVOLVING
AIRCRAFT OVER SYRIA?
>> Reporter: THE HOTLINE WAS SET
UP TO DECONFLICT THE AIRCRAFT
FLYING MISSIONS OVER SYRIA, SO
THE U.S. AND RUSSIAN AIRCRAFT
DON'T RUN INTO EACH OTHER.
BUT THERE ARE RADARS AND OTHER
BACKUPS.
SO THERE IS NOT A GREAT DEAL OF
CONCERN.
BUT ANOTHER SIGN, THE RUSSIANS
ARE NOT HAPPY WITH THE AMERICAN
ATTACKS ON SYRIA.
>> MARTHA, THANK YOU.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE SAYING THIS
WAS A CAREFULLY TARGETED STRIKE,
AIMED TO SEND A CLEAR MESSAGE.
I WANT TO BRING IN RETIRED
COLONEL STEPHEN GANYARD, WHO HAS
FLOWN OVER THAT REGION.
59 TOMAHAWK MISSILES WERE
LAUNCHED FROM THE MEDITERRANEAN,
AND GUIDED BY ADVANCED
NAVIGATION SYSTEMS TO AVOID
DETECTION?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
THE MISSILES DROP DOWN LOW.
THEY FLEW OVER THE MEDITERRANEAN
SEA FOR SOMEWHERE BETWEEN 30
MINUTES AND AN HOUR.
AND PROBABLY CAME ASHORE OVER
LEBANON TO AVOID SOME OF THE
SURFACE TO AIR MISSILE SYSTEMS
THE RUSSIANS HAVE IN THE
NORTHWEST OF THE COUNTRY.
AND WENT NORTH, WENT AFTER 59
CAREFULLY PICKED TARGETS AROUND
THE AIRFIELD.
>> JUST 30 TO 40 MINUTES,
INCREDIBLE SPEED.
AND TAKE US DEEPER INTO THE
MILITARY CHOICE THEY MADE HERE.
WE KNOW PRESIDENT OBAMA
CONSIDERED MILITARY ACTION AFTER
THE CHEMICAL ATTACK IN 2013.
PARTS OF THAT PLAN WERE FAR MORE
INVOLVED THAN WHAT WE SAW
OVERNIGHT.
>> THE PENTAGON OFFERED
PRESIDENT TRUMP SEVERAL CHOICES.
HE COULD GO WITH A LARGE STRIKE
WITH A SUSTAINED CAMPAIGN, OR
SOMETHING VERY FOCUSED THAT
WOULD SEND A MESSAGE.
HE KNEW HE WOULD NOT OVERTHROW
ASSAD, BUT WAS MAKING A VERY
CLEAR STATEMENT, SAYING YOU NEED
TO STOP GASSING YOUR PEOPLE, OR
WE'LL BE BACK IN A BIG WAY.
>> COLONEL GANYARD, THANK YOU.
>>> AND THIS EVENING, WE'RE ALSO
LEARNING WHO WAS IN THE WAR ROOM
AS THIS UNFOLDED.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS HOSTING
CHINA'S PRESIDENT.
AND WE HAVE LEARNED THE MOMENT
HE TOLD PRESIDENT XI WHAT WAS
HAPPENING.
JONATHAN KARL HAS THE STORY.
>> Reporter: THAT IMAGE OF THE
PRESIDENT GETTING HIS FIRST
REPORTS ON THE SYRIAN AIR
STRIKES.
A PORTRAIT OF A NEW COMMANDER IN
CHIEF AND HIS NATIONAL SECURITY
TEAM.
AT THE TABLE, HIS SON-IN-LAW
JARED KUSHNER.
ALSO PRESENT, BUT TAKING A BACK
SEAT, RECENTLY DEMOTED CHIEF
STRATEGIST STEVE BANNON.
THE PHOTO EDITED.
THE PAPERS MADE BLANK, TO
PROTECT CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
IT'S A REMARKABLE TURN FOR A MAN
WHO HAS CONSISTENTLY URGED AN
AMERICA FIRST APPROACH TO WAR
AND PEACE.
SYRIA, HE ONCE SAID, IS NOT
AMERICA'S PROBLEM.
BUT THIS WEEK, THE PRESIDENT SAW
THOSE IMAGES.
THE HORRORS OF CHILDREN HIT WITH
DEADLY NERVE GAS.
>> I WILL TELL YOU, THAT ATTACK
ON CHILDREN YESTERDAY HAD A BIG
IMPACT ON ME.
BIG IMPACT.
>> Reporter: IN TAKING THIS
ACTION, TRUMP SEEMED MORE LIKE
HILLARY CLINTON, WHO HAD URGED
PRESIDENT OBAMA TO ACT IN SYRIA.
AND JUST HOURS BEFORE TRUMP
ORDERED THE AIR STRIKES, MRS.
CLINTON BASICALLY ENDORSED THE
MOVE AGAINST BASHAR AL ASSAD.
>> I REALLY BELIEVE THAT WE
SHOULD HAVE AND STILL SHOULD
TAKE OUT HIS AIRFIELDS AND
PREVENT HIM FROM BEING ABLE TO
USE THEM TO BOMB INNOCENT PEOPLE
AND DROP SARIN GAS ON THEM.
SO --
>> Reporter: THE AIR STRIKE
COMES AMID NEW PROVOCATIONS FROM
NORTH KOREA, AND ON THE SAME DAY
TRUMP WAS MEETING WITH CHINA'S
PRESIDENT XI JINPING.
AT THE END OF THEIR FORMAL
DINNER, PRESIDENT TRUMP INFORMED
PRESIDENT XI ABOUT HIS MILITARY
ATTACK.
NOT LONG AGO, TRUMP CALLED CHINA
A JOB-KILLING ENEMY OF AMERICA.
TODAY, THAT TALK WAS GONE.
REPLACED BY SOMETHING CLOSER TO
FRIENDSHIP.
>> THE RELATIONSHIP DEVELOPED BY
PRESIDENT XI AND MYSELF I THINK
IS OUTSTANDING.
WE LOOK FORWARD TO BEING
TOGETHER MANY TIMES IN THE
FUTURE.
>> Reporter: BUT THE
ADMINISTRATION'S TONE IS ALSO
CHANGING TOWARDS ANOTHER WORLD
POWER -- RUSSIA.
CANDIDATE TRUMP OFTEN TALKED OF
PARTNERING WITH VLADIMIR PUTIN.
BUT NOW SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON BLAMED RUSSIA IN PART
FOR THE ACTIONS OF ITS ALLY
SYRIA, SAYING RUSSIA WAS EITHER
COMPLICIT IN THE CHEMICAL ATTACK
P JUST INCOMPETENT.A TH THE
RESIDENT.
WE HEARD AMBASSADOR HALEY SAYING
WE'RE PREPARED TO DO MORE.
AND STRONG WORDS TONIGHT FROM
SECRETARY OF STATE TILLERSON.
HE'S HEADING TO RUSSIA NEXT
WEEK?
>> Reporter: YES, THIS WILL BE
THE HIGHEST-LEVEL TRUMP OFFICIAL
TO VISIT MOSCOW YET.
AND THE BIG TEST OVER WHETHER
THIS DISAGREEMENT WILL END HOPES
OF A WARMER RELATIONSHIP WITH
VLADIMIR PUTIN.
>> JON, THANK YOU.
>>> AND TONIGHT, RUSSIA, WITH A
WARNING FOR THE UNITED STATES.
AND A MESSAGE AIMED AT PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS CALLING WHAT
THEY SAW LAST NIGHT, A CLEAR ACT
OF AGGRESSION.
TESTING WHAT JON JUST POINTED
OUT, HOPE FOR A BETTER
RELATIONSHIP WITH VLADIMIR
PUTIN.
HERE'S BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: THE RUSSIAN
PROPAGANDA MACHINE IS WORKING
OVERTIME TONIGHT.
RUSSIAN TV OUTLETS QUICKLY
DISTRIBUTED THIS FOOTAGE OF WHAT
IT CALLED THE FAILED U.S.
ATTACK.
A REPORTER INSIDE A FORTIFIED
HANGAR, DAMAGED BUT STILL
STANDING.
FIVE JET FIGHTERS SEEMINGLY
UNTOUCHED.
AND THE RUNWAY WITH NO APPARENT
DAMAGE, WHERE THE TWO JETS TOOK
OFF TODAY, LESS THAN 24 HOURS
AFTER THE ATTACK.
THE RUSSIAN PRIME MINISTER
TAKING TO FACEBOOK TO SAY HIS
COUNTRY'S HIGH HOPES FOR DONALD
TRUMP HAD BEEN SMASHED, THAT IT
TOOK ONLY 2 1/2 MONTHS FOR
"TRUMP'S ELECTION PROMISES" TO
BE BROKEN "BY THE EXISTING POWER
MACHINE."
>> LOOK, HEY, PUTIN LIKES ME.
>> Reporter: IT WASN'T THAT LONG
AGO THAT TRUMP HAD NOTHING BUT
PRAISE FOR RUSSIA.
>> I THINK I'D GET ALONG WITH
HIM.
I RESPECT PUTIN.
HE'S A STRONG LEADER.
>> Reporter: BUT NOW THE TRUMP
LOVE AFFAIR WITH RUSSIA SEEMS TO
BE OVER, AT LEAST BASED ON THE
WORDS TODAY OF HIS AMBASSADOR TO
THE UNITED NATIONS WHO CALLED
RUSSIA EITHER COMPLICIT,
INCOMPETENT OR --
>> IT COULD BE THAT THE ASSAD
REGIME IS PLAYING THE RUSSIANS
FOR FOOLS.
>> Reporter: IN RESPONSE, RUSSIA
AND SYRIA SAID THE U.S. ATTACK
ONLY HELPED ISIS AND OTHER
TERRORISTS WHO ARE FIGHTING
AGAINST THE ASSAD REGIME IN
SYRIA.
>> IT MAKES THE UNITED STATES OF
AMERICA A PARTNER OF ISIL, JABRA
AL NUSRA AND OTHER TERRORIST
GROUPS.
>> Reporter: BUT THE U.S. SAYS
THERE IS NO DOUBT OF THE ROLE OF
SYRIA IN THE HORRIFIC CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
>> BRIAN, WE KNOW OFFICIALS AT
THE PENTAGON REVEALED ON THE
SAME DAY OF THE ATTACK, A
HOSPITAL TREATING VICTIMS WAS
HIT BY A SECOND BOMB ATTACK, A
MORE CONVENTIONAL BOMB, IN THIS
CASE.
WAS IT THE RUSSIANS?
>> THAT'S THE QUESTION.
THEY'RE LOOKING AT THIS VIDEO
YOU SEE HERE.
INSIDE THE HOSPITAL, THE BOMB
WENT OFF.
THE PENTAGON LOOKING CLOSELY.
THEY KNOW IT WAS A RUSSIAN JET,
THEY DON'T KNOW WHO WAS PILOTING
IT, BUT THEY CAN'T RULE OUT THAT
IT WAS A RUSSIAN PILOT.
AND IT WAS REPORTED TWO MORE
JETS TOOK OFF FROM THAT AIRFIELD
TODAY.
>> BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> WE MOVE ON TO THE OTHER
MAJOR STORY DEVELOPING AT THIS
HOUR.
THE DEADLY TRUCK ATTACK IN
SWEDEN, WITH ALL THE HALLMARKS
OF TERRORISM.
THE ATTACKER USING A STOLEN
TRUCK, SPEEDING FOR BLOCKS DOWN
A CROWDED PEDESTRIAN MALL,
SLAMMING INTO A DEPARTMENT
STORE.
PEOPLE RUNNING FOR THEIR LIVES.
TONIGHT, AN ARREST HAS BEEN
MADE.
WAS THIS THE MAN BEHIND THE
WHEEL?
TERRY MORAN ON THE SCENE IN
STOCKHOLM.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, SHOPPERS
IN DISBELIEF, THEN PANIC.
THE TRUCK BARRELING THROUGH THE
SHOPPING DISTRICT.
POLICE SCOURING VIDEOS SEARCHING
FOR CLUES.
THIS VIDEO SHOWS THE TRUCK
MOWING DOWN PEDESTRIANS,
CRASHING INTO THIS DEPARTMENT
STORE.
THICK, BLACK SMOKE BILLOWING
OUT.
AT LEAST FOUR DEAD, MORE THAN A
DOZEN INJURED.
NINE OF THEM CRITICAL.
AT THIS HOUR, A NATIONWIDE
MANHUNT IS UNDER WAY.
POLICE REPORTING ONE ARREST HAS
BEEN MADE HERE, 20 MILES AWAY
FROM THE CRIME SCENE.
A MAN WHO MATCHES THESE PHOTOS
ON AN ESCALATOR WEARING A HOODIE
AND BLACK PANTS.
SWEDEN'S PRIME MINISTER, WITH
REPORTERS HERE, SAYING SWEDEN
HAS BEEN ATTACKED.
EVERYTHING INDICATES THIS HAS
BEEN A TERRORIST ACT.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE CARNAGE
BEGAN JUST BEFORE 3:00 P.M.
TODAY.
A BEER DELIVERY TRUCK WAS
HIJACKED BY A MAN IN A MASK, AND
THEN HE DROVE ABOUT 1,600 FEET
RIGHT TOWARDS SHOPPERS BEFORE
CRASHING.
FROM AN OFFICE WINDOW, SO MANY
COULD BE SEEN FLEEING FOR THEIR
LIVES.
ON THE GROUND, ARMED OFFICERS
WERE TRYING TO CONTROL THE
CHAOS.
AT THE GRIM SCENE, THE TIRE
MARKS COULD BE SEEN IN THE BLOOD
IN THE IMMEDIATE AFTERMATH OF
THE ATTACK, AS SHOPPERS TEND TO
THE INJURED.
FIREFIGHTERS DOUSE THE FLAME,
ALLOWING POLICE TO SEARCH THE
SCENE.
WITNESSES DESCRIBE THE PANIC AND
TERROR.
>> YOU CAN SEE BODIES LYING ON
THE STREET.
POLICE COVERING THE BODIES WITH
AN ORANGE BLANKET.
>> A HORRIFIC SCENE.
TERRY MORAN JOINS US.
POLICE STILL AT THE SCENE AT
THIS HOUR, AND A WARNING FOR
AMERICANS TONIGHT?
>> Reporter: THEY ARE.
THEY HAVE OPENED THE STREETS,
AND AT THIS MOMENT, THEY'RE
REMOVING THE TRUCK FROM THE
DEPARTMENT STORE IT RAMMED.
THE U.S. DEPARTMENT OF HOMELAND
SECURITY HAS BEEN WARNING
AMERICANS TO BE VIGILANT FOR
MONTHS ABOUT THESE SO-CALLED
RAMMING ATTACKS.
SO CHEAP, SO SIMPLE, SO DEADLY.
>> TERRY, THANK YOU.
>>> BACK HOME TO AMERICA, THE
SENATE CONFIRMING SUPREME COURT
NOMINEE NEIL GORSUCH.
AFTER A BITTER PARTISAN BATTLE.
REPUBLICANS USING THE NUCLEAR
OPTION.
ENDING MORE THAN A YEAR OF
FIGHTING TO FILL THE VACANT
SEAT.
GORSUCH SCHEDULED TO BE SWORN IN
ON MONDAY.
>>> THERE'S STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS FRIDAY.
THE NATIONWIDE MANHUNT IN THIS
COUNTRY.
SCHOOLS SHUT DOWN.
THE SUSPECT ALLEGEDLY ROBBING A
GUN STORE.
CONSIDERED EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
POLICE SAYING HE MADE THIS
VIDEO, MAILING A MESSAGE TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>>> THE POLICE OFFICER KILLED
WHILE REPORTING TO DUTY.
INVESTIGATORS NOW BELIEVE THE
SUSPECT SCOUTED THE SCENE THE
DAY BEFORE THE SHOOTING.
>>> AND PICTURES COMING IN AT
THIS HOUR.
THE WILDFIRE BREAKING OUT ALONG
THIS HIGHWAY IN FLORIDA, RIGHT
DURING SPRING BREAK.
SO MANY VACATIONERS.
THOUSANDS OF ACRES ALREADY
DESTROYED.
EVACUATIONS UNDER WAY AT THIS
HOUR.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
the market.redict
But through good
times and bad...
...at T. Rowe Price...
...we've helped
our investors
stay confident for
over 75 years.
Call us or
your advisor.
T. Rowe Price.
Invest With Confidence.
Hey Scout, what's with the
itchys and scratchys?
It's these fleas and ticks.
OW!
I'm getting bit like crazy.
Got any ideas for me?
Well, not all products
work the same.
That's why my owner
gives me K9 Advantix II.
It kills fleas,
ticks and mosquitoes.
Mosquitoes too?
Yep kills all three
through contact --
no biting required.
Wish my owner knew about
K9 Advantix II. Ow!
Well...could be worse.
Ooh. Glorious.
Protect against the bites
that can spread disease.
K9 Advantix II. Wise choice.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, A NATIONWIDE
ALERT FOR A SUSPECT CONSIDERED
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
SCHOOLS SHUT DOWN.
THE SUSPECT LAST SEEN IN
WISCONSIN, LEAVING A TRAIL OF
EVIDENCE.
HERE'S PIERRE THOMAS.
>> Reporter: THIS IS JOSEPH
JAKUBOWSKI, SEEN HERE IN A
DISTURBING VIDEO POSTED TO HIS
SOCIAL MEDIA ACCOUNT.
>> WILL NEVER FORGET THIS FACE,
EVER.
>> Reporter: A MAN WANTED BY
WISCONSIN POLICE AND THE FBI,
AND BELIEVED TO BE PLOTTING AN
ACT OF MASS VIOLENCE.
>> HE FEELS THAT GOVERNMENT AND
LAW ENFORCEMENT IN PARTICULAR
ARE ACTING AS TERRORISTS AND ARE
ENSLAVING THE PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY YOU CAN
SEE HIM IN THIS SURVEILLANCE
PHOTO, STEALING 16 FIREARMS FROM
THE ARMAGEDDON GUN SHOP BEFORE
SETTING HIS CAR ON FIRE AND
DISAPPEARING.
150 LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS
NOW ENGAGED IN AN URGENT
MANHUNT, SAYING HE IS APPARENTLY
FIXATED ON PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HERE HE IS ACTUALLY MAILING A
161-PAGE ANTIGOVERNMENT
MANIFESTO TO THE PRESIDENT.
POLICE SO CONCERNED THEY SHUT
DOWN LOCAL SCHOOLS AFTER HE
ALLEGEDLY MADE THREATS AGAINST
THEM TOO.
TONIGHT AUTHORITIES SAY
JAKUBOWSKI COULD BE ANYWHERE.
SO THIS IS A NOW A NATIONWIDE
MANHUNT, AND THE FBI IS ASKING
FOR THE PUBLIC'S HELP.
DAVID?
>> PIERRE, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
EVACUATIONS AT THIS HOUR.
THE WILDFIRE DESTROYING
THOUSANDS OF ACRES IN FLORIDA.
RIGHT DURING SPRING BREAK.
>>> AND NEWS ABOUT A POLICE
OFFICER AMBUSHED WHILE SHOWING
UP TO WORK.
NEW SURVEILLANCE VIDEO NOW IN.
d.
Because as we live longer...
And markets continue to
rise and fall...
Predictable is one thing you
need in retirement
to help protect what you've
earned and ensure it lasts.
Introducing
Brighthouse Financial.
A new company established
by MetLife
to specialize in annuities
& life insurance.
Talk to your advisor about a
brighter financial future.
We can't stay here!
Why?
Terrible toilet paper!
I'll never get clean!
Way ahead of you.
Charmin Ultra Strong.
It cleans better.
It's four times stronger...
...and you can use less.
Enjoy the go with Charmin.
(de♪p breath)
(phone ringing)
They'll call back.
No one knows your Ford better
than Ford and Ford Service.
Right now, during
The Big Tire Event,
get a $140 rebate by mail,
on four select tires.
♪
As after a DVT blood clot,ital
I sure had a lot
to think about.
What about the
people I care about?
...including this little girl.
And what if this
happened again?
I was given warfarin
in the hospital,
but wondered, was this the
best treatment for me?
So I asked my doctor.
And he recommended ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots
and reduces the risk of
them happening again.
Yes, ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots.
ELIQUIS also had
significantly
less major
bleeding
than the
standard
treatment.
Both made me
turn around my
thinking.
Don't stop ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal injection
while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling,
numbness, or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
...and it may take longer
than usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned
medical or dental
procedures.
ELIQUIS treats
DVT and PE
blood clots.
Plus had
less major
bleeding.
Both made ELIQUIS
the right treatment for me.
Ask your doctor if switching
to ELIQUIS is right for you.
gave us the power to turn this
enemy into an ally?
Microsoft and its partners are
using smart traps to capture
mosquitoes and sequence their
DNA to fight disease.
There are over 100 million
pieces of DNA in every sample.
With the Microsoft Cloud,
we can analyze the data
faster than ever before.
If we can detect new viruses
before they spread,
we may someday prevent outbreaks
before they begin.
>>> TO THE "INDEX."
NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN THE MANHUNT
FOR THE SUSPECTED KILLER OF A
POLICE OFFICER NEAR HOUSTON.
ASSISTANT CHIEF DEPUTY CLINTON
GREENWOOD AMBUSHED BY A GUNMAN
OUTSIDE THE COURTHOUSE.
POLICE NOW RELEASING
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO SHOWING THE
ALLEGED GUNMAN AT THE COURTHOUSE
THE DAY BEFORE THE SHOOTING.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE SAME PERSON
AND THE SAME CAR WERE ALSO SEEN
IN THE PARKING LOT MOMENTS AFTER
THE SHOOTING.
>>> EVACUATIONS IN PARTS OF
FLORIDA.
FLAMES BURNING ACROSS 5,000
ACRES IN BROWARD COUNTY.
FAMILIES AND TOURISTS
EVACUATING.
FIRE AND SMOKE CLOSING IN ON THE
HIGHWAYS AND NEARBY CAMPGROUNDS.
>>> BETTER NEWS FROM CALIFORNIA
TONIGHT.
THE HISTORIC DROUGHT IS
OFFICIALLY OVER.
GOVERNOR JERRY BROWN TODAY
LIFTING EMERGENCY WATER
RESTRICTIONS.
THE FIVE-YEAR DROUGHT CRIPPLING
THE STATE, AFFECTING DRINKING
WATER, FARM PRODUCTION AND
KILLING ABOUT 100 MILLION TREES.
ANY BONE-DRY RESERVOIRS NOW
FILLED TO CAPACITY.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
MOMENT ON STAGE THAT STUNNED AN
ENTIRE AUDIENCE.
WHO IS OUR PERSON OF THE WEEK?
I realize that ah,
that $100K is not
exactly a fortune.
Well, a 103
How long did it take you two
to save that?
A long time.
Then it's a fortune.
I told you we had a fortune.
Get closer to your
investment goals
with a conversation.
...studying to be a dentist
and she gave me advice.
She said Dad...
... Go Pro with
Crest Pro-Health.
4 out of 5 dentists
confirm these
Crest Pro-Health products...
&help maintain a
professional clean.
Crest Pro-Health...
...really brought my mouth...
...to the next lev
Go Pro with Crest Pro-Health
WHY PAUSE A
SPONTANEOUS MOMENT?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
or how high the pollen count,
Flonase Allergy Relief
keeps your eyes and nose clear.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause nasal congestion
and itchy, watery eyes.
For relief beyond the nose.
Flonase.
nitrites or artificial Mesquite
preservatives.added nitrates,
Now it's good for us all.
Like introverts.
Extroverts.
(Cheering)
And even Bert.
Man you gotta' try this
sandwich.
Who's just overt.
Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
So good!
My belly pain
I could build a small city
with all the over-the-counter
products I've used.
Enough!
I've tried enough laxatives
to cover
the Eastern Seaboard.
I've climbed a Mount Everest
of fiber.
Probiotics?
Enough!
(AVO)
If you've had enough,
tell your doctor
what you've tried
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults
with IBS with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help
relieve your belly pain,
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.
Do not give LINZESS
to children under six,
and it should not be given
to children
six to less than eighteen.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS if you have
a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop unusual
or severe stomach pain,
especially with bloody
or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor right away.
Other side effects include gas,
stomach-area pain
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
>>> FINALLY, OUR PERSON OF THE
WEEK.
THE DEVOTED MOM MAKING GOOD ON A
PROMISE.
YVONNE LLANES OF SAN ANTONIO WAS
A TEACHER, A PRINCIPAL.
SHE IS A DEVOTED MOM OF FOUR.
NEARLY 12 YEARS AGO, A FREAK
ACCIDENT CHANGED HER LIFE.
LEAVING HER WITH INJURIES SO
SERIOUS, BOTH OF HER LEGS NEEDED
TO BE AMPUTATED ABOVE THE KNEE.
SHE NEEDED TO USE A WHEELCHAIR.
>> I WAS JUST DEPRESSED, SAD.
I WAS MAD AT THE WORLD.
AND I WANTED MY LIFE BACK.
I WANTED MY LEGS BACK.
>> Reporter: AFTER NEARLY TEN
YEARS IN THAT WHEELCHAIR, A
PROMISE TO HER LATE FATHER
BROUGHT HER HERE.
THE HANGAR CLINIC'S BOOT CAMP
FOR AMPUTEES IN OKLAHOMA CITY.
>> I MET A GROUP OF AMAZING
AMPUTEES.
THEY WERE UP AND THEY WERE
WALKING AND THEY WERE OUT OF
THEIR WHEELCHAIRS.
AND I WAS JUST INCREDIBLY AMAZED
AND I TOLD MYSELF, I WANT TO BE
LIKE THEM.
>> Reporter: AND SHE WAS ON HER
WAY.
STOMACH CRUNCHES, PART OF THE
WORKOUT.
WEARING PROSTHETIC LEGS.
AND AFTER MONTHS OF
DETERMINATION AND HARD WORK, SHE
WAS DETERMINED TO GET OUT OF
THAT CHAIR HERSELF.
>> I HAD SAT IN THAT THING FOR
NINE YEARS AND SEVEN MONTHS.
I WAS GOING TO GET UP AND GET ON
WITH LIFE.
>> Reporter: JUST THIS WEEK,
YVONNE WAS BACK AT THAT CLINIC.
THIS TIME, SHE'S THE ONE
INSPIRING OTHERS.
>> I WANT TO BE ABLE TO SHOW
PEOPLE THAT IT'S NEVER TOO LATE
TO GET UP AND LIVE OUT YOUR
DREAMS.
>> AND SO WE CHOOSE YVONNE
LLANES.
WE NEEDED THAT TONIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> ON THE RADAR, RAIN, BUT IT'S
WHAT YOU CAN'T SEE THAT POSES
THE BIGGEST WEATHER THREAT
TONIGHT.
>>> THIS MUD HAS MADE OAKLAND
HOMES UNINHABITABLE AND IT MAY
BE A LONG TIME BEFORE PEOPLE CAN
MOVE BACK IN.
>>> SOMEWHERE UNDER THE WATERS
OF THE BAY LIES A SUNK BARGE
NAMED "VENGEANCE."
>>> WE WENT FROM CLOUDS TO
SHOWERS THAT YOU CAN SEE IN THIS
LIVE VIEW FROM MT. TAN AND IT IS
SPREADING ACROSS THE BAY AREA.
ONE LIKE LOOK AT THE CONDITIONS
MAKINGS IT CLEAR IF YOU'RE NOT
ALREADY IN THE SIERRA, BETTER
NOT DRIVE.
>> THIS IS THE SECOND OF TWO
DAYS OF STORMS AND THE GOOD NEWS
IS IT WON'T LAST MUCH LONG EVER.
ABC7 NEWS WEATHER ANCHOR SPENCER
CHRISTIAN IS TRACKING THE WORST
OF IT NOW.
>> WE HAVE A SURGE OF STORMY
WEATHER MOVING ONSHORE RIGHT
NOW.
WE HAVE GOT SCATTERED DOWNMORES
MOVING ACROSS THE BAY TO OAKLAND
AND HAYWARD AND SAN LEANDRO, SO
WE HAVE GOT OUR NEXT STORM AND
THE WINDS ARE BEGINNING TO GET A
LITTLE GUSTY AS WELL.
WE HAVE GOT GUSTS ACROSS MUCH OF
THE BAY AREA RIGHT NOW.
THIS ONE RANKS ONE ON THE STORM
IMPACT SCALE.
RAINFALL AMOUNTS WILL BE LESS
THAN HALF AN INCH FOR MOST OF
THE BAY AREA, GUSTS COULD REACH
50 MILES AN HOUR IN THE HILLS.
HERE'S THE FORECAST ANIMATION,
STARTING AT 7:00 THIS EVENING,
NOTICE THAT WE'LL CONTINUE TO
SEE WAVES AND SOME HEAVY
DOWNPOURS AT TIMES, AGAIN,
MAINLY IN THE NORTH BAY, AND
DOWN INTO THE