>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS AS WE
COME ON, WHAT COULD BE A NEW
BOMBSHELL.
DID PRESIDENT TRUMP ASK FORMER
FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY -- TO
SHUT DOWN THE FEDERAL
INVESTIGATION INTO RETIRED
GENERAL MICHAEL FLYNN, THE
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER WHO
SURVIVED JUST 24 DAYS ON THE
JOB.
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" REPORTING
MOMENTS AGO, THE PRESIDENT SAID
TO COMEY, "I HOPE YOU CAN LET
THIS GO."
COMEY WAS FIRED LAST WEEK.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, THE WHITE
HOUSE, REFUSING TO SAY WHETHER
PRESIDENT TRUMP GAVE THE
RUSSIANS CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
TONIGHT, WHAT THE PRESIDENT IS
NOW SAYING HIMSELF.
>>> IN OTHER NEWS, THE DEADLY
HIGHWAY COLLISION IN THE EAST,
ALONG I-95.
SEVERAL BIG RIGS AND CARS
COLLIDING, THE CHARRED WRECKAGE.
THE HIGHWAY SHUT DOWN.
>>> THE TORNADO THREAT AS WE
COME ON TONIGHT.
ONE ON THE GROUND JUST A SHORT
TIME AGO.
MILLIONS IN THE PATH OF THE
STORMS TONIGHT.
>>> AND THE NEW CAFFEINE
CONCERN.
THE 16-YEAR-OLD WHO HAD A
COFFEE, AND SEVERAL OTHER DRINKS
WITH CAFFEINE, THE CORONER WHO
SAYS IT KILLED HIM.
THE NEW WARNING, HOW MUCH
CAFFEINE IS TOO MUCH.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A TUESDAY NIGHT.
>>> AND WE BEGIN WITH THAT
BREAKING HEADLINE AS WE COME ON
THE AIR.
TONIGHT, OUR TEAM NOW CONFIRMING
A REPORT LATE TODAY IN "THE NEW
YORK TIMES" THAT FIRED FBI
DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY WROTE A
MEMO, DOCUMENTING SOME OF HIS
INTERACTION WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
AND TONIGHT, THIS QUESTION, DID
THE PRESIDENT ASK JAMES COMEY
TO, QUOTE, LET THIS GO, WHILE
TALKING ABOUT THE INVESTIGATION
INTO THIS MAN, RETIRED GENERAL
MICHAEL FLYNN, AND RUSSIA.
FLYNN OF COURSE RESIGNED JUST A
FEW DAYS INTO THE
ADMINISTRATION.
COMEY WAS FIRED ONE WEEK AGO
TONIGHT.
ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, ANOTHER
BOMBSHELL AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
ABC NEWS CONFIRMS PRESIDENT
TRUMP ALLEGEDLY SUGGESTED FORMER
FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY SHUT
DOWN HIS INVESTIGATION INTO
FORMER NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER
MICHAEL FLYNN.
A SOURCE CLOSE TO COMEY TELLS
ABC NEWS, COMEY WROTE A MEMO IN
FEBRUARY THE DAY AFTER FLYNN WAS
FIRED.
I HOPE YOU CAN LET THIS GO, THE
PRESIDENT ALLEGEDLY TOLD COMEY.
ACCORDING TO THE SOURCE, HE IS A
GOOD GUY, I HOPE YOU CAN LET
THIS GO.
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" WHO FIRST
REPORTED THE MEMO SAYS IT WAS
PART OF A PAPER TRAIL COMEY
WANTED TO LEAVE BEHIND AS
EVIDENCE INTO WHAT HE CALLED
IMPROPER INFLUENCE INTO HIS
INVESTIGATION.
THE TIMES DIDN'T VIEW A COPY OF
THAT MEMO.
BUT SAYS ASSOCIATES OF COMEY
READ IT TO A REPORTER.
TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE IS
DISPUTING THE STORY.
SAYING IN STATEMENT, THE
PRESIDENT HAS NEVER ASKED MR.
COMEY OR ANYONE ELSE TO END ANY
INVESTIGATION,
INCLUDING ANY INVESTIGATION
INVOLVING GENERAL FLYNN.
THIS IS NOT A TRUTHFUL OR
ACCURATE PORTRAYAL OF THE
CONVERSATION BETWEEN THE
PRESIDENT AND MR. COMEY.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID COMEY WAS
FIRED BECAUSE HE WAS NOT
COMPETENT, CALLING HIM A
SHOWBOAT.
THIS GALVANIZED MANY IN THE FBI.
THE ACTING DIRECTOR COMING TO
COMEY'S DEFENSE LAST WEEK.
>> IS IT ACCURATE THAT THE RANK
AND FILE NO LONGER SUPPORTED
DIRECTOR COMEY?
>> NO SIR, THAT'S NOT ACCURATE.
>> Reporter: BUT HE ALSO SAID
YOU CANNOT STOP THE FBI FROM
DOING THE RIGHT THING.
>> SO THERE HAS BEEN NO EFFORT
TO IMPEDE OUR INVESTIGATION TO
DATE.
>> LET'S GET TO CECILIA VEGA.
THE WHITE HOUSE I KNOW IS
DENYING THIS.
BUT "THE NEW YORK TIMES" REPORT,
IS BASED IN PART LATE TODAY ON
TWO PEOPLE THEY SAY READ THE
JAMES COMEY MEMO.
PART OF A PAPER TRAIL THAT COMEY
DOCUMENTED AS THE TIMES PUT IT,
"IMPROPER EFFORTS TO INFLUENCE
THE ONGOING INVESTIGATION INTO
FLYNN AND RUSSIA."
>> Reporter: AND, DAVID, THE
TIMES SAID THEY DIDN'T SEE THIS
MEMO THEMSELVES BUT THEY SOURCED
THESE TWO PEOPLE THEY SAY THEY
READ IT.
THE REACTION HAS BEEN POURING
IN.
DEMOCRATS ARE ALREADY TALKING
ABOUT THE POSSIBILITY -- RAISING
THE POSSIBILITY OF OBSTRUCTION
OF JUSTICE.
THAT'S OF COURSE A FEDERAL
CRIME.
ONE SENATOR SAID THAT WE MAY BE
TALKING ABOUT AN IMPEACHMENT
PROCESS.
DAVID, I WAS JUST SPEAKING WITH
A SOURCE ON CAPITOL HILL.
THIS JUST CAME IN, "I DON'T
THINK WE COULD BE STUNNED
ANYMORE GIVEN THE PAST WEEK.
THIS BLEW THAT OUT OF THE
WATER."
THE SAME REACTION AT THE WHITE
HOUSE TONIGHT.
>> ANOTHER LONG NIGHT AHEAD FOR
YOU, CECILIA.
>>> I WANT TO BRING IN PIERRE
THOMAS, WHO COVERS THE FBI.
PIERRE, YOU ACTUALLY CONFIRMED
THIS EVENING THAT COMEY DID
WRITE A MEMO TO DOCUMENT HIS
INTERACTIONS WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
THE SOURCE TOLD YOU THAT THE
PRESIDENT TRUMP ALLEGEDLY ASKED
HIM TO GO EASY ON FLYNN.
>> DAVID, THE SOURCE SAID HE'S
SEEN THE COMEY MEMO, AND HE
CONFIRMED THE QUOTES IN "THE NEW
YORK TIMES" SPECIFICALLY,
PRESIDENT TRUMP ALLEGEDLY
SAYING, I HOPE YOU CAN LET THIS
GO, HE'S A GOOD GUY.
DAVID, WHAT YOU'RE SEEING IS A
LOT OF PEOPLE COMING TO THE
DEFENSE OF COMEY WHO BELIEVE
HE'S A MAN OF INTEGRITY AND
HONOR, NOT PERFECT.
BUT A MAN OF INTEGRITY.
AS FOR THE MOOD AT THE FBI
THEY'RE PROFESSIONALS AND
THEY'RE CARRYING ON THEIR WORK.
BUT MAKE NO MISTAKE,
A NUMBER OF FORMER FBI AGENTS I
TALKED WITH ARE EXTREMELY ANGRY
AT THE WAY COMEY WAS FIRED.
DAVID.
>> PIERRE THOMAS WITH US
TONIGHT.
PIERRE, THANK YOU.
>>> ALL OF THIS COMES AS THE
WHITE HOUSE REFUSES TO SAY
WHETHER THE WHITE HOUSE
THE PRESIDENT GAVE CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION TO THE RUSSIANS.
THAT HEADLINE BROKE LAST NIGHT
AS WE CAME ON.
OUR TEAM COULD HEAR THE YELLING
BEHIND THE WALLS OF THE WEST
WING.
THE PRESIDENT REPORTEDLY
REVEALING CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
ABOUT AN ISIS PLOT.
THAT INFORMATION COMING FROM AN
U.S. ALLY WHO HAD NOT GIVEN
PERMISSION TO SHARE IT.
TONIGHT, DID THE PRESIDENT'S
REVEAL PUT ANY SOURCES ALREADY
IN HARM'S WAY AT GREATER RISK?
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL.
>> Reporter: AS PRESIDENT TRUMP
MET WITH THE PRESIDENT OF TURKEY
TODAY, HE WAS HOUNDED WITH
QUESTIONS --
>> DID YOU REVEAL CLASSIFIED
INTELLIGENCE INFORMATION WITH
THE RUSSIANS?
>> MR. PRESIDENT, DID YOU SHARE
CLASSIFIED INTELLIGENCE
INFORMATION WITH THE RUSSIANS?
>> THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: BUT A LITTLE LATER,
HE TOUTED HIS MEETING WITH THE
RUSSIANS AS A SUCCESS.
>> WE HAD A VERY, VERY
SUCCESSFUL MEETING WITH THE
FOREIGN MINISTER OF RUSSIA.
OUR FIGHT IS AGAINST ISIS.
>> Reporter: AT ISSUE, WHAT THE
PRESIDENT SAID WHEN HE MET WITH
THE RUSSIAN FOREIGN MINISTER AND
AMBASSADOR IN THE OVAL OFFICE
LAST WEEK.
THE "WASHINGTON POST" FIRST
REPORTED THAT THE PRESIDENT
SHARED HIGHLY SENSITIVE
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION ABOUT AN
ISIS PLOT TO TARGET CIVILIAN
AIRPLANES WITH LAPTOP BOMBS --
SECRET INFORMATION, ABC NEWS HAS
LEARNED, GIVEN TO THE UNITED
STATES BY ISRAELI INTELLIGENCE.
LESS THAN TWO HOURS AFTER THE
STORY BROKE, THE NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER EMERGED FROM
THE WEST WING TO SHOOT IT DOWN.
>> THE STORY THAT CAME OUT
TONIGHT AS REPORTED IS FALSE.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING, THE
PRESIDENT SEEMED TO CONFIRM HE
SHARED SENSITIVE INFORMATION
WITH THE RUSSIANS, TWEETING --
"AS PRESIDENT I WANTED TO SHARE
WITH RUSSIA, AT AN OPENLY
SCHEDULED WHITE HOUSE MEETING,
WHICH I HAVE THE ABSOLUTE RIGHT
TO DO, FACTS PRETRAINING TO
TERRORISM AND AIRLINE FLIGHT
SAFETY.
TODAY McMASTER WAS BACK,
CONFIRMING MANY OF THE DETAILS
IN THE "POST" STORY AND NOT
DENYING THE INFORMATION SHARED
WAS CLASSIFIED.
>> GENERAL, WHEN YOU CAME OUT
AFTER THE STORY BROKE, YOU SAID
THAT THE PRESIDENT DID NOT
DISCLOSE ANY SOURCES OR METHODS.
HE DID NOT REVEAL ANYTHING ABOUT
MILITARY OPERATIONS.
WHY WERE YOU DENYING THINGS THAT
WERE NOT EVEN REPORTED?
WHAT THE REPORT SAID IS THAT THE
PRESIDENT REVEALED CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION THAT HAD BEEN SHARED
BY ONE OF OUR ALLIES IN THE
MIDDLE EAST.
SO THE QUESTION IS SIMPLY A YES
OR NO QUESTION HERE.
DID THE PRESIDENT SHARE
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION WITH THE
RUSSIANS IN THAT MEETING?
>> AS I MENTIONED ALREADY, WE
DON'T SAY WHAT'S CLASSIFIED,
WHAT'S NOT CLASSIFIED.
WHAT I WILL TELL YOU AGAIN IS
THAT WHAT THE PRESIDENT SHARED
WAS WHOLLY APPROPRIATE.
THE STORY COMBINED WHAT WAS
LEAKED WITH OTHER INFORMATION,
AND THEN INSINUATED ABOUT
SOURCES AND METHODS, SO I WANTED
TO MAKE CLEAR TO EVERYBODY THAT
THE PRESIDENT IN NO WAY
COMPROMISED ANY SOURCES OR
METHODS IN THE COURSE OF THIS
CONVERSATION.
>> Reporter: THE STORY IS A
POLITICAL NIGHTMARE FOR THE
TRUMP WHITE HOUSE, ESPECIALLY
BECAUSE, AS A CANDIDATE, DONALD
TRUMP MADE SUCH AN ISSUE OUT OF
HILLARY CLINTON'S HANDLING OF
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
>> WE CAN'T HAVE SOMEONE IN THE
OVAL OFFICE WHO DOESN'T
UNDERSTAND THE MEANING OF THE
WORD CONFIDENTIAL OR CLASSIFIED.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENTS HAVE THE
AUTHORITY TO DECLASSIFY
ANYTHING, THE QUESTION IS, WHY
HE WOULD SHARE IT WITH AN
ADVERSARY?
THE WHITE HOUSE INSISTS HE WAS
SOLICITING RUSSIAN HELP IN THE
FIGHT AGAINST ISIS.
THE "POST" STORY SUGGESTS TRUMP
WAS TRYING TO SHOW OFF, QUOTING
HIM TELLING THE RUSSIANS, "I GET
GREAT INTEL.
I HAVE PEOPLE BRIEF ME ON GREAT
INTEL EVERY DAY."
McMASTER SAID THE PRESIDENT
COULD NOT HAVE TOLD THE RUSSIANS
THE SOURCE OF THE INFORMATION
BECAUSE HE DIDN'T KNOW THE
SOURCE.
>> THE PRESIDENT WASN'T EVEN
AWARE OF WHERE THIS INFORMATION
CAME FROM.
HE WASN'T BRIEFED ON THE SOURCE
OR METHOD OF THE INFORMATION
EITHER.
>> WASN'T AWARE OF WHERE THE
INFORMATION CAME FROM.
JONATHAN KARL LIVE WITH US AS
WELL.
YOU WERE IN THAT BRIEFING ROOM.
THE WHITE HOUSE TODAY DIDN'T
SEEM CONCERNED ABOUT THE
POTENTIAL OF CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION GIVEN OUT.
THEY MADE IT CLEAR THAT THE
BIGGER CONCERN HERE, IN THEIR
OPINION, IS WHO LEAKED WHAT
HAPPENED.
JON, THE INITIAL CALL -- THE
INITIAL CALL OF CONCERN TO THE
CIA AND THE NSA YOU HAVE
REPORTED HAS COME FROM WITHIN
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: HERE'S WHAT WE
KNOW, SHORTLY AFTER THAT MEETING
WITH THE RUSSIANS, A TOP
OFFICIAL ON THE NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNCIL HERE AT THE
WHITE HOUSE PLACED CALLS TO THE
NSA AND THE CIA TO INFORM THEM
ABOUT WHAT THE PRESIDENT HAD
SAID, SO, CLEARLY THERE WAS
ENOUGH CONCERN HERE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE ABOUT WHAT THE PRESIDENT
REVEALED THAT THEY FELT THEY
NEEDED TO TELL THE CIA AND THE
NSA.
>> ALL RIGHT, JON, THANKS TO
YOU.
>>> AND ON CAPITOL HILL TONIGHT,
REACTION POURING IN ON BOTH
FRONTS.
ON THE REPORTED PRESSURE ON
JAMES COMEY, TO GO EASY ON
MICHAEL FLYNN, AND ON THE
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION ALLEGEDLY
GIVEN TO THE RUSSIANS.
BOTH DEMOCRATS AND REPUBLICANS
WANT THE TRANSCRIPT NOW, THE
NOTES, FROM INSIDE THAT OVAL
OFFICE MEETING.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE ON THE HILL
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
TONIGHT, NEW CALLS FROM BOTH
PARTIES FOR THE FORMER FBI
DIRECTOR TO TESTIFY ON CAPITOL
HILL.
>> I DON'T WANT TO READ A MEMO.
I WANT TO HEAR FROM HIM.
>> Reporter: THIS AS CONGRESS IS
REELING WHAT THE PRESIDENT
ALLEGEDLY REVEALED IN THAT
MEETING WITH THE RUSSIANS.
>> HOPEFUL TO HAVE LESS DRAMA
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: BUT HE'S STILL
STANDING BY THE PRESIDENT.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANY WORRY OF THE
PRESIDENT'S ABILITY TO PROPERLY
HANDLE CLASSIFIED INFO?
>> NO.
>> Reporter: STILL, ONE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S TOP ALLIES SAYS THE
WHITE HOUSE NEEDS TO GET ITS ACT
TOGETHER.
>> OBVIOUSLY, THEY'RE IN A
DOWNWARD SPIRAL RIGHT NOW AND
THEY'VE GOT TO FIGURE OUT A WAY
TO COME TO GRIPS WITH ALL THAT'S
HAPPENING.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S YOUR
CONCERN?
>> JUST A LITTLE BIT MORE
DISCIPLINE.
>> Reporter: WHILE DEMOCRATS ARE
POINTING OUT WHAT THE PRESIDENT
ONCE SAID ABOUT HILLARY CLINTON.
>> HOW MANY PEOPLE WERE OUT
CHANTING "LOCK HER UP" AND TRUMP
HIMSELF SAYING SHE WAS UNFIT TO
GOVERN BECAUSE OF THAT?
AND HERE HE IS NOW RELEASING
REAL SECRETS DIRECTLY TO THE
RUSSIANS.
AND THE IRONY OF THAT IS PRETTY
ASTOUNDING.
>> SO LET'S GET TO MARY BRUCE
WITH US AS WELL FROM CAPITOL
HILL.
HOUSE MEMBERS MEETING TONIGHT
WITH THE CIA DIRECTOR HOPING TO
GET MORE ON THE NEWS OF JAMES
COMEY AND THIS REPORTED PRESSURE
THAT WAS PLACED ON HIM TO GO
EASIER ON RETIRED GENERAL
MICHAEL FLYNN?
>> Reporter: DAVID, THE HOUSE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE JUST
FINISHED MEETING WITH THE CIA
DIRECTOR.
THEY WERE HOPING FOR ANSWERS BUT
EMERGED FROM THAT MEETING FACING
EVEN MORE QUESTIONS NOW ABOUT
THAT COMEY MEMO, THE TOP
DEMOCRAT ON THE COMMITTEE
REITERATING HIS CALLS FOR COMEY
TO TESTIFY HERE ON THE HILL.
DAVID.
>> MARY BRUCE WITH US TONIGHT,
AS WELL.
MARY, THANK YOU.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP IT'S
BELIEVED IN TALKING WITH THE
RUSSIANS IN OVAL OFFICE, WAS
TALKING ABOUT AN ISIS PLOT, WHAT
COULD BE THE BIGGEST PLOT TO
TAKE DOWN A PLANE SINCE 9/11.
TONIGHT, BY SHARING THAT
INFORMATION, ARE THE LIVES OF
SOURCES AT GREATER RISK, AND
WHAT ABOUT OUR RELATIONSHIP WITH
THE ALLY WHO GAVE THE WHITE
HOUSE THAT INFORMATION IN THE
FIRST PLACE.
HERE'S BRIAN ROSS TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S AT RISK
TONIGHT, ACCORDING TO CURRENT
AND FORMER U.S. OFFICIALS, IS
THE LIFE OF A SPY INSIDE ISIS,
PLACED THERE BY ISRAEL,
PROVIDING SENSITIVE INFORMATION
ABOUT TERROR PLOTS AGAINST
AMERICA ON THE CONDITION THE
U.S. KEEP THE SOURCE SECRET.
>> THE REAL RISK IS NOT JUST
THIS SOURCE, BUT FUTURE SOURCES
OF INFORMATION ABOUT PLOTS
AGAINST US.
>> Reporter: THE CURRENT
INTELLIGENCE FROM INSIDE ISIS
INVOLVES AN ACTIVE PLOT TO BRING
DOWN A PASSENGER JET EN ROUTE TO
THE U.S., WITH A BOMB HIDDEN IN
A LAPTOP THAT THE U.S. BELIEVES
CAN GET THROUGH AIRPORT
SCREENING MACHINES UNDETECTED.
THE INFORMATION IS SO RELIABLE
THAT THE U.S. IS CONSIDERING A
BAN ON LAPTOPS ON ALL FLIGHTS
FROM EUROPE TO THE U.S.
>> WHAT THEY WANT TO DO THE MOST
IS THEY WANT TO HAVE A LARGE
AIRPLANE BLOW UP IN FLIGHT.
>> Reporter: ISIS HAS ALREADY
TAKEN CREDIT FOR BLOWING UP A
RUSSIAN AIRLINER TWO YEARS AGO,
KILLING MORE THAN 200 PEOPLE,
CLAIMING THE BOMB WAS HIDDEN IN
A SOFT DRINK CAN.
THE WHITE HOUSE NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER SAYS THAT
JUSTIFIES PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
DISCLOSURES TO THE RUSSIANS.
>> THIS WAS THE CONTEXT OF THE
CONVERSATION IN WHICH IT WAS
WHOLLY APPROPRIATE TO SHARE WHAT
THE THREAT WAS AS A BASIS FOR
COMMON ACTION AND COORDINATION.
>> Reporter: BUT MANY IN THE
COUNTERTERRORISM COMMUNITY SAY
WHAT THE PRESIDENT DID WAS A
MISTAKE.
>> RUSSIA IS NOT PART OF THE
ISIS COALITION.
THEY ARE NOT OUR PARTNER.
>> AND BRIAN ROSS WITH US NOW.
BRIAN REPORTED THERE THAT IT'S
BELIEVED IT WAS ISRAEL, OUR
ALLY, WHO GAVE US THAT
INFORMATION.
LOT OF PEOPLE ARE POINTING TO
THE FACT IF THIS CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION WAS GIVE ON THE
RUSSIANS THEY COULD GIVE IT TO
PLAYERS WHO ARE CLEARLY NOT
FRIENDS WITH ISRAEL.
>> THAT'S RIGHT -- DAVID.
INCLUDING IRAN, ALSO A SWORN
ENEMY OF ISRAEL.
>> BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> WE DO HAVE OTHER NEWS WE'RE
FOLLOWING AT THIS HOUR.
A FIERY CRASH ON I-95, SEVERAL
BIG RIGS AND SEVERAL CARS
INVOLVED.
THE HIGHWAY SHUT DOWN IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS.
PART OF IT IS STILL CLOSED AS
WE'RE ON THE AIR.
HERE'S ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI.
>> Reporter: THE FIRE CAUSED BY
THIS ACCIDENT WAS SO GREAT YOU
COULD SEE IT FROM THE SKY FOR
MILES.
IT CLOSED INTERSTATE 95 IN BOTH
DIRECTIONS, NEAR THE NORTH
CAROLINA AND SOUTH CAROLINA
BORDER.
POLICE WORKING THE SCENE TONIGHT
SAY THAT THE SOUTHBOUND LANE
WHERE THE ACCIDENT HAPPENED
WON'T REOPEN UNTIL AT LEAST
MIDNIGHT.
AT LEAST FOUR PEOPLE WERE KILLED
AFTER A CRASH INVOLVING THREE
TRACTOR-TRAILERS AND THREE
SMALLER VEHICLES.
WITNESSES SAY THAT FUEL TANKS OF
ONE OF THE LARGER TRUCKS CAUGHT
FIRE.
THE LEAKING FUEL SPREAD THE FIRE
TO THE OTHER VEHICLES.
THE FLAMES MOVED OVER THE
HIGHWAY AND INTO NEARBY WOODS.
DRIVERS ARE HAVING TO WORK THEIR
WAY AROUND THE SCENE.
ONE OF THE TRUCKS WAS CARRYING
HAZARDOUS CHEMICALS BUT
AUTHORITIES SAY THERE'S NO
REASON FOR CONCERN OR
EVACUATIONS, DAVID.
>> STEVE, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE WEATHER AND WHAT
COULD BE A DANGEROUS NIGHT
AHEAD.
TORNADO WATCHES IN EIGHT STATES
AT THIS HOUR.
OMINOUS SKIES.
AT LEAST THREE TORNADOES
REPORTED ALREADY.
ONE ON THE GROUND AS WE CAME ON.
THIS ONE TOUCHING IN McLEAN,
TEXAS.
JUST A SHORT TIME AGO.
LET'S GET TO GINGER ZEE, SHE'S
TRACKING THE SEVERE WEATHER
THREAT TONIGHT.
HEY, GINGER.
>> Reporter: DAVID, A TORNADO ON
THE GROUND RIGHT NOW IN
WISCONSIN, JUST EAST OF RICELAKE
IN THAT NORTHEAST REGION, YOU
SEE IN THE TORNADO WATCH THERE.
ALSO, THAT PARTICULARLY
DANGEROUS SITUATION IN WESTERN
OKLAHOMA AND TEXAS, THAT'S WHERE
THOSE SUPERCELLS ALREADY HAVE
BEEN PUTTING UP TORNADOES.
TOMORROW, THE THREAT STAYS WITH
US.
AHEAD ALL OF THAT, WE COULD HAVE
NEAR-RECORD HIGHS ON THE EAST
COAST.
DAVID.
>> GINGER ZEE WITH US TONIGHT.
>>> THERE'S STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD THIS TUESDAY -- THE SMALL
PLANE LOST IN THE BERMUDA
TRIANGLE.
FAMILY MEMBERS ONBOARD.
THERE ARE NEW DEVELOPMENTS
TONIGHT, SIGNS OF WRECKAGE.
>>> THE NEW CAFFEINE CONCERN.
THE 16-YEAR-OLD WHO HAD A COFFEE
AND SEVERAL OTHER DRINKS WITH
CAFFEINE.
THE CORONER WHO NOW SAID IT
KILLED HIM.
AND THE ALERT, HOW MUCH CAFFEINE
IS TOO MUCH.
>>> THE MANHUNT FOR AN ARSON
SUSPECT.
ACCUSED OF SETTING FIRE TO A
MOSQUE.
THIS NEW SURVEILLANCE PEOPLE
ASKING FOR YOU HELP TONIGHT.
>>> AND LATER THIS EVENING --
THE SURPRISE FROM BON JOVI.
WHAT THIS CROWD ASKED FOR.
YOU WON'T BELIEVE IT.
But with my back pain I couldn't
sleep or get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
The only one to combine
a safe sleep aid
plus the 12 hour pain
relieving strength of Aleve.
And now. I'm back!
Aleve PM for a better AM.
Beggin' Skinny Strips or
Beggin' Black Label?
There's two?!
Now this is a delicious dilemma!
Introducing New Beggin' Strips
Premium Edition.
TWWWOOOOOO?!?!
With real meat as
ingredient one.
Everything to your liking?
Mmm Mmmmm...
New Beggin' Strips Premium.
Becaussssseeee Beggin'!
(Becky) I started smoking when I
Now I have end-stage COPD.
My tip is; if you keep smoking,
your freedom may only go
as far as your oxygen tube.
(Announcer) You can quit.
For free help,
call 1-800-QUIT-NOW.
♪
Predictable.
The comfort in knowing where
things are headed.
Because as we live longer...
And markets continue to
rise and fall...
Predictable is one thing you
need in retirement
to help protect what you've
earned and ensure it lasts.
Introducing
Brighthouse Financial.
A new company established
by MetLife
to specialize in annuities
& life insurance.
Talk to your advisor about a
brighter financial future.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, A NEW
WARNING ABOUT TEENAGERS AND
CAFFEINE.
A 16-YEAR-OLD STUDENT WHO
COLLAPSED IN SCHOOL AND DIED.
THE CORONER NOW REVEALING IT WAS
CAFFEINE, TOO MUCH OF IT.
HERE'S ABC'S ADRIENNE BANKERT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, KILLED BY
CAFFEINE.
IT'S UNTHINKABLE -- A
16-YEAR-OLD CHILD DEAD AFTER
DRINKING A McDONALD'S LATTE,
LARGE MOUNTAIN DEW, AND AN
ENERGY DRINK.
>> I STAND BEFORE YOU AS A
BROKEN-HEARTED FATHER, AND HOPE
THAT SOMETHING GOOD CAN COME
FROM THIS.
>> Reporter: DAVIS SUFFERING A
FATAL HEART ARRHYTHMIA.
>> DAVIS, LIKE SO MANY OTHER
KIDS AND SO MANY OTHER PEOPLE
OUT THERE TODAY, WERE DOING
SOMETHING THAT THEY THOUGHT WAS
TOTALLY HARMLESS.
>> Reporter: TOXICOLOGY REPORTS
SHOW THAT DAVIS WAS HEALTHY,
WITHOUT ANY PRE-EXISTING HEART
CONDITION.
HIS FAMILY SAYS HE NEVER DID
DRUGS OR DRANK ALCOHOL.
THE MAYO CLINIC SAYS THE MOST
CAFFEINE A TEEN SHOULD CONSUME
IS 100 MILLIGRAMS, EQUAL TO AN
8-OUNCE COFFEE OR 16-OUNCE SODA.
THE COMBINATION OF THE THREE
BEVERAGES DAVIS DRANK MAY HAVE
ADDED UP TO ALMOST SIX TIMES
THAT AMOUNT.
EXPERTS SAY WHAT'S DANGEROUS,
YOU DON'T KNOW HOW YOUR BODY OR
YOUR CHILD'S BODY WILL RESPOND.
DAVID.
>> ADRIENNE, THANK YOU.
>>> AND WHEN WE COME BACK
TONIGHT -- THE PLANE
DISAPPEARING IN THE BERMUDA
TRIANGLE.
THE NEW DETAILS COMING IN.
>>> AND THE EXPLOSION AT
IN A PRESCHOOL.
THE SCIENCE EXPERIMENT GONE
WRONG.
THE CHILDREN WHO WERE JUST
3-YEAR-OLDS, THEY WERE RACED
AWAY WITH BURNS.
BACK IN A MOMENT.
after a DVT blood clot,
I sure had a lot
to think about.
What about the
people I care about?
...including this little girl.
And what if this
happened again?
I was given warfarin
in the hospital,
but wondered, was this the
best treatment for me?
So I asked my doctor.
And he recommended ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots
and reduces the risk of
them happening again.
Yes, ELIQUIS treats DVT
and PE blood clots.
ELIQUIS also had
significantly
less major
bleeding
than the
standard
treatment.
Both made me
turn around my
thinking.
Don't stop ELIQUIS
unless your doctor tells you to.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you have
an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
If you had a spinal injection
while on ELIQUIS
call your doctor right away
if you have tingling,
numbness, or muscle weakness.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily
...and it may take longer
than usual for bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate medical care
for sudden signs of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor
about all planned
medical or dental
procedures.
ELIQUIS treats
DVT and PE
blood clots.
Plus had
less major
bleeding.
Both made ELIQUIS
the right treatment for me.
Ask your doctor if switching
to ELIQUIS is right for you.
How do you become America's
best-selling brand?
You make it detect what
they don't.
Stop, stop, STOP!
Sorry.
You make it sense what's coming.
Watch, watch, WATCH!
Mom. Relax!
I'm relaxed.
You make it for 16-year olds...
Whoa-whoa-WHOA!!!
and the parents who worry
about them.
You saw him, right?
Going further to help make
drivers, better drivers.
Don't freak out on me.
That's Ford.
And that's how you become
America's Best-Selling Brand.
♪
Depression is a tangle
of multiple symptoms.
♪
That's why there's Trintellix,
a prescription medication
for depression.
Trintellix may help you take
a step forward
in improving your depression.
Tell your healthcare
professional right away
if your depression worsens,
or you have unusual changes
in mood,
behavior or thoughts of suicide.
Antidepressants can increase
these in children,
teens and young adults.
Do not take with MAOIs.
Tell your healthcare
professional about
your medications, including
migraine, psychiatric
and depression medications,
to avoid a potentially
life-threatening condition.
Increased risk of bleeding or
bruising may occur,
especially if taken with NSAID
pain relievers,
aspirin or blood thinners.
Manic episodes or
vision problems
may occur in some people.
May cause low sodium levels.
The most common side effects
were nausea,
constipation and vomiting.
TRINTELLIX had no significant
impact on weight
in clinical trials.
Ask your healthcare
professional about TRINTELLIX.
MMMM.  MMMM.
MMMM... UGH.
Nothing spoils a moment
like heartburn.
Try new Alka-Seltzer Ultra
Strength heartburn Relief Chews.
It's fast, powerful relief
with no chalky taste.
[ sings high note ]
Ultra Strength, new
from Alka-Seltzer.
Enjoy the Relief.
>>> TO THE "INDEX" AND THE
PRESCHOOL SCIENCE EXPERIMENT
GONE WRONG IN HOUSTON.
12 CHILDREN INJURED AT A CHURCH
SCHOOL, 11 OF THEM BURNED.
ALL OF THEM JUST 3-YEAR-OLDS.
THE CHILDREN RUSHED TO NEARBY
AMBULANCES AND AWAITING PARENTS.
FIREFIGHTERS SAID THE EXPERIMENT
TURNED INTO AN OUT OF CONTROL
FIREBALL.
THE CHILDREN ARE EXPECTED TO
RECOVER.
>>> TO THE SEARCH FOR A MISSING
PLANE IN THE BERMUDA TRIANGLE.
THE SMALL PLANE DISAPPEARING OFF
THE BAHAMAS.
THE COAST GUARD FINDING DEBRIS
IN THE WATER.
AUTHORITIES SAY FOUR PEOPLE WERE
ONBOARD.
THEY WERE FLYING FROM PUERTO
RICO TO FLORIDA.
>>> AND THE MANHUNT TONIGHT FOR
AN ARSON SUSPECT NEAR TAMPA.
POLICE RELEASING SURVEILLANCE OF
THE SUSPECT.
ALLEGEDLY SETTING FIRE TO A
MOSQUE IN FEBRUARY.
THE SUSPECT SEEN POURING A TRAIL
OF ACCELERANT, THEN IGNITING THE
FIRE.
AUTHORITIES ARE NOW ASKING FOR
THE PUBLIC'S HELP.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT --
BON JOVI, THIS ONE, THIS GIFT
WAS BIG.
When you have allergies,
it can seem like triggers
pop up everywhere.
Luckily there's Powerful,
24-hour, non-drowsy Claritin.
It provides relief
of symptoms
that can be triggered by over
200 different allergens.
Live Claritin Clear.
I hafor my belly painking
overand constipation.ucts
I've had it up to here!
It's been month after month
of fiber.
Weeks taking probiotics!
Days and nights
of laxatives,
only to have
my symptoms return.
(VO)
If you've had enough,
tell your doctor
what you've tried
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults with IBS
with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help relieve
your belly pain,
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.
Do not give LINZESS
to children less than six,
and it should not be given
to children six to less than 18.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS
if you have a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop
unusual or severe stomach pain,
especially with bloody
or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe,
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor
right away.
Other side effects include gas,
stomach-area pain,
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
We asked people to write down
the things they love to do
most on these balloons.
Travel with my daughter.
Roller Derby.
♪
Now give up half of 'em.
Do I have to?
This is a tough financial choice
we could face when we retire.
But, if we start saving
even just 1% more
of our annual income...
We could keep doing all
the things we love.
Prudential. Bring Your
Challenges.
What bad back?Gels work so fast
you'll ask
What pulled hammy?
Advil Liqui - Gels make pain a
distant memory
Nothing works faster
Stronger
Or Longer
What
Pain?
Advil.
WILL YOU BE READY WHEN
THE MOMENT TURNS ROMANTIC?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
>>> "AMERICA STRONG" AND BON
JOVI'S GIFT TO THE CLASS OF
2017.
HERE'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> I'M JON BON JOVI.
AND I WANT TO CRASH YOUR
COMMENCEMENT.
>> Reporter: THAT WAS BACK IN
MARCH, WHEN THE ROCK STAR
ANNOUNCED A CONTEST TO GIVE
COLLEGE SENIORS A CHANCE TO HAVE
HIM PERFORM AT THEIR GRADUATION.
STUDENTS TOOK TO SOCIAL MEDIA,
TWEETING OUT THEIR BEST COLLEGE
MOMENTS.
RIGHT BEFORE GOING OUT ON STAGE,
HE REVEALED THE WINNER.
>> HERE WE ARE, BACKSTAGE IN
METLIFE STADIUM, FOR THE
GRADUATION OF FAIRLEIGH
DICKINSON UNIVERSITY.
>> PLEASE WELCOME BON JOVI!
♪
♪ MAKE IT THE BEST OF THE REST
OF YOUR DAYS ♪
♪
♪ THIS ISN'T HOW YOUR STORY
ENDS, MY FRIENDS, IT'S JUST A
FORK ALONG THE ROAD ♪
>> THANK YOU, GOOD LUCK.
CLASS OF 2017.
WE'LL SEE YOU.
>>> NOT A BAD GIFT.
>>> AND I HOPE TO SEE YOU
TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NO.
>>> NO ROPES, NO SAFETY NETS.
>> THIS WOMAN HAS BEEN ARRESTED
THREE TIMES.
TONIGHT WE'RE ASKING IF HER
HUSBAND'S JOB IS THE REASON NO
CHARGES HAVE BEEN FILED.
>>> IT'S AN EYESORE THAT COULD
START GETTING VERY EXPENSIVE FOR
ONE OF THE BAY AREA'S BIGGEST
CITIES.
>> WHEN WE SAW THE LINK, I WAS
VERY CONCERNED THAT THESE TWO
RECKLESS INDIVIDUALS WERE
PUTTING MOTORISTS AT RISK.
>> BIG QUESTIONS ABOUT THE
SECURITY OF THE BAY AREA'S MOST
ICONIC STRUCTURE.
GOOD EVENING AND THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US TONIGHT.
>>> THIS STUNT HAPPENED LAST
MONTH, BUT THE VIDEO WAS
RELEASED TO THE PUBLIC TODAY BY
THE TEENAGERS WHO CLIMBED THAT
BRIDGE.
>> IT GOES WITHOUT SAYING DO NOT
TRY THIS YOURSELF.
THE VIDEO SHOWS THEM CLIMBING UP
THE MAIN CABLE TO THE TOP OF THE
NORTH TOWER.
>> YOU'LL NOTICE THEY'RE NOT
WEARING ANY SAFETY EQUIPMENT.
LIVE AFT
.
>> Reporter: CAN I SAY THAT THIS
IS NOT EASY TO WATCH.
NOW THESE GUYS WERE UP THERE FOR
ABOUT AN HOUR AND ONE OF THEM
TOLD ME THAT THEY HAD INITIALLY
THOUGHT ABOUT STAYING THERE TO
WATCH THE SUN RISE, BUT THEN
THOUGHT THAT IF THEY DID, THEY
WOULD GET CAUGHT.
THESE TEENS FROM MILWAUKEE NEVER
PLANNED ON CLIMBING THE GOLDEN
GATE BRIDGE, THEY WERE JUST
COMING TO VISIT FRIENDS DURING
SPRING BREAK.
18-YEAR-OLD PETER TEATIME IS A
SENIOR IN HIGH SCHOOL, I FACE
TIMED HIM TAKING ME THROUGH STEP
BY STEP THE DARING IS STUNT THAT
BEGAN EARLY IN THE MORNING THEY
CLIMBED THE MAIN CABLE THAT TOOK
THEM T