>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT TAKING AIM, AMERICA
WEIGHS MILITARY ACTION AGAINST
SYRIA AND TONIGHT WE TAKE YOU
INSIDE THE MIND OF THE LEADER
ACCUSED OF UNLEASHING CHEMICAL
WAR.
COULD HE MAKE A DIRECT HIT ON
THE UNITED STATES?
OUR MARTHA RADDATZ IS IN THE
REGION WITH THE NEWS.
>>> EXTREME WEATHER FORCING
CHILDREN TO COOL OFF IN ICE
CUBES, SCHOOLS CLOSED IN SIX
STATES AND OUT WEST HAVE
FEARLESS FIREFIGHTERS STOPPED
THE BLAZE NEAR YOSEMITE.
>>> WATCH DOG, WE FIND $1
MILLION OF TAXPAYER MONEY GOING
TO WASTE IN A CLOSET.
TRYING TO GET ACTION TONIGHT.
>>> HIDDEN WORLD, THE CLOSED
LIFE OF THE AMISH, IS IT FINALLY
EXPOSED AND IS THERE REALLY AN
AMISH MAFIA?
>> GOOD EVENING.
AS WE BEGIN TONIGHT, THE CLOCK
IS TICKING ON U.S. MILITARY
ACTION IN SYRIA.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS A DECISION
IS NEAR AND U.S. WAR SHIPS ARE
IN POSITION.
AND THE REST OF THE WORLD IS
ALSO JOINING THE DEBATE ABOUT
WHAT KIND OF ACTION AND EXACTLY
WHEN.
THE GOAL, TO STOP A MAN USING
BRUTAL CHEMICAL WEAPONS 5,000
MILES AWAY.
ABC'S MARTHA RADDATZ HAS IT ALL
FROM THE MIDDLE EAST.
>> Reporter: HE IS THE MAN AT
THE CENTER OF THIS HORROR.
A BRUTAL DICTATOR WHO THE VICE
PRESIDENT SAID TODAY IS
UNDENIABLY RESPONSIBLE FOR
GASSING HIS OWN INNOCENT PEOPLE.
>> THERE IS NO DOUBT WHO IS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS HEINOUS USE
OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS IN SYRIA.
THE SYRIAN REGIME.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THERE SEEMS
NO QUESTION THAT THE U.S. IS
READY TO STRIKE A PUNISHING BLOW
TO ASSAD.
U.S. WAR SHIPS ARE IN PLACE,
CRUISE MISSILES AT THE READY,
THE TARGETS IN SYRIA SELECTED.
>> YOU'RE READY TO GO LIKE THAT?
>> WE'RE READY TO GO LIKE THAT.
>> Reporter: WHAT MIGHT ASSAD DO
IN RESPONSE?
THE SYRIAN REGIME HAS HUNDREDS
OF TONS OF MUSTARD GAS AND STOCK
PILES OF SARIN.
ADD TO THAT 100,000 MISSILES AND
ROCKETS INCLUDING THOUSANDS OF
POWERFUL SCUD MISSILES WHICH
COULD REACH ANY TARGET IN
NEIGHBORING ISRAEL.
TODAY IN ISRAEL A RUN ON GAS
MASKS, REQUESTS INCREASING FOUR
FOLD.
PRIME MINISTER BENJAMIN
NETANYAHU SAYING ISRAEL IS READY
FOR ANY SCENARIO AND IF WE
IDENTIFY ANY ATTEMPT WHATSOEVER
TO HARM US, WE WILL RESPOND IN
STRENGTH.
THERE IS NO ONE STRONGER IN THIS
REGION.
NUCLEAR ARMED ISRAEL HAS THE
MOST ADVANCED BALLISTIC
MISSILES, CRUISE MISSILES AND
MISSILE DEFENSE SYSTEMS MAKING
EXPERTS BELIEVE ASSAD WOULD BE
CRAZY TO TRY TO HIT ISRAEL.
>> IT MIGHT CREATE AN
OPPORTUNITY FOR ISRAEL THAT THEY
WOULD BE GLAD TO TAKE ADVANTAGE
OF AND PERHAPS ASSAD WOULD RUE
THE DAY THAT HE GAVE THEM THIS
OPPORTUNITY.
>> Reporter: IF ASSAD IS MADMAN
ENOUGH TO RAIN CHEMICALS DOWN
ON HIS PEOPLE KNOWING THE
POSSIBLE CONSEQUENCES THERE IS
NO TELLING WHAT HE WOULD DO IF
CREWS MISSILES START RAINING
DOWN ON HIS OWN REGIME.
>> MARTHA RADDATZ JOINS ME FROM
JERUSALEM TONIGHT.
>> ARE THEY GOING TO TARGET HIM?
>> THEY'RE NOT GOING TO TARGET
HIM PERSONALLY.
THEY HAVE MADE A POINT OF THAT
BUT CERTAINLY MILITARY TARGETS
IN HIS REGIME.
THAT'S GOT TO MAKE HIS NERVOUS.
>> I REMEMBER MEETING HIM AND
INTERVIEWING HIM.
I SHOULD REMIND EVERYBODY HE
GREW UP A LOT OF HIS LIFE IN
LONDON.
HE'S A PHYSICIAN, EDUCATED
THERE.
WHY WOULDN'T THEY TARGET HIM?
WHAT DO THEY EXPECT FROM HIM
NEXT?
>> I THINK THEY'RE AFRAID OF
REACTION AND THEY DON'T WANT
REGIME CHANGE.
THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN VERY
CLEAR ABOUT THAT.
THIS IS A LIMITED STRIKE.
IT'S ONLY TO PREVENT ANY FURTHER
CHEMICAL ATTACKS.
THEY DON'T WANT TO GET INVOLVED
IN THIS CIVIL WAR BUT IT MUST BE
EXTRAORDINARY FOR YOU TO LOOK AT
THIS MAN AS YOU SAY EDUCATED IN
LONDON WHO IS DOING THESE KINDS
OF BRUTAL, BRUTAL THINGS.
>> HE'S SOMEONE WHO NEVER
EXPECTED TO TAKE OVER FROM HIS
FATHER.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, MARTHA
RADDATZ AGAIN REPORTING FROM
JERUSALEM TONIGHT.
>>> NOW THE NEWS BACK HERE AT
HOME, THERE ARE HOPEFUL SIGNS
TONIGHT THAT FIREFIGHTERS MAY
HAVE SAVED YOSEMITE NATIONAL
PARK IN THE NICK OF TIME.
THE FIRE STOPPED BEFORE IT
REACHED THE GATES.
ABC'S NEAL KARLINSKY NOW ON THE
FRONT LINE ONCE AGAIN.
>> Reporter: DIANE, GOOD EVENING
FROM INSIDE THE FIRE ZONE
TONIGHT WHERE FOR THE FIRST TIME
OFFICIALS BELIEVE THEY HAVE
TURNED A CORNER ON THIS ONE.
THEY SAY THE FIRE IS ROUGHLY 20
PERCENT CONTAINED.
THE AREAS OF CONCERN RIGHT NOW
ARE TO THE NORTHWEST, TOWARDS
THE CITY OF TUOLUMNE.
THEY BELIEVE THAT HAVE THAT ONE
FAIRLY WELL IN HAND AND ALSO TO
THE EAST INTO DENSE FOREST LAND
THAT OFFICIALS SAY THEY'RE NOT
CONCERNED ABOUT.
AT THE SAME TIME PEOPLE WHO LIVE
IN THE AREA HAVE BEEN DEALING
WITH DENSE HEAVY SMOKE FOR MORE
THAN A WEEK NOW.
SCHOOLS HAVE BEEN CLOSED.
TOURISM IS WAY DOWN.
WE TALKED TO ONE BUSINESS OWNER
WHO SAYS HE'S LOST ABOUT 98
PERCENT OF THE BUSINESS HE
NORMALLY HAS THIS TIME OF YEAR.
HOWEVER, YOSEMITE, THE HEART OF
IT, REMAINS WIDE OPEN WITH BLUE
SKIES, CLEAR SAILING, THEY SAY,
FOR THE HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
>> STILL HOPING PEOPLE WILL
COME.
THANK YOU, NEIL.
THAT'S GREAT NEWS.
WHAT A DEBT OWED THOSE
FIREFIGHTERS.
>>> THE MIDWEST LIKE A
CONVECTION OVEN.
LOOK AT THIS MAP.
HEAT WARNINGS STRETCHING FROM
NEBRASKA AND ILLINOIS TO
MINNESOTA WHERE THE TEMPERATURE
FELT LIKE MORE THAN 100 DEGREES.
NEAR RECORD TEMPERATURES FORCED
SOME SCHOOLS TO CLOSE TODAY, AND
THE SCHOOLS THAT WERE OPEN HAD
FANS ON FULL BLAST AND THEY GAVE
CHILDREN POPSICLES AND ICE TO
KEEP COOL.
THERE MAY NOT BE RELIEF UNTIL
THIS WEEKEND.
>>> THERE IS A LOT OF CLEANING
UP TO DO IN PHOENIX TONIGHT
AFTER AN EERY DUST STORM, A
HABOOB.
IT LOOKED LIKE A HUGE DOOMSDAY
TIDAL WAVE 4,000 FEET HIGH
SLOWLY MOVING OVER THE AREA,
DAYLIGHT SUDDENLY VANISHING, A
PICTURE CAPTURED THE CLOUD
MOVING TOWARD A BASEBALL STADIUM
PUSHED BY 60 MILE PER HOUR
WINDS.
THE STADIUM CLEARED OUT.
AROUND TOWN, VISIBILITY WAS LESS
THAN 100 FEET.
>>> SHE HAD SO MANY ROOTING FOR
HER AND NOW TONIGHT THE LITTLE
GIRL WHO SPENT SIX MONTHS IN THE
HOSPITAL GETTING A NEW SET OF
LUNGS IS HOME AND LOOKING
FORWARD TO STARTING HER NEW
LIFE.
ABC'S LINZIE JANIS ON A
HOMECOMING.
>> Reporter: 11-YEAR-OLD SARAH
MURNAGHAN IS HOME TONIGHT AFTER
TWO LUNG TRANSPLANTS AND MORE
THAN SIX MONTHS IN THE HOSPITAL.
>> SARAH IS LOOKING FORWARD TO
BEING A REGULAR LITTLE KID.
>> Reporter: ABOUT FOUR MONTHS
AGO SARAH WAS DYING OF LATE
STAGE CYSTIC FIBROSIS AND THE
MURNAGHANS SUED TO GET HER ON
THE ADULT TRANSPLANT LIST,
SOMETHING SHE WAS DENIED.
BECAUSE OF A LAW THAT
PRIORITIZES CHILDREN 12 AND
OLDER.
HER PARENTS REACHED OUT TO THE
MEDIA MONTHS AGO IN HOPES OF
HIGHLIGHTING HER PLIGHT AND
SPARKED A NATIONAL DEBATE OVER
TRANSPLANT RULES.
IN JUNE, A FEDERAL JUDGE ORDERED
A TEMPORARY HALT TO THE SO
CALLED UNDER 12 RULE AND SARAH
GOT HER LUNGS.
AFTER HER LITTLE BODY REJECTED
THE FIRST PAIR, DOCTORS TRIED A
SECOND TRANSPLANT THREE DAYS
LATER.
SO FAR THEY SAY HER PROGNOSIS IS
GOOD.
>> HOW DOES IT FEEL TO BE HOME?
>> GOOD.
>> Reporter: SARAH'S PARENTS SAY
THEY'LL CONTINUE TO FIGHT THE
UNDER 12 RULE BUT SOME SAY
SARAH'S CASE MAY HAVE SET A
PRECEDENT FOR ALLOWING MEDICAL
DECISIONS TO BE MADE IN THE
COURTROOM.
>> PEOPLE MIGHT RIGHTLY ASK
WHETHER IT'S FAIR FOR LUNGS TO
BE ALLOCATED FOR PEOPLE WHO CAN
CREATE THE BIGGEST MEDIA SPLASH.
>> Reporter: SARAH IS NOW READY
TO MAKE THE BEST OF HER NEW
LIFE, SHARING HER PLANS FOR
RECOVERY IN HER FIRST POST
TRANSPLANT INTERVIEW WITH CNN.
>> YOU'RE NOT GOING TO BE EASY.
>> I'M JUST GOING FOR POSSIBLE,
AND WHAT'S IN FRONT OF ME RIGHT
NOW IS POSSIBLE.
>> Reporter: WISDOM, HER PARENTS
SAY, COMES FROM A LIFETIME OF
BEING A FIGHTER.
LINZIE JANIS, ABC NEWS,
PENNSYLVANIA.
>> LOOKING AT THE POSSIBLE
TONIGHT.
>>> GINGER ZEE.
>> GEORGE ZIMMERMAN WANTS THE
STATE THAT PUT HIM ON TRIAL TO
PAY A LOT OF HIS LEGAL COSTS, NO
SMALL AMOUNT AND FLORIDA MAY
HAVE TO DO IT.
HERE'S ABC'S MATT GUTMAN.
>> Reporter: GEORGE ZIMMERMAN IS
A FREE MAN BUT HIS NOT GUILTY
VERDICT COULD COST THE STATE OF
FLORIDA A PRETTY PENNY.
S.
>> WE'RE STILL TALLYING UP THE
FIGURES BUT IT'S GOING TO BE
$200,000 OR $300,000 IN COST
MONEY.
>> Reporter: HE WAS ACQUITTED
LAST MONTH OF A SINGLE COUNT OF
SECOND DEGREE MURDER AFTER
SHOOTING 17-YEAR-OLD TRAYVON
MARTIN IN FEBRUARY 2012.
ACCORDING TO FLORIDA LAW,
BECAUSE OF THAT HE HAS THE RIGHT
TO EXPENSE, QUOTE,
REASONABLE EXPENSES BUT NOT
LAWYERS FEES.
HE CAN EXPENSE EXPERT WITNESSES,
TRAVEL, PHOTO COPIES AND
POSSIBLY THE 3-D PHOTO USED IN
THE COURTROOM.
HIS LAWYERS EXPECT A FIGHT.
>> THERE IS A LOT OF MONEY
OUTSTANDING THAT HAS NOT BEEN
COVERED.
>> Reporter: ZIMMERMAN'S
ATTORNEYS SAY THEIR CLIENT HAS
BEEN LIVING OFF OF DONATIONS TO
HIS WEBSITE.
THE FEE FOR THEIR SERVICES COULD
HAVE TOPPED $2 MILLION.
AS FOR HIS WHEREABOUTS, THEY ARE
STILL UNKNOWN.
HIS LAWYERS SAY HE'S IN HIDING,
BUT HE'S BEEN SPOTTED LAST MONTH
IN TEXAS BY A STATE TROOPER WHO
DIDN'T SEEM TO KNOW WHO HE WAS.
>> YOU DIDN'T SEE MY NAME?
>> NO.
WHAT A COINCIDENCE.
>> Reporter: THREE WEEKS LATER
THIS PHOTO WITH THE OWN OF A GUN
FACTORY IN FLORIDA, THE SAME
MANUFACTURER THAT MADE THE GUN
USED TO SHOOT MARTIN.
HE MAY BE BACK IN COURT SOON,
HIS WIFE FACES A PERJURY CHARGE
FOR LYING TO THE COURT ABOUT
DONATIONS.
HIS WIFE PLEADED NOT GUILTY AND
HAS A COURT HEARING TOMORROW.
MATT GUTMAN, ABC NEWS, MIAMI.
>>> NOW TONIGHT WE HEAR A FORMER
PRESIDENT TALK ABOUT THE MOMENT
SOMEONE TRIED TO ASSASSINATE
HIM.
IT'S A LONG LOST TAPE OF
PRESIDENT GERALD FORD
TESTIFYING, DESCRIBING THE
MOMENT BACK IN 1975 WHEN THAT
STRANGE WOMAN IN RED, A MEMBER
OF THE MANSON FAMILY CALLED
SQUEAKY FROMME EMERGED FROM A
CROWD IN SACRAMENTO.
HE SAYS HE LOOKED AT HER FACE.
HE DESCRIBED IT AS WEATHERED AND
THEN HE SAYS HE SAW THE GUN.
HERE ARE HIS WORDS.
>> I HAD THE IMPRESSION SHE
WANTED TO SPEAK TO ME OR SHAKE
MY HAND AND AS I MOVED TO EITHER
SHAKE HANDS OR SPEAK TO HER, I
THEN NOTICED THE GUN.
>> SQUEAKY FROMME WORE A KIND OF
NUN'S RED ROBE THAT DAY.
SHE SAID SHE ONLY WANTED TO GET
FORD'S ATTENTION TO DISCUSS RED
WOOD TREES WITH HIM.
SHE DIDN'T FIRE A SHOT, SERVED
34 YEARS IN PRISON AND IS NOW
OUT ON PAROLE LIVING IN UPSTATE
NEW YORK.
>>> AND FROM WASHINGTON TONIGHT,
THE GOVERNMENT PROGRAM SPENDING
BILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN TAXPAYER
MONEY SO EVERYONE CAN WORK
FASTER ONLINE.
BUT WHAT ABOUT THE $1 MILLION WE
FOUND GOING TO WASTE IN JUST ONE
CLOSET.
ENOUGH MONEY TO PAY FOR DOZENS
OF TEACHERS.
OUR WATCH DOG, DAVID KERLEY,
BACK ON THE CASE OF THE COSTLY
PROGRAM.
>> Reporter: SPEED, WE CRAVE IT
ON THE INTERNET.
A FAST CONNECTION.
AND WE NEED IT TO REMAIN
COMPETITIVE IN A GLOBAL ECONOMY
SAYS THE PRESIDENT.
>> TO HARNESS THE FULL POWER OF
THE INTERNET.
THAT MEANS FASTER AND MORE
WIDELY AVAILABLE BROADBAND.
>> Reporter: TO SPREAD BROADBAND
ACROSS THE COUNTRY THE
GOVERNMENT CAME UP WITH $7
BILLION AND THOUSANDS OF
COMMUNITIES HAVE BEEN HOOKED UP.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS.
THESE BOXES STACKED IN A WEST
VIRGINIA CLOSET ARE BLAZING
FAST, HIGH SPEED ROUTERS.
YOU PAID FOR THEM, 20 GRAND
EACH.
THEY'RE UNUSED.
THE STATE BOUGHT TOO MANY AND
THE WRONG ONES.
ONE AND A QUARTER MILLION JUST
IN THIS CLOSET GATHERING DUST
FOR THREE YEARS NOW, ENOUGH FOR
A YEAR'S PAY FOR 30 TEACHERS.
THAT'S NOT ALL.
CONGRESSIONAL INVESTIGATORS
QUESTIONED OTHER SPENDING ASKING
IF UP TO $230 MILLION WAS
WASTED.
>> IT'S THE PEOPLE'S DOLLARS
THAT WE'RE DEALING WITH.
NONE OF IT SHOULD BE WASTED.
IN THIS CASE IT'S OBSCENE.
>> Reporter: IN WEST VIRGINIA
ALONE, $14 MILLION WASTED
ACCORDING TO THE STATE AUDITOR
THERE.
CRITICS WORRY ABOUT WHERE THE
MONEY WAS SPENT.
WHEN THEY DID USE THOSE ROUTERS
IN WEST VIRGINIA, THEY PUT SOME
IN PLACES LIKE THIS, THE SMALL
COMMUNITY LIBRARY IN
SHEPHERDSTOWN.
THERE ARE LESS THAN 5,000 ANNUAL
VISITORS TO THIS LIBRARY WHO NOW
HAVE SCREAMING FAST SERVICE, BUT
TWO LOCAL HIGH SCHOOLS NEARBY
GOT NONE OF THOSE ROUTERS.
>> OF COURSE THE HIGH SCHOOLS
SHOULD GET IT.
>> I DON'T THINK THE GOVERNMENT
REALLY DOES A GOOD JOB SPENDING
MONEY AT ALL.
>> Reporter: IS THE GOVERNMENT
DOING ENOUGH TO MAKE SURE THE
MONEY IS WELL SPENT?
WE WENT TO ASK A TOP OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION OFFICIAL
RESPONSIBLE FOR MOST OF THE
SPENDING, LARRY STRICKLING.
>> CAN WE ASK HIM A COUPLE OF
QUESTIONS BEFORE THE HEARING?
>> NO, NO.
>> Reporter: AFTER BEING GRILLED
BY MEMBERS OF CONGRESS --
>> WHAT HAVE WE GOT FOR $2.8
MILLION?
>> Reporter: HE REFUSED TO STOP.
HE DID DEFEND THE PROGRAM.
>> WE'RE QUITE HAPPY WITH THE
PROGRAM.
>> Reporter: HAPPY?
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS SAY THEY
STILL CAN'T GET ANSWERS, AND ASK
HOW MUCH REALLY WAS WASTED?
DAVID KERLEY, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> AND WE THANK ALL OF YOU WHO
WROTE US ABOUT OUR WATCH DOG
REPORTS ON FACEBOOK LAST NIGHT.
WE WANT TO HEAR MORE OF YOUR
THOUGHTS.
KEEP THEM COMING.
>>> STILL AHEAD HERE ON "WORLD
NEWS," A CLOSE SOCIETY UNDER THE
SPOTLIGHT TONIGHT, SECRETS
REVEALED.
DO THE AMISH REALLY HAVE A
MAFIA?
>> AND THE IMAGE ROCKETED AROUND
THE WORLD, THE STORY BEHIND THIS
NOW VERY FAMOUS PICTURE.
AT HUMANA, OUR MEDICARE AGENTS
SIT DOWN WITH YOU AND ASK.
HANGING OUT WITH THIS GUY.
HE'S JUST THE LOVE OF MY LIFE.
[ Male Announcer ]
GETTING TO KNOW YOU
IS HOW WE HELP YOU CHOOSE
THE HUMANA MEDICARE PLAN
THAT WORKS BEST FOR YOU.
MI FAMILIA.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
WE WANT TO HELP YOU ACHIEVE
YOUR BEST HEALTH,
SO YOU CAN KEEP DOING
THE THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT TO YOU.
KEEPING UP WITH THEM.
I LOVE IT!
[ Male Announcer ]
HELPING YOU --
NOW THAT'S WHAT'S IMPORTANT
TO US.
We provide the exact
individualization
that your body needs.
This Labor Day, don't invest in
a mattress
until you visit a Sleep Number
store.
Once you experience it, there's
no going back. Oh, yeah!
At our Biggest Sale of the
Year,
every bed is on sale.
Queen mattresses now start
at just $599.
And through Labor Day
only,
save 50% on our Limited
Edition
Memory Foam mattress sets.
Only at a Sleep Number
store.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
I WORKED A PATROL UNIT FOR 17
YEARS IN THE CITY OF BALTIMORE.
WHEN I FIRST STARTED
EXPERIENCING THE PAIN,
IT'S, IT'S HARD TO DESCRIBE
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A NUMBNESS...
BUT YET YOU HAVE THE PAIN
LIKE THOUSANDS OF NEEDLES
STICKING IN YOUR FOOT.
IT WAS PROGRESSIVELY
GETTING WORSE,
AND AT THAT POINT
I KNEW I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
WHEN I WENT BACK
TO MY HEALTHCARE PROFESSIONAL...
THAT'S WHEN SHE SUGGESTED
THE LYRICA.
ONCE I STARTED
TAKING THE LYRICA,
THE PAIN STARTED SUBSIDING.
[ Male Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW, OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYESIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO HAVE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
TO HEAR MORE OF TERRY'S STORY,
VISIT LYRICA.COM.
>>> THERE ARE ABOUT 250,000
AMISH LIVING PEACEFUL, SIMPLE
LIVES RIGHT HERE IN THE UNITED
STATES.
THE GROUP THAT SHUNS THE MODERN
WORLD SAYS TONIGHT THAT A
REALITY SHOW ABOUT THEM IS
ANYTHING BUT REAL.
ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS DECIDED TO
LOOK AT WHAT'S BEHIND THE AMISH
MAFIA.
>> Reporter: IN LANCASTER
COUNTY, PENNSYLVANIA, SOME
50,000 AMISH LIVE AS THEY HAVE
FOR NEARLY 300 YEARS, SIMPLY AND
HUMBLY, ALMOST NO MODERN
TECHNOLOGY.
BUT A HIT REALITY SHOW IS
PAINTING THIS PEACEFUL CHRISTIAN
COMMUNITY AS BRIMMING WITH
INTRIGUE AND CONTROVERSY.
>> THE MAFIA OPERATES OUTSIDE OF
AMISH LAW.
>> Reporter: "THE AMISH MAFIA,"
IN ITS SECOND SEASON, AIRING
TONIGHT ON DISCOVERY CHANNEL
FOLLOWS THIS MAN, "LEBANON
LEVI," AND HIS ASSISTANTS, WHO
PURPORTEDLY LOOK AFTER THE AMISH
COMMUNITY HERE IN LANCASTER
COUNTY, AND DO THE DIRTY WORK
THE CHURCH CAN'T.
>> LEVI'S A GREAT GUY, BUT IF
YOU CROSS HIM, HE'S NOT AFRAID
TO CRACK SOME SKULLS.
>> Reporter: THEY ARE SAID TO
WORK AS AN INTERNAL POLICE
SYSTEM THAT TAKES THE MATTERS OF
THEIR COMMUNITY INTO THEIR OWN
HANDS.
THEY ALSO KEEP AN EYE ON THE
TEENAGERS, WHO TAKE TIME OFF TO
EXPERIENCE THE OUTSIDE WORLD
BEFORE COMMITTING THEIR LIVES TO
THE SECT.
>> I MAKE SURE THE PEACE IS
BEING KEPT AND EVERYBODY IS
OBEYING THE RULES.
>> Reporter: AS A WHOLE, THE
AMISH DENY THE EXISTENCE OF THE
AMISH MAFIA.
MUCH OF THE SHOW'S CONTENT HAS
BEEN STRONGLY CRITICIZED BY
AMISH SCHOLARS.
QUESTIONS HAVE EVEN BEEN RAISED
AS TO WHETHER SOME OF THE CAST
MEMBERS ARE ACTORS.
BUT PRODUCERS SAY THE MAIN CAST
MEMBERS AREN'T ACTORS, THEY JUST
HAVEN'T BEEN BAPTIZED IN THE
AMISH CHURCH SO TECHNICALLY THE
STRICT RULES DON'T APPLY.
SO WHY HAVE YOU NOT DECIDED NOT
TO GET BAPTIZED?
>> I'D RATHER HAVE A COMPUTER
AND WATCH TV, MAYBE.
DRIVE A CAR, AND NOT DRIVE A
HORSE.
>> Reporter: IF THIS SHOW IS
REAL REALITY TV, THEN THE
"CENTURIES-OLD PLAIN" LIFESTYLE
CERTAINLY ISN'T WHAT IT USED TO
BE.
LINSEY DAVIS, ABC NEWS,
LANCASTER COUNTY, PENNSYLVANIA.
>> THERE WILL BE MORE OF THE
HIDDEN AMISH COMMUNITY TONIGHT
ON "NIGHTLINE."
BE SURE TO WATCH.
>>> STILL AHEAD HERE, A
SURVEILLANCE TAPE WE NEVER
EXPECTED TO SEE.
HERE'S THE WONDERFUL STORY
COMING UP NEXT.
EXPECTED TO SEE.
HERE'S THE WONDERFUL STORY
COMING UP NEXT.
Does your mouth often feel like
it lacks enough saliva
to keep it comfortably moist?
Losing saliva's natural
protection can triple your risk
of cavities, bad breath, or
mouth infections.
Do more than just sip water.
Try number-one dentist
recommended Biotène.
Do more th♪n just sip water.
(Announcer) Answer the call of
the grill
with new Friskies Grillers,
full of meaty tenders and
crunchy bites.
SEE, I KNEW TESTOSTERONE
COULD AFFECT SEX DRIVE,
BUT NOT ENERGY
OR EVEN MY MOOD.
THAT'S WHEN I TALKED
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD TESTS...
SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.
THAT'S IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.
[ Male Announcer ]
TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T
HAVE ANDROGEL
1.62% TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED
TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY
INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.
WOMEN AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WITH APPLICATION SITES.
DISCONTINUE ANDROGEL
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED SIGNS
OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,
WHICH MAY INCLUDE
CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE,
POSSIBLY DUE
TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER
OR WHO HAVE OR MIGHT HAVE
PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING,
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
WORSENING
OF AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,
POSSIBLE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER,
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING
OF ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY,
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS,
PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP,
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS,
ESPECIALLY INSULIN,
CORTICOSTEROIDS, OR MEDICINES
TO DECREASE BLOOD CLOTTING.
IN A CLINICAL STUDY, OVER 80%
OF TREATED MEN HAD THEIR
T LEVELS RESTORED TO NORMAL.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.
CHANGE YOUR NUMBER. TURN IT UP.
ANDROGEL 1.62%.
>>> RIGHAT THE
>>> Right at the top of our
"Instant Index" tonight,
finally someone caught on tape
doing the right thing.
At buddy small lots in New
Jersey, several shoppers were in
the store to make purchases.
there is no clerk around because
it turns out the door was
mistakenly left wide open.
the store was closed to be
closed.
the men got sunglasses,
batteries, waited for a cashier
but finally gave up.
so they added up their own bill
and left the money on the
counter.
the owner said he wanted them to
come back.
today they did and he let them
go on a shopping spree for free.
>>> we have a glimpse of Cher
noble tonight nearly 30 years
after the disaster of the
nuclear plant.
it's being reclaimed by mother
earth.
new images showing how the trees
and weeds sprung up around the
nuclear site, tops of buildings
peeking out.
here's what the city of 49,000
looked like before the radiation
and here it is now.
scientists say it will not be
safe for human habitation for
another 20,000 years.
>>> tonight a father is
defending his daughter.
hate it or not, people were
outraged by the performance at
the video music awards.
that's Miley Cyrus with Robin
Thicke.
so many parents angry, but
tonight her father, Billy ray
CYRUS, is weighing in,
supporting his daughter and
saying, "I love her
unconditionally and that will
never change."
>>> when we come back here, a
smiling couple and why America
is smiling with them, a now
famous photo, the inspiring
story behind it.
PHOTO, THE INSPIRING
STORY BEHIND IT.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR HELP
RELIEVING HEARTBURN,
CAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES
24-HOUR HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL
PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
A MAN WHO DOESN'T STAND STILL.
BUT JIM HAS AFIB,
ATRIAL FIBRILLATION --
AN IRREGULAR HEARTBEAT,
NOT CAUSED
BY A HEART VALVE PROBLEM.
THAT PUTS JIM AT A GREATER RISK
OF STROKE.
FOR YEARS,
JIM'S MEDICINE TIED HIM
TO A MONTHLY TRIP TO THE CLINIC
TO GET HIS BLOOD TESTED.
BUT NOW, WITH ONCE-A-DAY
XARELTO®, JIM'S ON THE MOVE.
JIM'S DOCTOR
RECOMMENDED XARELTO®.
LIKE WARFARIN,
XARELTO® IS PROVEN EFFECTIVE
TO REDUCE AFIB-RELATED
STROKE RISK.
BUT XARELTO® IS THE FIRST
AND ONLY ONCE-A-DAY
PRESCRIPTION BLOOD THINNER
FOR PATIENTS WITH AFIB
NOT CAUSED
BY A HEART VALVE PROBLEM.
THAT DOESN'T REQUIRE
ROUTINE BLOOD MONITORING.
SO JIM'S NOT TIED
TO THAT MONITORING ROUTINE.
[ GPS ]
PROCEED TO THE DESIGNATED ROUTE.
NOT TODAY.
[ Male Announcer ]
FOR PATIENTS CURRENTLY
WELL MANAGED ON WARFARIN,
THERE IS LIMITED INFORMATION
ON HOW XARELTO®
AND WARFARIN COMPARE
IN REDUCING THE RISK OF STROKE.
XARELTO® IS JUST ONE PILL A DAY
TAKEN WITH THE EVENING MEAL.
PLUS, WITH NO KNOWN
DIETARY RESTRICTIONS,
JIM CAN EAT
THE HEALTHY FOODS HE LIKES.
DO NOT STOP TAKING XARELTO®,
RIVAROXABAN,
WITHOUT TALKING TO THE DOCTOR
WHO PRESCRIBES IT
AS THIS MAY INCREASE THE RISK
OF HAVING A STROKE.
GET HELP RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU DEVELOP ANY SYMPTOMS
LIKE BLEEDING,
UNUSUAL BRUISING,
OR TINGLING.
YOU MAY HAVE
A HIGHER RISK OF BLEEDING
IF YOU TAKE XARELTO®
WITH ASPIRIN PRODUCTS,
NSAIDS OR BLOOD THINNERS.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
BEFORE TAKING XARELTO®
IF YOU HAVE ABNORMAL BLEEDING.
XARELTO® CAN CAUSE BLEEDING,
WHICH CAN BE SERIOUS,
AND RARELY MAY LEAD TO DEATH.
YOU ARE LIKELY TO BRUISE
MORE EASILY ON XARELTO®
AND IT MAY TAKE LONGER
FOR BLEEDING TO STOP.
TELL YOUR DOCTORS
YOU ARE TAKING XARELTO®
BEFORE ANY PLANNED MEDICAL
OR DENTAL PROCEDURES.
BEFORE STARTING XARELTO®,
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ANY CONDITIONS
SUCH AS KIDNEY, LIVER,
OR BLEEDING PROBLEMS.
XARELTO® IS NOT FOR PATIENTS
WITH ARTIFICIAL HEART VALVES.
JIM CHANGED HIS ROUTINE.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT XARELTO®.
ONCE A DAY XARELTO® MEANS
NO REGULAR BLOOD MONITORING --
NO KNOWN DIETARY RESTRICTIONS.
FOR MORE INFORMATION
AND SAVINGS OPTIONS,
CALL 1-888-XARELTO
OR VISIT GOXARELTO.COM.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT THERE IS A
PHOTO OF A PICTURE PERFECT
COUPLE.
YOU MIGHT HAVE NO IDEA OF THE
STORY BEHIND IT, BUT IT IS
INCREDIBLY BEAUTIFUL ABOUT
SOMEONE WHO IS BRAVE, SOMEONE
WHO IS LIKE SUNLIGHT AND
TOGETHER HOW THEY GAVE A LESSON
TO EVERYONE.
ABC'S JON DONVAN.
>> Reporter: IN THE
"PICTURE'S-WORTH-A-THOUSAND-
WORDS" CATEGORY, WHAT ARE SOME
WORDS THIS ONE CALLS UP?
OF A COUPLE TAKING THE DAY A
PHOTOGRAPHER DROPPED BY FOR A
BUNCH OF FAMILY PHOTOS.
BUT THIS ONE, SPONTANEOUS, THE
PHOTOGRAPHER HAPPENED TO PUT ON
FACEBOOK, AND THEN IT ROCKETED.
AN INTIMATE MOMENT -- SHE HELPS
HIM LIKE THIS A LOT -- THAT WENT
VIRAL BECAUSE OF THE WORDS THAT
WERE NOT SPOKEN.
LIKE THE WORD SERIOUS AS IN
SERIOUS PAIN.
BACK IN AFGHANISTAN JESSE COTTLE
STEPPED ON AN IED, THE AFTER
MATH
OVERHEARD VIA A FELLOW MARINE'S
HELMET CAMERA -- JOINING HIM TO
BACK THEN, 2009, HOME BUT NOT
HOME, AS HIS MOM SAID THEN --
>> SHE CAME INTO HIS LIFE WHEN
MANY WOULD LOOK AWAY.
KELLY BECAME HIS WIFE WHEN THE
TRUTH IS MANY WOULD BACK AWAY.
WHEN SHE LOOKS AT JESSE --
>> HIS PERSONALITY AND THE WAY
HE IS OUTWEIGHS HIS INJURIES BY
SO MUCH THAT YOU SORT OF FORGET
ABOUT IT AFTER A WHILE.
>> Reporter: HOW ABOUT THE WORD
STRENGTH, THE PURE PHYSICAL KIND
IT TAKES TO DO THIS, HER BACK,
HER ARMS.
THESE WIVES NEED THAT KIND OF
STRENGTH AND THE OTHER KIND.
>> HER INTERNAL STRENGTH IS
PROBABLY EVEN GREATER AND
SOMETHING I'M VERY THANKFUL FOR
AS WELL.
>> Reporter: FINALLY WORD
GRATIFYING FOR IT IS FOR THE
REST OF US WHO DO NOT KNOW THE
WAR WOUNDED THAT THESE TWO GAVE
US A STORY OF THE TRUTH OF THE
LOSS HE GAVE TO US THAT SAYS
WITHOUT WORDS THAT THERE IS A
WAY BACK HOME.
JON DONVAN, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>> WE THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
WATCHING TONIGHT.
WE'RE ALWAYS THERE AT
ABCNEWS.COM, "NIGHTLINE" LATER
AND I'LL SEE YOU AGAIN RIGHT
BACK HERE TOMORROW NIGHT.
>> TONIGHT A FAIRFIELD GRASS
FIRE SPREADS THROUGHOUT THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> ALSO, FLAMES FROM THE RIM
FIRE HAVE NOW REACHES HETCH
HETCHY.
WE'RE LIVE AS FIREFIGHTERS
THERE BEGIN TO MAKE HEADWAY.
>> AND HOW TO GET 280,000
COMMUTER AS CROSS THE BAY
TRANCE YILT AGENCIES REV UP
FOR A BRIDGE CLOSURE.
>> THE TRAFFIC APP HELPING
EVERYBODY GET AROUND WHEN THE
BAY BRIDGE SHUTS DOWN IS NOW
HANDS FREE.
>> THAT BREAKING NEWS IS THE
STORY WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING.
A LIVE PICTURE OVER A
NEIGHBORHOOD IN FAIRFIELD
TODAY THAT WENT UP IN FLAMES
THIS AFTERNOON.
SEVERAL HOMES HAVE BEEN
DESTROYED IN WHAT APPEARS TO
BE A STRING OF SPOT FIRES
ALONG INTERSTATE 80.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYBODY, I'M
LARRY BEIL.
>> AND I'M CAROLYN JOHNSON.
THE STARTED AS A GRASS FIRE,
FIRST REPORTED AFTER 3:30 THIS
AFTERNOON, NEAR INTERSTATE 80
BUT QUICKLY SPREAD THROUGH THE
ADJACENT NEIGHBORHOOD AND
DESTROYED SEVERAL HOMES.
>> WITHIN A HALF HOUR, SKY 7
WAS ON THE SCENE.
IT WAS CLEAR THIS WAS NO
ORDINARY VEGETATION BLAZE.
FLAMES SPREAD ACROSS THE
STRETCH OF HOMES ALONG THE
FREEWAY.
WE SAW SEVERAL HOMES LIVE,
ENGULFED IN FLAMES, WE CAN
TELL YOU FIVE, POSSIBLY SIX
HOMES WERE DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED.
>> NOW 50 OTHERS HAVE BEEN
EVACUATED INCLUDING AN
APARTMENT BUILDING ON NORTH
TEXAS STREET.
AND AN EVACUATION CENTER HAS
BEEN ESTABLISHED FOR ALL OF
THE PEOPLE WHO HAD TO LEAVE
THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
>> WE HAVE A VIEW OF THE FIRE
FIGHT.
THE ROARER NEWSPAPER SHARED US
THIS VIDEO USING TOUT VIDEO
SHARING APP.
CREWS FOUGHT THE FIRE USING
LADDER CREWS, YOU CAN SEE THE
CONCERNED NEIGHBORS LOOKING ON
AS FIREFIGHTERS RUSHED TO THE
SCENE OF BASICALLY EVERY TIME
THEY TURNED ANOTHER FIRE WAS
BREAKING OUT.
>> TRAVIS AIR FORCE BASE SENT
CREWS TO HELP BATTLE THIS,
THEY DO NOW HAVE FOUR UNITS ON
THE SCENE.
WE HAVE A VIEW TO SHARE WITH
YOU THIS,