>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND POSSIBLE
MILITARY ACTION AGAINST SYRIA.
THE PRESIDENT NOW SAYING,
"SOMETHING SHOULD HAPPEN" AFTER
THE CHEMICAL ATTACK IN SYRIA.
THIS EVENING, THE PRESIDENT AND
THE DEFENSE DEPARTMENT NOW
WEIGHING OPTIONS AFTER TRUMP
REPEATEDLY SAID BEFORE THAT THE
U.S. SHOULD NOT GET INVOLVED IN
SYRIA.
MARTHA RADDATZ, JON KARL, AND
BRIAN ROSS STANDING BY.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, THE SUDDEN
MOVE TO STEP ASIDE.
THE REPUBLICAN LEADING THE HOUSE
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIAN
MEDDLING AND ANY POSSIBLE
COLLUSION, NOW RECUSING HIMSELF.
>> DID YOU DISCLOSE ANY
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION?
>> WHAT NEXT IN THE
INVESTIGATION?
>>> IN THE SENATE TONIGHT, THE
SHOWDOWN OVER THE SUPREME COURT.
REPUBLICAN SENATORS CHANGING THE
RULES, USING THE SO-CALLED
"NUCLEAR" OPTION, SET TO PUSH
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S PICK THROUGH.
>>> SEVERE STORMS AS WE COME ON
THE AIR TONIGHT.
AT LEAST 13 REPORTED TORNADOES
ALREADY.
50 MILLION AMERICANS BRACING FOR
DANGEROUS STORMS TONIGHT.
>>> AND REMEMBERING AN AMERICAN
GREAT.
TONIGHT, WE CELEBRATE THE LIFE
OF DON RICKLES.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A THURSDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH
FAST-MOVING DEVELOPMENTS ON
SYRIA.
JUST 24 HOURS AFTER PRESIDENT
TRUMP SAID HIS MIND HAD BEEN
CHANGED ON SYRIA, ON BASHAR AL
ASSAD.
TODAY HE SIGNALED HE'S WEIGHING
MILITARY ACTION.
SAYING IN HIS WORDS, SOMETHING
SHOULD HAPPEN.
IT COMES AFTER THE IMAGES OF
THAT HORRIFIC CHEMICAL ATTACK.
DOZENS KILLED BY WHAT TURKISH
OFFICIALS NOW SAY WAS SARIN GAS.
CHILDREN AND BABIES AMONG THE
VICTIMS.
THE SURVIVORS SPRAYED DOWN.
MANY OF THE VICTIMS STRUGGLING
TO BREATHE.
TONIGHT, WE KNOW THAT THE
DEFENSE SECRETARY IS NOW
BRIEFING THE PRESIDENT ON THE
OPTIONS.
WHAT ARE THEY?
AND HOW SOON COULD THIS COME?
ABC'S CHIEF GLOBAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT MARTHA RADDATZ
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, PRESIDENT
TRUMP, WITH HIS STRONGEST WORDS
YET ON THE CRISIS IN SYRIA.
AS THIS PRESIDENT, NOW 77 DAYS
INTO HIS PRESIDENCY, DECIDES
WHETHER TO TAKE MILITARY ACTION.
>> I THINK WHAT ASSAD DID IS
TERRIBLE.
I THINK WHAT HAPPENED IN SYRIA
IS ONE OF THE TRULY EGREGIOUS
CRIMES.
AND IT SHOULDN'T HAVE HAPPENED.
AND IT SHOULDN'T BE ALLOWED TO
HAPPEN.
>> HAVE YOU TALKED TO THE
RUSSIAN PRESIDENT ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED?
>> AT SOME POINT I MAY.
I HAVEN'T, BUT AT SOME POINT I
MAY.
>> DO YOU THINK THAT ASSAD
SHOULD LEAVE POWER IN SYRIA?
>> I THINK WHAT HAPPENED IN
SYRIA IS A DISGRACE TO HUMANITY.
AND HE'S THERE AND I GUESS HE'S
RUNNING THINGS, SO SOMETHING
SHOULD HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT'S
SECRETARY OF STATE, REX
TILLERSON, A MAN OF FEW WORDS
SINCE TAKING OFFICE, TONIGHT
WITH HIS STRONGEST SIGNAL YET,
FOCUSING ON SYRIA'S PRESIDENT.
>> SIR, DOES ASSAD HAVE TO GO?
>> ASSAD'S ROLE IN THE FUTURE IS
UNCERTAIN CLEARLY, AND WITH THE
ACTS HE HAS TAKEN, IT WOULD SEEM
THERE IS NO ROLE FOR HIM TO
GOVERN THE SYRIAN PEOPLE.
>> WILL YOU AND PRESIDENT TRUMP
ORGANIZE AN INTERNATIONAL
COALITION TO REMOVE ASSAD?
>> THOSE STEPS ARE UNDER WAY.
>> Reporter: BUT IT WAS JUST ONE
WEEK AGO, THE SECRETARY OF STATE
SUGGESTED SOMETHING FAR
DIFFERENT, SAYING THE SYRIAN
PEOPLE SHOULD DECIDE WHETHER TO
GET RID OF ASSAD.
THIS SHIFT COMES JUST 24 HOURS
AFTER THE PRESIDENT, WITH THE
WORLD WATCHING, SAID THOSE
IMAGES OF CHILDREN GASSED HAD
CHANGED HIS MIND.
>> I WILL TELL YOU, IT'S ALREADY
HAPPENED THAT MY ATTITUDE TOWARD
SYRIA AND ASSAD HAS CHANGED VERY
MUCH.
I'M NOT SAYING I'M DOING
ANYTHING ONE WAY OR THE OTHER,
BUT I'M CERTAINLY NOT GOING TO
BE TELLING YOU.
>> Reporter: BEFORE HE WAS
PRESIDENT, DONALD TRUMP HAD LONG
ARGUED AGAINST ACTION IN SYRIA,
REPEATEDLY TWEETING ABOUT IT.
BACK IN 2013, AFTER A CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK, WHEN PRESIDENT
OBAMA WAS WEIGHING MILITARY
ACTION, TRUMP TWEETING, "DO NOT
ATTACK SYRIA.
IF YOU DO, MANY BAD THINGS WILL
HAPPEN.
AND FROM THAT FIGHT, THE U.S.
GETS NOTHING!"
TONIGHT, HE IS SIGNALING HIS
STANCE HAS CHANGED.
AND THE RUSSIANS, WHO HAVE BEEN
SUPPORTING SYRIAN LEADER BASHAR
AL ASSAD, SAID TODAY SUPPORT FOR
ASSAD NOT UNCONDITIONAL, BUT
URGING CAUTION.
ON CAPITOL HILL, A LEADING
REPUBLICAN SAID THIS IS A TEST
FOR TRUMP.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS TO MAKE A
DECISION THAT'S GOING TO DEFINE
HIS PRESIDENCY ONE WAY OR THE
OTHER.
IF HE DOES NOTHING, THEN IT'S
GOING TO BE OBAMA ON STEROIDS.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT
HASN'T SAID WHAT HE WOULD DO IN
SYRIA, BUT THERE ARE MANY
MILITARY OPTIONS.
HIT SYRIAN AIRFIELDS TO GROUND
ASSAD'S AIR FORCE.
GO AFTER MILITARY TARGETS SUCH
AS COMMAND AND CONTROL CENTERS.
WHAT COULD WE USE?
SEA-BASED CRUISE MISSILES OR
U.S.-MANNED AIRCRAFT.
RISKIER BUT WE HAVE HIGHLY
SOPHISTICATED WARPLANES.
>> AND MARTHA JOINS ME NOW.
MARTHA WE KNOW
THE PRESIDENT AND THE DEFENSE
SECRETARY ARE NOW TOGETHER.
HE'S BEING BRIEFED ON THE
POTENTIAL OPTIONS.
WE LEARNED THAT THE AIRCRAFT
THAT DROPPED THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS WAS IN FACT A SYRIAN
MILITARY AIRCRAFT.
>> THEY SAY THERE'S NO QUESTION
IT WAS A SYRIAN MILITARY
AIRCRAFT.
WE HAVE SO MUCH MORE EQUIPMENT
THERE OVER SYRIA NOW THEY COULD
ACTUALLY WATCH, GO BACK AND SEE
WHAT KIND OF AIRCRAFT DROPPED
THOSE MUNITIONS.
>> WE HAVE MORE EQUIPMENT THERE.
MARTHA, AS YOU BEEN REPORTING WE
HAVE MORE AMERICAN TROOPS THERE
IN RECENT WEEKS, WE LEARNED OF
HUNDREDS BEING SENT INTO SYRIA.
>> WE DO, DAVID, AND THAT'S A
REAL CONCERN.
IF MILITARY ACTION IS TAKEN
THERE WILL BE A WARNING TO
ASSAD -- DON'T GO ANYWHERE NEAR
THOSE AMERICAN TROOPS, DO NOT
TARGET THEM, BUT THERE'S A RISK.
>> MARTHA, THANK YOU.
>>> AND AS YOU HEARD MARTHA
REPORT, ANY ACTION IF TAKEN
COMES WITH GREAT RISK.
OBAMA WEIGHED MILITARY ACTION
BEFORE.
NOW, RUSSIANS ARE INVOLVED AND
AMERICAN TROOPS ARE THERE.
WHAT ARE THE POSSIBLE TARGET?
AND WHAT ARE THE GREATEST RISKS?
HERE'S BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: FOR THE U.S.
MILITARY TONIGHT, AMONG THE
OPTIONS BEING CONSIDERED ARE THE
VERY PLANS THE PENTAGON PLANNED
FOUR YEARS AGO WHEN A PRIME
TARGET WAS THE SPECIFIC MILITARY
UNIT THAT GUARDED AND DEPLOYED
SYRIA'S CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
UNIT 450, OF THE SYRIAN AIR
FORCE.
>> IF YOU ARE GOING TO STRIKE IN
A WAY THAT IS DIRECTLY RELATED
TO CHEMICAL WEAPONS USE, YOU'D
HAVE TO HIT SOME PART OF UNIT
450.
>> Reporter: THE HORRIFIC IMAGES
THIS WEEK FROM SYRIA PUT A LIE
TO THE SYRIAN AND USA CLAIMS
THAT THE COUNTRY'S STOCKPILE OF
SARIN GAS AND OTHER CHEMICAL
WEAPONS HAD BEEN DESTROYED.
BUT EVEN WITH A DIMINISHED
SUPPLY, A DIRECT STRIKE ON
WHATEVER CHEMICAL WEAPONS REMAIN
STILL RUNS A SERIOUS RISK.
>> IF YOU ARE GOING TO HIT THEM,
IF YOU ARE GOING TO TRY TO BLOW
THEM UP, YOU KNOW, ARE YOU GOING
TO CREATE AGENT PLUMES, WHICH
ARE GOING TO DAMAGE, YOU KNOW,
CIVILIAN AREAS.
>> Reporter: THE U.S. ATTACK
PLAN IN 2013 INCLUDED SYRIAN
AIRFIELDS, TANK DEPOTS AND EVEN
THE MINISTRY OF DEFENSE IN
DOWNTOWN DAMASCUS.
>> THEY CAN GO RIGHT THROUGH A
TEN-FOOT BLOCK OF THAT BUILDING,
SO RIGHT INTO A PARTICULAR
OFFICE.
>> Reporter: BUT ANY ATTACK NOW
COULD BE LESS SWEEPING BECAUSE
OF THE PRESENCE OF RUSSIAN
SOLDIERS AND ADVISERS ACROSS
SYRIAN MILITARY INSTALLATIONS.
ALONG WITH ADVANCED RUSSIAN
ANTI-AIRCRAFT DEFENSE SYSTEMS.
>> LET'S BRING IN BRIAN ROSS.
BRIAN, WE SHOULD CAUTION, WE
DON'T KNOW ANY ACTION IF ANY AT
ALL IS GOING TO BE TAKEN
TONIGHT.
BUT WE HEARD THOSE WORDS JUST 24
HOURS AGO FROM THE U.S.
AMBASSADOR, NIKKI HALEY ASKING
HOW MANY MORE CHILDREN HAVE TO
DIE BEFORE RUSSIA CARES?
THOSE WERE STRONG WORDS.
AIMED AT RUSSIA, VLADIMIR PUTIN.
WE HAVEN'T HEARD PRESIDENT TRUMP
ADDRESS PUTIN IN THAT WAY.
IS THAT A TEST OF THAT
RELATIONSHIP TOO?
>> IN FACT, THE WORLD IS
WATCHING TO SEE IF THE PRESIDENT
IS NOW PREPARED TO CHALLENGE
RUSSIA AND ITS LEADER WHO HE HAS
PRAISED SO MUCH, VLADIMIR PUTIN.
>> BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> AND AS WE KNOW,
SYRIA IS NOT THE ONLY FOREIGN
CRISIS TESTING PRESIDENT TRUMP
TONIGHT.
HIS HIGH-STAKES MEETINGS NOW
WITH CHINA'S PRESIDENT ARRIVING
AT MAR-A-LAGO.
PRESIDENT TRUMP EXPECTED TO TALK
ABOUT NORTH KOREA WITH HIM.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAVING JUST
SAID THAT, IF CHINA DOESN'T FIX
THE NORTH KOREAN ISSUE, THE U.S.
WILL.
ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL IN
FLORIDA TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: AS HE CONSIDERS
OPTIONS ON SYRIA, TODAY, WITH A
MASSIVE STORM HITTING
WASHINGTON, PRESIDENT TRUMP FLEW
TO MAR-A-LAGO TO FACE ANOTHER
CRISIS, NORTH KOREA'S ADVANCING
NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
AND TONIGHT, HIS MOST IMPORTANT
FOREIGN MEETING YET, GREETING
THE LEADER OF THE COUNTRY HE'S
PREVIOUSLY CALLED OUR ENEMY,
CHINESE PRESIDENT XI JINPING.
>> WE'RE GOING TO BE TALKING
ABOUT BOTH TRADE, NORTH KOREA
AND MANY OTHER THINGS.
>> Reporter: THROUGHOUT HIS
CAMPAIGN, TRUMP HAD HARSH WORDS
FOR CHINA.
>> WE CAN'T CONTINUE TO ALLOW
CHINA TO RAPE OUR COUNTRY AND
THAT'S WHAT THEY ARE DOING.
THEY'RE TAKING OUR BUSINESS.
THEY'RE TAKING OUR JOBS.
THEY'RE MAKING OUR PRODUCT.
CHINA'S WONDERFUL, BUT THEY'RE
GETTING AWAY WITH MURDER.
>> Reporter: BUT NOW TRUMP NEEDS
CHINA TO TURN UP THE HEAT ON
NORTH KOREA.
JUST A FEW WEEKS AGO TWEETING,
"NORTH KOREA IS BEHAVING VERY
BADLY.
CHINA HAS DONE LITTLE TO HELP!"
AND AS HE FACES THESE
HIGH-STAKES INTERNATIONAL
CHALLENGES, MORE DETAILS ABOUT
THAT WHITE HOUSE SHAKE-UP
INVOLVING THE PRESIDENT'S CHIEF
STRATEGIST, STEVE BANNON.
A HIGHLY CONTROVERSIAL FIGURE,
BANNON WAS DUBBED "THE GREAT
MANIPULATOR" BY "TIME" MAGAZINE.
BUT ACCORDING TO WHITE HOUSE
SOURCES, HE HAS RECENTLY CLASHED
WITH JARED KUSHNER, THE
PRESIDENT'S SON-IN-LAW.
AND YESTERDAY, HE WAS REMOVED
FROM THE NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL.
WHILE WHITE HOUSE SOURCES TELL
US HE THREATENED TO QUIT THE
ADMINISTRATION OVER THE MOVE,
BANNON HIMSELF TELLS ABC NEWS
THAT'S NOT TRUE, CALLING IT
ABSURD.
>> I THINK WE HAVE SHAKEN THINGS
UP, BUT I THINK WE'VE HAD ONE OF
THE MOST SUCCESSFUL 13 WEEKS IN
THE HISTORY OF THE PRESIDENCY.
>> Reporter: THE CHALLENGES
AHEAD ARE SHAPING UP TO BE FAR
GREATER THAN THE ONES HE HAS
FACED SO FAR.
>>> LET'S BRING IN JON KARL.
LIVE IN WEST PALM BEACH.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND CHINA'S
PRESIDENT XI SITTING DOWN
TONIGHT FOR THE FIRST TIME.
WE ALL REMEMBER, AS YOU REPORTED
THERE, THE PRESIDENT'S ATTACKS
ON CHINA DURING THE CAMPAIGN AT
ONE POINT CALLING THEM OUR
ENEMY.
BUT THE WHITE HOUSE REALLY
THINKS THERE'S AN OPPORTUNITY
HERE?
>> THEY DO.
THEY EXPECT THAT THERE WILL BE
AGREEMENTS COMING OUT OF THIS
THAT WILL MEAN CHINESE
INVESTMENT AND AMERICAN JOBS
AND, REGARDING NORTH KOREA THE
PRESIDENT HIMSELF SAID TODAY,
QUOTE, I THINK CHINA WILL BE
STEPPING UP.
DAVID.
>> A LOT ON THE AGENDA THERE IN
FLORIDA.
JON KARL, THANKS TO YOU.
>>> MEANTIME ON CAPITOL HILL,
TONIGHT, THE SUDDEN MOVE TO STEP
ASIDE.
THE REPUBLICAN LEADING THE HOUSE
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIAN
MEDDLING AND POSSIBLE COLLUSION
IS NOW RECUSING HIMSELF.
OUR CORRESPONDENT FINDING HIM AS
HE LEFT THE CAPITOL HILL.
HERE'S ABC'S CECILIA VEGA.
>> Reporter: ON CAPITOL HILL
TODAY, HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE CHAIRMAN DEVIN NUNES
RUSHING TO GET OUT OF TOWN.
>> CONGRESSMAN?
>> Reporter: DODGING QUESTIONS
AFTER RECUSING HIMSELF FROM THE
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION BECAUSE HE
IS NOW THE SUBJECT OF A HOUSE
ETHICS PROBE.
>> DID YOU DISCLOSE ANY
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION?
>> I ISSUED A STATEMENT, AND YOU
GUYS HAVE IT, SO.
>> WHY DID YOU CHANGE YOUR MIND
THOUGH?
YOU HAD SAID THIS WAS ALL
POLITICS?
>> I SENT OUT A STATEMENT AND
THAT'S MY -- MY STATEMENT WILL
STAND.
>> BUT YOUR RESPONSE TO THE
COMPLAINT SPECIFICALLY.
DID YOU DISCLOSE ANY CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION?
>> I TOLD YOU I SENT OUT A
STATEMENT AND MY STATEMENT WILL
STAND.
>> Reporter: THE HOUSE ETHICS
COMMITTEE RELEASING FEW DETAILS,
SAYING ONLY THAT THE COMMITTEE
IS AWARE OF PUBLIC ALLEGATIONS
THAT REPRESENTATIVE DEVIN NUNES
MAY HAVE MADE UNAUTHORIZED
DISCLOSURES OF CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION.
NUNES BLAMING SEVERAL LEFT-WING
ACTIVIST GROUPS, ADDING, "THE
CHARGES ARE ENTIRELY FALSE AND
POLITICALLY MOTIVATED."
THE CONGRESSMAN HAS BEEN UNDER
FIRE FOR WEEKS.
A MEMBER OF THE PRESIDENT'S
TRANSITION TEAM, NUNES ACCUSED
OF BEING TOO CLOSE TO THE WHITE
HOUSE TO CONDUCT AN IMPARTIAL
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIAN
MEDDLING IN THE ELECTION AND
POSSIBLE COLLUSION, ESPECIALLY
AFTER HE CLAIMED TO HAVE
EVIDENCE THAT MEMBERS OF TEAM
TRUMP WERE PICKED UP IN
INCIDENTAL SURVEILLANCE, AND HE
RUSHED TO THE WHITE HOUSE TO
BRIEF THE PRESIDENT.
>> WHAT I'VE READ BOTHERS ME,
AND I THINK IT SHOULD BOTHER THE
PRESIDENT HIMSELF AND HIS TEAM.
>> Reporter: BUT JUST DAYS
LATER, IT WAS REVEALED THAT VERY
INTELLIGENCE NUNES SHARED WITH
THE PRESIDENT WAS GIVEN TO HIM
BY WHITE HOUSE AIDES.
TODAY, THE TOP DEMOCRAT ON THE
HOUSE INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE,
APPLAUDING NUNES FOR RECUSING
HIMSELF.
>> IS THIS ENOUGH TO PUT YOUR
INVESTIGATION BACK ON TRACK IN
TERMS OF PUBLIC PERCEPTION?
>> I CERTAINLY HOPE SO.
IT SHOULD BE.
>> CECILIA VEGA WITH US NOW LIVE
AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
NOW THAT CONGRESSMAN NUNES HAS
RECUSED HIMSELF, WHO WILL BE
HEADING UP THE HOUSE
INVESTIGATION INTO RUSSIA.
>> DAVID, THAT JOB GOES TO TEXAS
CONGRESSMAN MICHAEL CONAWAY.
HE'S NOW PROMISING TO CONDUCT A
BIPARTISAN INVESTIGATION.
ALSO HELPING THEM THOUGH TREY
GOWDY, THE PERSON WHO CHAIRED
THAT SELECT COMMITTEE
INVESTIGATING BENGHAZI.
DAVID.
>> CECILIA VEGA BACK AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
AFTER THAT MOMENT ON CAPITOL
HILL.
THANK YOU, CECILIA.
>>> NOW TO THE SHOWDOWN OVER THE
SUPREME COURT TONIGHT AND TO
THAT HISTORIC MOVE IN THE
SENATE.
REPUBLICANS TRIGGERING THE
THE REPUBLICANS TRIGGERING THE
SO-CALLED NUCLEAR OPTION, THAT
SETS UP A VOTE TOMORROW.
NOW TO CONFIRM SUPREME COURT
NOMINEE NEIL GORSUCH BY A SIMPLE
MAJORITY.
THE REPUBLICANS WON'T NEED ANY
VOTES FROM DEMOCRATS.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE TONIGHT ON THE
FALLOUT.
>> Reporter: THE REPUBLICAN
LEADER TODAY EMERGED FROM THE
PARTISAN BATTLEFIELD WITH A
THUMBS UP.
THE TOP DEMOCRAT, HIS HEAD HUNG
LOW IN DEFEAT.
LEFT BEHIND, THE CASUALTIES, A
SENATE AND A SUPREME COURT
FUNDAMENTALLY ALTERED.
>> THE YEAs ARE 48 AND THE NAYs
ARE 52.
>> Reporter: WITH DEMOCRATS
BLOCKING THE PRESIDENT'S NOMINEE
NEIL GORSUCH, REPUBLICANS MAKING
A CONTROVERSIAL PLAY, CHANGING
THE SENATE RULES TO CONFIRM
SUPREME COURT NOMINEES FROM NOW
ON WITH A SIMPLE MAJORITY VOTE,
LOWERING THE THRESHOLD FROM 60
VOTES TO JUST 51.
A MOVE SO DRASTIC IT'S KNOWN AS
THE "NUCLEAR OPTION."
FOR TWO DAYS, DEMOCRATS PUT UP A
FIGHT ON THE FLOOR, ONE SENATOR
TALKING FOR 15 HOURS STRAIGHT.
>> THIS IS AN EXTREME NOMINEE
FROM THE FAR RIGHT.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING, THEY
HAD THE VOTES TO BLOCK GORSUCH,
BUT REPUBLICANS WERE PREPARED TO
GO NUCLEAR.
>> CERTAINLY, I THINK THIS STEP
IS WORTH IT.
>> Reporter: MANY OTHERS WERE
HESITANT, WARNING THE MOVE COULD
HAVE LASTING CONSEQUENCES ON THE
COURT.
>> IT'S A BAD DAY FOR THE
SENATE.
IT MEANS YOU WILL PROBABLY GET
MORE IDEOLOGICAL JUDGES, BUT WE
ARE WHO WE ARE.
>> IF YOU HAVE THESE
RESERVATIONS, WHY DO IT?
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO HAVE A
SYSTEM WHERE REPUBLICANS CAN'T
GET JUDGES AND DEMOCRATS CAN.
>> BUT MANY DEMOCRATS ARE STILL
FUMING, AFTER REPUBLICANS
REFUSED TO EVEN CONSIDER
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S NOMINEE TO
FILL THIS SEAT, MERRICK GARLAND.
>> IT DOESN'T HAVE TO BE THIS
WAY.
>> Reporter: AFTERWARDS, EVEN
REPUBLICANS WHO SUPPORTED IT,
WARNED OF THE FALLOUT.
>> IT MAKES THINGS MORE
DIFFICULT IN AN
ALREADY-DIFFICULT ENVIRONMENT.
THIS WILL CONTRIBUTE TO THE
TYRANNY OF THE MAJORITY.
>> SO LET'S BRING MARY BRUCE
LIVE FROM CAPITOL HILL TONIGHT.
THIS NOW PAVES THE WAY FOR A
FINAL VOTE ON NEIL GORSUCH
TOMORROW.
>> DAVID, NOW THAT THE PATH IS
CLEAR THE SENATE IS IN ITS FINAL
ROUND OF DEBATE.
DEMOCRATS ARE STILL SPEAKING OUT
ON THE FLOOR, BUT IT'S TOO LATE.
THE SENATE IS EXPECTED TO VOTE
AND CONFIRM NEIL GORSUCH
TOMORROW.
DAVID.
>> MARY BRUCE, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE'S STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS THURSDAY --
THE SEVERE STORM MOVING AHEAD.
THE SYSTEM MAKING ITS WAY INTO
THE NORTHEAST.
AT LEAST 13 REPORTED TORNADOES
ALREADY.
50 MILLION AMERICANS BRACING FOR
DANGEROUS WEATHER TONIGHT.
GINGER ZEE STANDING BY LIVE WITH
THE NEW TRACK TONIGHT.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT --
THE PASSENGER PLANE SCARE, THE
DISCOVERY IN THE LUGGAGE THAT
KEPT PASSENGERS ON THE GROUND
FOR HOURS.
>>> AND TONIGHT, WE CELEBRATE AN
AMERICAN GREAT.
THERE WAS ONLY ONE DON RICKLES.
BACK IN A MOMENT.
...nerve pain shoots and
burns its way into your day...e
...I hear you.
When that pain makes simple
errands simply unbearable...
...I hear you.
I hear you because my dad
struggled with this pain.
Make sure your doctor
hears you too.
So folks, don't wait.
Step On Up.
And talk to your doctor.
Because you have places to go...
...and people who can't wait
for you to get there.
If you have diabetes and
burning, shooting pain
in your feet or hands...
Step On Up and talk to
your doctor today.
...have you tried
the tissue test?
Question, are my teeth yellow?
ugh, yellow... what do you use?
Crest Whitestrips
Crest 3D whitestrips whiten...
25 times better than a
leading whitening toothpaste
I passed the tissue test.
Oh yeah.
Crest whitestrips are
the way to whiten
or how high the pollen count,
Flonase Allergy Relief
keeps your eyes and nose clear.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause nasal congestion
and itchy, watery eyes.
For relief beyond the nose.
Flonase.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, THE
SEVERE WEATHER OUTBREAK.
MORE THAN A DOZEN REPORTED
TORNADOES ACROSS SEVEN STATES.
50 MILLION AMERICANS UNDER FLOOD
WATCHES.
THERE'S REAL CONCERN IN THE
NORTHEAST TONIGHT.
TORNADO WARNING THERE FOR A TIME
IN VIRGINIA BEACH, SENDING
STUDENTS INTO THE HALLWAY OF A
VIRGINIA HIGH SCHOOL.
MORE THAN A 1,000 FLIGHTS
CANCELLED COAST TO COAST.
THOUSANDS WITHOUT POWER AS WELL.
LET'S GET TO CHIEF METEOROLOGIST
GINGER ZEE WITH US LIVE TONIGHT.
SHE HAS THE NEW TRACK.
HEY, GINGER.
>> HEY, DAVID, THE HEAVY RAIN
THE THUNDER, LIGHTNING, ALL
MOVED THROUGH HERE.
WE DRIED OUT,
BUT THAT STORM IS STILL ON THE
MOVE.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO THOSE MAPS.
FLOOD WATCHES IN NORTHEAST AND
NEW ENGLAND.
THE WIND ADVISORIES THAT STRETCH
FROM ANN ARBOR, MICHIGAN,
TO JACKSONVILLE, FLORIDA, WE
STILL HAVE THE POTENTIAL OF
TWO INCHES OF FLASH FLOODING.
BAYSIDE, QUEENS, SAW FLASH
FLOODING.
LOOK AT THAT BEHIND IT, DAVID,
COLD AND SNOW BEHIND IT.
2 TO EVEN 5 INCHES COMING WITH
THIS.
GET READY FOR THE WIND AND COLD.
>> NOT DONE WITH THE SNOW YET.
GINGER, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
THE M.I.T. GRADUATE FACING
TERROR CHARGES.
THE DISCOVERY POLICE ALLEGEDLY
MADE IN HIS HOME.
>>> ALSO, THE PASSENGER JET
SCARE KEEPING PASSENGERS ON THE
GROUND FOR SEVERAL HOURS.
WHAT SECURITY FOUND IN THE
LUGGAGE.
>>> AND CELEBRATING AN AMERICAN
ORIGINAL, COMEDIAN DON RICKLES
WHO MADE SURE EVERYONE -- WE
MEAN EVERYONE -- WAS FAIR GAME.
MEAN EVERYONE -- WAS THAT FAIR
GAME.
The comfort in knowing where
things are headed.
Because as we live longer...
And markets continue to
rise and fall...
Predictable is one thing you
need in retirement
to help protect what you've
earned and ensure it lasts.
Introducing
Brighthouse Financial.
A new company established
by MetLife
to specialize in annuities
& life insurance.
Talk to your advisor about a
brighter financial future.
WHY PAUSE A
SPONTANEOUS MOMENT?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
(I wanted him to eat healthy.,
So I feed Jake Purina Cat Chow
Naturals Indoor,
a nutritious formula with no
artificial flavors.
Made specifically for indoor
cats.
Purina Cat Chow. Nutrition to
build better lives.
Yet up 90% fall short in getting
key nutrients from food alone.
Let's do more.
Add One A Day 50+
a complete multi-vitamin
with 100% daily value
of more than 15
key nutrients.
One A Day 50+.
(de♪p breath)
(phone ringing)
They'll call back.
No one knows your Ford better
than Ford and Ford Service.
Right now, during
The Big Tire Event,
get a $140 rebate by mail,
on four select tires.
♪
W...I was always searching for
ways to manage my symptoms.
I thought I had it covered.
Then I realized managing was
all I was doing.
When I finally told my doctor,
he said HUMIRA was for people
like me
who have tried other
medications,...
but still experience the
symptoms
of moderate to severe
Crohn's disease.
In clinical studies,
the majority of patients
on HUMIRA
saw significant symptom
relief...
...and many achieved remission.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections...
...including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,...
including lymphoma, have
happened;
as have blood, liver, and
nervous system problems,
serious allergic
reactions,...
...and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested
for TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,...
...hepatitis B, are prone to
infections,
...or have flu-like symptoms
or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
If you're still just managing
your symptoms,
ask your gastroenterologist
about HUMIRA.
With HUMIRA, remission
is possible.
>>> TO THE INDEX OF OTHER NEWS
TONIGHT.
AN M.I.T. BUSINESS SCHOOL
GRADUATE HAS BEEN INDICTED ON
TERROR CHARGES.
AUTHORITIES SAY THIS 40-YEAR-OLD
WAS PLANNING TO DETONATE
EXPLOSIVE DEVICES AT SEVERAL
LOCATIONS IN LAS VEGAS AND
HENDERSON, NEVADA.
MORE THAN 250 POUNDS OF NITRATE
AND OTHER EXPLOSIVE CHEMICALS
ALLEGEDLY RECOVERED AT HIS HOME.
HE'S BEING HELD ON $8 MILLION
BAIL.
HIS ATTORNEY SAID THE MATERIALS
WERE LEGALLY OBTAINED.
AND WERE GOING TO BE USED FOR
FIREARMS TARGET PRACTICE.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO THE BOMB
SCARE ON THE TARMAC.
UNITED AIRLINES FLIGHT FROM
TORONTO TO CHICAGO GROUNDED
BEFORE TAKEOFF.
A MOCK IED FOUND IN A
PASSENGER'S SUITCASE.
THE PLANE WAS HELD FOR SEVERAL
HOURS.
PASSENGERS HAD TO BE
RE-SCREENED.
THE OWNER OF THE BAG WHO WAS
AMERICAN WAS ARRESTED.
NO EXPLOSIVES WERE FOUND.
>>> AN AMERICAN HERO LAID TO
REST TONIGHT.
FORMER ASTRONAUT AND SENATOR
JOHN GLENN BURIED TODAY DURING A
PRIVATE SERVICE AT ARLINGTON
NATIONAL CEMETERY.
A 21-GUN SALUTE.
FOLDED AMERICAN FLAG PRESENTED
TO HIS WIDOW ANNIE.
HIS FAMILY SCHEDULING THE
FUNERAL FOR WHAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
THEIR 74th WEDDING ANNIVERSARY.
HE DIED IN DECEMBER, HE WAS 95.
>>> AND WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT -- WE CELEBRATE ANOTHER
AMERICAN GREAT.
WHO HAD US LAUGHING AT EVERYONE
ELSE'S EXPENSE.
SOME OF HIS FUNNIEST MOMENTS,
NEXT.
ONE
ELSE'S EXPENSE.
SOME OF HIS FUNNIEST MOMENTS,
NEXT.
Ray's always been different.
Last year, he said he was going
to dig a hole to China.
AT&T is working with farmers to
improve irrigation techniques.
Remote moisture sensors use a
reliable network
to tell them when and where to
water.
So that farmers like Ray can
compete in big ways.
China.
Oh ... he got there.
That's the power of and.
...it shouldn't be
Whateverfleas and ticks. home...
No, no no no no...
Seresto® kills and
repels fleas and ticks
for 8 continuous months -
for effective protection
in an easy-to-use,
non-greasy collar.
8-month Seresto®. From Bayer.
Remember when you said
men are supeYeah...ivers?
Yeah, then how'd I get this...
...Allstate Safe
Driving Bonus Check?
...only Allstate sends
you a bonus check
for every six months
you're accident free.
Silence.
It's good to be IN, Good Hands.
nitrites or artificial Mesquite
preservatives.added nitrates,
Now it's good for us all.
Like introverts.
Extroverts.
(Cheering)
And even Bert.
Man you gotta' try this
sandwich.
Who's just overt.
Oscar Mayer Deli Fresh.
So good!
I USE WHAT'S ALREADY
INSIDE ME TO REACH MY GOALS.
SO I LIKED WHEN MY
DOCTOR TOLD ME
I MAY REACH MY BLOOD
SUGAR AND A1C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING
WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE MY BODY TO
DO WHAT IT'S SUPPOSED TO DO
RELEASE ITS OWN INSULIN.
TRULICITY RESPONDS WHEN
MY BLOOD SUGAR RISES.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS ITCHING, RASH,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING;
A LUMP OR SWELLING IN YOUR NECK;
OR SEVERE PAIN IN
YOUR STOMACH AREA.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCLUDE PANCREATITIS,
WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS WORSE.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING YOUR
A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR NUMBERS
WITH A NON-INSULIN OPTION,
CLICK TO ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, CELEBRATING
DON RICKLES.
NO ONE WAS EVER OFF-LIMITS, EVEN
FRANK SINATRA.
HERE'S ABC'S DAVID WRIGHT.
>> WILL YOU WELCOME MR. WARMTH
DON RICKLES?
>> Reporter: HE WAS THE KING OF
ZING.
>> IS THAT YOUR WIFE?
I'LL TELL YOU THIS --
>> Reporter: DON RICKLES MADE
HIS NAME SPEAKING COMEDY TO
POWER, WHETHER IT WAS THE
CHAIRMAN OF THE BOARD --
>> AND FRANK, I LOVE YOU --
>> Reporter: OR THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES.
>> GOOD EVENING, MR. PRESIDENT,
NICE TO SEE YOU, SIR.
AND YOUR LOVELY WIFE, NANCY.
IT'S A BIG TREAT FOR ME TO FLY
ALL THE WAY FROM CALIFORNIA TO
BE HERE FOR THIS KIND OF MONEY.
>> Reporter: THEY LOVED HIM FOR
IT.
FOR DON RICKLES, EVERYBODY WAS
FAIR GAME.
>> I LAUGH ABOUT PEOPLE NO
MATTER WHAT THE HELL YOU ARE.
IRISH, JEWISH --
>> Reporter: A RELIABLE GUEST ON
THE TALK SHOW CIRCUIT, AND A
FIXTURE ON THE VEGAS STRIP SINCE
THE DAYS OF THE RAT PACK.
>> WHEN I FIRST STARTED OUT
THERE WAS A LOT OF SAND AND A
LOT OF GUYS WHO TALKED LIKE,
"HEY, FRANK, WHAT DO YOU WANNA
DO LATER?"
>> Reporter: HE ONCE SAID, YOU
KNOW WHAT'S FUNNY, ATTITUDE.
DAVID WRIGHT, ABC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>> CELEBRATING MR. WARMTH.
>>> THANKS FOR WATCHING ON A
THURSDAY.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
.
>>> LIVE, WHERE YOU LIVE, THIS
IS ABC7 NEWS.
>> DON'T GET USED TO THIS VIEW.
IT'S GOING TO STICK AROUND THE
NEXT FEW HOURS AND BE BACK AGAIN
TOMORROW.
GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> TODAY'S STORM IS ABOUT TO
PEAK AND IT SPREAD ACROSS THE
WHOLE BAY AREA.
>> WHAT IT'S LIKE FOR DRIVERS ON
THE EAST BAY AND NORTH BAY.
IT COMES WITH GUSTY WINDS WHICH
MAKES CROSSING THESE BRIDGES
MORE CHALLENGING.
>> "ABC NEWS" AS THE SCATTER OF
RAINDROPS STARTED.
AND IT STARTED COMING DOWN ON
THE CAMPUS OF UC BERKELEY AND
MORE IS COMING.
SPENCER CHRISTIAN POINTS WHERE
AND WHEN IT WILL HIT.
SPENCER.
>> WE HAVE MORE THAN LIGHT
RAINDROPS NOW.
A WAVE OF MODERATE DOWNPOURS.
SAN MOST AATEO AND SAN FRANCISC
THIS STORM RANKS 2 ON THE STORM
IMPACT SCALE, WE WILL SEE RAIN
GUSTING TO 60 MILES AN HOUR.
7:00 THIS EVENING, NOTICE AT
9:00 TONIGHT, THE SAME