THANK YOU FOR SUPPORTING IT.
>> WORLD NEWS IS NEXT.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT ON THE BRINK.
IS AMERICA ABOUT TO TAKE
MILITARY ACTION AGAINST SYRIA
BECAUSE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS?
TONIGHT A NEW WARNING AND U.N.
INSPECTORS UNDER FIRE.
>>> SAVING YOSEMITE, 3,500
FIREFIGHTERS BATTLING THE
LARGEST WILDFIRE IN AMERICA,
TRYING TO SAVE AN AMERICAN
TREASURE.
>>> WATCH DOG, WE ARE LOOKING
OUT FOR WASTE OF TAXPAYER
DOLLARS.
WHY ARE TWO GOVERNMENT AGENCIES
SPENDING MILLIONS ON ONE FISH?
>>> AND AMERICAN HERO, THE STAFF
SERGEANT HONORED FOR BRAVERY
OVERSEAS AND THE NEW COURAGEOUS
BATTLE HE IS FIGHTING FOR OTHERS
RIGHT HERE AT HOME.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AS WE COME ON THE AIR THIS
MONDAY NIGHT THE UNITED STATES
IS ABOUT TO MAKE A VERY TOUGH
CHOICE.
WILL THE U.S. MILITARY TAKE
ACTION AGAINST SYRIA?
LATE TODAY SECRETARY OF STATE
JOHN KERRY SAID IT IS CLEAR
CHEMICAL WEAPONS WERE DEPLOYED
AGAINST THE SYRIAN PEOPLE, BUT
WHO GAVE THAT ORDER AND WOULD
THIS DRAW AMERICA INTO ANOTHER
CONFLICT?
ABC'S MARTHA RADDATZ IS IN EGYPT
TONIGHT COVERING THE REGION AND
THE QUESTION, WHAT HAPPENS NOW?
>> Reporter: AFTER COMING UNDER
REPEATED SNIPER FIRE, U.N.
INVESTIGATORS DONNED HELMETS AND
BULLETPROOF VESTS TODAY AND
RETURNED TO THE DAMASCUS SUBURBS
TO INTERVIEW SURVIVORS OF THE
HORRIFIC ATTACK.
THIS IS THE EFFECT OF CHEMICALS,
ONE DOCTOR TOLD THE
INVESTIGATORS, AND TONIGHT THE
U.S. SECRETARY OF STATE SAID THE
U.S. HAS LITTLE DOUBT THAT IT IS
TRUE.
>> MAKE NO MISTAKE, PRESIDENT
OBAMA BELIEVES THERE MUST BE
ACCOUNTABILITY FOR THOSE WHO
WOULD USE THE WORLD'S MOST
HEINOUS WEAPONS AGAINST THE
WORLD'S MOST VULNERABLE PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: IMAGES FROM THE
ATTACK ARE HARD TO WATCH.
SECRETARY KERRY SPOKE ABOUT THE
HUNDREDS, MAYBE THOUSANDS OF
INNOCENTS WHO WERE KILLED.
>> AS A FATHER, I CAN'T GET THE
IMAGE OUT OF MY HEAD OF A MAN
WHO HELD UP HIS DEAD CHILD,
WAILING WHILE CHAOS SWIRLED
AROUND HIM, THE IMAGES OF ENTIRE
FAMILIES DEAD IN THEIR BEDS
WITHOUT A DROP OF BLOOD OR A
VISIBLE WOUND, BODIES CONTORTING
IN SPASMS, HUMAN SUFFERING THAT
WE CAN NEVER IGNORE OR FORGET.
>> Reporter: SUCH STRONG WORDS
FROM TOP U.S. OFFICIALS LEAVE
LITTLE DOUBT THE U.S. PLANS
MILITARY ACTION AGAINST SYRIA'S
ASSAD REGIME AS THREE KEY
ALLIES, BRITAIN, FRANCE AND
TURKEY, SAY THEY WILL BACK A
MILITARY RESPONSE, U.N. MANDATE
OR NOT.
ASSAD HIMSELF REMAINS DEFIANT,
WARNING THAT THE U.S. WOULD FAIL
AS IN VIETNAM.
DIANE, U.S. OFFICIALS SAY THE
PURPOSE OF ANY MILITARY STRIKE
WOULD BE TO DETER AND PREVENT
SYRIA FROM LAUNCHING ANY MORE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACKS WHICH
MEANS THE MILITARY STRIKE WOULD
LIKELY COME WITHIN DAYS OR
WEEKS.
>> MARTHA, OUR THANKS TO YOU.
>>> NOW A QUICK LOOK AT THE U.S.
MILITARY MIGHT IN THE REGION.
AS OF TONIGHT FOUR WAR SHIPS AND
AT LEAST ONE SUBMARINE ARE OFF
THE COAST OF SYRIA, 100 TO 200
MILES, AND AT LEAST HALF A DOZEN
BASES MANNED BY MORE THAN 15,000
TROOPS.
LET'S BRING IN ABC NEWS ANALYST,
FORMER FIGHTER PILOT, FORMER
DEPUTY ASSISTANT SECRETARY OF
STATE, STEVE GANYARD.
IS THERE ANY CHANCE THEY ARE
TRYING TO TARGET CHEMICAL
WEAPONS THEMSELVES?
>> PROBABLY NOT THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS THEMSELVES.
TO DESTROY A CHEMICAL WEAPON YOU
HAVE TO GET IT HOT.
A BOMB IS NOT GOING TO DO THAT.
IT'S GOING TO THROW IT AROUND
THE SURROUNDING AREA AND YOU
COULD SPREAD THE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS UP TO TWO MILES AWAY.
WE ALSO DON'T WANT THE SITES
OPEN SO SOMEONE CAN COME IN AND
STEAL THEM AND USE THEM IN A
TERRORIST ATTACK LATER ON.
>> WHAT DO YOU THINK THE TARGETS
WILL BE AND WHAT WILL IT TAKE TO
HIT THEM?
>> THEY WILL PROBABLY HAVE TWO
CHARACTERISTICS.
THE FIRST CHARACTERISTIC IS THEY
WANT TO DEGRADE ASSAD'S MILITARY
CAPABILITY TO A SIGNIFICANT
DEGREE.
THEY'LL PROBABLY GO AFTER AIR
FIELDS SUCH AS THE ONE IN
DAMASCUS AND THE ONE THAT
DESTROYED HELICOPTERS AND
AIRCRAFT AND WANT TO CREATE A
RUNWAY SO THEY CAN NOT BE USED
AGAINST THEIR OWN PEOPLE.
THEY'LL PROBABLY WANT TO DO
SOMETHING THAT'S VISIBLY
COMPELLING SO THE WORLD CAN SEE
THAT ASSAD HAS BEEN DELIVERED A
PUNCH AND WE HAVE DONE SOMETHING
ABOUT HIS USE OF CHEMICAL
WEAPONS AGAINST CIVILIANS.
>> THANK YOU, STEVE GANYARD.
>>> AND RIGHT BACK HERE AT HOME
THERE ARE TWO PICTURES THAT SAY
SO MUCH ABOUT THE INCREDIBLY
BRAVE AND EXHAUSTED FIREFIGHTERS
NEAR YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
THE WIND IS WHIPPING THE FLAMES
ABOVE THE SEQUOIA TREES AND THEY
ARE TREASURES, SOME OF THE
OLDEST LIVING THINGS ON EARTH.
MORE THAN 3,000 MEN AND WOMEN
ARE INSIDE THE FLAMES WHERE THE
HEAT CAN REACH MORE THAN 800
DEGREES.
ABC'S NEAL KARLINSKY IS IN THE
HEART OF THE BATTLE.
>> Reporter: ALONG THE EDGE OF
YOSEMITE, A FIRE NOW SO FIERCE
IT'S CREATING ITS OWN WEATHER
PATTERNS, SO-CALLED THUNDEROUS
PYRO CUMULUS CLOUDS BIG ENOUGH
TO BE SEEN FROM SPACE THAT CAN
ALTER THE WIND DIRECTION RAPIDLY
AND POTENTIALLY TRAP
FIREFIGHTERS.
>> WE HAVE HAD UP TO 43,000
QUICK PLUMES.
THAT CREATES ITS OWN WEATHER.
>> Reporter: FIREFIGHTERS ARE
STRUGGLING TO PROTECT THIS HUGE
RESERVOIR WHICH SUPPLIES 85
PERCENT OF SAN FRANCISCO'S WATER
AND IS BEING SLOWLY POLLUTED BY
FALLING ASH.
THE FIRE IS BEING SPREAD BY
CROWNING WHERE THE TOPS OF TREES
TORCH, SPREADING FASTER THAN ON
THE GROUND.
>> ARE YOU WORRIED THAT ANY OF
THESE TREES ARE GOING TO COME
DOWN WHILE YOU ARE IN THERE
WORKING?
>> THAT'S WHY WE TRAIN THE WAY
WE DO, KEEP OUR EYES UP.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN 3,500
FIREFIGHTERS ARE IN THIS BATTLE
STAGED ALONG THREE FLANKS.
TO THE NORTHEAST, NEST AND
SOUTHEAST, STILL ABOUT 20 MILES
FROM EL CAPITAN AND OTHER
YOSEMITE TREASURES.
THEIR JOB, DIG UP DRY SHRUBS,
BULLDOZE THE LAND AND SET
BACKFIRES AT NIGHT, ALL TO ROB
THE BIGGEST FLAMES OF MORE FUEL.
THEY ALSO HAVE SMALL TEAMS
PUTTING OUT SPOT FIRES THAT
SPRING UP.
HERE'S ONE OF THE CHALLENGES.
NO FIRE HERE, BLUE SKY AND THEN
ALL OF A SUDDEN, A SPOT FIRE
BREAKS OUT.
IT'S LIKE THIS FOR MILES UP AND
DOWN THE ROAD.
THEN THERE IS THIS, A FIRE TEAM
DEPLOYED TO PROTECT THREE DOZEN
OF YOSEMITE'S ANCIENT SEQUOIA
TREES, SOME OF THE OLDEST LIVING
THINGS ON EARTH, IN NEED OF
PROTECTION NOW.
NEAL KARLINSKY, ABC NEWS,
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
>>> WE ALSO WANT TO SHOW YOU
SOME DANGEROUS FLASH FLOODING
TONIGHT IN THE SOUTHWEST,
INCLUDING THE DESERT CITY, LAS
VEGAS.
INTERSTATES AWASH IN WATER AND
CARS HAVE BEEN SWAMPED THERE.
>>> AND NEXT TONIGHT AN
EXCLUSIVE REPORT ON A GIANT NEW
STUDY ABOUT ALL OF US WHO THINK
WE CAN WALK AND TALK ON CELL
PHONES AND TEXT AT THE SAME
TIME.
IT'S A BRAND NEW REPORT OUT
TONIGHT AND A WAKEUP CALL FOR
EVERYONE ABOUT THE SERIOUS
DANGER WHIZZING RIGHT BY.
HERE'S ABC'S PAULA FARIS.
>> Reporter: THIS CAR NEARLY
HITS A PEDESTRIAN PAYING MORE
ATTENTION TO HIS MOBILE DEVICE
THAN TRAFFIC.
WATCH AGAIN, THE PEDESTRIAN SO
DISTRACTED, HE EVEN CONTINUES TO
TEXT.
CROSSING THE STREET, DISTRACTED
BY PHONES, HEADPHONES, TABLETS
IS A DEADLY PROBLEM.
>> THEY JUST THINK IT'S NEVER
GOING TO HAPPEN TO ME.
>> Reporter: WE SAW IT ON THE
STREETS OF L.A., CHICAGO AND
D.C., AND EVEN IN BROAD DAYLIGHT
PEDESTRIANS WERE TOO DISTRACTED
TO NOTICE OUR CAMERA CREW IN NEW
YORK.
>> YOU'RE TEXTING AND YOUR HEAD
IS DOWN AND YOU STEP ONTO THE
STREET.
>> YOU'RE COMPLETELY UNAWARE.
>> RIGHT.
>> Reporter: WATCH THIS MAN
TALKING ON HIS PHONE, DOESN'T
EVEN NOTICE HE'S WALKING INTO
TRAFFIC.
THIS WOMAN, TOO BUSY TEXTING.
>> BUSTED!
DO YOU FEEL LIKE YOU WERE
BUSTED?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: SHE WASN'T THE ONLY
ONE.
>> HOW LONG DO YOU THINK YOU
WERE LOOKING DOWN?
>> PROBABLY THE WHOLE TIME I WAS
CROSSING THE STREET.
>> Reporter: THE PROBLEM IS ONLY
GETTING WORSE, ESPECIALLY AMONG
TEENS.
SAFE KIDS STUDIED 35,000 AND
FOUND THAT FATALITY RATES HAVE
INCREASED 25 PERCENT DUE TO
DEVICE DISTRACTIONS IN THE LAST
FIVE YEARS.
WHILE TEENS MIGHT BE THE WORST
OFFENDERS, MOST OF US ARE
GUILTY.
>> I FEEL AS IF I CAN FOCUS ON
THE LIGHT AND THE CARS AT THE
SAME TIME.
>> Reporter: STILL MOST AGREED
ON THE DANGERS.
>> DO YOU THINK YOU CAN GET OUT
OF HARM'S WAY WITH YOUR HEAD
DOWN AND TEXTING?
>> PROBABLY NOT.
>>> AND NEXT TONIGHT A SHOCKER
OF A HEADLINE ABOUT THAT FAMOUS
BATTLE OF THE SEXES.
MILLIONS AND MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS WATCHED TENNIS
CHAMPION BILLIE JEAN KING
TROUNCE BOBBY RIGGS ON LIVE TV.
NOW TONIGHT 40 YEARS LATER AN
ESPN REPORT SAYS BOBBY RIGGS MAY
HAVE THROWN THE MATCH TO PAY OFF
GAMBLING DEBTS.
ABC'S GIO BENITEZ ON THE
ALLEGATIONS.
>> Reporter: IT WAS DUBBED THE
BATTLE OF THE SEXES.
SEPTEMBER 20, 1973, ONE OF THE
TOP TENNIS PLAYERS EVER, BOBBY
RIGGS, CAME OUT OF RETIREMENT TO
CHALLENGE ONE OF THE WORLD'S
GREATEST FEMALE PLAYERS, BILLIE
JEAN KING.
AND LOST.
NOW IN AN ESPN "OUTSIDE THE
LINES" EXCLUSIVE WITH DON VAN
NATTA, THIS MAN IS SHARING WHAT
HE SAYS HE KEPT SECRET FOR 40
YEARS.
HAL SHAWL WORKED AT A FLORIDA
COUNTRY CLUB AND SAID THAT
MONTHS BEFORE THE MATCH HE
OVER HEARD TWO INFAMOUS MOB
BOSSES IN A LATE NIGHT MEETING
SAYING
RIGGS OWED THE MOB A GAMBLING
DEBT OF MORE THAN 100 GRAND.
>> THEY BROUGHT UP THE NAME OF
BOBBY RIGGS.
HE SAID HE WILL MAKE IT LOOK AND
APPEAR THAT HE IS TRYING HIS
BEST BUT BILLIE JEAN KING IS
OVERWHELMING HIM.
>> Reporter: BILLIE JEAN KING
CALLS THE STORY RIDICULOUS.
>> I WOULD BET MY LIFE THAT
BOBBY NEVER HAD THAT DISCUSSION.
HE DIDN'T GET INVOLVED WITH
MOBSTERS.
>> ACTUALLY, BILLIE, HE DID.
>> Reporter: ESPN SAT DOWN WITH
RIGGS' SON LARRY.
>> DID HE KNOW MAFIA GUYS,
POSSIBLY.
IS IT POSSIBLE THESE GUYS WERE
TALKING [ BLEEP ]?
YES.
IS IT POSSIBLE THAT THEY TALKED
TO HIM ABOUT DOING IT?
POSSIBLE.
>> Reporter: WE'LL NEVER BE ABLE
TO ASK RIGGS HIMSELF.
HE DIED IN 1995.
GIO BENITEZ, ABC NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> AND UP NEXT, OUR WASHINGTON
WATCH DOG SERIES, LOOKING OUT
FOR WASTE OF TAXPAYER DOLLARS.
TONIGHT ABC'S DAVID KERLEY HAS
SOME TOUGH QUESTIONS ABOUT
SOMETHING HE FOUND, TWO
AGENCIES, ONE FISH, AND MILLIONS
IN TAXPAYER MONEY.
>>> Reporter: DICK STEVENS --
>> HOW MUCH MORE DO YOU ALL GOT
TO GO TODAY?
>> Reporter: -- IS A CATFISH
LEGEND IN MISSISSIPPI.
>> WE CAN DO 400,000.
>> Reporter: 400,000 IN ONE DAY?
>> POUNDS, YES.
>> THAT IS A LOT OF FISH.
>> Reporter: HE'S ONE OF THE
BIGGEST CATFISH PROCESSORS IN
THE COUNTRY AND ONE OF THE
DRIVING FORCES FOR GETTING THE
U.S. DEPARTMENT OF AGRICULTURE
TO INSPECT CATFISH GROWN HERE
AND IMPORTED.
CRITICS CALL THAT A HUGE WASTE
OF TAXPAYER MONEY.
THERE IS ONE BIG PROBLEM.
>> YOU ALREADY HAVE THE FDA
INSPECTING SEAFOOD.
>> THAT'S NOT CORRECT.
WE HAVE FDA BUT THAT'S A
NONEXISTENT INSPECTION.
>> Reporter: BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
TWO FEDERAL AGENCIES ARE
SUPPOSED TO INSPECT THE SAME
FISH.
THE USDA SPENT $20 MILLION JUST
FOR PLANNING THOSE INSPECTIONS.
WHILE THERE HAVE BEEN CONCERNS
ABOUT THE ADEQUACY OF
INSPECTIONS OF IMPORTED FISH IN
THE PAST, DO WE NEED USDA
INSPECTION, TOO?
>> WE WOULD SAY THERE IS FOOD
SAFETY CONCERN.
>> NO.
A CATFISH IS A CATFISH IS A
CATFISH.
IT'S A SAFE FOOD.
>> Reporter: DAVID ACHESON IS
ONE OF THE COUNTRY'S FOREMOST
FOOD SAFETY EXPERTS WHO SAYS
CATFISH IS NOT A HIGH RISK FOOD
AND THE FDA SHOULD CONTINUE TO
BE IN CHARGE OF INSPECTING IT.
>> THE ONLY THING YOU'RE LEFT
WITH, IT'S ABOUT POLITICS.
>> Reporter: WHY POLITICS?
BECAUSE THE ADDITIONAL
INSPECTION MAKES IT HARDER FOR
FISH IMPORTERS TO GET THEIR FISH
INTO THE U.S., THOSE IMPORTERS
ARE THE AMERICAN CATFISH GROWERS
MAIN COMPETITION.
GET THIS, WITH THAT $20 MILLION
IN FIVE YEARS, THE USDA HAS NOT
INSPECTED A SINGLE FISH BUT HAVE
USED SOME OF THAT MONEY TO ORDER
SOME REALLY NICE PENS THAT
PROCLAIM "OFFICE OF CATFISH
INSPECTION PROGRAM."
WE WENT TO JACKSON, MISSISSIPPI
TO SEE THAD COCHRAN, THE SENATOR
WHO WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR GETTING
THE LAW CHANGED.
>> WE CAME OUT TO TALK TO THE
SENATOR ABOUT THE FDA AND THE
USDA.
>> HE'S DEFINITELY THE RIGHT
PERSON TO SPEAK WITH --
>> Reporter: BUT HE WASN'T THERE
AND HAS DECLINED OUR REQUEST FOR
INTERVIEW.
>> DO YOU THINK WHAT YOU'VE
ASKED FOR IS WASTING TAXPAYER
MONEY?
>> NO, I DON'T.
I THINK IT'S WELL SPENT.
>> Reporter: $20 MILLION AND
COUNTING.
DAVID KERLEY, ABC NEWS,
MISSISSIPPI.
>>> WE WANT TO HEAR FROM YOU SO
SOUND OFF ON WASHINGTON WASTE.
YOU'RE INVITED TO DO SO ON OUR
FACEBOOK PAGE.
>>> TODAY IN WASHINGTON AN
AMERICAN HERO RECEIVED A MEDAL
OF HONOR FOR UNCOMMON BRAVERY.
STAFF SERGEANT TY MICHAEL CARTER
WHO EMBODIED COURAGE AND ACTION
DURING A DEADLY FIRE FIGHT AT A
REMOTE OUTPOST IN AFGHANISTAN IN
2009.
>> IT WAS CHAOS, THE BLIZZARD OF
BULLETS AND STEEL INTO WHICH TY
RAN, NOT ONCE OR TWICE OR A FEW
TIMES, BUT PERHAPS TEN TIMES.
IN DOING SO, HE DISPLAYED THE
ESSENCE OF TRUE HEROISM.
NOT THE URGE TO SURPASS ALL
OTHERS AT WHATEVER COST BUT THE
URGE TO SERVE OTHERS AT WHATEVER
COST.
>> AND THE PRESIDENT HAD ANOTHER
REASON TO PRAISE CARTER, FOR
TALKING OPENLY ABOUT HIS
STRUGGLE WITH POSTTRAUMATIC
STRESS DISORDER TO TRY TO HELP
HIS FELLOW SOLDIERS.
>>> STILL AHEAD RIGHT HERE ON
"WORLD NEWS," DONALD TRUMP
FIGHTS BACK AFTER HE'S ACCUSED
OF FRAUD.
WHAT HAS HIM SO RILED UP EVEN
WITH OUR REPORTER TONIGHT.
>> I KNOW YOU'RE TRYING TO
BECOME THE NEXT BIG DEAL BUT --
>>> AND ALSO TONIGHT DID YOU SEE
THAT WILD SCENE AT THE MTV
AWARDS?
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU WHY SOME
VERY FAMOUS PEOPLE WERE
COMPLETELY STUNNED.
JAMIE TO CHECKOUT, PLEASE.
THERE ARE LOTS OF
"JAMIES" OUT THERE,...
HUH?
BUT THAT DOESN'T MEAN
WE'RE ALL THE SAME.
JUST LIKE GREEK YOGURTS.
THAT'S WHY I PREFER
ACTIVIA GREEK.
YOU GOT THAT RIGHT JAMIE,
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE IT!
EXACTLY, BECAUSE ACTIVIA
GREEK IS THE ONLY GREEK
WITH EXCLUSIVE PROBIOTIC
BIFIDUS REGULARIS,
AND IT HELPS REGULATE
YOUR DIGESTIVE SYSTEM.
I LOVE ITS THICK
CREAMY TEXTURE!
MMM!
THE GREEK NONFAT YOGURT
THAT HELPS TUMMIES SMILE!
ACTIVIA GREEK...
LIKE NO OTHER GREEK YOGURT.
♪ DANNON
We provide the exact
individualization
that your body needs.
This Labor Day, don't invest in
a mattress
until you visit a Sleep Number
store.
Once you experience it, there's
no going back. Oh, yeah!
At our Biggest Sale of the
Year,
every bed is on sale.
Queen mattresses now start
at just $599.
And through Labor Day
only,
save 50% on our Limited
Edition
Memory Foam mattress sets.
Only at a Sleep Number
store.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
BUT CHANTIX HELPED ME DO IT.
I TOLD MY DOCTOR I THINK I'M...
I'M READY.
[ Male Announcer ]
ALONG WITH SUPPORT,
CHANTIX (VARENICLINE) IS PROVEN
TO HELP PEOPLE QUIT SMOKING.
IT REDUCES THE URGE TO SMOKE.
I KNEW THAT I COULD SMOKE
FOR THE FIRST 7 DAYS.
I KNEW THAT I WASN'T
PUTTING NICOTINE
BACK INTO MY BODY
TO TRY TO QUIT.
[ Male Announcer ] SOME PEOPLE
HAD CHANGES IN BEHAVIOR,
THINKING OR MOOD,
HOSTILITY, AGITATION,
DEPRESSED MOOD AND SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS OR ACTIONS
WHILE TAKING
OR AFTER STOPPING CHANTIX.
IF YOU NOTICE ANY OF THESE,
STOP CHANTIX AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ANY HISTORY OF MENTAL
HEALTH PROBLEMS,
WHICH COULD GET WORSE
WHILE TAKING CHANTIX.
DON'T TAKE CHANTIX IF
YOU'VE HAD A SERIOUS ALLERGIC
OR SKIN REACTION TO IT.
IF YOU DEVELOP THESE,
STOP CHANTIX
AND SEE YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
AS SOME
CAN BE LIFE-THREATENING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HISTORY
OF HEART
OR BLOOD VESSEL PROBLEMS,
OR IF YOU DEVELOP
NEW OR WORSE SYMPTOMS.
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
OF A HEART ATTACK OR STROKE.
USE CAUTION WHEN DRIVING
OR OPERATING MACHINERY.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
INCLUDE NAUSEA,
TROUBLE SLEEPING
AND UNUSUAL DREAMS.
IF I COULD DESCRIBE
BEING A NONSMOKER,
I WOULD SAY "AWESOME."
[ Male Announcer ]
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
IF CHANTIX IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
>>> TONIGHT DONALD TRUMP IS
FIGHTING BACK WITH ALL HIS
SIZABLE POWER AFTER THE NEW YORK
STATE ATTORNEY GENERAL FILED A
$40 MILLION LAWSUIT AGAINST HIM.
THE SUBJECT?
ALLEGATIONS BY SOME PEOPLE WHO
TOOK REAL ESTATE CLASSES AT HIS
TRUMP UNIVERSITY.
HERE'S ABC'S LINZIE JANIS WITH
THE PUBLIC SHOWDOWN.
>> Reporter: WHETHER YOU LOVE
HIM OR HATE HIM, DONALD TRUMP'S
NAME SELLS THINGS, BUT WHEN HE
PUT HIS NAME ON TRUMP
UNIVERSITY, PROMISING THE TRICKS
OF THE REAL ESTATE TRADE --
>> WE TEACH SUCCESS.
THAT'S WHAT IT'S ALL ABOUT.
>> Reporter: NEW YORK'S ATTORNEY
GENERAL SAYS IT WAS A RIPOFF.
>> THEY FLEECED MORE THAN 5,000
PEOPLE OUT OF MORE THAN $40
MILLION.
>> Reporter: THE COMPLAINT
ALLEGES THE SCHOOL PROMISED
INSTRUCTORS HAND PICKED
BY TRUMP THAT WOULD GIVE SECRETS
TO RICHES BUT MANY STUDENTS WERE
DEEP IN DEBT.
THE SCHOOL SHUT DOWN IN 2011.
BOB SAYS HE SPENT $35,000 UNDER
THE IMPRESSION HE WOULD GET
SECRETS, TIPS AND A FIRST CRACK
AT INVESTING IN TRUMP
PROPERTIES.
>> HE TOOK MY SELF-RESPECT AND
EMBARRASSED ME.
>> Reporter: IN RESPONSE TRUMP'S
OFFICE FORWARDED US THIS SURVEY
THEY SAY HE FILLED OUT GIVING
THE PROGRAM AN EXCELLENT RATING.
>> IF YOU TALK WITH THE
INVESTORS WITH MADOFF BEFORE
THEY LEARNED THEIR MONEY WAS
GONE, THEY THOUGHT HE
WAS THE GREATEST THING THAT
HAPPENED TO THEM, SAME WITH MR.
TRUMP.
>> BECAUSE SOME OF THESE PEOPLE
ARE ESSENTIALLY UNSATISFIED
CUSTOMERS --
>> EXCUSE ME.
WE HAVE A 98% SATISFACTION RATE,
LINZIE.
I KNOW YOUR TRYING TO BECOME THE
NEXT BIG DEAL SO WHEN YOU SAY
SOME OF THE PEOPLE, WHY DON'T
YOU TALK ABOUT THE 98 PERCENT OF
THE PEOPLE THAT WERE HAPPY.
>> Reporter: TOUGH WORDS FROM A
MAN WHO DOESN'T SHY AWAY FROM A
FIGHT.
LINZIE JANIS, ABC NEWS.
>>> NEXT HERE, MOMENTS FROM NOW,
IS THAT PRINCE CHARLES WATER
SKIING ON A CHAIR?
PRIVATE PHOTOS COMING UP.
ON A CHAIR?
SHE'S ALWAYS HAD A PLAYFUL SIDE.
AND YOU LOVE HER FOR IT.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A
QUESTION OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME
THE MOMENT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS
THE ONLY DAILY ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED
AND SYMPTOMS OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL YOUR MEDICAL
CONDITIONS AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN 4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC
REACTIONS SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
AT HUMANA, OUR MEDICARE AGENTS
SIT DOWN WITH YOU AND ASK.
BEING ACTIVE.
AND BEING WITH THIS GUY.
[ Male Announcer ]
GETTING TO KNOW YOU
IS HOW WE HELP YOU CHOOSE
THE HUMANA MEDICARE PLAN
THAT WORKS BEST FOR YOU.
MI FAMILIA.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
WE WANT TO HELP YOU ACHIEVE
YOUR BEST HEALTH,
SO YOU CAN KEEP DOING
THE THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT TO YOU.
TAKING CARE
OF OUR CUSTOMERS.
TAKING CARE OF HER.
AND THE NEXT THING ON OUR LIST
IS BUNGEE JUMPING.
[ Male Announcer ]
HELPING YOU --
NOW THAT'S WHAT'S IMPORTANT
TO US.
ICAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEVING HEARTBURN,U --
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES
24-HOUR HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL
PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
MAYO? CORN DOGS?
YOU ARE SO OUTTA HERE!
AAH!
[ Female Announcer ]
THE COMPLETE BALANCED NUTRITION
OF GREAT-TASTING ENSURE.
24 VITAMINS AND MINERALS,
ANTIOXIDANTS,
AND 9 GRAMS OF PROTEIN.
[ Bottle ] ENSURE®.
NUTRITION IN CHARGE™.
>>> OUR "INSTANT INDEX" TONIGHT
BEGINS WITH AN ENCOURAGING
UPDATE ON
THE 11-YEAR-OLD PENNSYLVANIA
GIRL, SARAH MURNAGHAN, WHO
RECEIVED THE DOUBLE LUNG
TRANSPLANT AFTER HER FAMILY WENT
TO COURT.
HER FIRST TRANSPLANT FAILED BUT
TWO AND A HALF MONTHS AFTER THE
SECOND OPERATION, WE HAVE
LEARNED SHE'S EXPECTED TO GO
HOME AS EARLY AS TOMORROW.
>>> AND WE HAVE A STUNNING
DAUNTING PIECE OF NEWS FOR
COLLEGE STUDENTS.
STARTING THIS SPRING, 200
AMERICAN COLLEGES WILL ALSO
GRADUATE AN EXIT EXAM, NOT
ENTRANCE BUT EXIT EXAM TO
MEASURE YOUR CRITICAL THINKING,
WHAT YOU LEARNED.
THE RESULTS WILL BE GIVEN TO
FUTURE EMPLOYERS WHO MAY HAVE
QUESTIONS ABOUT WHAT YOU DID IN
SCHOOL.
LET THE DEBATES BEGIN ABOUT
WHETHER THIS IS A GOOD IDEA.
>>> AND THE MOST PHOTOGRAPHED
FAMILY IN THE WORLD IN THEIR
MOST UNGUARDED MOMENTS, THE
ROYAL FAMILY OF ENGLAND.
20,000 PHOTOS TAKEN BY A MAN WHO
WAS OBSESSED WITH TRACKING THEM.
HERE PRINCE CHARLES WATER SKIING
ON A CHAIR IN 1970.
PRINCESS ANN FALLING OFF HER
HORSE DURING A COMPETITION.
AND IS THAT REALLY THE QUEEN
DANCING THE TWIST?
RAY BELISARIO FOLLOWED THE ROYAL
FAMILY'S EVERY MOVE FROM THE
'50s TO THE '70s AND THEY WERE
NOT HAPPY TO KNOW THAT HE WAS
ALWAYS WATCHING.
NOW HE'S PUTTING THEM UP FOR
AUCTION.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, DID YOU
SEE IT, THE DANCING LAST NIGHT,
THE GOOD, THE GREAT, THE REALLY
BAD, AND WHAT CREATED THIS
FAMILY PORTRAIT, HAD EVERYBODY
GASPING.
GRASPING.
EN.
ASPING.
SCREECH ]
♪
AND YOUR FAVORITE SONGS
ALWAYS PLAYING.
[ BEEPING ]
♪
MAY YOU NEVER BE STUCK
BEHIND A STINKY TRUCK.
[ BEEPING ]
♪
MAY YOUR LANES
ALWAYS BE CLEAR.
[ ENGINE REVS ]
♪
AND YOUR DAYS BE
SUNNY AND BRIGHT.
♪
MAY THINGS
ALWAYS GO YOUR WAY.
BUT IT'S GOOD TO BE PREPARED...
JUST IN CASE THEY DON'T.
LET'S GO PLACES, SAFELY.
THE BLISTERS WERE OOZING,
AND PAINFUL TO TOUCH.
I WOKE UP TO A BLISTERING
ON MY SHOULDER.
I SPENT 23 YEARS AS A
DEPUTY UNITED STATES MARSHAL
AND I'VE BEEN PRETTY
WELL BANGED UP
BUT THE WORST PAIN
I'VE EXPERIENCED
WAS WHEN I HAD SHINGLES.
WHEN I WENT TO THE CLINIC,
THE NURSE TOLD ME
THAT IT WAS A RESULT OF
HAVING HAD CHICKENPOX.
I WOULDN'T WISH IT
ON MY WORST ENEMY.
I TOOK MY SON FISHING
EVERY YEAR.
WE HAD A GREAT SPOT,
NOT EASY TO FIND, BUT WORTH IT.
BUT WITH COPD
MAKING IT HARD TO BREATHE,
I THOUGHT
THOSE DAYS MIGHT BE OVER.
SO MY DOCTOR
PRESCRIBED SYMBICORT.
IT HELPS SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE
MY LUNG FUNCTION
STARTING WITHIN FIVE MINUTES.
SYMBICORT DOESN'T REPLACE
A RESCUE INHALER
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS.
WITH SYMBICORT,
TODAY I'M BREATHING BETTER.
AND THAT MEANS...FISH ON!
SYMBICORT IS FOR COPD
INCLUDING CHRONIC BRONCHITIS
AND EMPHYSEMA.
IT SHOULD NOT BE TAKEN
MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
SYMBICORT MAY INCREASE YOUR RISK
OF LUNG INFECTIONS,
OSTEOPOROSIS,
AND SOME EYE PROBLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HEART CONDITION
OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING IT.
WITH COPD, I THOUGHT
I'D MISS OUR FAMILY TRADITION.
NOW SYMBICORT SIGNIFICANTLY
IMPROVES MY LUNG FUNCTION,
STARTING WITHIN 5 MINUTES.
AND THAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE
IN MY BREATHING.
TODAY, WE'RE READY
FOR WHATEVER SWIMS OUR WAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT SYMBICORT.
I GOT MY FIRST
PRESCRIPTION FREE.
CALL OR CLICK
TO LEARN MORE.
[ Male Announcer ] IF YOU CAN'T
AFFORD YOUR MEDICATION,
ASTRAZENECA
MAY BE ABLE TO HELP.
>>> AND NOW IT WAS THE TALK OF
THE TOWN TODAY, THOSE MUSIC
VIDEO AWARDS LAST NIGHT, THE
THRILLS, THE SHOCKS AND THE
WHAT-WERE-THEY-THINKING.
ABC'S DAN HARRIS HAS THE HIGHS
AND LOWS.
>> Reporter: IF MILEY CYRUS WAS
LOOKING TO TAKE THE PRIZE FOR
MOST ATTENTION, EVEN IF IT WAS
NEGATIVE ATTENTION, SHE
UNQUESTIONABLY SUCCEEDED.
HER TIGHT CLOTHING, TWERKING,
TONGUE-ALL-OVER-THE-PLACE
PERFORMANCE PROVOKED THIS
REACTION BACK STAGE, WHILE
RIHANNA SAT THERE, CLEARLY
UNIMPRESSED.
BUT THE REACTION SHOT GENERATING
THE MOST BUZZ TONIGHT IS THIS
ONE OF WILL SMITH AND HIS
FAMILY, ALTHOUGH THEY WEREN'T
REACTING TO MILEY BUT TO LADY
GAGA AND HER BACK SIDE.
PERHAPS THE BUSIEST 110 SECONDS
OF THE NIGHT WAS THE REUNION OF
THE 1990s BOY BAND SENSATION IN
SYNC AS MANY NOTED THEY WERE AT
TIMES A LITTLE BIT OUT OF SYNC.
♪ JUST HIT ME WITH THE TRUTH
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE BAND IN
THEIR HEYDAY.
THIS IS THEM LAST NIGHT.
SAME MOVES, DIFFERENT BODIES.
THERE WAS BUZZ OF A MORE HEART
WARMING KIND.
SO MANY PEOPLE TALKING TONIGHT
ABOUT JENNIFER HUDSON'S SURPRISE
APPEARANCE WALKING OUT ON STAGE
AS MACKLEMORE, RYAN LEWIS AND
MARY LAMBERT WERE PERFORMING
"SAME LOVE", AN ODE TO GAY
RIGHTS.
PROOF THAT NOT ALL BUZZ IS
PRODUCED THROUGH BAD BEHAVIOR.
SOMETIMES, SOMETIMES WHAT THE
WORLD REALLY WANTS IS A LITTLE
HEART.
DAN HARRIS, ABC NEWS, NEW YORK.
>> AND WE THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR
WATCHING TONIGHT.
GOOD TO BEGIN THE WEEK WITH YOU.
WE'RE ALWAYS THERE AT
ABCNEWS.COM.
"NIGHTLINE" WILL BE HERE LATER
AND I'LL SEE YOU RIGHT BACK HERE
AGAIN TOMORROW NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
YOU RIGHT BACK HERE
AGAIN TOMORROW NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> THE WIND FIRE NEAR
YOSEMITE, CONTAIN SMT GROWING
AND SOME PEOPLE ARE MOVING
BACK INTO HOMES.
>> WILL THE SMOKE SPOIL THE
LAST GET WAY WEEKEND OF THE
SUMMER?
TONIGHT A THREAT TO OUR WATER
SUPPLY.
>> AT 6:00 AND ONLY ON ABC 7
NEWS A KMUMPXZ ERROR AT THE
GOLDEN GATE TRANSIT DISTRICT.
>> PLUS A HOMETOWN SOLDIER
RECEIVES THE NATION'S HIGHEST
MILITARY HONOR AND DELIVERS A
MESSAGE TO HIS HOMETOWN
COMMUNITY.
>> IT'S FIREFIGHTERS HAVE A
REAL CHALLENGE ON THEIR HANDS
THCHL IS ONE OF THE WORST AND
JUST UNDER SCORES HOW
IMPORTANT IT IS TO HAVE
FUNDING, TO HAVE THE TALENT
AND LEADERSHIP AT BOTH STATE,
LOCAL AND FEDERAL LEVEL AND
THAT IS HAPPENING.
>> GOVERNOR BROWN TAKES A LOOK
AT THE RIM FIRE NOW ONE OF THE
WORST WILDFIRES IN CALIFORNIA
HISTORY.
GOOD EVENING.
>> TONIGHT WE'RE AWAITING NEW
FIGURES ON THE RIM FIRE,
UPDATED TWICE DAILY AT 8:00
A.M.
AND 58 P.M.
FIREFIGHTERS DID MAKE PROGRESS
OVERNIGHT DECLARING IT 15%
CONTAINED.
THE FLAMES ARE STILL SEVEN TO
10 MILES WAY FROM GROVES OF
GIANT SEQUOIAS.
YOU CAN SEE CONDITIONS ARE
RUGGED AND JUST UNDER 150,000
ACRES THE RIM FIRE IS NOW THE
BIGGEST ON RECORD IN THE
SIERRA.
ABC 7 NEWS REPORTER JOHN
ALSTON KICKS OFF OUR COVERAGE
TONIGHT.
>> THIS IS ONE OF THE
NEIGHBORHOODS OFFICIALS ARE
VERY, VERY CONCERNED ABOUT.
THERE ARE MANY HOUSES HERE IN
THIS AREA THIS, AREA HAS BEEN
LIKE AN AIRPORT.
HELICOPTERS COME BY PICKING UP
WATER THEN DROPPING IT OFF IN
HOT SPOTS.
FIXED WING AIRCRAFT DROPPING
FIRE RETARDANT.
THE FIRE IS ABOUT FOUR MILES