SELLER AND BUYER WERE
ANONYMOUS.
>> THAT IS WHAT I'M
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, BREAK IN THE CASE.
NEW LEADS ON THE BOMBER AT THE
BOSTON MARATHON.
WAS THE BOMBER CAUGHT ON TAPE BY
A STORE SURVEILLANCE CAMERA?
THE ABC NEWS TEAM STANDING BY
WITH THE LATEST.
>>> BREAKING NEWS IN THAT POISON
ALERT.
AN ARREST IN THE CASE OF THE
DEADLY LETTERS LACED WITH RICIN
SENT TO THE PRESIDENT AND A
SENATOR.
WE HAVE DETAILS COMING UP NOW.
>>> VOTED DOWN.
A HUGE DEFEAT FOR THE BIG
GUN BILL.
TONIGHT, OUTRAGE FROM THE
FAMILIES OF THE VICTIMS OF
GUN VIOLENCE.
>> OUR HEARTS ARE BROKEN.
OUR SPIRIT IS NOT.
>>> AND IN THEIR OWN WORDS,
TONIGHT AS THE PEOPLE OF BOSTON
RECOVER, THEIR PROUD MESSAGE TO
THE WORLD.
>> WE'RE A STRONG PEOPLE.
AND WE'RE NOT GOING TO LET
ANYONE PUSH US AROUND.
YOU MESS WITH ONE OF US, YOU
MESS WITH ALL OF US.
>>> GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
WE BEGIN IN BOSTON TONIGHT AMID
REPORTS OF A BREAK IN THE CASE.
AND HERE'S THE QUESTION --
HAS THE BOMBER BEEN SPOTTED
ON A SURVEILLANCE TAPE?
AS WE'VE HEARD THERE WAS
VIDEOTAPE EVERYWHERE AT THAT
MOMENT ON THAT DAY OF THE
MARATHON.
EXPERTS HAVE BEEN SCOURING THE
IMAGES.
AND WE ALSO KNOW THAT ON THIS
NIGHT, 62 INJURED ARE STILL
FIGHTING FOR RECOVERY IN THE
HOSPITAL, AND 12 OF THEM REMAIN
IN CRITICAL CONDITION.
SO LET'S GET STRAIGHT TO THE
LATEST NEWS RIGHT NOW FROM
ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT, BRIAN ROSS.
BRIAN?
>> Reporter: DIANE, AUTHORITIES
PUT OUT THE WORD TODAY, JUST 48
HOURS AFTER THE BOMBS WENT OFF,
THAT THEY MIGHT HAVE FOUND THE
BOMBER.
THE DEVELOPMENTS CAME ON A DAY
OF UNFULFILLED EXPECTATIONS
AND A SERIOUS CASE OF SECURITY
JITTERS.
>> THIS IS NOT A DRILL.
THIS IS NOT A DRILL.
>> Reporter: THE FEDERAL
COURTHOUSE, WHERE ANY SUSPECT
WOULD STAND TRIAL, WAS EVACUATED
LATE THIS AFTERNOON BECAUSE OF
A BOMB THREAT THAT,
UNDERSTANDABLY, WAS TAKEN VERY
SERIOUSLY.
>> WHAT ARE THEY TELLING YOU?
>> CODE RED EVACUATION.
>> CODE RED, EVACUATE THE
BUILDING.
>> Reporter: NO BOMB WAS FOUND.
BUT THE LAW ENFORCEMENT RESPONSE
FORCED A POSTPONEMENT OF A NEWS
CONFERENCE WHERE OFFICIALS HAD
PLANNED TO TALK ABOUT A POSSIBLE
SUSPECT.
AUTHORITIES SAY THE FBI IS
FOCUSED ON PHOTOGRAPHS,
INCLUDING SOME TAKEN BY A
SURVEILLANCE CAMERA AT THE
LORD & TAYLOR STORE, THAT SHOW
A MAN IN THE RACE-DAY CROWD,
USING A CELLPHONE, WITH A BLACK
BAG STRAPPED ACROSS HIS CHEST
THAT AUTHORITIES SAY MAY CONTAIN
THE BOMB.
THE KEY FRAMES ARE JUST A FEW OF
THE MILLIONS OF FRAMES OF VIDEO
EXAMINED IN THE LAST 36 HOURS BY
A SPECIAL TEAM OF FBI FORENSIC
EXPERTS, THE OPERATIONAL
TECHNOLOGY DIVISION.
THEY HAVE SET UP FACILITIES AT
A RESTRICTED LOCATION NEAR THE
BOSTON HARBOR.
AND THEY ARE MASTERS AT WHAT IS
KNOWN AS FACIAL RECOGNITION,
THE NEW SCIENCE OF CONVERTING A
FACE INTO A NAME, DEMONSTRATED
HERE BY AN INDIANA COMPANY THAT
WAS USED BY THE FBI FOLLOWING
THE 9/11 ATTACKS.
>> IN THIS INVESTIGATION, THERE
WILL BE HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS OF
IMAGES.
IF THEY HAVE A SUSPECT
IDENTIFIED, THEY KNOW THE AREA
THAT SUSPECT WAS IN, THEY'LL BE
ABLE TO THEN TRACK THE PERSON
BACK TO AN IMAGE AND SAY, HERE
WE HAVE HIM.
>> Reporter: THE FBI TECH AGENTS
ARE ALSO EXAMINING TINY BITS OF
DEBRIS RECOVERED AT THE CRIME
SCENE.
THERE ARE WIRE FRAGMENTS WITH
MANUFACTURING NAMES, TINY NAILS
USED AS SHRAPNEL, AS WELL AS THE
MANGLED REMAINS OF THE PRESSURE
COOKER THAT AGENTS SAY WAS USED
TO BUILD THE BOMB, AND MAY WELL
HAVE FINGERPRINTS STILL ON IT.
>> ONE OF THE KEYS IN ANY TRIAL
IS LINKING THE EVIDENCE YOU HAVE
TO THE SUSPECT.
IT'S EXTREMELY IMPORTANT TO
MATCH THE BOMB TO THE BAD GUY.
>> Reporter: ULTIMATELY, WHOEVER
IS ARRESTED WILL ALMOST
CERTAINLY FACE AT LEAST THREE
COUNTS OF PREMEDITATED MURDER,
FOR THE DEATHS OF 8-YEAR-OLD
MARTIN RICHARD, 29-YEAR-OLD
KRYSTLE CAMPBELL, AND THE THIRD
VICTIM IDENTIFIED JUST TODAY,
BOSTON UNIVERSITY GRADUATE
STUDENT LINGZI LU, A NATIVE OF
CHINA.
THERE MAY BE AS MANY AS A
THOUSAND AGENTS ASSIGNED TO THIS
CASE.
TONIGHT THERE'S A SENSE FROM
MANY OF THEM THAT THEY'RE
GETTING MUCH CLOSER.
>> BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> WE WANT TO BRING IN RICHARD
CLARK, WHO IS WAS A NATIONAL
COUNTERTERRORISM ADVISER AT THE
WHITE HOUSE UNDER TWO
ADMINISTRATIONS.
>> THERE'S GOOD NEWS THERE
APPARENTLY THAT THEY HAVE SOME
FACES.
SO WE MAY BE IN ONE OF THOSE
CASES THAT GETS CRACKED QUICKLY.
TO.
TOO EARLY TO TELL YET.
>> YOU REMINDED US THAT THEY PUT
BACK TOGETHER THE PLANE AT
LOCKERBIE PAN AM 103.
>> IT WAS A 747 THAT BLEW UP AT
ALTITUDE, SPREAD OVER A HUNDRED
SQUARE MILES.
THE FBI PUT THAT PLANE BACK
TOGETHER JUST AS THEY ARE TODAY
PUTTING THE BOMBS BACK TOGETHER.
>> I KNOW YOU'LL BE STANDING BY
WITH US THROUGHOUT THE EVENING
AS WE BRING EVERYONE THE LATEST
DEVELOPMENTS.
>> NOW WE TURN NEXT TO THAT
BREAKING NEWS IN THE DANGEROUS
DRAMA UNFOLDING OUT OF
WASHINGTON, D.C.
WONDER OF AN ARREST IN THE CASE
OF THOSE LETTERS THAT APPEAR TO
HAVE BEEN LACED WITH A DEADLY
TOXIN -- LETTERS SENT TO THE
PRESIDENT AND TO A CENTER.
THE TOXIN IS RICIN WHICH CAN
KILL WITHIN 36 HOURS AND THERE'S
NO ANTIDOTE.
ABC'S JIM AVILA HAS THE BREAKING
NEWS.
>> HAZMAT SUITED INSPECTORS
GATHERED EVIDENCE LINKED TO A
LETTER ADDRESSED TO THE
PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED STATES,
ANOTHER TO A MISSISSIPPI
SENATOR, FEDERAL SOURCES TELL
ABC NEWS THEY'VE ARRESTED A
SUSPECT FROM TUPELO,
MISSISSIPPI.
A SCARE THAT STOPPED MAIL
DELIVERY ON CAPITOL HILL THIS
WEEK.
>> ALL STAFF AND OTHER PERSONNEL
ARE DIRECTED TO AVOID THIS AREA
UNTIL FURTHER NOTICE.
>> Reporter: THE FEAR, RICIN.
EASILY MADE FROM CASTOR BEANS,
BY WOULD-BE BIOTERRORISTS.
>> IF YOU INGEST ENOUGH, IT
COULD BE VERY DAMAGING AND IT
COULD KILL YOU.
>> Reporter: TWO LETTERS, ONE TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA, ANOTHER TWO
ROGER WICKER, SHOWED INITIAL
POSITIVE RESULTS IN FIELD TESTS.
THE LETTERS NEVER REACHED THE
WHITE HOUSE OR CAPITAL.
>> THE MAIL SENT HERE IS
SCREENED AND THE TESTS ARE TAKEN
AT REMOTE SITES TO MITIGATE THE
RISKS.
>> THE FIRST WAS STOPPED THEN
MILES FROM ITS TARGET TO CAPITOL
HILL.
THE SECOND LETTER TO THE WHITE
HOUSE WAS INTERCEPTED SIX AND A
HALF MILES AWAY ON A MILITARY
BASE ON THE OUTSKIRTS OF D.C.
A THIRD POST OFFICE SORTING
FACILITY SUFFERED POSSIBLE
CONTAMINATION TO ITS FILTERING
SYSTEM FROM AN UNKNOWN SOURCE,
TEN MILES FROM DOWNTOWN
WASHINGTON.
PROTECTIONS INCLUDING AIR
SENSORS AT SCREENING CENTERS,
SET UP AFTER THE ANTHRAX ATTACK
IN 2001, THAT KILLED FIVE
AMERICANS AND INJURED 17 OTHERS,
IT HAPPENED JUST AFTER 9/11.
TODAY'S APPARENT ATTEMPT, SO
CLOSE TO ANOTHER INCIDENT OF
DOMESTIC TERROR IS AN EERIE
REMINDER OF THOSE FRIGHTENING
DAYS.
>> THE LETTERS TO THE PROBLEM
AND THE SENATOR WERE BOTH SIGNED
WITH THE INITIALS K.C. WHICH
MATCHES THE NAME OF THE MAN
ARRESTED IN TUPELO, MISSISSIPPI.
DIANE?
>>> AND NOW WE TURN TO THAT BIG
VOTE IN WASHINGTON AND JOLTING
DEFEAT FOR THE PRESIDENT ON THE
GUN BILL CRAFTED IN RESPONSE TO
THE NEWTOWN SHOOTING.
TONIGHT, IT HAS FAILED IN THE
SENATE, AND THE PRESIDENT SPOKE
JUST THIS AFTERNOON.
ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT, JONATHAN KARL, IS
THERE NOW.
>> Reporter: THIS WAS THE SINGLE
BEST CHANCE TO PASS ANY PART OF
THE PRESIDENT'S PLAN TO COMBAT
GUN VIOLENCE AND IT COULDN'T
EVEN GET PASSED IN THE
DEMOCRATICALLY-CONTROLLED
SENATE.
SURROUNDED BY VICTIMS OF GUN
VIOLENCE, THE PRESIDENT ANGRILY
DENOUNCED THE VOTE.
>> THERE ARE NO COHERENT
ARGUMENTS AS TO WHY WE WOULDN'T
DO THIS.
IT CAME DOWN TO POLITICS.
SO ALL IN ALL THIS WAS A PRETTY
SHAMEFUL DAY IN WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT WAS
JOINED BY MARK BARDEN, WHO LOST
HIS SON DANIEL IN THE SANDY HOOK
MASSACRE.
>> WE'LL RETURN HOME NOW,
DISAPPOINTED, BUT NOT DEFEATED.
WE RETURN HOME WITH THE
DETERMINATION THAT CHANGE WILL
HAPPEN.
MAYBE NOT TODAY, BUT IT WILL
IT WILL HAPPEN SOON.
>> THE AMENDMENT IS NOT AGREED
TO.
>> Reporter: WITH THE VICE
PRESIDENT PRESIDING, THE BILL
FELL SHORT OF THE 60 VOTES IT
NEEDED TO PASS.
PROMPTING SOMEONE IN THE
GALLERIES TO SHOUT OUT.
>> ORDER IN THE SENATE.
>> Reporter: THE VOTE WAS A
CRUSHING DISAPPOINTMENT TO THE
VICTIMS OF GUN VIOLENCE WHO HAD
BEEN PLEADING WITH SENATORS TO
PASS THE BILL.
MANY OF THEM WERE HERE TO WATCH
AS THE VOTE WENT DOWN.
12-YEAR-OLD JAMES BARDEN WHOSE
LITTLE BROTHER WAS MURDERED AT
SANDY HOOK WAS THERE.
>> I FEEL WE OWE IT TO DANIEL.
'CAUSE HIS LIFE NEEDS TO MEAN
SOMETHING.
AND NO ONE ELSE SHOULD HAVE TO
DO THIS.
>> Reporter: THIS WAS JUST ONE
PART OF THE PRESIDENT'S PLAN
THAT WOULD HAVE EXPANDED
BACKGROUND CHECKS TO ALL
PURCHASES AT GUN SHOWS AND
ONLINE.
THEY'RE NOW ONLY REQUIRED FOR
GUNS BOUGHT AT GUN DEALERS.
IT MEANS THE REST OF THE
PRESIDENT'S PLAN IS EFFECTIVELY
DEAD.
ALTHOUGH JOE BIDEN TOLD US THE
FIGHT IS NOT OVER.
>> IT'S TIME FOR THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE TO MAKE IT CLEAR JUST
HOW DISPLEASED THEY ARE WITH
THIS VOTE AND LET THEIR
REPRESENTATIVES KNOW THAT.
THIS IS FAR FROM OVER.
>> Reporter: I JUST FINISHED
TALKING TO THOSE SANDY HOOK
FAMILIES.
THEY ARE TIRED, EMOTIONALLY
DRAINED, BUT THEY TELL ME
THEY'RE ABSOLUTELY DETERMINED
TO CONTINUE THIS FIGHT.
BUT AS FAR AS THIS BILL, THIS
EFFORT TO EXPAND BACKGROUND
CHECKS, IT IS ALL BUT DEAD FOR
THE REST OF THE YEAR.
THERE'S VIRTUALLY NO CHANCE IT
WILL BE REVIVED.
>> THANKS SO MUCH, JON.
>>> NOW WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
EVERYONE OVERSEAS FOR A MOMENT
FOR THE FUNERAL FOR MARGARET
THATCHER IN LONDON.
♪
>> THERE WERE THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE LINING THE STREETS TO
HONOR HER, A FEW DOZEN
PROTESTERS SHOWING UP AS WELL,
BUT MORE THAN 2,000 MOURNERS
PACKED ST. PAUL'S CATHEDRAL.
AMONG THEM DICK CHENEY, HENRY
KISSINGER, AND QUEEN ELIZABETH
PAYING TRIBUTE TO THE IRON LADY
IN THE LARGEST FUNERAL FOR A
NON-ROYAL SINCE WINSTON
CHURCHILL IN 1965.
>>> NEXT WE TURN BACK HOME TO
THE MAJOR HEADACHE FOR ANYONE
FLYING AMERICAN AIRLINES.
24 HOURS AFTER THEY GROUNDED
THEIR FLEET AND CANCELED MORE
THAN 1,000 FLIGHTS, ABC'S
DAVID KERLEY TAKES US INSIDE
THE CHAOS.
WHAT CAUSED THE SHORT-CIRCUIT
AND WHAT HAPPENED TODAY.
>> Reporter: THIS IS WHAT A
COMPUTER CRASH LOOKS LIKE.
THOUSANDS OF PASSENGERS IN
HOURS' LONG LINES, PLANES
GROUNDED, 1,200 FLIGHTS
CANCELED.
TODAY, AMERICAN AIRLINES
STRUGGLED TO GET BACK ON
SCHEDULE.
CARLOS MALDONADO WAS TRYING, FOR
A SECOND DAY, TO GET HOME TO
NEW MEXICO.
>> THERE WAS JUST ONE CONFLICT
AFTER ANOTHER, A LOT OF UNHAPPY
FOLKS.
>> Reporter: ALL THE AIRLINE
WOULD SAY IS THAT A SOFTWARE
ISSUE WITH ITS MAIN AND BACK-UP
SYSTEMS FORCED IT TO SHUT
EVERYTHING DOWN.
A STARK REMINDER OF HOW MUCH OUR
LIVES NOW NEED TECHNOLOGY TO
WORK.
>> WE'RE SO DEPENDENT ON IT NOW.
SO THE CONVENIENCE ENDS UP
BACKFIRING SOMETIMES.
>> Reporter: IT HAPPENED TO
UNITED AIRLINES LAST YEAR AS IT
WAS MERGING WITH CONTINENTAL AND
THE TWO RESERVATIONS SYSTEMS.
NO SHUTDOWN, BUT SEVERE DELAYS.
AND GUESS WHAT.
AMERICAN HOPES TO MERGE WITH
U.S. AIRWAYS LATER THIS YEAR.
SO AFTER THE COMPUTER GLITCH
AMERICAN QUICKLY TOOK TO
YOUTUBE.
>> WE'RE VERY SORRY FOR THAT.
>> Reporter: APOLOGIZING, BUT
NOT PROMISING THAT THIS WILL
NEVER HAPPEN AGAIN.
DAVID KERLEY, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON NATIONAL AIRPORT.
>>> STILL AHEAD ON THIS
FAST-MOVING NEWS DAY, A JUDGE'S
WIFE HAS BEEN CHARGED WITH
MURDERING THOSE TWO TEXAS
PROSECUTORS.
TONIGHT WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT A
CONFESSION AND A POSSIBLE
MOTIVE.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS IS KEVIN.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT Aleve
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HIM,
HE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HIM ALL DAY
AS HE GOES BACK
TO TAKING TYLENOL.
I WAS OKAY, BUT AFTER LUNCH
MY KNEE STARTED TO HURT AGAIN.
AND NOW I'VE GOT TO
TAKE MORE PILLS.
♪
YUP. ANOTHER PILL STOP.
CAN I GET MY Aleve BACK YET?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY Aleve.
[ Male Announcer ] LOOK FOR THE
EASY-OPEN RED ARTHRITIS CAP.
YOU'LL HAVE TO PAY FIVE HUNDRED
BUCKS FOR YOUR DEDUCTIBLE.
THE TRUTH?
AT Allstate, YOU COULD PAY ZERO.
Allstate GIVES YOU
A HUNDRED DOLLARS
OFF YOUR DEDUCTIBLE
THE DAY YOU SIGN UP.
THEN ANOTHER HUNDRED OFF EVERY
YEAR YOU DON'T HAVE AN ACCIDENT.
LET THE GOOD HANDS
REWARD YOUR SAFE DRIVING
WITH A DEDUCTIBLE
THAT GOES AWAY.
♪
DEDUCTIBLE REWARDS.
ONE MORE WAY YOU'RE IN
GOOD HANDS WITH Allstate.
♪
AND "MULTIPLE CHOICE,"
COME TO WALGREENS
FOR HELP FINDING THE ONE
THAT'S RIGHT FOR YOU...
LIKE CENTRUM.
NOW, GET FOUR DOLLARS OFF
SELECT CENTRUM PRODUCTS
WITH BALANCE REWARDS CARD.
AT THE CORNER
OF HAPPY AND HEALTHY.
FOR OVER 30 YEARS.
AND IT'S NOW
THE MOST DOCTOR RECOMMENDED,
THE MOST PREFERRED
AND THE MOST STUDIED.
SO WHEN IT COMES TO GETTING THE
MOST OUT OF YOUR MULTIVITAMIN,
THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
CENTRUM.
>>> AND NOW WE WANT TO TELL YOU
ABOUT A STARTLING DEVELOPMENT IN
THE POINT-BLANK MURDERS OF A
TEXAS DISTRICT ATTORNEY, HIS
WIFE, AT THEIR HOME AND ALSO AN
ASSISTANT PROSECUTOR.
HERE'S THE TWIST, THE CONFESSION
FROM SOMEONE FEW PEOPLE COULD
HAVE IMAGINED.
ABC'S SENIOR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT, PIERRE THOMAS,
WITH THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: FOR YEARS IN LITTLE
TOWN KAUFMAN, TEXAS, JUSTICE OF
THE PEACE ERIC WILLIAMS AND HIS
WIFE KIM WERE KNOWN AS SOLID
CITIZENS.
AND WHEN DISTRICT ATTORNEY MARK
McLELLAND AND HIS WIFE WERE
GUNNED DOWN IN THEIR OWN HOME,
WILLIAMS EXPRESSED HIS
SYMPATHIES.
>> MY HEART GOES OUT TO ALL THE
FAMILIES THAT HAVE BEEN AFFECTED
BY THIS TRAGEDY.
>> Reporter: THE CASE DREW
NATIONAL ATTENTION AND SUSPICION
FELL ON WHITE SUPREMACIST PRISON
GANGS.
>> ANYTHING THAT THE PUBLIC CAN
HELP WITH?
>> NOT THAT WE'RE RELEASING.
>> Reporter: BUT TODAY
AUTHORITIES SAY THE KILLERS WERE
NONE OTHER THAN ERIC AND KIM
WILLIAMS.
>> KIM LENE WILLIAMS, 46, OF
KAUFMAN, HAS BEEN ARRESTED AND
CHARGED WITH THE OFFENSE OF
CAPITAL MURDER.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY SHE
CONFESSED TO HER INVOLVEMENT IN
THE MURDER SCHEME.
ACCORDING TO COURT DOCUMENTS,
SHE TOLD INVESTIGATORS HER
HUSBAND SHOT TO DEATH THE
McLELLANDS AND ALSO ASSISTANT
DISTRICT ATTORNEY MARK HASSE,
GUNNED DOWN NEAR THE COURTHOUSE
IN JANUARY.
THE ALLEGED MOTIVE, REVENGE.
McLELLAND AND HASSE PROSECUTED
WILLIAMS SHOWN HERE ON
SURVEILLANCE TAPES, FOR STEALING
GOVERNMENT COMPUTERS.
IN THIS INTERVIEW, HE SUGGESTED
HE NEEDED THE EQUIPMENT TO WORK
FROM HOME.
>> SO YOU JUST TOOK THE MONITORS
AND THE MEMORY?
>> THAT'S WHAT I CAN REMEMBER.
DURING TRIAL PROSECUTOR MARK
HASSE CALLED WILLIAMS A FLAT-OUT
THIEF AND BURGLAR, AND NEEDS TO
BE REMOVED FROM OFFICE.
DISTRICT ATTORNEY MIKE McLELLAND
DESCRIBED THE CASE AS AN EXAMPLE
OF THE FOX WATCHING THE HEN
HOUSE.
WILLIAMS WAS CONVICTED OF THEFT,
HIS REPUTATION AND LIVELIHOOD
DESTROYED.
AFTER THE MOST RECENT MURDERS,
INVESTIGATORS QUICKLY SUSPECTED
WILLIAMS, HE DENIED EVERYTHING.
BUT POLICE STAYED ON THE CASE,
SEARCHING HIS HOME AND RENTAL
STORAGE PROPERTY.
>> IT MAKES ME FEEL THAT THE
POLICE ARE DOING THE THOROUGH
JOB THEY NEED TO.
>> Reporter: THEY APPARENTLY
DID.
CAPITAL MURDER CHARGES ARE
EXPECTED AGAINST ERIC WILLIAMS
AS EARLY AS TOMORROW.
PIERRE THOMAS, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> AND COMING UP NEXT IN OUR
INSTANT INDEX, AUDREY HEPBURN AS
HOLLY GOLIGHTLY, BUT DID THE
HEROINE OF "BREAKFAST AT
TIFFANY'S" ALMOST HAVE A VERY
DIFFERENT NAME?
A SIMPLE QUESTION:
HOW OLD IS THE OLDEST PERSON
YOU'VE KNOWN?
WE GAVE PEOPLE A STICKER
AND HAD THEM SHOW US.
WE LEARNED A LOT OF US
HAVE KNOWN SOMEONE
WHO'S LIVED WELL INTO THEIR 90S.
AND THAT'S A GREAT THING.
BUT EVEN THOUGH
WE'RE LIVING LONGER,
ONE THING THAT HASN'T CHANGED:
THE OFFICIAL RETIREMENT AGE.
♪
THE QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU MAKE
SURE YOU HAVE THE MONEY YOU NEED
TO ENJOY ALL OF THESE YEARS.
♪
THEY'RE ABOUT 10 TIMES SOFTER
AND MAY HAVE SURFACE PORES
WHERE BACTERIA CAN MULTIPLY.
POLIDENT KILLS 99.99%
OF ODOR CAUSING BACTERIA
AND HELPS DISSOLVE STAINS
SO DENTURES ARE CLEANER,
FRESHER, AND BRIGHTER.
[ Male Announcer ] POLIDENT.
>>> OUR INSTANT INDEX TONIGHT
Break a leg!
I used to love
hearing that phrase...
but not since I learned I have
postmenopausal osteoporosis
and a high risk for fracture.
I want to keep acting but a
broken bone could change that.
So my doctor and I chose PROLIA®
to reduce my risk of fractures.
PROLIA® is proven to help
make bones stronger.
I take PROLIA®. It's different-
it's two shots a year.
Do not take PROLIA® if you are
pregnant, are allergic to it or
if you take XGEVA®
..PROLIA® can cause serious
side effects, including low
blood calcium levels,
serious infections, some of
which may require
hospitalization...
...and skin inflammation, rash
and eczema. Tell your doctor if
you develop dental problems
..as severe jaw bone problems
may happen, or if you develop
new or unusual pain in your hip,
groin or thigh, as unusual thigh
bone fractures have occurred.
What's out there matters to me..
...so does what's in here.
Break a leg!
Ask your doctor if PROLIA®
is right for you.
[ slap! ]
[ Male Announcer ] YOUR
FAVORITE FOODS FIGHTING YOU?
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
CALCIUM-RICH TUMS
STARTS WORKING SO FAST
YOU'LL FORGET
YOU HAD HEARTBURN.
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUM TUMS
>>> OUR INSTANT INDEX TONIGHT
BEGINS WITH SOME MEMORABLE
HOLLYWOOD HISTORY.
IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO THINK OF
AUDREY HEPBURN IN "BREAKFAST AT
TIFFANY'S," WITHOUT THINKING OF
HOLLY GOLIGHTLY.
BUT LOOK THIS.
TRUMAN CAPOTE'S ORIGINAL
MANUSCRIPT HAS A NOTE ON IT.
THE ORIGINAL NAME, CONNIE
GUSTAFSON.
IT'S SCRATCHED OUT.
THE NAME "HOLLY GOLIGHTLY"
WRITTEN IN.
SO WE CAN ALL WONDER, WOULD
"CONNIE" EVER HAVE BEEN AS
MAGICAL?
>>> AND AN UNFORGETTABLE VOICE
STIRRING MILLIONS OF THE
FAITHFUL HAS GONE SILENT,
THE RICH BARITONE OF GEORGE
BEVERLY SHEA WHO HAS DIED AT
THE AGE OF 104.
♪
>> HE SANG WITH THE MOST FAMOUS
EVANGELIST OF HIS TIME, REVEREND
BILLY GRAHAM.
AND GRAHAM SAID OF HIS FRIEND,
THERE WAS NO SINGER HE WOULD
RATHER HEAR.
>>> AND WE HAVE A FOOTNOTE ON
THE TRAGIC EVENTS IN BOSTON FROM
COMEDIAN STEPHEN COLBERT WHO
USED LAUGHTER TO CREATE A
MESSAGE IN TRIBUTE TO THE TOUGH
PEOPLE OF A GREAT AMERICAN CITY.
>> NOTHING THESE TERRORISTS DO
WILL SHAKE THEM.
FOR PETE SAKE, BOSTON WAS
FOUNDED BY THE PILGRIMS, A
PEOPLE SO TOUGH THEY HAD TO
BUCKLE THEIR [ BLEEP ] HATS ON.
>> THESE MANIACS HAVE TRIED TO
MAKE LIFE BAD FOR THE PEOPLE OF
BOSTON, BUT ALL THEY CAN EVER DO
IS SHOW JUST HOW GOOD THOSE
PEOPLE ARE.
>>> AND ON THAT VERY NOTE, STAY
WITH US, BECAUSE ALL THE PEOPLE
AROUND THE COUNTRY WERE SINGING
BOSTON'S FAVORITE ANTHEM TODAY.
♪
BEFORE COPD...
I TOOK MY SON FISHING
EVERY YEAR.
WE HAD A GREAT SPOT,
NOT EASY TO FIND, BUT WORTH IT.
BUT WITH COPD
MAKING IT HARD TO BREATHE,
I THOUGHT
THOSE DAYS MIGHT BE OVER.
SO MY DOCTOR
PRESCRIBED SYMBICORT.
IT HELPS SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE
MY LUNG FUNCTION
STARTING WITHIN FIVE MINUTES.
SYMBICORT DOESN'T REPLACE
A RESCUE INHALER
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS.
WITH SYMBICORT,
TODAY I'M BREATHING BETTER.
AND THAT MEANS...FISH ON!
SYMBICORT IS FOR COPD
INCLUDING CHRONIC BRONCHITIS
AND EMPHYSEMA.
IT SHOULD NOT BE TAKEN
MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
SYMBICORT MAY INCREASE YOUR RISK
OF LUNG INFECTIONS,
OSTEOPOROSIS,
AND SOME EYE PROBLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HEART CONDITION
OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING IT.
WITH COPD, I THOUGHT
I'D MISS OUR FAMILY TRADITION.
NOW SYMBICORT SIGNIFICANTLY
IMPROVES MY LUNG FUNCTION,
STARTING WITHIN 5 MINUTES.
AND THAT MAKES A DIFFERENCE
IN MY BREATHING.
TODAY, WE'RE READY
FOR WHATEVER SWIMS OUR WAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT SYMBICORT.
I GOT MY FIRST
PRESCRIPTION FREE.
CALL OR CLICK
TO LEARN MORE.
[ Male Announcer ] IF YOU CAN'T
AFFORD YOUR MEDICATION,
ASTRAZENECA
MAY BE ABLE TO HELP.
I GOT THIS.
[Thinking] IS IT THAT TIME?
THE SON PICKS UP THE CHECK?
[Thinking] I'M STILL WORKING.
HE'S RETIRED.
I HOPE HE'S SAVING.
I HOPE HE SAVED ENOUGH.
WHO MATTERS MOST TO YOU
SAYS THE MOST ABOUT YOU.
AT MassMutual WE'RE OWNED
BY OUR POLICYOWNERS,
AND THEY MATTER MOST TO US.
WHETHER YOU'RE JUST STARTING
YOUR 401(k)
OR YOU ARE READY
FOR RETIREMENT,
WE'LL HELP YOU GET THERE.
ACCOMPLISHING EVEN LITTLE THINGS
CAN BECOME MAJOR VICTORIES.
I'M PHIL MICKELSON, PRO GOLFER.
WHEN I WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS,
MY RHEUMATOLOGIST
PRESCRIBED ENBREL
FOR MY PAIN AND STIFFNESS,
AND TO HELP STOP JOINT DAMAGE.
[ Male Announcer ]
ENBREL MAY LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS
INCLUDING INFECTIONS,
TUBERCULOSIS,
LYMPHOMA, OTHER CANCERS,
NERVOUS SYSTEM
AND BLOOD DISORDERS,
AND ALLERGIC REACTIONS
HAVE OCCURRED.
BEFORE STARTING ENBREL,
YOUR DOCTOR SHOULD TEST YOU
FOR TUBERCULOSIS
AND DISCUSS WHETHER
YOU'VE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL INFECTIONS
ARE COMMON.
YOU SHOULD NOT START ENBREL
IF YOU HAVE AN INFECTION
LIKE THE FLU.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU'RE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,
HAVE CUTS OR SORES,
HAVE HAD HEPATITIS B,
HAVE BEEN TREATED
FOR HEART FAILURE,
OR IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS PERSISTENT FEVER,
BRUISING, BLEEDING,
OR PALENESS.
SINCE ENBREL HELPED RELIEVE
MY JOINT PAIN,
IT'S THE LITTLE THINGS
THAT MEAN THE MOST.
ASK YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST
IF ENBREL IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
[ Doctor ] ENBREL,
THE NUMBER ONE BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
PRESCRIBED BY RHEUMATOLOGISTS.
>>> AND FINALLY TONIGHT, WE WERE
GLAD SO MANY OF YOU LOVED
HEARING THE PEOPLE OF BOSTON
SEND OUT THEIR OWN MESSAGE TO
THE WORLD LAST NIGHT.
SO WE THOUGHT TONIGHT WE'D GO
BACK TO THEM FOR EVEN MORE, A
SPIRITED, RALLYING CRY DELIVERED
AS ONLY BOSTONIANS CAN.
♪
>> THIS IS A CLOSE-KNIT PLACE,
THE CITY OF BOSTON.
HERE WE KNOW OUR NEIGHBORS.
WE GRIEVE FOR THEM.
>> AS AN AMERICAN, MY HEART IS
BROKEN.
BUT AS A BOSTONIAN, MY RESOLVE
FOR THE PURSUIT OF FREEDOM AND
LIBERTY HAS NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
>> I HAVE TO GIVE IT TO THE
BOSTONIANS.
PEOPLE WERE GIVING US WATER,
FOOD, BLANKETS TO WRAP ON.
EVERYBODY WAS LENDING A HAND --
AND THESE ARE COMPLETE
STRANGERS.
♪
>> IF YOU WANT TO KNOW WHO WE
ARE, WHAT AMERICA IS, HOW WE
RESPOND TO EVIL, THAT'S IT.
SELFLESSLY, COMPASSIONATELY,
UNAFRAID.
♪
>> WE'RE STRONG PEOPLE AND WE'RE
NOT GOING TO LET ANYONE PUSH US
AROUND.
YOU MESS WITH ONE OF US, YOU
MESS WITH ALL OF US.
>> THAT'S WHO WE ARE.
WE'RE FIGHTERS.
>> WE WILL NOT BE BULLIED.
WE WILL NOT BE PUSHED AROUND.
WE WILL NOT LET SOMEONE FORCE US
TO BE AFRAID OF OUR OWN SHADOW
IN THE CITY WE CALL HOME.
>> WE MUST NOT FEED THE TERROR.
THIS IS AMERICA, AND EVEN
GREATER THAN THAT, THIS IS
BOSTON -- A HOME OF THE PATRIOT.
>> AND DON'T FORGET "NIGHTLINE"
LATER TONIGHT.
WE'LL LEAVE YOU NOW WITH THE
SOUNDS OF "SWEET CAROLINE," THE
ANTHEM OF BOSTON BASEBALL FANS
AND TONIGHT, AMERICA'S ANTHEM
TOO.
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD ♪
♪ I'VE BEEN INCLINED
TO BELIEVE THERE NEVER WAS ♪
♪ BUT NOW I LOOK AT THE NIGHT
♪
AND IT DON'T SEEM SO LONELY
♪ WE FILL IT UP
>>> TONIGHT A BAY AREA COMPANY
TELLS HOW IT CAN HELP THE FBI
TRACK THE TERRORIST AUTOS
EXCLUSIVE VIDEO OF THE SEARCH
FOR EVIDENCE IN BOSTON.
>> WE'LL FOLLOW UP ON THE
SUICIDE OF A HIGH SCHOOL RAPE
VICTIM Y IT TOOK SO LONG FOR
CLASSMATES TO BE CHARGED.
>> AND OPENING DAY AT THE NEW
EXPLORATORIUM.
WE'RE LIVE AT ITS NEW HOME
WHERE THE CELEBRATION
CONTINUES INTO THE NIGHT.
>> THAT IS ONE OF THE
EXPLOSIONS THAT KILLED THREE
PEOPLE AT THE BOSTON MARATHON
ON MONDAY.
TONIGHT A BATTERY MAKER MAY
ABLE TO HELP FIGURE OUT WHO
SET IT OFF.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> DESPITE PERSISTENT REPORTS
THROUGHOUT THE DAY THE BOMBER
HAD BEEN IDENTIFIED AND
ARRESTED INVESTIGATORS ARE
STILL PORING OVER PHOTOS IN
SEARCH OF SUSPECTS.
THEY DID RELEASE PICTURES OF
ONE BOMB.
WHEN THE PEOPLE SAW ONE OF THE
BATTERIES IN THE PHOTOS THAT
YOU'RE LOOKING AT HERE, WELL,
THEY PICKED UP THE PHONE AND
CALLED THE FBI.
THEY ALSO SPOKE WITH ABC 7
NEWS.
SERGIO?
>> TENERGY MANUFACTURES A
RECHARGEABLE BATTERY THAT IS
POPULARLY USED IN REMOTE
CONTROL TOY CARS AND TRUCKS.
MORE COMPACT THAN A DOUBLE A
BUT GIVES MORE POWER, SO WHEN
EMPLOYEES NOTICE PICTURES OF
THE BOMB KPOENT SKPDZ
BATTERIES THEY IMMEDIATELY
REACHED OUT TO LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
THESE ARE PICTURES OF THE BITS
AND PIECES OF THE KPOENTS.
EMPLOYEES NOTICED ONE SINKED
BATTERY IN THE PICTURES THEY
CALLED THE AUTHORITIES.
>> WE CONTACTED BOTH BOSTON
POLICE DEPARTMENT AND THE FBI.
>> THIS VICE PRESIDENT AT
SYN -- TENERGY SAYS IT'S
USUALLY USED TO POWER REMOTE
CONTROL TOY AUTOS I DON'T
THINK THERE IS ANYTHING IN
PARTICULARLY UNIQUE