>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS IN THE
HEARTLAND.
TORNADOES TOUCHING DOWN RIGHT
NOW.
30 MILLION AMERICANS IN THE
STORM ZONE.
THIS EVENING, THE NEW WARNINGS
AND THE GIANT TWISTERS CAUGHT ON
TAPE.
METEOROLOGIST GINGER ZEE IN THE
MIDDLE OF IT ALL TONIGHT.
>>> OFF THE RAILS.
THE DRAMATIC MOMENTS RIGHT AFTER
THAT MAJOR COMMUTER TRAIN
DERAILED, SMASHING INTO ANOTHER.
AND TONIGHT, YET ANOTHER TRAIN
OFF THE TRACKS.
THE WARNINGS FOR TOMORROW
MORNING'S COMMUTE.
>>> THE ONE AND ONLY.
THAT RECORD POWERBALL JACKPOT.
AND WHAT WE LEARNED ABOUT THE
ONE WINNING TICKET.
AND WHY THIS WINNER HAS NO
CHOICE.
THEY WON'T BE ABLE TO STAY
ANONYMOUS.
>>> AND HER TURN.
AFTER THAT FAMOUS OSCAR MOMENT,
BEN AFFLECK TELLING THE WORLD
HIS MARRIAGE WAS WORK.
HIS WIFE, ACTRESS JENNIFER
GARNER, GETTING THE LAST LAUGH.
>> A GIFT.
I WOULD HAVE SAID, THANK YOU
TO MY WIFE.
OUR MARRIAGE IS A GIFT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A SUNDAY NIGHT.
AND WE DO BEGIN WITH A DANGEROUS
SCENE PLAYING OUT ACROSS MUCH OF
THE HEARTLAND AT THIS HOUR.
SEVERAL CITIES TAKING COVER.
AND THESE PICTURES JUST COMING
IN FROM OKLAHOMA CITY TONIGHT.
YOU CAN SEE THE FIERCE CLOUDS
THERE, DARKENING THE HORIZON,
SENDING DEBRIS IN EVERY
DIRECTION.
KNOCKING OUT POWER ALREADY.
GINGER ZEE HAD BEEN WARNING ALL
OF US OVER THE LAST 24 HOURS
THAT THIS SUNDAY EVENING, THE
SEVERE WEATHER WOULD TAKE AIM AT
FAR MORE POPULATED AREAS.
THAT'S WHAT'S UNFOLDING AT THIS
HOUR.
IT'S BELIEVED THERE'S
SIGNIFICANT DAMAGE.
ALL OF IT UNFOLDING RIGHT NOW.
I WANT TO BRING IN GINGER,
OUTSIDE WICHITA, KANSAS,
TONIGHT.
THE SKY DARKENING AS SHE WAS
JUST READY TO COME ON THE AIR
FOR US.
GINGER?
>> DAVID, WE'VE BEEN STORM
CHASING ALL AFTERNOON.
AND LOOK BEHIND ME.
THAT IS THE STORM THAT BROUGHT
THE TORNADO RIPPING THROUGH
WICHITA, KANSAS.
IT'S MOVING TO OUR NORTH AND
EAST.
THERE'S A TORNADO ON THE GROUND
NEAR OKLAHOMA CITY.
THIS IS AN ACTIVE AND FLUID
SITUATION.
WE'LL BRING YOU THE LATEST
DETAILS THROUGHOUT THE NIGHT.
BUT LOOK AT THE WILD WEATHER SO
FAR.
>> IT'S COMING RIGHT FOR US.
>> Reporter: TEARING ACROSS THE
KANSAS LANDSCAPE, MULTIPLE
VIOLENT TORNADOES.
WATCH AS LIGHTNING ILLUMINATES
THIS TWISTER IN SANFORD, KANSAS.
THAT TORNADO ALSO TOUCHED DOWN
NEAR ROSEL, WHERE IT WAS CAUGHT
FROM EVERY, SINGLE ANGLE.
AND BIG HAIL COMING DOWN.
PUMMELING THIS WINDSHIELD IN
NEBRASKA.
IN OKLAHOMA CITY,
60-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS TOPPLED
POWER LINES ON SATURDAY.
THERE'S BEEN NEARLY 400 REPORTS
OF SEVERE WEATHER IN JUST THE
LAST 2 DAYS.
MAJOR HIGHWAYS TURNING INTO
RIVERS.
THESE SEMIS STUCK IN NORTH
DAKOTA.
AND IN GEORGIA, PARTS OF ATLANTA
UNDER WATER.
ROADS CRUMBLED AFTER UP
TO SEVEN INCHES OF RAIN FELL
OVERNIGHT.
THE STEADY AND INTENSE DOWNPOUR,
FLOODING BACKYARDS.
THIS PLAYSET SUBMERGED FROM THE
RISING WATERS.
>> IT RAINED FROM 2:00 UNTIL
6:00, NONSTOP.
>> Reporter: AND TONIGHT, MORE
STORMS ON THE WAY.
DAVID, THE THREAT IS FAR FROM
OVER.
LET ME SHOW YOU THIS MAP.
TONIGHT, HERE IS WHO NEEDS TO BE
CONCERNED.
ANYWHERE FROM OKLAHOMA CITY TO
KANSAS CITY.
THAT'S THE IMMEDIATE THREAT.
BUT THE LARGE, SEVERE WEATHER
THREAT GOES FROM MINNESOTA TO
TEXAS.
AND TOMORROW, THE STORM MOVES
SLOWLY TO THE EAST, FROM
CHICAGO, DOWN TO TEXAS.
ALL OF THE PLAINS INCLUDED HERE.
GOING TO BE A TORNADIC AND
SEVERE WEATHER DAY.
DAVID?
>> THAT'S A HUGE STORM ZONE,
GINGER.
GINGER WILL STAY ON THIS
THROUGHOUT THE EVENING AND
STRAIGHT THROUGH TO "GOOD
MORNING AMERICA" FIRST THING IN
THE MORNING.
>>> AS THAT UNFOLDS, ANOTHER
MYSTERY UNFOLDING TONIGHT.
THE QUESTION, WHO IS AMERICA'S
NEW MULTIMILLIONAIRE?
HARD TO BELIEVE, BUT THERE WAS
JUST ONE WINNING TICKET
IN THE GIANT POWERBALL LOTTERY
OVERNIGHT.
AND IT WAS SOLD IN ZEPHYRHILLS,
FLORIDA.
HERE ARE THE WINNING NUMBERS,
10, 13, 14, 22, 52.
THE POWERBALL WAS 11.
AND YOU DON'T NEED US TO TELL
YOU.
THE JACKPOT WAS $590.5 MILLION.
SOMEONE HERE DID THE MATH TODAY,
LOOKING AT THE AVERAGE INCOME
FOR ZEPHYRHILLS.
IT WOULD TAKE THE AVERAGE PERSON
WHO LIVES THERE 28,000 YEARS TO
MAKE THAT MUCH.
BUT FOR SOMEONE OR SOME GROUP,
THEY MADE THAT IN AN INSTANT.
ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI, IN THAT
TOWN TONIGHT.
>> IT'S A RECORD-BREAKING
JACKPOT.
>> Reporter: IT'S THE BIGGEST
THING TO HAPPEN IN ZEPHYRHILLS,
FLORIDA.
KNOWN FOR ITS LARGE
NEIGHBORHOODS OF GROOVY SENIORS
AND A PRETTY POPULAR BRAND OF
BOTTLED WATER.
>> ZEPHYRHILLS.
>> Reporter: IT'S THE MOST
VALUABLE WINNING TICKET EVER.
WORTH MORE THAN $500 MILLION.
AND SOMEONE HERE IS WALKING
AROUND TOWN WITH IT BURNING IN
THEIR POCKET.
COULD BE A FRIEND.
COULD BE FAMILY.
>> I HOPE SO.
>> IT WILL BE KNOWN WHO WINS.
IT'S A SMALL TOWN.
AND EVERYBODY TALKS.
>> Reporter: OUTSIDE THE GROCERY
STORE THAT SOLD THE WINNING
TICKET, THEY TELL US THEY'VE
BEEN OVERWHELMED WITH CALLS FROM
ACROSS THE COUNTRY, FROM REALLY
FRIENDLY RELATIVES TO CHECK TO
SEE IF THEY WON.
THIS GUY TOLD US HE'S KEEPING
THE DREAM ALIVE, REFUSING TO
CHECK HIS TICKETS UNTIL LATER
TONIGHT.
>> I COULD BE THE WINNER.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: YES.
YOU DIDN'T FEEL LIKE AN URGENCY
TO CHECK?
>> YOU SEE, THE ANTICIPATION IS
MORE OF A PLEASURE THAN ACTUALLY
LOSING, WHICH IS MOSTLY WHAT
HAPPENS.
I ANTICIPATE LONGER.
AND I'M A BILLIONAIRE UNTIL I
FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: THE JACKPOT IS
WORTH $590.5 MILLION.
THAT'S ONLY IF THE WINNER TAKES
ANNUAL PAYMENTS.
TAKE IT AT ONCE AND IT'S NEARLY
$371 MILLION.
THE LOTTERY WITHHOLDS 25% IN
FEDERAL TAXES.
BUT IN FLORIDA, THERE'S NO STATE
TAX, GREAT NEWS FOR THE WINNER.
WHO IS LEFT WITH ABOUT
$278 MILLION AND CHANGE.
THE RUMOR MILL IS ON FIRE.
IS IT ONE OF THE TOWN'S SENIORS?
OR A YOUNG WOMAN WHO WORKS AT A
STORE?
FLORIDA SAW SAYS THE WINNER MUST
COME FORWARD TO CLAIM THE MONEY.
THE TICKET THAT WON IT ALL WAS
SOLD AT THIS FLORIDA GROCERY
STORE.
STATE LOTTERY OFFICIALS SAY
THEIR OFFICE IN TALLAHASSEE WILL
BE OPEN BRIGHT AND EARLY
TOMORROW MORNING.
THAT'S THE SOONEST WE COULD HEAR
FROM A WINNER.
DAVID?
>> STEVE, THANK YOU.
SOMEONE OR SOME GROUP NOT
HEADING BACK TO WORK TOMORROW
MORNING.
>>> BUT FOR THE REST OF US WHO
ARE, A MORNING HEADACHE IN MUCH
OF THE COUNTRY.
ANOTHER TRAIN OFF THE TRACKS
TONIGHT.
TWO THIS WEEKEND.
AMTRAK TRAIN DERAILING NEAR
CHICAGO'S UNION STATION TODAY.
197 PASSENGERS ONBOARD THE TRAIN
FROM NEW ORLEANS.
NO ONE WAS HURT.
BUT THIS COMES JUST AS WE GET
NEW IMAGES FROM THE DERAILMENT
FRIDAY NIGHT.
THAT TRAIN FROM NEW YORK TO
CONNECTICUT AND THE STRUGGLE TO
SAVE THE INJURED.
ABC'S GIO BENITEZ WITH THE NEWS
THAT THOSE TRACKS WILL NOT BE UP
AND RUNNING FOR SOME TIME TO
COME.
>> Reporter: THE MOMENT OF
IMPACT, CAPTURED BY TEENAGERS
SKATEBOARDING NEAR THE ACCIDENT
SITE.
>> ALL I HEAR IS A BIG BOMB
BEHIND ME, OVER THERE.
AND JUST A BIG DUST CLOUD.
>> Reporter: BRIAN ALVAREZ AND
HIS FRIENDS GOT UP CLOSE AND SAW
THE AFTERMATH.
>> THE TRACK, LIKE IT'S OFF THE
TRACKS.
>> LOOK AT THIS.
IT'S NOT SUPPOSED TO BE LIKE
THAT.
>> Reporter: FRIDAY NIGHT, A
METRO NORTH COMMUTER TRAIN, FROM
NEW YORK CITY TO NEW HAVEN,
CONNECTICUT, DERAILED IN
BRIDGEPORT CARRYING 300
PASSENGERS.
ANOTHER TRAIN WITH 400
PASSENGERS ONBOARD, HIT THAT
DERAILED TRAIN.
AT LEAST 70 PEOPLE WERE INJURED.
>> THE POLICE ARE COMING.
EVERYONE'S PANICKING.
>> Reporter: IN THIS VIDEO, WE
SEE THE CHAOS AND CONFUSION.
BUT ALSO, THE RUSH TO HELP THE
PASSENGERS ONBOARD.
ONE WOMAN, UNABLE TO WALK IS
PULLED OUT.
>> IS THERE A BABY IN THERE?
>> YOU HEAR ABOUT THE STORIES ON
THE TELEVISION.
YOU'RE LIKE, OH, IT'S NOT SO
BAD.
BUT TO ACTUALLY LIVE IT AND SEE
IT, DOCUMENT IT, IT'S LIKE A
WHOLE DIFFERENT THING.
AND IT JUST HITS.
YOU.
>> Reporter: EARLIER TODAY, ALL
OF THE TRAIN CARS WERE REMOVED.
INVESTIGATORS ARE SENDING A
BROKEN PIECE OF RAIL TO BE
ANALYZED AT A GOVERNMENT LAB.
>> IT COULD HAVE BEEN CAUSED BY
THE ACCIDENT ITSELF.
IT COULD HAVE BEEN BROKEN PRIOR
TO THE ACCIDENT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, ALL EYES
ARE ON THE MONDAY MORNING
COMMUTE.
HERE AT GRAND CENTRAL TERMINAL
IN NEW YORK, THE 30,000 PEOPLE
WHO RELY ON THAT LINE WILL HAVE
TO FIND A NEW WAY TO TRAVEL.
THAT'S BECAUSE PARTS OF THOSE
TRACKS WILL BE SHUT DOWN FOR
DAYS, DAVID.
>> AMTRAK SERVICE AFFECTED, AS
WELL, GIO.
AND OUR THANKS TO YOU, FROM
GRAND CENTRAL TONIGHT.
>>> WE TURN TO THE HORRIFIC HOME
INVASION IN WHICH A COLLEGE
STUDENT WAS KILLED.
HER TWIN SISTER, WITNESSING IT
ALL.
WHEN THE SUSPECT INSIDE, POLICE
ARRIVED AT THE SCENE.
THAT'S WHEN THE SUSPECT PUTS ONE
OF THE YOUNG WOMEN IN A HEADLOCK
AND TAKES AIM AT THE OFFICERS.
THEY SHOOT BACK.
THE YOUNG WOMAN WAS KILLED.
SHE WAS REMEMBERED, TODAY, AT
THE HOFSTRA GRADUATION.
HERE'S ABC'S LINZIE JANIS.
>> Reporter: WHAT SHOULD HAVE
BEEN A HAPPY DAY FOR SO MANY,
TURNED BITTERSWEET.
>> OUR THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS ARE
WITH ANDREA'S FAMILY.
AND WITH HER FRIENDS AND
CLASSMATES.
>> Reporter: GRADUATES AT
HOFSTRA UNIVERSITY, WEARING
WHITE RIBBONS AND PAUSING FOR A
MOMENT OF SILENCE TO HONOR
FELLOW STUDENT ANDREA REBELLO.
JUST TWO DAYS AGO, SHE WAS
KILLED DURING AN ARMED ROBBERY
AT HER OFFCAMPUS HOME.
AFTER A NIGHT OUT CELEBRATING
THE END OF FINALS, REBELLO AND
HER TWIN SISTER, JESSICA,
RETURNED HOME WITH A ROOMMATE
AND A FRIEND.
THAT'S WHEN POLICE SAY
30-YEAR-OLD DALTON SMITH CAME IN
THROUGH AN UNLOCKED DOOR AND
ROBBED THEM.
SMITH TOOK VALUABLES.
BUT HE WANTED MORE.
SO, HE SENT THE TWIN'S ROOMMATE
TO AN ATM.
SHE BOLTED AND CALLED 911.
>> HE TOLD HER IF SHE DID NOT
RETURN WITHIN EIGHT MINUTES, HE
WOULD KILL ONE OF THE
INDIVIDUALS IN THE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: MOMENTS LATER,
OFFICERS ARRIVED TO FIND SMITH
HOLDING REBELLO IN A HEADLOCK.
POINTING A GUN SAYING, I'LL KILL
HER.
>> ONE OFFICER INSIDE WITH THE
HOSTAGES AND THE GUNMAN.
SHOTS FIRED.
WE HAVE A SUBJECT DOWN.
>> EVERYBODY STAY OFF THE AIR.
>> Reporter: WHEN SMITH POINTED
HIS GUN AT THE POLICE OFFICER,
THE OFFICER FIRED EIGHT SHOTS.
SEVEN STRIKING AND KILLING THE
SUSPECT.
AND ONE BULLET TAKING REBELLO'S
LIFE, TOO.
TONIGHT, ANDREA'S FAMILY ARE
MOURNING THE LOSS OF THEIR
DAUGHTER, WHO WAS AN INSPIRATION
TO MANY.
>> ANDREA HAD A BIT OF ADVICE
SHE TOOK FROM A BOB MARLEY SONG.
IT WAS, LIVE THE LIFE YOU LOVE
AND LOVE THE LIFE YOU LIVE.
>> Reporter: THE OFFICER WHO
FIRED THE SHOTS IS DESCRIBED AS
HIGHLY DECORATED.
POLICE ARE INVESTIGATING THE
SHOOTING.
WE SPOKE TO SEVERAL LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS WHO SAY
THAT POLICE OFFICER HAD NO
CHOICE BUT TO SHOOT ONCE THE
SUSPECT TURNED THE GUN ON HIM.
>> AN AWFUL SCENE INSIDE THAT
HOME.
AND A TOUGH DAY AT HOFSTRA.
>>> WE'RE TURNING TO IRAN, WHERE
STATE RADIO IS REPORTING THAT
TWO MEN HAVE BEEN EXECUTED FOR
SPYING FOR THE CIA.
THEY'VE BEEN CONVICTED BY
TEHRAN'S REVOLUTIONARY GUARD
COURT AND WERE HANGED AT DAWN.
IRAN REGULARLY ACCUSES THE U.S.
AND ISRAEL OF SPYING.
PARTICULARLY ON ITS NUCLEAR
PROGRAM.
>>> AND NORTH KOREA, ADDING ONE
MORE ROCKET LAUNCH TO THIS
WEEKEND.
A SHORT-RANGE MISSILE FELL INTO
THE WATERS OFF NORTH KOREA'S
COAST TODAY.
THE LAUNCH HAS SET BACK RECENT
MOVES TO EASE TENSIONS ON THE
KOREAN PENINSULA AND APPEAR TO
HAVE BEEN PROVOKED BY THE
ARRIVAL OF THE U.S. AIRCRAFT
CARRIER, "NIMITZ" IN THE REGION.
>>> NOW, TO THE IRS TARGETING
TEA PARTY AND SPECIAL GROUPS FOR
SCRUTINY.
THE WHITE HOUSE OF COURSE UNDER
FIRE BECAUSE TREASURY DEPARTMENT
OFFICIALS WERE TOLD OF THE IRS
INVESTIGATION A YEAR AGO.
BUT TONIGHT, WE HAVE LEARNED
THAT SOME REPUBLICAN MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS WERE ALSO TOLD BACK
THEN.
ABC'S REENA NINAN JOINING US
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
REENA, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: DAVID, GOOD
EVENING.
A SENIOR OBAMA ADVISER SAID THE
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS WERE FIRST
MADE AWARE OF THE IRS PROBE IN
LATE.
NT OBAMA
LEARNED ABOUT IT WHEN THE STORY
WAS REPORTED IN THE MEDIA.
WHITE HOUSE AIDE DAN PFEIFFER
ALSO SAYS NO ORDERS WERE GIVEN
TO THE IRS TO GO AFTER TEA PARTY
GROUPS.
>> BOTTOM LINE, NO COMMUNICATION
AS FAR AS YOU KNOW FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE, TO THE IRS, ABOUT
THIS TARGETING?
>> NO.
ABSOLUTELY NOT.
WHETHER IT'S LEGAL OR ILLEGAL,
IS NOT IMPORTANT TO THE FACT
THAT THE CONDUCT OF THE MATTER.
WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE IT DOESN'T
HAPPEN AGAIN.
>> Reporter: SENIOR TREASURY
OFFICIALS LEARNED OF THE
INVESTIGATION LAST YEAR AND
APPARENTLY SO DID REPUBLICANS.
THE CHAIR OF THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT
COMMITTEE KNEW OF THE PROBE IN
JUNE.
AND ROUGHLY, WHAT WOULD BE IN AN
IRS INSPECTOR GENERAL'S REPORT.
>> I KNEW WHAT WAS APPROXIMATELY
IN IT WHEN WE MADE THE
ALLEGATIONS A YEAR AGO.
AN OPEN SECRET.
>> Reporter: AN OPEN SECRET SAYS
REPUBLICANS THAT CALLED FOR A
DEEPER INVESTIGATION.
>> I THINK A SPECIAL COUNCIL IS
GOING TO END UP BEING NECESSARY
HERE.
>> Reporter: PFEIFFER,
MEANWHILE, ADMITS THE TARGETING
WAS WRONG.
BUT THE WHITE HOUSE WILL ONLY GO
SO FAR.
>> WHAT WE'RE NOT PARTICIPATING
IN IS PARTISAN FISHING
EXPEDITIONS DESIGNED TO DISTRACT
FROM THE REAL ISSUES AT HAND.
>> Reporter: THERE'S MORE
HEARINGS ON THE HILL THIS WEEK.
AND REPUBLICANS ARE CALLING FOR
A WIDER INVESTIGATION.
AND QUESTIONING THE IRS' FUTURE
ROLE IN IMPLEMENTING HEALTH CARE
REFORM.
DAVID?
>> THIS IS NOT GOING AWAY.
REENA NINAN AT THE WHITE HOUSE
TONIGHT.
REENA, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW, A COMEBACK TO REPORT
TONIGHT.
THE TROUBLED DREAMLINER IS
RETURNING TO AMERICA'S SKIES.
UNITED AIRLINES WILL FLY
BOEING'S NEW JUMBO JET TOMORROW.
THE FIRST FLIGHT SINCE THE
ENTIRE FLEET WAS GROUNDED IN
JANUARY BECAUSE OF BATTERY
PROBLEMS.
A TEAM FROM ABC NEWS WILL BE ON
THE FLIGHT.
WE'LL BE REPORTING FROM HOUSTON
TO CHICAGO.
>>> THERE IS MUCH MORE AHEAD ON
"WORLD NEWS" THIS SUNDAY NIGHT.
HIGH-POWERED ADVICE FOR
GRADUATES.
FROM THE PRESIDENT.
FROM THE FIRST LADY.
FROM THE ACTRESS WHO DELIVERS
HER LINES IN THE WEST WING.
IT'S WHAT ONE FAMOUS MAYOR
SAID THAT LED TO THIS IMAGE, THE
PLUNGER ON HIS HEAD.
BUT DOES HE HAVE A POINT?
WEIGH IN, RIGHT AFTER THE BREAK.
ARE YOU FLO?
YES.         IS THIS THE THING
YOU GAVE MY HUSBAND?
WELL, YEAH, YES.
THE "NAME YOUR PRICE" TOOL.
YOU TELL US THE PRICE
YOU WANT TO PAY,
AND WE GIVE YOU A RANGE
OF OPTIONS TO CHOOSE FROM.
CAREFUL, THOUGH -- THAT KIND
OF POWER CAN GO TO YOUR HEAD.
THAT EXPLAINS
A LOT.
YO, BUDDY!
I GOT THIS.
GIMME ONE, GIMME ONE,
GIMME ONE!
THE POWER OF
THE "NAME YOUR PRICE" TOOL.
ONLY FROM PROGRESSIVE.
[ Female Announcer ]
OFF! Deep Woods Dry Repellent.
THE PROTECTION
OF OFF! Deep Woods
WITH A FORMULA THAT FEELS DRY
NOT GREASY.
OFF! Deep Woods Dry.
Keeps Bugs OFF!
SC Johnson.
OFF! Deep Woods Dry.
Keeps Bugs OFF!
SO YOU CAN CAPTURE
YOUR RECEIPTS, INK FOR
ALL BUSINESS PURCHASES.
AND MANAGE THEM
ONLINE WITH JOT,
THE LATEST APP FROM INK.
SO YOU CAN SPEND LESS
TIME DOING PAPERWORK.
AND MORE TIME DOING PAPERWORK.
INK FROM CHASE.
SO YOU CAN.
I WORKED A PATROL UNIT FOR 17
YEARS IN THE CITY OF BALTIMORE.
WHEN I FIRST STARTED
EXPERIENCING THE PAIN,
IT'S HARD TO DESCRIBE
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A NUMBNESS
BUT YET YOU HAVE THE PAIN
LIKE THOUSANDS OF NEEDLES
STICKING IN YOUR FOOT.
IT WAS PROGRESSIVELY
GETTING WORSE,
AND AT THAT POINT,
I KNEW I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
WHEN I WENT BACK
TO MY HEALTH CARE PROFESSIONAL,
THAT'S WHEN SHE SUGGESTED
THE LYRICA.
ONCE I STARTED
TAKING THE LYRICA,
THE PAIN STARTED SUBSIDING.
[ Male Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYE SIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN, AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS, AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO'VE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
TO HEAR MORE OF TERRY'S STORY,
VISIT LYRICA.COM.
>>> WELL, GRADUATION SEASON IS
UPON US TONIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT AMONG THE
HEADLINERS OFFERING ADVICE THIS
WEEKEND.
SOME OF IT A BIT STINGING.
AND THERE WAS THE FAMOUS MAYOR
WHO SUGGESTED STUDENTS WHO ARE
SO-SO, IN HIS WORDS, TO SKIP
COLLEGE COMPLETELY, BECOMING A
PLUMBER.
MAKING THE CASE WHY, ABC'S SUSAN
SAULNY.
>> I KNOW SOME OF YOU ARE JUST
GRADUATING, THANK YOU, LORDY.
>> Reporter: THERE WAS NO
SUGAR-COATING REALITY THE IN THE
COMMENCEMENT SPEECH PRESIDENT
OBAMA DELIVERED TO MOREHOUSE
COLLEGE IN THE RAIN.
>> WHATEVER YOU'VE GONE THROUGH,
IT PALES IN COMPARISON TO THE
HARDSHIPS OF PREVIOUS
GENERATIONS.
>> Reporter: THE SPEECH WAS MORE
REALITY THAN ANYTHING.
>> MICHELLE WILL TELL YOU I'M
NOT PERFECT.
>> Reporter: AND SHE DID.
FIRST LADY MICHELLE OBAMA TOLD A
HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATING CLASS IN
NASHVILLE, TO ACHIEVE SUCCESS,
THEY MUST EXPERIENCE FAILURE.
>> I COULD TAKE UP A WHOLE
AFTERNOON TALKING ABOUT HIS
FAILURES.
HE LOST HIS FIRST RACE FOR
CONGRESS.
AND NOW, HE GETS TO CALL HIMSELF
MY HUSBAND.
>> Reporter: SPEAKING OF
PRESIDENTS, KERRY WASHINGTON,
WHO PLAYS AN ADVISER TO ONE ON
ABC'S HIT "SCANDAL," ADDRESSED
STUDENTS AT HER ALMA MATER,
GEORGE WASHINGTON UNIVERSITY.
>> YOU CAN FOLLOW SOMEONE ELSE'S
SCRIPT, TRYING TO MAKE CHOICES
THAT MAKE OTHER PEOPLE HAPPY.
OR YOU CAN LOOK AT ALL
YOU HAVE ACCOMPLISHED TODAY AND
USE IT AS FUEL TO VENTURE FORTH
AND WRITE YOUR OWN STORY.
>> Reporter: WHAT IF THAT
INVOLVES SKIPPING COLLEGE
ALTOGETHER?
TO BE A PLUMBER?
THAT'S WHAT MIKE BLOOMBERG'S
DEBATABLE ADVICE TO WHAT HE
CALLED SO-SO STUDENTS ON HIS
WEEKLY RADIO SHOW.
THE "NEW YORK DAILY NEWS" HAD
FUN WITH THE IDEA.
>> BEING A PLUMBER ACTUALLY FOR
THE AVERAGE PERSON PROBABLY
WOULD BE A BETTER DEAL BECAUSE
YOU DON'T SPEND FOUR YEARS
SPENDING $40,000, $50,000,
TUITION WITH NO INCOME.
>> Reporter: A SOCIAL MEDIA LIT
UP AFTER THE MAYOR'S COMMENTS,
WITH MANY PEOPLE AGREEING WITH
HIM.
OTHERS SAID BY HIS LOGIC, EVEN
EINSTEIN, WHO WAS A SO-SO
STUDENT, WOULD HAVE BEEN A
PLUMBER.
>> EINSTEIN WAS A SO-SO STUDENT.
BUT WE NEED GOOD PLUMMERS.
IT'S HOW HE DELIVERED THAT
ADVICE.
SUSAN, GREAT TO HAVE YOU
ONBOARD, BY THE WAY.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, TO REMEMBERING THE
ACTRESS AND THAT NIGHTMARE
20,000 FEET.
>>> AND YOU'LL REMEMBER THIS.
BEN AFFLECK FAMOUSLY TELLING
TENS OF MILLIONS HIS MARRIAGE
WAS WORK AT THE OSCARS.
HIS WIFE, JENNIFER GARNER,
GETTING THE LAST LAUGH THIS
WEEKEND.
WAIT UNTIL YOU HEAR WHAT SHE
SAID ABOUT THEIR MARRIAGE BEHIND
SAID ABOTHE MIDDLEARRIAGE BEHIND
OF THIS SPECIT
AND I NEED TO RUN OFF
TO THE BATHROOM.
♪
I'M FED UP WITH ALWAYS HAVING TO
PUT MY BLADDER'S NEEDS
AHEAD OF MY DAUGHTER.
♪
SO TODAY, I'M FINALLY
TALKING TO MY DOCTOR
ABOUT
OVERACTIVE BLADDER SYMPTOMS.
[ Female Announcer ]
KNOW THAT GOTTA GO FEELING?
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT PRESCRIPTION TOVIAZ.
ONE TOVIAZ PILL A DAY
SIGNIFICANTLY REDUCES
SUDDEN URGES AND ACCIDENTS,
FOR 24 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE CERTAIN
STOMACH PROBLEMS OR GLAUCOMA,
OR CAN NOT EMPTY YOUR BLADDER,
YOU SHOULD NOT TAKE TOVIAZ.
GET EMERGENCY MEDICAL HELP
RIGHT AWAY
IF YOUR FACE, LIPS,
THROAT OR TONGUE SWELLS.
TOVIAZ CAN CAUSE
BLURRED VISION,
DIZZINESS, DROWSINESS
AND DECREASED SWEATING.
DO NOT DRIVE, OPERATE MACHINERY
OR DO UNSAFE TASKS
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW TOVIAZ AFFECTS YOU.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
ARE DRY MOUTH AND CONSTIPATION.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT TOVIAZ.
CONSTIPATED?
YEAH.
MM.
SOME LAXATIVES LIKE Dulcolax
CAN CAUSE CRAMPS.
BUT Phillips' Caplets
DON'T.
THEY HAVE MAGNESIUM.
FOR EFFECTIVE RELIEF
OF OCCASIONAL CONSTIPATION.
THANKS.
[ Phillips' Lady ]
LIVE THE REGULAR LIFE.
Phillips'.
OF MILD TO MODERATE
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE
IS EXELON PATCH.
NOW WITH
MORE TREATMENT OPTIONS,
EXELON PATCH MAY IMPROVE
OVERALL FUNCTION AND COGNITION.
YOUR LOVED ONE CAN GET
A FREE 30-DAY TRIAL.
AND YOU CAN HAVE
ACCESS TO NURSES.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE
HOW THE DISEASE PROGRESSES.
HOSPITALIZATION,
AND RARELY DEATH,
HAVE BEEN REPORTED FROM WEARING
MORE THAN ONE PATCH AT A TIME.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
ARE NAUSEA, VOMITING, DIARRHEA,
FALL, LOSS OF APPETITE
OR WEIGHT,
APPLICATION SITE REDNESS,
AND URINARY TRACT INFECTION.
THE LIKELIHOOD AND SEVERITY
OF THESE SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCREASE
AS THE DOSE INCREASES
OR IF PATIENTS
WEIGH LESS THAN 110 POUNDS.
PEOPLE AT RISK
FOR STOMACH ULCERS
WHO TAKE
CERTAIN OTHER MEDICINES
SHOULD TALK TO THEIR DOCTOR
AS SERIOUS STOMACH PROBLEMS
SUCH AS BLEEDING MAY WORSEN.
PATIENTS MAY EXPERIENCE
SLOW HEART RATE.
FREE TRIAL OFFER FOR THEM.
NURSES TO TALK TO FOR YOU.
VISIT EXELONPATCHOFFER.COM.
♪
WITH THERMACARE HEATWRAPS.
THE ONLY WRAP WITH PATENTED
HEAT CELLS THAT PENETRATE DEEP
TO RELAX, SOOTHE,
AND UNLOCK TIGHT MUSCLES.
AND NOW, INTRODUCING
REUSABLE THERMACARE COLD WRAPS.
PAIN RELIEF
WITHOUT THE SHOCK OF ICE.
>>> NOW, TO OUR "INSTANT INDEX"
WHAT'S TRENDING RIGHT NOW.
A HOLLYWOOD PASSING TO TELL YOU
ABOUT TONIGHT.
CHRISTINE WHITE, BEST KNOWN FOR
HER PORTRAYAL OF A WIFE OF A
YOUNG WILLIAM SHATNER.
SHE TURNED TO HER HUSBAND AS THE
FLIGHT IS TAKING OFF, AND SAYS,
HONEY, YOU ARE CURED.
HE SUFFERS ANOTHER NERVOUS
BREAKDOWN.
WHITE ALSO APPEARED ON EPISODES
OF "BONANZA," PERRY MASON," AND
"FATHER KNOWS BEST."
SHE WAS 86.
>>> THE ASK ANY MARRIED COUPLE
THAT A MARRIAGE IS WORK.
BUT WHEN YOU SAY THAT IN FRONT
OF TENS OF MILLIONS, IT GETS
SOME ATTENTION.
BEN AFFLECK, DURING A SPEECH HE
SAID TO HIS WIFE, JENNIFER
GARNER, IN THE AUDIENCE, I WANT
TO THANK YOU ON WORKING ON OUR
MARRIAGE.
IT'S WORK.
HE TOOK A LOT OF HEAT.
WHILE HOSTING "SNL" HE INVITED
HIS WIFE ON TO EXPLAIN HIMSELF.
AND SHE HAD A FEW CHOICE WORDS
FOR HIM.
>> OUR MARRIAGE IS A WORK OF
LOVE.
WHAT WOULD YOU HAVE CALLED IT IN
THE SPEECH?
>> A GIFT.
I WOULD HAVE SAID THANK YOU TO
MY WIFE.
OUR MARRIAGE IS A GIFT.
>> IT'S A GIFT, TO THE WORK OF
MARRIAGE, WHICH YOU GIFTED ME,
WITH ENORMOUS WORK.
>> IF WE'RE GOING TO BE
COMPLETELY HONEST HERE, WHY
DON'T WE MENTION WHO DOES ALL OF
THE WORK.
>> I WANT TO TELL YOU HOW I WISH
I HAD ENDED THAT SPEECH.
OKAY?
I COULDN'T DO ANY OF THE THINGS
THAT I DO, WITHOUT YOUR SUPPORT.
YOU ARE MY ANGEL, MY LIFE AND MY
WORLD.
>> YOU'RE READING THAT.
>> A LITTLE HELP ON THE CUE
CARD.
THEY LOOK PRETTY HAPPY TO ME.
>>> AND WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
STAR-MANGLED BANNER.
YOU HAVE TO HEAR THIS ONE TO
BELIEVE IT.
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
IN HIDDEN FEES
ON THEIR 401(K)S?!
GO TO E-TRADE
AND ROLL OVER YOUR OLD 401(K)S
TO A NEW E-TRADE
RETIREMENT ACCOUNT.
NONE OF THEM CHARGE
ANNUAL FEES
AND ALL OF THEM OFFER
LOW COST INVESTMENTS.
E-TRADE.
LESS FOR US. MORE FOR YOU.
[ Female Announcer ]
OFF! Deep Woods Dry Repellent.
THE PROTECTION
OF OFF! Deep Woods
WITH A FORMULA THAT FEELS DRY
NOT GREASY.
OFF! Deep Woods Dry.
Keeps Bugs OFF!
SC Johnson.
ARE PROVEN TO BE
EFFECTIVE PAIN RELIEVERS
Tylenol WORKS BY BLOCKING
PAIN SIGNALS TO YOUR BRAIN
Bayer Back & Body's
DUAL ACTION FORMULA
INCLUDES ASPIRIN,
WHICH BLOCKS PAIN AT THE SITE.
TRY THE POWER
OF Bayer
Back & Body.
>>> AND FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
"THE STAR-SPANGLED BANNER," LIKE
YOU'VE NEVER HEARD IT.
WE'VE SEEN IT BEFORE, WHEN YOU
COMBINE THE PRESSURE, ALL THOSE
FANS WATCHING.
TONIGHT, ONE BRAVE SINGER AND
ONE KIND CROWD.
♪ OH, SAY CAN YOU SEE
>> Reporter: SHE WAS OFF TO A
GOOD START.
ALEXIS NORMAN, THE CANADIAN JAZZ
SINGER, ASKED TO SING OUR
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
AS THE PORTLAND WINTERHAWKS
TRAVELED TO CANADA, TO PLAY THE
HALIFAX MOOSEHEADS.
BUT AROUND THE TWILIGHT'S LAST
GLEAMING.
THE AUDIENCE, WITH SOME
REASSURANCE.
♪ THROUGH THE PERILOUS NIGHT
>> Reporter: ONE OF THE AMERICAN
FANS, SHAKING HIS HEAD.
BUT SHE'S HARDLY THE FIRST TO
RAISE EYEBROWS.
JOSE FELICIANO, THE WORLD
SERIES.
IT WAS HIS INTERPRETATION THAT
ANGERED TRADITIONALISTS.
♪ OH, SAY CAN YOU SEE
BY THE DAWN'S EARLY LIGHT ♪
>> Reporter: AT LEAST HE
REMEMBERED THE WORDS.
MICHAEL BOLTON, SMARTLY WROTE IT
OUT BEFOREHAND.
♪ SO GALLANTLY STREAMING
>> Reporter: OF COURSE, THERE
WAS NATALIE GILBERT, JUST 13 AT
THE TIME.
20,000 IN THE STANDS FOR THAT
NBA GAME.
♪ AS THE STARS LAST --
>> Reporter: AND THE COACH WHO
CAME TO HER AID.
♪ OH, SAY DOES THAT
STAR-SPANGLED ♪
>> Reporter: HE OFFERED A
HELPING HAND, JUST LIKE THE
CROWD DID THIS WEEKEND.
♪ BANNER YET WAVE
O'ER THE LAND OF THE FREE ♪
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE BRAVE
>> YOU CAN ALWAYS COUNT ON THE
CROWD.
>>> "GOOD MORNING AMERICA" FIRST
THING IN THE MORNING.
AND DIANE SAWYER BACK HERE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
HAVE A GREAT EVENING.
FOR ALL OF US HERE AT ABC NEWS,
HAVE A GREAT WEEK AHEAD.
GOOD NIGHT.
>> FIRST BOLTS, NOW CABLES.
THE NEW CONSTRUCTION PROBLEMS ON
THE BAY BRIDGE.
>> THE RUNNERS, THE SECURITY,
AND THE ARREST.
A LOOK AT THE 102nd
102nd BAY-TO-BREAKERS RACE.
AND AN ACCIDENT IN THE EAST BAY
SHUTS DOWN TRAFFIC AND POWER.
HOW IT COULD AFFECT YOUR
COMMUTE.
ABC7 NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
>> Ama: BOTH RODS AND NOW
CABLES, CAUSE FOR THE
$6.5 BILLION BAY BRIDGE COULD
SKYROCKET AFTER THE DISCOVER OF
EVEN MORE PROBLEMS TONIGHT.
GOOD EVENING AND THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US, I'M AMA DAETZ.
SERGIO QUINTANA IS LIVE WITH A
LOOK AT THE NEW SAFETY CONCERNS.
SERGIO?
REPORTER: THE CONCERN WE'RE
TALKING ABOUT HERE IS ABOUT THE
SKYWAY APPROACH TO THE
SUSPENSION SPAN.
THAT SECTION RIGHT THERE.
WHEN IT WAS BEING BUILT RAIN AND
MOISTURE GOT INTO THE DUCTS.
AND RUST WAS DETECTED ON THE
STILL TEN DONS.
A UC BERKELEY ENGINEER LAID OUT
THE CONCERNS IN A STORY TODAY.
HE SAYS THEY DID TESTS THAT WERE
THE LEAST SENSITIVE TO THE
PRESENCE OF PITS, AND LO AND
BEHOLD, THE TEST SAYS THERE IS
NO PROBLEM.
THAT'S WHEN UC BERKELEY
ENGINEERING PROFESSOR THOMAS DEF
SIGN, WHO SAYS CALTRANS FOUND
RUST AND PITS IN THE DUCTS, BUT
HE SAID DIDN'T USE THE CORRECT
METHOD TO TEST HOW MUCH THEY
COULD COMPROMISE THE STRENGTH OF
THE STEEL INSIDE THIS SECTION OF
THE BRIDGE.
A BAY BRIDGE SPOKESPERSON SAYS
THIS PROBLEM IS NOT NEW, IT WAS
DISCOVERED IN 2008 WHEN THIS
SECTION OF THE BRIDGE WAS BEING
BUILT AND SAYS ENGINEERS AND
CONTRACTORS CAME UP WITH
SOLUTIONS TO THE RUST PROBLEM
AND THE DIE SIGN -- DESIGN OF
THE BRIDGE A