FOR WATCHING TONIGHT.
>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT ON THE RUN.
HOW ONE YOUNG MAN GOT HIS HANDS
ON MANY OF THE NATION'S TOP
SECRETS.
HE IS ON THE MOVE TONIGHT.
HOW DANGEROUS IS IT?
>>> ON THE GROUND TORNADOS
SPEEDING THROUGH KENTUCKY,
WASHINGTON D.C., BRACING FOR
TWISTERS, TOO.
>>> ON TRIAL, IT BEGINS, GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN ACCUSED OF MURDERING
TRAYVON MARTIN AMID A DEBATE
ABOUT RACE, GUNFIRE AND JUSTICE.
>> GOOD EVENING ON THIS MONDAY
NIGHT.
WE BEGIN WITH ONE YOUNG AMERICAN
MAN WHO SAYS HE HAS CONTROL OF A
LOT OF THE NATION'S SECRETS
TONIGHT.
EDWARD SNOWDEN, THE 29-YEAR-OLD
WHISTLE BLOWER BEHIND THAT
MASSIVE INTELLIGENCE BREACH AT
THE NSA.
TONIGHT HE SAID HE'S A
TARGET AND ON THE MOVE, HIDDEN
BEHIND CLOSED DOORS, SHROUDED IN
MYSTERY AND DRAMA.
BRIAN ROSS HAS THE LATEST ON WHO
HE IS AND WHAT ELSE HE HAS.
BRIAN.
>> Reporter: AS FBI AGENTS ARE
SCRAMBLING TO FIND HIM THERE ARE
REPORTS HE'S PREPARING TO MAKE
PUBLIC EVEN MORE OF THE NATION'S
MOST CLOSELY GUARDED SECRETS.
UNTIL HE CHECKED OUT SOME TIME
TODAY, EDWARD SNOWDEN HAS BEEN
HOLED UP IN LUXURY FOR THREE
WEEKS IN HONG KONG AT THE MEARA
HOTEL, ACCORDING TO EMPLOYEES
THERE.
BY HIS OWN ACCOUNT, EVERY MEAL
CAME FROM ROOM SERVICE, PILL
OH,S STUFFED UNDER THE DOOR TO
PREVENT EAVES DROPPING, AND HE
USED THE CODE NAME VERAX, LATIN
FOR TRUTH TELLER TO COMMUNICATE
WITH THE WASHINGTON POST.
HE TOLD THE GUARDIAN NEWSPAPER
HE KNEW THE U.S. WOULD BE COMING
AFTER HIM, MAYBE EVEN WITH HIT
TEAMS.
>> THAT'S A FEAR I'LL LIVE UNDER
FOR THE REST OF MY LIFE, HOWEVER
LONG THAT HAPPENS TO BE.
>> Reporter: U.S. OFFICIALS SAID
HE'S BEING PURSUED BECAUSE HE
REVEALED SECRETS USED TO TRACK
TERRORISTS.
>> LEAKS OF SENSITIVE CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION THAT CAUSE HARM TO
OUR NATIONAL SECURITY INTEREST
ARE A PROBLEM.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS AMERICANS
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT THE
SURVEILLANCE AND COLLECTIONS
THEIR GOVERNMENT IS CARRYING
OUT.
>> THE NSA SPECIFICALLY TARGETS
THE COMMUNICATIONS OF EVERYONE.
IT INGESTS THEM BY DEFAULT.
>> Reporter: SNOWDEN WAS NEVER
UNDER SUSPICION UNTIL HE
DISAPPEARED FROM HIS JOB AS A
TECHNICIAN AT THE NSA IN HAWAII
AROUND THE 1st OF MAY, CLAIMING
MEDICAL LEAVE FOR EP LEPSY.
NEIGHBORS SAID HE VANISHED ONE
DAY.
>> ONE DAY HE WAS THERE, THE
NEXT HE WAS GONE.
>> Reporter: HIS MOTHER IN
MARYLAND DECLINED TO COMMENT BUT
A NEIGHBOR SAID HE WAS ALWAYS AT
HIS COMPUTER AS A YOUNG MAN.
>> I THOUGHT HE WAS DOING SCHOOL
WORK AND COME TO FIND OUT HE
DIDN'T EVEN GRADUATE FROM HIGH
SCHOOL.
>> Reporter: BY THE AGE OF 29,
SNOWDEN CLAIMED HE HAD QUITE THE
TOP SECRET RESUME FOR SOMEONE
WHO DROPPED OUT OF HIGH SCHOOL.
STARTING WITH NSA SECURITY
GUARD, FOLLOWED BY A BRIEF
FAILED ATTEMPT TO BECOME A
SPECIAL FORCES SOLDIER.
THEN A HUGE JUMP, A CIA SPY IN
SWITZERLAND WORKING WITH
COMPUTERS.
THEN FOUR YEARS AS A CIVILIAN
CONTRACTOR WORKING WITH
COMPUTERS AT THE NSA IN JAPAN,
WASHINGTON AND HAWAII WHERE HE
SAYS HE DECIDED TO BLOW THE
WHISTLE ON WHAT HE CALLS THE
ABUSE OF THE PRIVACY RIGHTS OF
AMERICA.
>> I SITTING AT MY DESK
CERTAINLY HAVE THE AUTHORITIES
TO WIRE TAP ANYONE FROM YOU OR
YOUR ACCOUNTANT TO A FEDERAL
JUDGE TO EVEN A PRESIDENT IF I
HAD A PERSONAL E-MAIL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT WHEREVER HE
IS SNOWDEN HAS APPARENTLY WITH
HIM MORE TOP SECRET DOCUMENTS
INCLUDING THE NAMES OF HUNDREDS
OF SECRET AGENTS.
HE SAYS HE CHOSE TO GO TO HONG
KONG BECAUSE IT HAS A HISTORY OF
ALLOWING FREE SPEECH.
DIANE, IT ALSO HAS AN
EXTRADITION TREATY WITH THE U.S.
>> WHAT DO INTELLIGENCE
OFFICIALS SAY TO YOU ABOUT
SOMEONE OF THAT RANK WITH ACCESS
TO THOSE TOP SECRETS?
>> IT TURNS OUT HE IS ABOUT ONE
OF 850,000 PRIVATE CONTRACTORS
WHO HAVE SUCH TOP SECRET
CLEARANCE.
THAT'S PART OF A GROWING PROBLEM
UNDERSCORED BY THIS CASE IN
WHICH WHEN EVERYTHING IS SECRET
IT'S HARD TO KEEP THE TRUE AND
IMPORTANT SECRETS SECRET.
>> 850,000.
THANK YOU, BRIAN ROSS, REPORTING
IN TONIGHT.
>>> NOW WE TURN TO THAT OUTBREAK
OF SEVERE WEATHER WE'VE BEEN
WATCHING ACROSS THE EAST.
WE WANT TO BRING YOU THE LATEST
REPORTS RIGHT NOW, FLASH FLOOD
WARNINGS AND REPORTS OF TORNADOS
TOUCHING DOWN.
HERE'S ABC'S DAVID KERLEY.
>> Reporter: THE TORNADO TARGET
TONIGHT 40 MILES NORTH OF
NASHVILLE JUST ACROSS THE
BOARDER HITTING ADAIRVILLE,
KENTUCKY.
>> THIS JUST WENT OVERTOP OF US.
>> Reporter: A NEAR PERFECT
FUNNEL FORMATION OF THIS TORNADO
WHICH BLEW OVER THE SMALL TOWN.
ONE OFFICIAL TOLD US TWO ELDERLY
LADIES RODE OUT THE STORM
HUDDLED IN A BATHTUB.
>> THEIR HOUSE IS DESTROYED, BUT
THEY BOTH SURVIVED WITH MINOR
INJURIES, TAKEN TO THE HOSPITAL
AND RELEASED.
>> Reporter: WHILE THE TORNADO
WAS NOT THAT WIDE OR POWERFUL,
IT STILL LEFT ITS MARK.
>> WE HAD A TORNADO COME
THROUGH, DAMAGED FIVE TO SEVEN
HOUSES, PRETTY WELL DESTROYED
SEVERAL BARNS AND BUILDINGS.
NOBODY WAS INJURED SERIOUSLY.
>> Reporter: SOON THE SUN WAS
OUT AND BELONGINGS MOVED OUT OF
DAMAGED BUILDINGS, FIREFIGHTERS
LENDING A HAND.
TONIGHT KENTUCKY AND TENNESSEE,
A LARGE PART OF THE MID ATLANTIC
AS WELL ARE EXPECTING STRONG
THUNDERSTORMS.
THIS YEAR'S TORNADO SEASON
STARTED LATE BUT IT HAS BEEN A
MONTH TO REMEMBER, THE
DEVASTATION AND DEATH IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA AND JUST 11 DAYS LATER,
THE WIDEST PATH OF DESTRUCTION
ON RECORD.
>> THOSE ARE SUCTION BORDERS
GOING AROUND THE EDGE.
>> Reporter: FROM THE EL RENO
TORNADO MORE THAN TWO AND A HALF
MILES AT ITS WIDEST SPOT.
>> OH, MY GOD, THAT IS HUGE.
>> Reporter: IT WAS AND THIS IS
FAR FROM THE END OF TORNADO
SEASON.
DAVID KERLEY, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> NOW WE TURN TO THAT HIGH
PROFILE MURDER TRIAL.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN ACCUSED OF
MURDERING TRAYVON MARTIN.
TODAY IT BEGAN WITH LAWYERS
PROBING THE SECRET FEELINGS OF
PROSPECTIVE JURORS ABOUT RACE,
BIAS AND CRIME.
MATT GUTMAN WHO BROKE A LOT OF
NEWS ON THIS CASE FROM THE START
WAS BACK IN THE COURTROOM TODAY.
>> Reporter: TODAY 16 MONTHS
AFTER A SINGLE GUNSHOT IN THE
TINY COMMUNITY TRIGGERED A
NATIONAL DEBATE ABOUT RACE,
PROSPECTIVE JURORS IN THE GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN MURDER TRIAL WERE
ASKED THE FUNDAMENTAL QUESTION.
>> IS THERE ANY QUESTION IN YOUR
MIND YOU CAN BE FAIR?
>> NO QUESTION.
>> ZIMMERMAN, A WHITE HISPANIC
WATCHMAN SHOT 17-YEAR-OLD
TRAYVON MARTIN IN 2012.
FOR WEEKS NATIONAL PROTESTS AND
A WAVE OF HIGH SCHOOL WALKOUTS
GRIPPED THE NATION, EVEN
GRABBING THE ATTENTION OF THE
PRESIDENT.
>> IF I HAD A SON HE WOULD LOOK
LIKE TRAYVON.
>> THIS MORNING THE FIRST 100
MARCHED THROUGH THE DOORS
FILLING OUT A QUESTIONNAIRE
SPECIFICALLY DESIGNED FOR THIS
CASE.
>> THE BOTTOM LINE IS YOU'RE
LIKE A BLANK SLATE.
>> Reporter: LAWYERS IN COURT
TRYING TO WEED OUT JURORS WHO
ALREADY MADE UP THEIR MINDS,
TALKING WITH FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
>> WHAT SIGNS DO THEY TAKE?
>> THE CHILD, OF COURSE HE WAS A
CHILD.
>> LAWYERS GRAPPLING WITH THE
THORNY ISSUE OF RACIAL BIAS IN
THE JURY POOL.
>> WHAT LETS THE PROSECUTION OR
THE DEFENSE KNOW THAT SOMEONE IS
BIASSED?
>> THEY MAY BE SUBTLE BUT
CERTAINLY ONE OF THE SIGNS IS
WHAT ORGANIZATIONS DO YOU BELONG
TO AND ARE THOSE ORGANIZATIONS
ORGANIZATIONS THAT IN THE PAST
HAVE EXCLUDED MINORITIES.
>> LAST YEAR'S TENSION REMAINS
HIGH AS IS THE THREAT FOR BOTH
FAMILIES TANGLED UP IN THE
SHOOTING.
THE MARTIN'S.
>> PEOPLE TALK ABOUT YOUR KIDS
AND FAMILY MEMBERS BY NAME?
>> YES.
>> AND THE ZIMMERMANS.
>> WE HAVE DEATH THREATS
DIRECTED AT US FOR BEING
GEORGE'S FAMILY.
>> Reporter: IN COURT JURY
SELECTION BRINGING BROAD TEDIUM,
LEVITY AND ULTIMATELY IN A FEW
WEEKS, SIX JURORS WHO WILL
DECIDE ZIMMERMAN'S FATE.
MATT GUTMAN, FLORIDA.
>>> UP NEXT AN UPDATE ON THE
SHOOTING IN CALIFORNIA.
WE'RE LEARNING MORE ABOUT THE
MAN POLICE SUSPECT OF KILLING
FIVE PEOPLE.
23-YEAR-OLD JOHN ZAWAHRI.
THAT'S HIS HIGH SCHOOL YEAR BOOK
PHOTO AND HERE IN SURVEILLANCE
PHOTOS, DRESSED IN BLACK
CARRYING A SEMIAUTOMATIC RIFLE
AS HE WALKED INTO THE LIBRARY AT
SANTA MONICA COLLEGE.
THE LOS ANGELES TIMES SAYS HE
HAD MENTAL PROBLEMS BUT ABC NEWS
LEARNED INVESTIGATORS DO NOT
BELIEVE HE WAS ON RECORD WITH A
CLINICAL DIAGNOSIS, SOMETHING
THAT MIGHT HAVE PREVENTED HIM
FROM BUYING A FIREARM.
>>> WE HEAD OVERSEAS NEXT TO
SOUTH AFRICA WHERE NELSON
MANDELLA IS SPENDING HIS THIRD
DAY IN THE HOSPITAL BATTLING A
RECURRENT LUNG INFECTION, THE
94-YEAR-OLD SAID TO BE IN
SERIOUS BUT STABLE CONDITION.
TODAY HIS EX-WIFE, WINNIE, CAME
TO SEE HIM.
TONIGHT THE PRESIDENT OF SOUTH
AFRICA CALLING ON HIS COUNTRYMEN
PRAY FOR NELSON MANDELLA'S
RECOVERY.
>>> IN LONDON PRINCE PHILIP
CELEBRATED HIS 92nd BIRTHDAY
FROM HIS HOSPITAL BED RECOVERING
FROM EXPLORATORY SURGERY ON HIS
ABDOMEN.
HIS BIRTHDAY GIFT, A 25-MINUTE
VISIT FROM THE QUEEN WHO ARRIVED
HOLDING A BIRTHDAY CARD
ADDRESSED TO HIM.
>>> WE HAVE A HEADLINE TONIGHT
FOR ANYONE WITH A SMART PHONE.
WE TOLD YOU ABOUT THE HUGE SPIKE
IN CRIME CAUSED BY THIEVES
STEALING iPHONES.
LAST YEAR 1.6 MILLION AMERICANS
HAD THEIR SMART PHONES STOLEN.
POLICE PUSHED PHONE COMPANIES TO
COME UP WITH A WAY TO DETER
THEFT.
TODAY APPLE REVEALED A NEW IDEA.
ABC'S GIO BENITEZ ON WHAT THEY
ANNOUNCED.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT APPLE MAY
BE TAKING A PAGE FROM MISSION
IMPOSSIBLE.
>> THIS TAPE WILL SELF-DESTRUCT
IN FIVE SECONDS.
>> Reporter: DEVICES SET TO
SELF-DESTRUCT?
PERHAPS NOT PHYSICALLY BUT AT
THE COMPANY'S BIG UNVEILING THIS
AFTERNOON, A SOLUTION THAT LAW
ENFORCEMENT HAS BEEN BEGGING
FOR, A SO CALLED KILL SWITCH
THAT COULD TURN A STOLEN iPHONE
INTO A USELESS BOX, IT COULD BE
THE STRONGEST WEAPON YET TO
COMBAT THE RECENT WAVE OF iPHONE
THEFTS.
THEFTS HAVE BECOME SUCH A
PROBLEM, THERE'S EVEN A TERM FOR
IT, APPLE PICKING, A 40%
INCREASE IN
THEFTS JUST LAST YEAR.
LOOK AT THIS DRAMATIC
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO FROM A NEW
YORK SUBWAY IN MARCH.
POLICE SAY THIS MAN TURNED TO
VIOLENCE JUST TO STEAL A CELL
PHONE.
THIS WOMAN KNOCKED OVER AND
PUNCHED SPEAKING TO LINSEY
DAVIS.
>> THE GUY SNATCHED THE PHONE
OUT OF MY HAND AND KEPT RUNNING.
>> Reporter: IT WORKS WITH THE
PHONE'S CURRENT SOFTWARE CALLED
FIND MY iPHONE WHICH HELPS YOU
TRACK A LOST PHONE.
>> NOW WITH ACTIVATION LOCK, IF
A THIEF TRIES TO TURN OFF FIND
MY iPHONE OR IF THEY EVEN WIPE
THE DEVICE ENTIRELY, THEY WILL
NOT BE ABLE TO REACTIVATE IT.
>> THE GOVERNMENT HAS BEEN
CALLING ON TECH COMPANIES TO
ADDRESS THE ISSUE OF SMART
PHONES THEFT.
THE IDEA THAT, SURE YOU CAN
TRACK YOUR PHONE BUT WHEN
SOMEONE STEALS THE PHONE THE
ROBBER OR THIEF CAN START USING
IT.
APPLE HAS COME UP WITH A FEATURE
THAT WON'T ALLOW THAT TO HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: NOW ALL EYES ARE ON
OTHER CELL PHONE MAKERS TO SEE
IF THEY FOLLOW APPLE'S LEAD.
GIO BENITEZ, ABC NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> AMERICA'S CREDIT RATING
BATTLING BACK TONIGHT.
REMEMBER THE U.S. WAS STRIPPED
OF ITS AAA RATING BY STANDARD
AND POOR NEARLY TWO YEARS AGO
IN THE HEAT OF THE BATTLE OVER
THE DEBT CEILING.
TODAY STANDARD AND POOR RAISED
THE OUTLOOK FROM NEGATIVE TO
STABLE.
S&P CITING SMALLER DEFICITS AND
BETTER COOPERATION IN
WASHINGTON.
>>> THE ECONOMY IS ABOUT TO GET
A BIG BOOST, THE AUTO INDUSTRY
REV BE UP FOR A LOT OF NEW HIRE,
CAR MAKERS IN DETROIT LOOKING
FOR ENGINEERS, TECHNICIANS AND
FACTORY WORKERS.
35,000 WORKERS EXPECTED TO JOIN
THE INDUSTRY THIS YEAR AS AUTO
SALES ARE EXPECTED TO SOAR IN
2013 UP TO MORE THAN 15 MILLION
VEHICLES WHICH WOULD BE THE
HIGHEST IN SIX YEARS.
>>> STILL AHEAD HERE ON "WORLD
NEWS," AN AMERICAN SECRET SO
MANY COUPLES SLEEP APART TO GET
A GOOD NIGHT'S REST.
IS IT REALLY YOUR SPOUSE'S
FAULT?
OUR EXPERIMENT EXPLORES HOW TO
SLEEP IN PEACE.
>>> LATER AN URGENT EFFORT TO
SAVE CHEETAHS, CRANES, PANDAS
AND LEOPARDS FROM
EXTINCTION.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS WHERE THIS IS
HAPPENING TONIGHT.
EXTINCTION.
YOU'LL NEVER GUESS WHERE THIS IS
HAPPENING TONIGHT.
HE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HIM ALL DAY
AS HE GOES BACK
TO TAKING TYLENOL.
I WAS OKAY, BUT AFTER LUNCH
MY KNEE STARTED TO HURT AGAIN.
AND NOW I'VE GOT TO
TAKE MORE PILLS.
♪
YUP. ANOTHER PILL STOP.
CAN I GET MY Aleve BACK YET?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY Aleve.
[ Male Announcer ] LOOK FOR THE
EASY-OPEN RED ARTHRITIS CAP.
MOMMY'S HAVING
A FRENCH FRY.
YES SHE IS, YES SHE IS.
[ bop ]
[ Male Announcer ]
COULD'VE HAD A V8.
100% VEGETABLE JUICE,
WITH THREE OF YOUR DAILY
VEGETABLE SERVINGS
IN EVERY LITTLE BOTTLE.
[ girl ] THERE ARE MAN-EATING
SHARKS IN EVERY OCEAN...
BUT WE STILL SWIM.
EVERY SECOND,
SOMEWHERE IN THE WORLD,
LIGHTNING STRIKES...
BUT WE STILL PLAY IN THE RAIN.
POISONOUS SNAKES CAN BE FOUND
IN 49 OF THE 50 STATES,
BUT WE STILL GO LOOKING
FOR ADVENTURE.
A CAR CAN CRASH...
A HOUSE CAN CRUMBLE...
BUT WE STILL DRIVE...
AND LOVE COMING HOME.
BECAUSE I THINK DEEP DOWN
WE KNOW...
ALL THE BAD THINGS
THAT CAN HAPPEN IN LIFE...
THEY CAN'T STOP US
FROM MAKING OUR LIVES...
GOOD.
♪
THEY'RE ABOUT 10 TIMES SOFTER
AND MAY HAVE SURFACE PORES
WHERE BACTERIA CAN MULTIPLY.
POLIDENT KILLS 99.99%
OF ODOR CAUSING BACTERIA
AND HELPS DISSOLVE STAINS
SO DENTURES ARE CLEANER,
FRESHER, AND BRIGHTER.
[ Male Announcer ] POLIDENT.
SO DENTURES ARE CLEANER,
FRESHER, AND BRIGHTER.
THE BLISTERS WERE OOZING,
AND PAINFUL TO TOUCH.
I WOKE UP TO A BLISTERING
ON MY SHOULDER.
I SPENT 23 YEARS AS A
DEPUTY UNITED STATES MARSHAL
AND I'VE BEEN PRETTY
WELL BANGED UP
BUT THE WORST PAIN
I'VE EXPERIENCED
WAS WHEN I HAD SHINGLES.
WHEN I WENT TO THE CLINIC,
THE NURSE TOLD ME
THAT IT WAS A RESULT OF
HAVING HAD CHICKENPOX.
I WOULDN'T WISH IT
ON MY WORST ENEMY.
>>> NOW TONIGHT AN EPIDEMIC NOT
A LOT OF PEOPLE DISCUSS.
THERE ARE MILLIONS AND MILLIONS
OF AMERICAN COUPLES WHO SAY THEY
CANNOT GET ENOUGH SLEEP IF THEIR
PARTNER IS IN THE SAME BED.
OUR OWN MEDICAL CONTRIBUTOR DR.
JENNIFER ASHTON AND HER HUSBAND
DECIDED TO BRING US A REALITY
CHECK, AGREEING TO TAKE US
INSIDE THEIR OWN SLEEP WARS AT
HOME.
>> Reporter: A QUARTER OF
MARRIED COUPLES SAY THEY SLEEP
IN SEPARATE BEDS JUST TO GET A
GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
>> I CAN'T DEAL WITH THIS
ANYMORE.
I CAN'T SLEEP.
>> IT USUALLY TURNS OUT TO BE
SOMEONE STOMPING OFF TO THE
COUCH.
>> I'M EMBARRASSED TO ADMIT I
OFTEN MOVE TO A DIFFERENT ROOM.
>> SHE SAYS I DISRUPT HER SLEEP.
I SNORE.
>> IT CAUSES ME TO WAKE UP FROM
MY SLEEP THREE OR FOUR TIMES A
NIGHT.
>> EVEN THOUGH WE'RE BOTH
DOCTORS, WE HAVE LONG LAUGHED
AND DEBATED WHAT'S REALLY GOING
ON, SO WE CALLED IN PROFESSIONAL
HELP --
>> THANK GOODNESS YOU'RE HERE.
>> SLEEP RESEARCHER,
DR. WENDY TROXEL.
>> WHAT'S YOUR GOAL HERE?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SLEEP NEXT TO
MY HUSBAND EVERY SINGLE NIGHT.
>> SHE PUT US TO THE TEST,
MEASURING OUR BRAIN ACTIVITY
WHILE WE SLEPT.
THE SLEEP STUDY WILL CONFIRM
SCIENTIFICALLY THAT ROB'S
SNORING DISRUPTS MY SLEEP.
>> Reporter: THE FIRST NIGHT
SIDE BY SIDE.
>> SNORING WOKE ME UP.
WITH ROB, I HAD 173 AWAKENINGS,
WHICH IS SLEEP SCIENCE LINGO FOR
COMING OUT OF DEEP SLEEP.
THE NEXT NIGHT COULDN'T COME
SOON ENOUGH.
I GET TO SLEEP BY MYSELF.
BUT TO MY GREAT SURPRISE, ALONE
I HAD 135 AWAKENINGS, NEARLY AS
MANY AS WHEN I SLEPT WITH ROB.
>> THERE WAS A LINK BETWEEN
ROB'S SNORING AND YOU HAVING
THESE LITTLE AWAKENINGS FROM
SLEEP.
BUT IT WASN'T ALL ROB'S FAULT.
YOU CONTINUED TO HAVE AWAKENINGS
THROUGHOUT THE NIGHT, EVEN WHEN
ROB HAD STOPPED SNORING.
>> Reporter: THAT'S BECAUSE
SCIENCE CONFIRMS WOMEN ARE
LIGHTER SLEEPERS THAN MEN.
BIOLOGICALLY, OUR BRAINS ARE
CONDITIONED TO JUST WAKE UP.
BUT THE GOOD NEWS IS WOMEN ARE
BETTER SLEEPERS THAN MEN AND
QUICKLY FALL BACK ASLEEP AGAIN.
BUT DR. TROXEL SAYS THE BAD NEWS
FOR WOMEN IS WE OFTEN THINK WE
SLEEP WORSE THAN WE REALLY DO.
I WAS PROOF.
THE STUDY ACTUALLY SHOWED MY
OVERALL SLEEP QUALITY WAS
ACTUALLY EXCELLENT BOTH NIGHTS.
>> YOUR SLEEP WHEN YOU WERE
SLEEPING WITH ROB COMPARED TO
THE NIGHT YOU WERE SLEEPING
ALONE WAS VIRTUALLY IDENTICAL.
>> Reporter: BUT FOR ROB, A
BIGGER IMPACT.
HE GOT AN EXTRA 20 MINUTES OF
DEEP SLEEP WITH ME BY HIS SIDE.
>> SO, I AM TELLING YOU THERE IS
ACTUALLY HEALTH BENEFITS, AT
LEAST FOR ROB, TO SLEEPING WITH
YOU.
>> NOW I FEEL REALLY GUILTY.
>> BECAUSE RESEARCH SHOWS THAT
MEN
SLEEP BETTER WITH A PARTNER THAN
ALONE, AND PROTECTING SLEEP FOR
BOTH OF US MEANS PROTECTING OUR
MARRIAGE.
>> REMEMBER IT IS IMPORTANT TO
EXCLUDE MEDICAL CAUSES SUCH AS
SLEEP APNEA WHICH CAN BE
DANGEROUS.
>> WE KNOW APNEA IS VERY SERIOUS
BUT IS THE REST OF IT ANNOYING?
WHAT'S THE MOOD IN WHICH WE
APPROACH THIS?
>> TAKE IT SERIOUSLY BUT DON'T
BECOME TOO ANXIOUS OVER A SLEEP
ISSUE.
SOMETIMES THAT CAN BE WORSE THAN
THE POSSIBLE ITSELF.
>> THANK YOU, DR. ASHTON AND DR.
ASHTON.
THE TWO DOCTORS, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
>>> COMING UP NEXT, TAKE A CLOSE
LOOK AT THIS PICTURE.
DOES IT LOOK LIKE A UFO TO YOU?
WE TAKE YOU CLOSER TO A NEW
MYSTERY TONIGHT.
OUR "INSTANT INDEX."
♪
[ slap! ]
[ slap! slap! slap! slap! ]
OW! OW!
[ Male Announcer ] YOUR
FAVORITE FOODS FIGHTING YOU?
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
CALCIUM-RICH TUMS
STARTS WORKING SO FAST
YOU'LL FORGET
YOU HAD HEARTBURN.
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUM TUMS
YOU'LL FORGET
YOU HAD HEARTBURN.
ALWAYS GO THE EXTRA MILE.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE,
I DID MY RESEARCH.
MY DOCTOR AND I
WENT WITH AXIRON,
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
>>> OUR "INSTANT INDEX" TONIGHT
BEGINS WITH A REMINDER.
HUMANS AREN'T THE ONLY ONES TO
SUCCUMB TO TEMPTATION.
POLICE IN FLORIDA CAME TO THE
RESCUE OF THIS LITTLE FAWN, HER
HEAD STUCK IN A BAG OF DORITOS.
SHE WANDERED OVER TO THE POLICE
CAR AND LET THE POLICE REMOVE
THE BAG AND SCAMPERED BACK INTO
THE WOODS.
ONE OFFICER SAID SHE MUST HAVE
REALLY WANTED THAT LAST CHIP IN
THE BOTTOM OF THE BAG.
>>> A TIP OF THE HAT TO CYNDI
LAUPER.
OUR PERSON OF THE WEEK,
SHE TOOK HOME THE TONY FOR KINKY
BOOTS.
SHE TWEETED OUT THIS PICTURE.
LAUPER THE FIRST WOMAN TO WIN
THE SOLO AWARD FOR BEST SCORE.
>>> STRAIGHT FROM THE X FILES, A
MOTHER AND DAUGHTER THINK THEY
STUMBLED ON A UFO WHILE ON
VACATION.
SNAPSHOTS FROM THEIR TRIP TO THE
NETHERLANDS AND THE FIRST
PICTURES, A CLEAR SKY OVER THE
CASTLE BUT THEN, LOOK, A STRANGE
OBJECT, SMALL FINS IN THE SKY.
HERE IT IS AGAIN COLOR DRAINED
TO HIGHLIGHT THE MYSTERIOUS
OBJECT.
BELIEVERS SAY THOSE PHOTOS PROVE
IT WAS MOVING AT SUPER SONIC
SPEED.
CRITICS SAY IT'S A BUG ON THE
LENS.
>>> COMING UP NEXT, TO THE
RESCUE, THE RACE TO SAVE
CHEETAHS, CRANES, PANDAS, AND
LEOPARDS FROM THE BRINK OF
EXTINCTION.
SOME ARE CALLING IT A MODERN DAY
NOAH'S ARC.
I stepped on the machine, and it
showed me the pressure points on
my feet and exactly where I
needed more support.
I had tired, achy feet.
Until I got my number.
My Dr. Scholl's Custom Fit
Orthotics Number.
Now I'm a believer.
You'll be a believer, too.
Learn where to find your number
at DrScholls.com.
OF MILD TO MODERATE
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE
IS EXELON PATCH.
NOW WITH
MORE TREATMENT OPTIONS,
EXELON PATCH MAY IMPROVE
OVERALL FUNCTION AND COGNITION.
YOUR LOVED ONE CAN GET
A FREE 30-DAY TRIAL.
AND YOU CAN HAVE
ACCESS TO NURSES.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE
HOW THE DISEASE PROGRESSES.
HOSPITALIZATION,
AND RARELY DEATH,
HAVE BEEN REPORTED FROM WEARING
MORE THAN ONE PATCH AT A TIME.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
ARE NAUSEA, VOMITING, DIARRHEA,
FALL, LOSS OF APPETITE
OR WEIGHT,
APPLICATION SITE REDNESS,
AND URINARY TRACT INFECTION.
THE LIKELIHOOD AND SEVERITY
OF THESE SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCREASE
AS THE DOSE INCREASES
OR IF PATIENTS
WEIGH LESS THAN 110 POUNDS.
PEOPLE AT RISK
FOR STOMACH ULCERS
WHO TAKE
CERTAIN OTHER MEDICINES
SHOULD TALK TO THEIR DOCTOR
AS SERIOUS STOMACH PROBLEMS
SUCH AS BLEEDING MAY WORSEN.
PATIENTS MAY EXPERIENCE
SLOW HEART RATE.
FREE TRIAL OFFER FOR THEM.
NURSES TO TALK TO FOR YOU.
VISIT EXELONPATCHOFFER.COM.
♪
NOW YOU CAN GIVE YOURSELF
A KICK IN THE REAR!
V8 V-FUSION PLUS ENERGY.
NATURAL ENERGY FROM GREEN TEA
PLUS FRUITS AND VEGGIES.
NEED A LITTLE KICK?
OOH!
COULD'VE HAD A V8.
IN THE JUICE AISLE.
ACCOMPLISHING EVEN LITTLE THINGS
CAN BECOME MAJOR VICTORIES.
I'M PHIL MICKELSON, PRO GOLFER.
WHEN I WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS,
MY RHEUMATOLOGIST
PRESCRIBED ENBREL
FOR MY PAIN AND STIFFNESS,
AND TO HELP STOP JOINT DAMAGE.
[ Male Announcer ]
ENBREL MAY LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS
INCLUDING INFECTIONS,
TUBERCULOSIS,
LYMPHOMA, OTHER CANCERS,
NERVOUS SYSTEM
AND BLOOD DISORDERS,
AND ALLERGIC REACTIONS
HAVE OCCURRED.
BEFORE STARTINEN
YOUR DOCTOR SHOULD TEST YOU
FOR TUBERCULOSIS
AND DISCUSS WHETHER
YOU'VE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL INFECTIONS
ARE COMMON.
YOU SHOULD NOT START ENBREL
IF YOU HAVE AN INFECTION
LIKE THE FLU.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU'RE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,
HAVE CUTS OR SORES,
HAVE HAD HEPATITIS B,
HAVE BEEN TREATED
FOR HEART FAILURE,
OR IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS PERSISTENT FEVER,
BRUISING, BLEEDING,
OR PALENESS.
SINCE ENBREL HELPED RELIEVE
MY JOINT PAIN,
IT'S THE LITTLE THINGS
THAT MEAN THE MOST.
ASK YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST
IF ENBREL IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
[ Doctor ] ENBREL,
THE NUMBER ONE BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
PRESCRIBED BY RHEUMATOLOGISTS.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT WE'RE GOING
TO TAKE YOU TO A MYSTERIOUS
PLACE DESIGNED TO CREATE MORE
LIFE FOR SOME OF THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL CREATURES ON EARTH.
COME WITH US, BELIEVE IT OR NOT,
TO THE HILLS OF VIRGINIA AND
INSIDE A PASSIONATE RACE AGAINST
TIME WITH ABC'S RON CLAIBORNE.
>> Reporter: NOBODY WANTS THIS
TO DISAPPEAR.
A 3-MONTH-OLD CLOUDED LEOPARD IS
ONE OF THE LAST OF A VANISHING
BREED.
THIS THREE-MONTH-OLD CUB'S
DAZZLING LIQUID BLUE WILL DARKEN
SOON.
THAT'S ONE OF THE SECRETS OF
THESE MYSTERIOUS CATS -- NATIVE
TO INDONESIA -- THAT ARE BEING
UNLOCKED BY RESEARCHERS AT A
LITTLE-KNOWN ANIMAL CONSERVATION
FACILITY.
>> THESE CLOUDED LEOPARD CUBS
ARE JUST 100 DAYS OLD.
BROTHER AND SISTER.
VERY SOFT AND VERY FRIENDLY.
>> Reporter: THEY SEEM TO THINK
I'M ANOTHER LEOPARD.
THE POPULATION OF CLOUDED
LEOPARDS IN THE WILD HAS BEEN
DECIMATED BY HUNTERS AND
POACHERS.
BUT HERE, SCIENTISTS ARE
STUDYING THESE ANIMALS TO TRY TO
SAVE THEM.
ONE THING THEY'VE LEARNT --
THE HIGHER THE TREES THEY'VE GOT
TO CLIMB, THE LOWER THE CATS'
STRESS LEVELS.
AND THAT HELPS THEM BREED.
SO FAR, THEY'VE SUCCESSFULLY
RAISED 80 OF THESE MAGNIFICENT
CATS.
MANY OF THESE EXOTIC ANIMALS
WILL EVENTUALLY BE RETURNED TO
NATURE.
LIKE THESE MONTH-OLD BABY
BLACK-FOOTED FERRETS.
ONCE ALL BUT WIPED OUT, THE
INSTITUTE HAS BRED AND RELEASED
THOUSANDS OF THEM.
>> THEY CAN END UP IN ARIZONA,
KANSAS.
>> BUT THEY'LL BE IN THE WILD?
>> THEY'LL BE IN THE WILD.
>> Reporter: OVER 3,000 ACRES OF
OPEN SPACE.
THERE ARE PANDAS, CRANES.
>> WHEN IT COMES TO ALL THESE
ANIMALS, THE ONE COMMON
DENOMINATOR IS LOSS OF HABITAT.
>> Reporter: IT'S A RACE AGAINST
TIME.
RON CLAIBORNE, ABC NEWS.
>>> IT'S GREAT TO BEGIN THE WEEK
WITH YOU.
WE'RE ALWAYS THERE AT ABC
NEWS.COM, "NIGHTLINE" LATER AND
I'LL SEE YOU BACK HERE TOMORROW
NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
NIGHTLINE" LATER AND
I'LL SEE YOU BACK HERE TOMORROW
NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> APPLE PLEDGED TO COMBAT
APPLE PICKING AN UPGRADE THAT
WILL GIVE YOUR iPHONE A NEW
LOOK.
>> THE VICTIM OF THE LIMOUSINE
FIRE, WERE THERE TOO MANY
PEOPLE ON BOARD?
TONIGHT A SURPRISE DECISION
FROM SFPD RANK AND FILE.
>>> A FOLLOW UP FROM THE I
TEAM.
THE RIGHTS HAVE YOU WHEN THE
COUNTY CUTS YOU OFF FROM YOUR
FRIENDS AND FAMILY.
>> APPLE GIVES iPHONE A NEW
LOOK GIVING YOU A NEW SENSE OF
SECURITY IF THE PHONE IS EVER
STOLEN.
GOOD EVENING.
I'M CHERYL JENNINGS.
>> APPLE TODAY UNVEILED A NEW
WAY TO MAKE iPHONES USELESS IN
THE WRONG HANDS THAT IS GET
BEING PRAISE FROM LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
THE ANNOUNCEMENT CAME FROM THE
DEVELOPER'S CONFERENCE IN SAN
FRANCISCO.
DAVID?
>> THERE IS NO QUESTION THE
THEFT OF MOBILE PHONES HAS
BECOME A NATIONAL EPIDEMIC
FROM COAST TO COAST.
THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY IS
PLANNING ON MEETING WITH
OWNERS OR MAKERS.
AND A NEW ANTITHEFT FEATURE
CALLED ON THE PHONES.
IT WILL BE PART OF IOS 7.
>> IF A THIEF TRIES TO TURN
OFF FIND MY iPHONE OR IF THEY
WIPE THE DEVICE ENTIRELY
THEY'LL NOT BE TIBL REACTIVATE
IT BECAUSE THEY DON'T KNOW
YOUR iPOD USER NAME.
>> IO 7 SCREEN FOTORS WILL
APPEAR THREE DIMENSIONAL.
THE IK YONZ WILL BE FLATTER
AND TEXT, SHARPER.