>>> TONIGHT, SEVERAL BREAKING
STORIES AS WE COME ON THE AIR.
IN LAS VEGAS, THE STUNNING
IMAGES.
OUR REPORTER IN A HELICOPTER,
FLYING BESIDE THE HOTEL.
YOU WILL SEE INTO THAT ROOM.
AND THE NEW AND CHILLING VIDEO
FROM THAT NIGHT.
ALSO TONIGHT, WERE THERE TWO
OTHER CITIES THE GUNMAN WAS
LOOKING INTO?
CHICAGO AND BOSTON.
AND THE GIRLFRIEND, THE FBI
INTERVIEW AND WHAT SHE'S NOW
SAYING.
AND ABC NEWS OBTAINING THIS
CHECK.
THEIR PURCHASE IN THE WEEKS
BEFORE.
>>> A STATE OF EMERGENCY
DECLARED TONIGHT IN NEW ORLEANS.
PREPARING FOR A POSSIBLE
HURRICANE.
THE DEADLY STORM ALREADY.
THE PATHS THEN HAVING IT
TRAVELING RIGHT UP TO THE
NORTHEAST.
>>> BREAKING NOW.
THE REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN
CAUGHT UP IN A SEX SCANDAL.
HE HAS JUST GIVEN HIS TWO WEEKS
NOTICE.
>>> THE NFL STAR UNDER FIRE
TONIGHT.
RESPONDING TO A FEMALE REPORTER,
TELLING HER, "IT'S FUNNY TO HEAR
A FEMALE TALK ABOUT ROUTES."
>>> AND THE MAN BEHIND SOME OF
THE BIGGEST MOVIES OF OUR TIME,
AND TONIGHT, HIS VERY PUBLIC
APOLOGY TO THE WOMEN HE'S WORKED
WITH.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A THURSDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH MAJOR
NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN THE LAS
VEGAS MASSACRE.
WE ARE LEARNING THE KILLER MAY
HAVE SCOUTED OTHER POTENTIAL
TARGETS IN CHICAGO AND IN
BOSTON.
AND THE DRAMATIC NEW VIDEO FROM
THAT NIGHT.
>> RUN!
KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
GO!
GO.
>> JUST AFTER THE GUNFIRE BEGAN,
CAN YOU HEAR THE OFFICERS
TELLING THE THOUSANDS TO RUN FOR
THEIR LIVES.
HELPING THE VICTIMS WHO HAD BEEN
SHOT AND WHO HAD FALLEN.
AND TONIGHT, OUR TEAM FLYING
BESIDE THE HOTEL AND OVER THE
MASSIVE CRIME SCENE WHERE THE
FBI IS STILL CAREFULLY COMBING
THROUGH THE EVIDENCE.
ABC'S SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN
LEADING US OFF AGAIN TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: WE BOARDED A
HELICOPTER HERE IN LAS VEGAS FOR
THE FIRST LOOK TONIGHT INTO
STEPHEN PADDOCK'S SNIPER'S NEST.
HIGH ABOVE THE LAS VEGAS STRIP
AT THE GILDED DE.CAFATHF  OE
INSIDE ONE SHATTERED WINDOW,
PILLOWS STACKED HIGH ON A
STRIPPED BED.
THE OTHER WINDOW, PARTIALLY
BLOCKED BY PLYWOOD.
BUT INSIDE, INVESTIGATORS
CAREFULLY DISSECTING THE SCENE.
DOWN BELOW, YOU CAN SEE FBI
AGENTS PICKING THROUGH EVERY
SINGLE PIECE OF DEBRIS DOWN
THERE ON THE FAIRGROUNDS FLOOR.
THEY DON'T WANT TO MISS
ANYTHING, A SINGLE BULLET
FRAGMENT OR A SINGLE PIECE OF
EVIDENCE.
THIS IS THE AFTERMATH.
BUT TONIGHT, NEW VIDEO GIVES NEW
INSIGHT INTO THE CHAOS ON THE
GROUND.
>> GET DOWN!
>> Reporter: THAT GUNFIRE
TRIGGERING HYSTERIA, CONFUSION.
SHOCKINGLY, PEOPLE SEEM UNABLE
TO PROCESS WHAT'S HAPPENING.
>> RUN!
THOSE ARE SHOTS!
RUN!
DON'T WALK!
>> Reporter: POLICE OFFICERS
YELLING AT THEM THAT THEY'RE
UNDER ATTACK.
>> EVERYBODY
>> Reporter: RIGHT THERE,
THERE'S A WOMAN ON THE GROUND,
AS THE CROWDS RUN PAST HER.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Reporter: THAT VIDEO SHOT BY
RAY PAGE, WHO WENT TO GET HIS
TRUCK, PARKED NEARBY, DRIVING IT
BACK INTO THE KILL ZONE, TURNING
IT INTO A MAKESHIFT AMBULANCE.
>> RIGHT HERE, COME IN HERE.
>> Reporter: THE WOUNDED LOADED
IN, ONE AFTER ANOTHER.
>> GET IN THE TRUCK, GET IN THE
TRUCK.
DO WE HAVE ANY OTHER WOUNDED
PEOPLE WE CAN TAKE?
>> NOT RIGHT NOW.
>> Reporter: RAY THEN JUMPS
BEHIND THE WHEEL, DRIVES THEM
BACK DOWN THE STRIP TO
PARAMEDICS.
>> I GOT FIVE WOUNDED.
GUNSHOT WOUND TO THE CHEST HERE.
>> SOMEONE HELP, PLEASE, PLEASE.
I'M BLEEDING SO MUCH.
>> Reporter: TODAY, FROM HIGH
ABOVE, EVIDENCE OF A MASSACRE
STILL FROZEN IN TIME.
IT DOESN'T LOOK SO MUCH LIKE
THERE WAS A CONCERT THERE, BUT
AATTH
THOSE OVERTURNED LAWN CHAIRS,
WE'VE SEEN STROLLERS THERE,
WE'VE SEEN WALKERS THERE.
EVIDENCE OF JUST THE ABSOLUTE
CHAOS.
AND TONIGHT, WE ARE LEARNING
THAT STEPHEN PADDOCK MAY HAVE
SCOUTED OTHER TARGETS AS FAR
AWAY AS BOSTON AND CHICAGO.
ACCORDING TO SOURCES BRIEFED ON
THE INVESTIGATION, HE BOOKED
ROOMS AT CHICAGO'S BLACKSTONE
HOTEL IN AUGUST, THE SAME DATES
AS THE LOLLAPALOOZA FESTIVAL
RIGHT ACROSS THE STREET IN GRANT
PARK.
ABOUT 100,000 PEOPLE ATTENDED
EACH DAY.
BUT PADDOCK NEVER CHECKED IN.
LAW ENFORCEMENT SOCES ALSO
TELL US HIS PHONE SHOWS A GOOGLE
PARK" IN BOSTON.LS AROUND FENWAY
THAT BALLPARK'S CAPACITY?
NEARLY 38,000 PEOPLE.
BUT NO EVIDENCE HE TRAVELED TO
BOSTON, EITHER.
INSTEAD, HE STAYED CLOSE TO
HOME, HOLING UP IN ONE OF THE
CASINOS HE KNEW SO WELL, LOOKING
DOWN ON THAT HELPLESS CROWD.
>> SO, LET'S GET TO MATT GUTMAN
LIVE WITH US AGAIN TONIGHT.
AND MATT, NOW YOU'RE LEARNING,
THERE MIGHT BE SOMEONE ELSE
AUTHORITIES WANT TO TALK TO?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THAT PADDOCK
WAS SEEN WITH A MYSTERY WOMAN IN
HIS LAST DAYS.
NOW, SHE WAS NOT HIS GIRLFRIEND,
MARILOU DANLEY.
THEY'RE TRYING TO FIND OUT WHO
SHE IS AND WHAT SHE KNOWS.
ALSO, GIVEN THE ARSENAL THAT HE
AMASSED, ALONG WITH EXPLOSIVE
MATERIALS AND THE FACT THAT HE
MAY HAVE HAD AN ESCAPE PLAN,
THEY'RE NOW SAYING THAT THEY
CANNOT RULE OUT THAT HE HAD AN
ACCOMPLICE.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN LEADING US OFF.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> THE OTHER MAJOR HEADLINE
INVOLVES THE GIRLFRIEND, NOW
QUESTIONED BY THE FBI BACK HERE
IN THE U.S.
WHAT MARILOU DANLEY SAYS WHEN
ASKED IF SHE KNEW ANYTHING.
AND TONIGHT, ABC NEWS OBTAINING
A CHECK.
WHAT THEY PAID CASH FOR IN THE
WEEKS BEFORE.
AND HOW THE SALESPERSON
DESCRIBED THE COUPLE.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: NEW INSIGHTS
TONIGHT FROM AN UNLIKELY PLACE
ABOUT STEPHEN PADDOCK -- THE
RENO CAR DEALERSHIP WHERE HE
BOUGHT THIS CAR ON AUGUST 1st.
PAYING CASH, WITH A CHECK FOR
$14,411 -- NOT A SIGN OF SOMEONE
WITH FINANCIAL PROBLEMS.
EMPLOYEES HERE TODAY TOLD US THE
FBI QUESTIONED THEM ABOUT
EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED WITH
PADDOCK AND HIS GIRLFRIEND,
MARILOU DANLEY, WHEN THEY CAME
TO BUY THE CAR.
>> MARILOU EVEN WANTED TO GET A
LEXUS, BUT HE WAS LIKE, I'M NOT
GOING TO SPEND $10,000 MORE FOR
A CAR THAT'S GOT THE EXACT SAM
T.PMEQ
>> Reporter: AND WHEN DANLEY
WENT ON A TEST DRIVE, SHE TOLD
THE FEMALE SALESPERSON THAT
PADDOCK HAD SAHED VEOMFRR  A
TROUBLED MARRIAGE.
>> SHE SAID SHE HAD A BAD
RELATIONSHIP PRIOR TO HIM.
AND HOW HE HAD, YOU KNOW, TURNED
HER LIFE AROUND AND REALLY
HELPED HER OUT.
>> Reporter: DANLEY'S
RELATIONSHIP WITH PADDOCK HAS
NOW BECOME A KEY FOCUS OF THE
INVESTIGATION.
AGENTS PADDOCK WAS A CARING MAN
WHO SHOWED NO SIGN OF VIOLENCE.
AND THE FBI ALSO WANTED TO KNOW
ABOUT THE MORE THAN $100,000
THAT PADDOCK WIRED TO THE
PHILIPPINES FOR DANLEY, BEFORE
SENDING HER THERE JUST TWO WEEKS
IN ADVANCE OF THE SHOOTING.
HER LAWYER READ HER STATEMENT.
>> I WAS GRATEFUL, BUT HONESTLY,
I WAS WORRIED THAT FIRST, THE
UNEXPECTED TRIP HOME AND THEN
THE MONEY WAS A WAY OF BREAKING
UP WITH ME.
>> Reporter: FOUR DAYS INTO THE
INVESTIGATION, THE FBI SAYS IT
HAS RULED OUT MONEY PROBLEMS AND
RULED OUT ANY CONNECTION TO
ANARCHIST GROUPS, TO
ANTI-GOVERNMENT GROUPS, TO
OVERSEAS TERROR GROUPS.
>> AND BRIAN ROSS WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT.
FOUR DAYS LATER, STILL NO
MOTIVE.
BUT AS YOU BEGAN TO POINT OUT
RIGHT THERE, YOU HAVE LEARNED
WHAT THEY HAVE BEGUN TO RULE
OUT.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
THEY'RE STILL STUMPED, BUT
THEY'RE CERTAIN THEY WILL FIND
OUT A MOTIVE, SOONER OR LATER.
DRILLING DOWN FURTHER NOW ON HIS
FINANCES, HIS COMPUTER AND HIS
MENTAL HEALTH, DAVID.
>> ONE THING, BRIAN, SO MANY
PEOPLE ARE ASKING ABOUT IS THIS
BELIEF HE DIDN'T SNAP IN THE
MOMENT, BECAUSE THERE'S SO MANY
SIGNS NOW HE HAD BEEN PREPARING
THIS FOR SOME TIME.
>> Reporter: EXACTLY.
THIS WAS A WELL-PLANNED ATTACK.
NEARLY TWO DOZEN WEAPONS IN HIS
HOTEL SUITE, HALF OF THEM
CONVERTED TO BE FULLY AUTOMATIC,
AS WELL AS THOSE CAMERAS,
INCLUDING THE ONE IN THAT ROOM
SERVICE CART OUTSIDE HIS ROOM,
PLACED TO GIVE HIM EARLY WARNING
ABOUT ANYONE COMING TO STOP HIM,
DAVID.
>> STILL TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
THAT MOTIVE.
BRIAN ROSS TONIGHT, THANK YOU.
>>> AFTER THE MASSACRE TOOK 58
LIVES, COULD THERE BE BIPARTISAN
MOVEMENT NOW ON THIS IN
WASHINGTON?
THE GROWING CALL TONIGHT TO BAN
OR REGULATE THOSE SO-CALLED BUMP
STOCKS.
THE DEVICE USED BY THE GUNMAN,
ATTACHING IT TO SOME OF HIS
WEAPONS, TURNING SEMIAUTOMATIC
WEAPONS TO FIRE LIKE AN
AUTOMATIC.
DEMOCRATS, SOME REPUBLICANS AND
A SIGNAL TODAY FROM THE NRA ON
THIS?
HERE'S ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA.
>> Reporter: FROM THE NATION'S
MOST POWERFUL GUN LOBBY, TODAY,
A CALL FOR CHANGE IN THE WAKE OF
THE NATION'S DEADLIEST MASS
SHOOTING.
FOUND ON A DOZEN OF THE LAS
VEGAS SHOOTER'S WEAPONS, THOSE
BUMP STOCK ATTACHMENTS THAT
ALLOW A RIFLE TO FIRE LIKE A
MACHINE GUN.
THE NRA NOW SAYS, "DEVICES
DESIGNED TO ALLOW SEMIAUTOMATIC
RIFLES TO FUNCTION LIKE FULLY
AUTOMATIC RIFLES SHOULD BE
SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL
REGULATIONS."
AND TONIGHT, A GROWING NUMBER OF
TOP REPUBLICANS SAY THEY WOULD
CONSIDER LEGISLATION BANNING
BUMP STOCKS ALTOGETHER.
>> IF THIS IS A MODIFICATION TO
A FIREARM THAT BREACHES THE
SPIRIT OF THE LAW AGAINST
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS, THEN I THINK
THERE WOULD BE BIPARTISAN
SUPPORT TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> CLEARLY, THAT'S SOMETHING WE
NEED TO LOOK INTO.
>> Reporter: ONE FLORIDA
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN EVEN
VOWING TO INTRODUCE HIS OWN
BILL.
WITH A BUMP STOCK, ASSAULT
RIFLES CAN FIRE HUNDREDS OF
ROUNDS PER MINUTE, CHANGING A
GUN FROM THIS TO THIS.
BUT NOT ALL REPUBLICANS ARE
ONBOARD WITH TOUGHER LAWS.
>> I DON'T THINK THE 80 OR
90 MILLION AMERICANS WHO
EXERCISE THEIR SECOND AMENDMENT
RIGHTS TO OWN A GUN SHOULD BE
PUNISHED FOR THE ACT OF ONE EVIL
PERSON.
>> Reporter: THE WHITE HOUSE, SO
FAR SILENT ON GUN CONTROL IN THE
WAKE OF THE LAS VEGAS MASSACRE,
BUT LATE TODAY, PRESIDENT TRUMP
SIGNALED HE'LL BE WEIGHING IN ON
THE BUMP STOCK DEBATE, TOO.
>> WE'LL BE LOOKING INTO THAT
OV TER
TIME.
>> ALL RIGHT, CECILIA VEGA LIVE
FROM THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE PRESIDENT THERE SAYING HE
WILL LOOK INTO WHAT CAN BE DONE
ON THESE BUMP STOCKS.
IN THE MEANTIME, CECILIA, I WANT
TO ASK YOU ABOUT ANOTHER REPORT
BREAKING TONIGHT INVOLVING THE
WHITE HOUSE CHIEF OF STAFF.
REPORTS IN POLITICO THAT JOHN
KELLY'S PHONE MIGHT HAVE BEEN
COMPROMISED?
>> Reporter: YEAH, DAVID, THIS
REPORT SAYS THAT GENERAL KELLY'S
PERSONAL CELL PHONE WAS
COMPROMISED.
NO INDICATION OF HOW OF BY WHOM
OR EVEN WHETHER ANY DATA MAY
HAVE BEEN ACCESSED.
THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT TELLS US
THAT THE GENERAL'S PHONE STOPPED
WORKING IN DECEMBER, SO, HE
STOPPED USING IT THEN.
THIS IS BEFORE HE EVEN JOINED
THIS ADMINISTRATION, BUT DAVID,
DEFINITELY RAISING QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHETHER ANY SENSITIVE INFO
MAY HAVE BEEN ACCESSED.
>> ALL RIGHT, CECILIA VEGA WITH
US AGAIN TONIGHT.
CECILIA, THANKS, AS ALWAYS.
>>> AND WE SHOULD MENTION, BACK
ON THE LAS VEGAS MASSACRE, THAT
ABC NEWS AND "20/20" WILL AIR A
SPECIAL DOCUMENTARY PRESENTATION
TOMORROW NIGHT, WITH NEW FIRST
ON THE
HEROISM AMID THE TRAGEDY.
"WHAT HAPPENED IN VEGAS" AIRS
TOMORROW AT 10:00 P.M. EASTERN.
I'LL SEE YOU THEN.
WE HOPE YOU WATCH, OR SET YOUR
DVR.
THAT'S TOMORROW NIGHT.
>>> IN THE MEANTIME, OVERSEAS
TONIGHT, AND THE DEADLY AMBUSH
TARGETING AMERICAN TROOPS IN
THE PENTAGON CONFIRMING THREE
ARMY GREEN BERETS KILLED AND TWO
WOUNDED DURING AN ATTACK BY
ABOUT 50 EXTREMISTS NEAR THE
MALI BORDER.
THEY WERE ON A JOINT PATROL AT
THE TIME.
THE AMERICANS PART OF A TEAM
ASSISTING A COUNTER-TERRORISM
OPERATION THERE.
>>> BACK HERE AT HOME TONIGHT,
AND LOUISIANA AND FLORIDA
DECLARING STATES OF EMERGENCY
TONIGHT.
PREPARING FOR A POSSIBLE
HURRICANE, HEADED STRAIGHT FOR
THE U.S.
THE MASSIVE TROPICAL STORM,
NATE, ALREADY BLAMED FOR MORE
THAN A DOZEN DEATHS IN NICARAGUA
AND COSTA RICA.
AS IT MAKES ITS WAY TOWARD THE
GULF TONIGHT, THE PATHS TAKE IT
RIGHT UP THROUGH THE COUNTRY,
RIGHT INTO THE NORTHEAST.
SO, LET'S GET RIGHT TO ROB,
BECAUSE HURRICANE SEASON IS NOT
OVER YET.
>> Reporter: YEAH, DAVID.
UNLIKE THE OTHER STORMS, THIS
ONE IS GOING TO BE MOVING
QUICKLY.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S OVER LAND.
OVER HONDURAS, AND ONCE IT GETS
INTO THE CARIBBEAN LATER ON
TONIGHT, LOOK OUT.
THE WATERS THERE, VERY WARM.
WE'VE GOT HURRICANE WATCHES NOW
THAT ARE POSTED FOR CANCUN, SO,
IT GOES ACROSS THE YUCATAN
TOMORROW NIGHT.
THEN INTO THE GULF OF MEXICO,
INTENSIFYING AS IT DOES.
SO, HOW STRONG?
WE'RE NOT QUITE SURE, BECAUSE IT
WILL BE MOVING SO QUICKLY, BUT
AT LEAST A CATEGORY 1, INTO AND
AROUND NEW ORLEANS AND THE
CENTRAL GULF COAST EARLY SUNDAY
MORNING.
THERE ARE THE TRACKS, MORE
CONFIDENCE THERE.
LOOK AT THE WARM WATERS, DAVID.
MID 80s.
THAT, AS YOU KNOW, IS FUEL FOR
HURRICANES.
>> ALL RIGHT, ON THE WATCH IN
THE GULF TONIGHT.
ROB, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT THIS EVENING, THE
BREAKING HEADLINE INVOLVING A
REPUBLICAN CONGRESSMAN AND HIS
SEX SCANDAL.
TIM MURPHY OF PENNSYLVANIA, A
HUSBAND AND FATHER, GIVING HIS
TWO WEEKS NOTICE TODAY.
HERE'S ABC'S DAVID WRIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THIS
PENNSYLVANIA REPUBLICAN CAUGHT
IN A SEX SCANDAL.
CONGRESSMAN TIM MURPHY
EFFECTIVELY GAVE TWO WEEKS
NOTICE.
HE'S OUT OF CONGRESS, EFFECTIVE
OCTOBER 21st.
>> I THINK IT'S APPROPRIATE THAT
HE MOVES ONTO THE NEXT CHAPTER
OF HIS LIFE.
>> Reporter: CONGRESSMAN MURPHY
IS KNOWN FOR HIS ANTI-ABORTION
VIEWS.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF WOMEN WHO GO
IN FOR AN ABORTION REALLY KNOW
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> Reporter: BUT THIS WEEK, "THE
PITTSBURGH POST GAZETTE"
PUBLISHED TEXT MESSAGES BETWEEN
HIM AND HIS FORMER MISTRESS,
MAKING IT CLEAR THAT WHILE HE'S
AGAINST ABORTION, HE WANTED HER
TO HAVE ONE.
IN JANUARY, SHE TOOK HIM TO TASK
FOR "POSTING YOUR PRO-LIFE
STANCE ALL OVER THE PLACE WHEN
YOU HAD NO ISSUE ASKING ME TO
ABORT OUR UNBORN CHILD JUST LAST
WEEK."
HE TEXTED BACK, EXPRESSING
REMORSE.
TURNS OUT, IT WAS A FALSE ALARM.
BUT THE AFFAIR BECAME PUBLIC AS
A RESULT OF HER DIVORCE
PROCEEDINGS, MUCH TO THE
CONGRESSMAN'S EMBARRASSMENT.
THE CONGRESSMAN IS MARRIED, TOO.
HE SAYS HE'LL TAKE SOME PERSONAL
TIME TO GET HELP, AS HE AND HIS
FAMILY SORT OUT THEIR
DIFFICULTIES.
DAVID?
>> DAVID, THANK YOU.
>>> AND ONE MORE HEADLINE OUT OF
WASHINGTON TONIGHT.
ATTORNEY GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS
TODAY REVERSING AN OBAMA-ERA
POLICY, SAYING FEDERAL CIVIL
RIGHTS LAWS DO NOT PROTECT
TRANSGENDER PEOPLE FROM
DISCRIMINATION IN THE WORKPLACE.
SESSIONS SUGGESTING
DISCRIMINATION BASED ON SEX DOES
NOT INCLUDE ISSUES OF GENDER
IDENTITY.
>>> WE TURN TONIGHT TO FOOTBALL
STAR IGNITING A NEW OUTRAGE THIS
EVENING.
CAROLINA PANTHERS QUARTERBACK
CAM NEWTON UNDER FIRE, ACCUSED
OF MAKING SEXIST REMARKS TO A
FEMALE REPORTER.
AT LEAST ONE SPONSOR ALREADY
CUTTING TIES.
AND HERE'S ABC'S PAULA FARIS
NOW.
>> Reporter: THE FALLOUT FOR CAM
NEWTON HAS BEEN SWIFT.
>> NEW DANNON OIKOS IS MY GO-TWO
PROTEIN SNACK.
>> Reporter: DANNON PULLING ALL
OF NEWTON'S ADS.
AND GATORADE CALLING HIS
COMMENTS "DISRESPECTFUL TO ALL
WOMEN."
IT'S ALL BECAUSE OF THIS
EXCHANGE WITH A FEMALE REPORTER.
>> DEVIN FUNCHESS SEEMS TO
REALLY EMBRACE THE PHYSICALITY
OF HIS ROUTES.
>> IT'S FUNNY TO HEAR A FEMALE
TALK ABOUT ROUTES.
LIKE -- IT'S FUNNY.
>> Reporter: THAT REPORTER,
25-YEAR-OLD JOURDAN RODRIGUE,
SHOT BACK ON TWITTER.
"I DON'T THINK IT'S FUNNY TO BE
A FEMALE AND TALK ABOUT ROUTES.
I THINK IT'S MY JOB."
BUT RODRIGUE ALSO IN HOT WATER,
APOLOGIZING FOR YEARS OLD
OFFENSIVE TWEETS THAT SURFACED
THIS WEEK.
RODRIGUE WAS BACK AT PANTHERS
PRACTICE TODAY, BUT NOT
COMMENTING.
THE TEAM, QUIET, AS WELL.
BUT THE NFL, WITH NEARLY HALF
ITS FANBASE NOW CONSISTING OF
WOMEN, SAYING "THE COMMENTS ARE
JUST PLAIN WRONG AND
DISRESPECTFUL."
>> IF YOU LOOK AT EVERYTHING
THAT HAS ADDED UP, THE DOMESTIC
VIOLENCE ISSUES, THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM CONTROVERSY, THEY'RE
HAVING SOME TROUBLE WITH
RATINGS.
>> Reporter: AND RATINGS ARE A
BIG CONCERN FOR THE NFL.
THIS IS WHERE THE LEAGUE MAKES
ITS MONEY.
AND SO FAR THIS SEASON, RATINGS
ARE DOWN 9%.
DAVID?
>> PAULA, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS THURSDAY.
THE MURDER AT A CONSTRUCTION
SITE, RIGHT HERE IN NEW YORK
CITY.
THE FOREMAN FATALLY SHOT ON THE
37th FLOOR.
POLICE ON THE SCENE.
>>> THE TRAIN DERAILMENT, 14
CARS TOPPLING OFF THE TRACKS.
ONE OF THEM SLAMMING RIGHT INTO
A HOME AS THE RESIDENT WAS
SLEEPING.
>>> AND THE BREAKING HEADLINE
TONIGHT FROM HOLLYWOOD.
THE MAN BEHIND SOME OF THE
BIGGEST MOVIES OF OUR TIME AND
HIS VERY PUBLIC APOLOGY TO THE
WOMEN HE'S WORKED WITH.
A LOT MORE NEWS AHEAD.
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
[radi♪ alarm]
♪
Julie is living with metastatic
breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women with hormone receptor-
positive HER2- metastatic breast
cancer as the first
hormonal based therapy.
♪
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
And IBRANCE plus letrozole
shrunk tumors in over half of
these patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE can
develop low white blood cell
counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if you have
fever, chills,
or other signs of infection
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts...
...infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver
blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Julie calls it her "new" normal.
Because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one-prescribed,
FDA-approved oral combination
treatment for HR+/HER2- MBC.
>>> THE NEW HEADLINE TONIGHT
INVOLVING ONE OF THE MOST
POWERFUL FIGURES IN HOLLYWOOD.
SEVERAL ALLEGATIONS OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT AGAINST MOVIE
PRODUCER HARVEY WEINSTEIN.
FROM YOUNG ASSISTANTS TO A
FAMOUS ACTRESS.
TONIGHT HERE, HIS RESPONSE.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS NOW.
>> Reporter: EXPLOSIVE NEW
ALLEGATIONS TONIGHT FROM "THE
NEW YORK TIMES" ABOUT HARVEY
WEINSTEIN, THE STUDIO EXEC KNOWN
FOR PRODUCING BLOCKBUSTER MOVIES
LIKE "GOOD WILL HUNTING," "PULP
FICTION" AND "SILVER LININGS
PLAYBOOK."
>> BECAUSE I'M SO MUCH CRAZIER
THAN YOU.
>> KEEP YOUR VOICE DOWN.
>> Reporter: HE'S BEEN LAUDED
REPEATEDLY, BY MALE AND FEMALE
OSCAR WINNERS ALIKE.
>> HARVEY WEINSTEIN, WHO
BELIEVED IN US AND MADE THIS
MOVIE.
>> MY FRIENDS AT MIRAMAX FOR
MAKING THIS FILM, ESPECIALLY
HARVEY.
>> Reporter: NOW, WEINSTEIN SAYS
HE IS PLANNINGTAO  T L AKE EA
OF ABSENCE TO "DEAL WITH THIS
ISSUE HEAD-ON."
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" DESCRIBES
SEVERAL SEXUAL HARASSMENT
ACCUSATIONS, INCLUDING FROM
ACTRESS ASHLEY JUDD, WHO TOLD
"VARIETY" BACK IN 2015, "I WAS
SEXUALLY HARASSED BY ONE OF OUR
INDUSTRY'S MOST FAMOUS,
ADMIRED-SLASH-REVILED BOSSES."
SHE DID NOT NAME HIM AT THE
TIME, BUT "VARIETY" DESCRIBES
HOW HE "KEPT SUMMONING HER TO
HIS HOTEL ROOM UNDER THE
PRETENSE OF TALKING ABOUT ROLES
IN HIS MOVIES" AND "TRIED TO G
JUDD T
ACCORDING TO "THE NEW YORK
TIMES," WEINSTEIN REACHED
SETTLEMENTS WITH AT LEAST EIGHT
WOMEN.
IN RESPONSE TO THE ALLEGATIONS,
WEINSTEIN SAID IN A STATEMENT,
"I CAME OF AGE IN THE '60s AND
'70s WHEN ALL THE RULES ABOUT
BEHAVIOR AND WORKPLACES WERE
DIFFERENT.
I APPRECIATE THE WAY I'VE
BEHAVED WITH COLLEAGUES IN THE
PAST HAS CAUSED A LOT OF PAIN,
AND I SINCERELY APOLOGIZE FOR
IT."
ATTORNEY LISA BLOOM, DAUGHTER OF
FEMINIST LAWYER GLORIA ALLRED,
IS ADVISING WEINSTEIN AND
RELEASED A STATEMENT, CALLING
HIM "AN OLD DINOSAUR LEARNING
NEW WAYS."
BUT ALSO SAYS, "HE DENIES MANY
OF THE ACCUSATIONS AS PATENTLY
FALSE."
WEINSTEIN'S LAWYER TELLS ABC
NEWS THEY PLAN TO SUE "THE NEW
YORK TIMES," SAYING THE STORY IS
SATURATED WITH FALSE AND
DEFAMATORY STATEMENTS.
ARE CONFIDENT IN THEIR
REPORTING.
DAVID?
>> LINSEY DAVIS, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE MAJOR
HEADLINE INVOLVING JON BON JOVI.
>>> AND THAT MURDER ON A
CONSTRUCTION SITE ON THE 37th
FLOOR OF A HIGH RISE.
>>> AND THE TRAIN DERAILMENT, 14
CARS RIGHT THROUGH A HOME.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
♪ Stare with me into the abyss
( ♪ )
with some big news
about type 2 diabetes.
You have type 2 diabetes,
right?
Yes.
So let me ask
you this...
How does diabetes
affect your heart?
It doesn't, does it?
Actually, it does.
Type 2 diabetes
can make you twice
as likely to die
from a cardiovascular event,
like a heart attack or stroke.
And with heart disease,
your risk is even higher.
You didn't know that.
No.
Yeah.
But, wait, there's good news
for adults who have
type 2 diabetes
and heart disease.
JARDIANCE is the only
type 2 diabetes pill
with a lifesaving
cardiovascular benefit.
JARDIANCE is proven to both
significantly reduce
the chance of dying from a
cardiovascular event
in adults who have type 2
diabetes and heart disease
and lower your A1C.
JARDIANCE can cause
serious side effects
This may cause you
to feel dizzy,
faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious
side effect
that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting,
stomach pain, tiredness,
and trouble breathing.
Stop taking NCanIARDcallEy
if you have symptoms
of ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic reaction
include rash, swelling,
and difficulty breathing
or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects
are sudden kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE
with a sulfonylurea
or insulin may cause
low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So now that you know all that,
what do you think?
That it's time to think
about JARDIANCE.
Ask your doctor about JARDIANCE.
And get to the heart
of what matters.
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night,
so he got home safe.
Yeah, my dad says our
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Let's get the lady of the house
back on her feet.
And help her feel more strength
and energy in just two weeks.
YAAAY!
The complete balanced
nutrition of Ensure
with 9 grams of protein and
26 vitamins and minerals.
Ensure. Always be you.
We cut the price of trades to
give investors even more value.
And at $4.95, you can trade
with a clear advantage.
Fidelity, where smarter
investors will always be.
>>> TO THE INDEX OF OTHER NEWS,
AND A MURDER OF THE ROOF OF A
HIGH RISE CONSTRUCTION SITE HERE
IN NEW YORK CITY.
THE SUSPECT, WHO AUTHORITIES
BELIEVE HAD BEEN FIRED, FATALLY
SHOOTING THE 37-YEAR-OLD FOREMAN
ON THE 37th FLOOR.ECT EN TURNINN
ON HIMSELF.
INVESTIGATORS ARE ON THE SCENE.
>>> A RESIDENT IN ATLANTA IS IN
THE HOSPITAL TONIGHT AFTER A
TRAIN DERAILED RIGHT INTO HIS
HOME.
14 CARS ON THE CSX FREIGHT TRAIN
BOUND FOR CINCINNATI CAME OFF
THE TRACKS, SLAMMING INTO THE
HOME.
THE VICTIM WAS ASLEEP AT THE
TIME, SUFFERING MINOR INJURIES
TO HIS LEGS. THE ROCK AND ROLL
TONIGHT.
♪ SHOT THROUGH THE HEART
♪ AND YOU'RE TO BLAME
>> JON BON JOVI AMONG THE 19
PERFORMERS DOMINATED FOR THE
CLASS OF 2018.
AMONG THE OTHERS, RADIOHEAD,
EURYTHMICS, THE MOODY BLUES,
UNCED NI
IN DECEMBER.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, AMERICA
STRONG TONIGHT.
THE HUSBAND, FATHER AND
GRANDFATHER CONQUERING SO MANY
CHALLENGES, BUT HERE'S THE
QUESTION --
WOULD YOU DO THIS?
DON'T LOOK DOWN.
I wanted to know who I am
and where I came from.
I did my AncestryDNA
and I couldn't wait
to get my pie chart.
The most shocking result was
that I'm 26% Native American.
I had no idea.
Just to know this
is what I'm made of,
this is where
my ancestors came from.
And I absolutely want to know
more about my
Native American heritage.
It's opened up
a whole new world for me.
Discover the story
only your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now at
AncestryDNA.com.
I have no idea how we're going
to get through this.
Follow me.
UnitedHealthcare has the people
and tools
to help guide you through the
confusion.
Well that wasn't so bad at all.
That's how we like it.
UnitedHealthcare.
...What are you doing??
I thought you had a cold?
I don't need all this.
Mucinex Fast-Max can handle
pretty much every symptom.
Even...
Yea - I can read, you know.
Ahhh!
Mucinex Fast-Max.
9 symptoms. 1 dose.
Max strength.
Whentrust the brand doctors
trust for themselves.
Nexium 24HR is the number one
choice of doctors
and pharmacists for their
own frequent heartburn.
And all day
all night protection.
When it comes to frequent
heartburn, trust Nexium 24HR.
I've always had that issue
with the seeds
getting under my denture.
Super Poligrip Free.
reates a seal c
of the dentures
in my mouth.
Just a few dabs
is clinically
proven
to seal out more
food particles.
Try Super
Poligrip Free.
♪
Woman: Every year we
take a girl's trip.
Remember Nashville?
Both:
Kimchi BBQ!
Amazing honky-tonk!
I can't believe
you got us tickets!
didn't pay for anything.
Amazing honky-tonk!
(Sigh)
You never do.
Send me what I owe.
I've got it.
I mean, You did find money
to buy those boots.
(Alert beep)
Are you serious? Is that
why you don't like them?
Those boots could
make a unicorn cry.
Yeah! Tears of joy.
(Groan)
Settle up with your friends
on October 17th
with the Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
AMERICA STRONG.
THE HUSBAND, FATHER AND
GRANDFATHER WHO HAS CONQUERED SO
MANY CHALLENGES, AND TURNING 80
YEARS OLD, HE SENT US THIS.
DOLPH HATFIELD IS FROM
WASHINGTON, D.C., A FATHER,
HUSBAND, GRANDFATHER.
AND RETIRED SCIENTIST FROM THE
NATIONAL CANCER INSTITUTE.
HE'S ALSO A BLACK BELT IN TAE
KWON DO.
HE'S CONQUERED CHALLENGES
THROUGHOUT HIS WHOLE LIFE.
HE'S GONE SKYDIVING, CLIMBED
KILIMANJARO AND EL CAPITAN.
HE WENT RUNNING WITH THE BULLS.
BUT JUST A FEW YEARS AGO, HE
FACED HIS TOUGHEST CHALLENGE
YET -- COMPLICATIONS DURING A
SURGERY LEFT IT NEARLY
IMPOSSIBLE FOR HIM TO WALK.
BUT HE CONQUERED THAT, TOO, AND
SO WHEN IT CAME TIME TO
CELEBRATE HIS 80th BIRTHDAY THIS
WEEK, HE HAD AN IDEA AND INVITED
US ALONG.
>> THANK YOU, DAVID, FOR SHARING
MY 80th BIRTHDAY WITH YOUR
VIEWERS.
>> Reporter: TAKING US 764 FEET
UP TO THE WORLD'S HIGHEST BUNGEE
JUMP IN CHINA.
DOLPH WAS READY.
>> I'M READY TO GO.
LET'S GET IT ON.
>> Reporter: STRAPPING HIM IN,
WALKING OUT TO THAT LEDGE AND
DOWN BELOW, ANXIOUSLY WATCHING,
HIS WIFE, MARY, AND DAUGHTER,
SANDY.
AND THEN, THE COUNTDOWN.
>> HERE WE GO.
FIVE, FOUR, THREE, TWO, ONE --
>> Reporter: THE JUMP OVER, BUT
STILL HANGING, DOLPH WITH THIS
MESSAGE --
>> WHAT AN 80th BIRTHDAY, I GOT
TO TELL YOU.
>> Reporter: AND THEN, BACK ON
LAND.
>> HAPPY BIRTHDAY!
>> Reporter: AND HIS WIFE AND
DAUGHTER, GLAD HE'S BACK ON
SOLID GROUND.
HAPPY 80th, DOLPH.
BETTER YOU THAN ME.
THANKS FOR WATCHING HERE ON A
THURSDAY NIGHT, I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
UNTIL THEN, GOOD NIGHT.
>>> IT'S A FEAST FOR THE EYES
ANDTONIGHT U'REOINGOAR M ET AS.
BLUE ANGEL PILOT FOR WHOM FLEET
WEEK ISOMING.
♪
>> THE BAY AREA'S BIGGEST MUSIC
FESTIVAL KICKS OFF TOMORROW, IF
EVER MINDFUL THAT IT COULD BE A
TARGET.
>>> SOME RENTERS BIDDING TO GET
THEIR APARTMENT.
MICHAEL FINNEY, 7 ON YOUR SIDE,
THE CONTROVERSY OVER THE NEW WAY
TO FIND A
>>> THEY'RE HERE.
THE SIGHTS AND SOUNDS OF THE
BLUE ANGELS.
OBVIOUS OVER THE SAN FRANCISCO
BAY THIS AFTERNOON.
AND THIS IS JUST PRACTICE.
GOOD EVENING, I'M DAN ASHLEY.
>> AND I'M KRISTEN SZE, IN FOR
AMA DAETZ.
NOT OFFICIAL AIR SHOW, JUST A
PRACTICE BUT THRILLED ONLOOKERS
AROUND THE BAY.
>> AWE INSPIRING.
REAL SHOW IS TOMORROW AND NOT
ONLY EVENT DRAWING ATTENTION AND
THOUSANDS TO SAN FRANCISCO.
>>
>>.
>> YOU CTALKING TO LOCAL PILOT.
>> Reporter: FLEET WEEK SET UP
IS UNDER WAY AND BAY AREA WILL
BE WELL REPRESENTED IN THE SKY.
HALF THE TEAM GREW UP AROUND
HERE, SPOKE WITH ONE PILOT FROM
FREMONT.
THAT SOUND CAN ONLY MEAN ONE
THING, FLEET WEEK IN
SAN FRANCISCO.
BLUE ANGELS SOARED OVER THE CITY
FOR A SITE SURVEY AHEAD O SHOW.
EXCITED SPECTATORS WATCHED AND
TOOK PICTURES FROM THE MARINA
GREEN LIKE HIS AND HER
THREE-YEAR-OLD SON.
>> FIRST COUPLE OF YEARS, WHAT
IS THIS?
THEN GOTTEN MORE EXCITING EVERY
YEAR.
>> Reporter: