STAGE.
>> THE NEW SHOW CALLED CIRQE
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, SHOTS FIRED.
THE DRAMATIC NEW VIDEO OF POLICE
TAKING DOWN THE LONDON ATTACKER.
AND TONIGHT THE REMARKABLE WOMEN
ON THE SCENE WHO DEFIED THOSE
ATTACKERS IN THIS BLOODY STREET.
>>> STORM FRONT.
VIOLENT WEATHER ROLLING ACROSS
AMERICA RIGHT BEFORE THE BIG
MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND, AND A
WORRISOME WARNING TONIGHT ABOUT
THE COMING HURRICANE SEASON.
>>> SKYFALL.
IMAGINE THIS, A PLANE FLYING
OVER YOUR HOUSE WHEN PIECES
BREAK UP AND CRASH RIGHT THROUGH
YOUR ROOF.
WHAT IS HAPPENING UP IN THE SKY
TONIGHT?
>>> AND TWIN CITY.
24 SETS OF TWINS, NOT ONLY IN
THE SAME TOWN, THE SAME SCHOOL,
BUT IN THE SAME GRADE.
HOW THEY ARE MAKING HISTORY
TONIGHT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
WE BEGIN WITH NEW DETAILS AND
NEW FOOTAGE OF THAT TRULY
HORRIFYING TERROR ATTACK.
A YOUNG WAR VETERAN BEHEADED IN
THE STREETS OF LONDON, A CITY
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS VISIT
EVERY YEAR.
HERE IT IS, THE NEW VIDEO,
SHOWING THE CHAOS AS POLICE MOVE
IN TO RESTRAIN THE SUSPECTS.
ALSO TONIGHT, WE HAVE LEARNED
THE IDENTITY OF THE VICTIM.
A 25-YEAR-OLD FATHER, HIS NAME
AND FACE REVEALED TODAY.
HE LOOKS SO YOUNG.
AND THERE ARE NEW DETAILS ON THE
HEROES OF THIS CRISIS.
WOMEN WHOSE WORDS, PRAYERS, AND
ACTION SENT AN UNMISTAKABLE
MESSAGE --
WE WILL NOT COWER.
LAMA HASAN IS ON THE STORY.
>> Reporter: THE FINAL MOMENTS
OF THE SHOWDOWN CAPTURED ON A
CELLPHONE.
LISTEN AS EIGHT SHOTS RING OUT.
[ GUNFIRE ]
>> Reporter: POLICE GUNNING DOWN
THE TWO SUSPECTS IN THE STREET,
AFTER THEIR BRUTAL ATTACK ON
25-YEAR-OLD LEE RIGBY, AN AFGHAN
WAR VET AND FATHER OF A
2-YEAR-OLD, WHO WAS BRUTALLY
STABBED AND BEHEADED IN BROAD
DAYLIGHT.
>> THE ONLY REASON WE HAVE
KILLED THIS MAN TODAY IS BECAUSE
MUSLIMS ARE DYING DAILY BY
BRITISH SOLDIERS.
AN EYE FOR AN EYE AND A TOOTH
FOR A TOOTH.
>> Reporter: TODAY NEW DETAILS
EMERGING.
THE MAN COVERED IN BLOOD IN THE
VIDEO IS BELIEVED TO BE A
BRITISH MAN OF NIGERIAN DESCENT,
MICHAEL ADEBOLAJO, A CHRISTIAN
CONVERT TO ISLAM.
TODAY AUTHORITIES RAIDING HOUSES
ACROSS LONDON, MAKING TWO
ARRESTS ON CHARGES OF CONSPIRACY
TO MURDER, TRYING TO DETERMINE
HOW MANY OTHERS WERE INVOLVED IN
THE PLOT.
YOU LIVE HERE?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: DID YOU HEAR WHAT
HAPPENED THIS MORNING WHEN THERE
WAS A POLICE RAID?
>> WE SAW ONE MAN -- ONE COLORED
MAN HANDCUFFED AND TWO LADIES
HANDCUFFED.
>> Reporter: WE'RE LEARNING MORE
ABOUT THE EXTRAORDINARY ACTS OF
HEROISM, THE CUB SCOUT LEADER
STANDING IN THE FACE OF TERROR,
TALKING DOWN ONE OF THE
ATTACKERS WHO TOLD HER HE WAS
STARTING A WAR IN LONDON.
DEFIANTLY, HER REPLY, YOU ARE
GOING TO LOSE.
IT IS YOU VERSUS MANY.
A SECOND PRAYING OVER THE BODY
OF THE MURDERED SOLDIER WITH THE
SUSPECT STILL THERE.
INVESTIGATORS REVEALING THAT
BOTH SUSPECTS DIRECTLY INVOLVED
IN THE ATTACK WERE KNOWN TO LAW
ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES, MONITORING
EXTREMISTS, BUT HAD DONE NOTHING
TO WARRANT AN ARREST.
>> THE ATTACKS IN BOTH BOSTON
AND LONDON, DEMONSTRATE
SOMETHING THAT AUTHORITIES HAVE
LONG FEARED, WHICH IS SMALL
CELLS OF ONE OR TWO PEOPLE,
SELF-RADICALIZED, SOMETHING THAT
AUTHORITIES FIND IT VERY
DIFFICULT TO DETECT AND VERY
DIFFICULT TO STOP.
>> Reporter: WHILE TONIGHT THE
TWO SUSPECTS REMAIN UNDER ARMED
GUARD RECOVERING FROM GUNSHOT
WOUNDS IN SEPARATE LONDON
HOSPITALS, THEIR CONDITION IS
SAID TO BE NOT LIFE-THREATENING.
DAN?
>> LAMA, THANK YOU.
AGAIN, THE ACTIONS OF THOSE
WOMEN, SO BRAVE.
>>> THIS NEWS OUT OF LONDON
COMING ON A DAY WHEN PRESIDENT
OBAMA REDEFINED AMERICA'S WAR ON
TERROR.
DELIVERING A MAJOR SPEECH,
CAUSING FIREWORKS RIGHT THERE IN
THE ROOM.
HERE'S ABC'S JONATHAN KARL.
>> Reporter: IT'S A SECRET WAR,
UNMANNED AIRCRAFT OPERATED OUT
OF NONDESCRIPT ROOMS, TRACKING
SUSPECTED TERRORISTS, FIRING ON
TARGETS HALF A WORLD AWAY.
NOT A VIDEO GAME, THIS IS
DEADLY.
BY MOST ESTIMATES, KILLING MORE
THAN 2,000 PEOPLE SINCE BARACK
OBAMA BECAME PRESIDENT.
UNDER CRITICISM THIS IS A SECRET
WAR WITH NO ACCOUNTABILITY, THE
PRESIDENT NOW WANTS TO TAKE IT
OUT OF THE SHADOWS, AND IS
CALLING FOR NEW LIMITS, EVEN
SAYING THE WAR ON TERROR MUST
EVENTUALLY END.
>> THIS WAR, LIKE ALL WARS, MUST
END.
THAT'S WHAT HISTORY ADVISES.
THAT'S WHAT OUR DEMOCRACY
DEMANDS.
>> Reporter: IN THE MEANTIME,
STRICT RULES ON THE USE OF
DRONES.
NOW ONLY TO BE USED ON TARGETS
POSING AN IMMINENT AND ONGOING
THREAT TO THE U.S., AND ONLY
WHEN THERE IS NEAR CERTAINTY NO
CIVILIANS WILL BE HURT OR
KILLED, AND THEY ARE NEVER TO BE
USED TO PUNISH TERRORISTS FOR
PAST ATTACKS.
AS FOR THE CONTROVERSIAL
TARGETING OF AMERICAN CITIZENS
TURNED TERRORISTS --
>> I DO NOT BELIEVE IT WOULD BE
CONSTITUTIONAL FOR THE
GOVERNMENT TO TARGET AND KILL
ANY U.S. CITIZEN, WITH A DRONE
OR WITH A SHOTGUN, WITHOUT DUE
PROCESS.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT ONCE
AGAIN MADE THE CASE FOR CLOSING
THE PRISON AT GUANTANAMO BAY.
AT ONE POINT A PROTESTER TRIED
TO SHOUT HIM DOWN.
>> WHY WAS HE KILLED?
>> LET ME FINISH, MA'AM.
THIS IS PART OF FREE SPEECH, YOU
BEING ABLE TO SPEAK, BUT ALSO
YOU LISTENING AND ME BEING ABLE
TO SPEAK.
>> Reporter: SHE INTERRUPTED HIM
THREE SEPARATE TIMES.
>> IT'S OUT OF THE HANDS OF THE
CIA.
>> I'M WILLING TO CUT THE YOUNG
LADY WHO INTERRUPTED ME SOME
SLACK, BECAUSE IT'S WORTH BEING
PASSIONATE ABOUT.
>> JON, THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN
TALKING ABOUT CLOSING GITMO FOR
YEARS NOW.
WHAT ARE THE ODDS HE CAN GET IT
DONE THIS TIME?
>> DAN, ONE THING HE SAID, HE'S
GOING TO SPEED UP THE TRANSFER
OF SOME OF THE DETAINEES BACK TO
THEIR HOME COUNTRIES.
BUT TO CLOSE GUANTANAMO HE NEEDS
CONGRESS TO GET IT DONE.
TO TRY TO APPEAL TO SOME OF
THOSE REPUBLICANS, THOSE
CONSERVATIVES, HE'S TALKING
ABOUT HOW EXPENSIVE IT IS, 166
DETAINEES THERE, THE COST, A
MILLION DOLLARS A YEAR TO KEEP
THEM THERE.
HE'S MAKING THE CASE IT'S JUST
TOO EXPENSIVE.
>> JON KARL, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO BIG NEWS FOR FAMILIES
ACROSS THIS COUNTRY.
A BIG VOTE TONIGHT AT THE BOY
SCOUTS.
THEY'VE DECIDED TO OVERTURN
THEIR BAN ON GAY SCOUTS, A BAN
THAT'S BEEN IN PLACE FOR 103
YEARS.
ABC'S DAVID KERLEY ON THIS MAJOR
CHANGE FOR AN AMERICAN
INSTITUTION.
>> Reporter: VOTING IN TEXAS
WITH SUPPORTERS AND CRITICS
OUTSIDE, THE BOY SCOUTS NATIONAL
COUNCIL'S HISTORIC MOVE MATCHES
THE COUNTRY'S EVOLVING VIEW ON
GAY RIGHTS.
FOR MORE THAN A CENTURY,
MILLIONS OF BOYS HAVE LEARNED
OUTDOOR AND LEADERSHIP SKILLS AS
PART OF SCOUTING.
BUT GAY MEMBERS HAVE ALWAYS BEEN
BANNED.
PASCAL TESSIER OF MARYLAND, A
SCOUT FOR NEARLY A DECADE,
ANNOUNCED HE WAS GAY AND WAS
TOLD HE WOULD NOT BE ABLE TO
EARN THE HIGHEST RANK --
UNTIL TONIGHT.
>> IT'S ACTUALLY GREAT.
THEY ARE FINALLY TAKING A STEP
IN THE RIGHT DIRECTION, WITH
ALLOWING GAY YOUTH INTO BOY
SCOUTS.
>> Reporter: SOME PARENTS OF
SCOUTS ARE DISMAYED.
>> WE'LL BE REQUIRED TO TEACH
HOMOSEXUALITY TO YOUNG BOYS AS
YOUNG AS 6 AND AS OLD AS 17.
>> Reporter: THE SCOUTS DENY
THAT WILL BE THE CASE.
BUT THIS REPEAL COULD MEAN THE
LOSS OF SOME SPONSORSHIPS.
AND BY ONE ESTIMATE, UP TO ONE
IN TEN SCOUTS COULD LEAVE THE
PROGRAM.
WHILE THE BAN IS LIFTED TONIGHT
ON SCOUTS, GAY LEADERS ARE STILL
BANNED.
THE BATTLE IS NOT OVER.
DAVID KERLEY, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>> DAVID, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE'S SEVERE WEATHER
MOVING ACROSS AMERICA, HEADING
INTO THE MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND.
HAIL IN THE HEARTLAND, SEVERE
STORMS IN THE EAST, FAMILIES
HOPING FOR A HOLIDAY GET-AWAY
ARE IN FOR A SOGGY SLOG.
ABC'S METEOROLOGIST, GINGER ZEE,
IS TRACKING IT ALL.
>> Reporter: LIKE CLOCKWORK, AS
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS PREPARE TO
HIT THE ROADS AND THE AIRPORTS
THIS HOLIDAY WEEKEND, THE
OMINOUS WEATHER ROLLS IN.
FROM FLASH FLOODS IN NEW YORK,
TO DANGEROUS WINDS IN CHICAGO,
AND THE MISERABLE CONDITIONS
HOVERING OVER TORNADO-SHATTERED
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
SKIES ARE FAR FROM CLEAR, AND
NEITHER ARE THE NATION'S
AIRPORTS.
DELAYS AND CANCELLATIONS,
ESPECIALLY IN THE NORTHEAST,
WHERE SOME FLIGHTS INBOUND TO
NEW YORK, DELAYED MORE THAN FOUR
HOURS.
THE STRANDED INCLUDE ALEX AND
ANDI CHAMBERS, TRYING TO GET TO
NEWARK FROM AUSTIN.
>> WE ARE STUCK IN AUSTIN,
STILL.
THE FLIGHT IS DELAYED THREE
HOURS.
>> Reporter: AND THIS LITTLE GUY
IN CHICAGO, NOT HAPPY AT ALL
WITH HIS THREE-HOUR DELAY.
AMIDST THESE WEATHER WOES, NEW
PREDICTIONS TODAY ABOUT THE
COMING HURRICANE SEASON.
IT STARTS JUNE 1.
FEDERAL FORECASTERS SAY IT'S
GOING TO BE ACTIVE.
THEY EXPECT THREE TO SIX MAJOR
ATLANTIC HURRICANES, BUT
REMEMBER, THAT DOESN'T MEAN THEY
ALL NECESSARILY MAKE LANDFALL.
EITHER WAY, IT'S TOO SOON FOR
MOST FOLKS ALONG THE EAST COAST,
STILL REBUILDING, POST HURRICANE
SANDY.
LOOK AT THIS.
TIME LAPSED VIDEO OF THE SEASIDE
HEIGHTS BOARDWALK IN NEW JERSEY,
ALL SET TO OPEN FOR MEMORIAL
DAY.
>> AND GINGER JOINS US NOW.
GINGER, TAKE US THROUGH THE
FORECAST FOR THE BIG WEEKEND.
>> IT'S A SOGGY MEMORIAL DAY FOR
THE JERSEY COAST AND A LOT OF
OTHER FOLKS IN THE NORTHEAST.
THIS TAKES US THROUGH NOT ONLY
TONIGHT WHICH WILL BE POTENTIAL
FOR SOME SEVERE STORMS IN THE
NORTHEAST, BUT ALSO THROUGH
TOMORROW AND SATURDAY, VERY
SOGGY.
DON'T GET AWAY FROM IT EVEN IF
YOU'RE IN THE MID PART OF THE
COUNTRY OR THE FAR EAST.
-- FAR NORTHWEST.
IF YOU WANT SUNSHINE AND HEAT,
GOT TO GO SOUTHWEST OR
SOUTHEAST.
>> JUST TO UNDERSCORE SOMETHING
YOU SAID IN YOUR PIECE.
JUST BECAUSE WE'LL SEE A
HYPERACTIVE HURRICANE SEASON,
DOESN'T MEAN THOSE STORMS WILL
HIT LAND.
>> THEY COULD, THEY COULD NOT.
NOAA DOESN'T PREDICT WHETHER OR
NOT THEY'LL MAKE LANDFALL.
JUST SAY IT'S GOING TO BE AN
ACTIVE SEASON.
SO MANY OF THEM COULD STAY OUT
TO SEA.
EVEN THOUGH WE HAVE A LET OF
HURRICANES HAPPENING.
>> AN IMPORTANT BIT OF CONTEXT
FROM GINGER ZEE.
THANK YOU.
>>> AND IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA,
TODAY, THE FIRST FUNERALS FOR
THE PEOPLE KILLED BY THAT EF-5
TORNADO AND ON WHAT WOULD HAVE
BEEN THE LAST DAY OF SCHOOL,
SOME TEACHERS RETURNED TO THE
SCENE OF SO MUCH HORROR THREE
DAYS AFTER THAT DIRECT HIT
TWISTER OUTBREAK.
ABC'S BYRON PITTS IS THERE
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: HI, VERY GOOD TO
SEE YOU.
KINDERGARTEN TEACHER JENNIFER
SIMONS ARRIVED BACK AT PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY LATE TODAY FOR
THE FIRST TIME SINCE MONDAY'S
TORNADO.
HERE, WHERE SEVEN CHILDREN DIED,
HER SIX STUDENTS LIVED.
SHIELDED BENEATH HER BODY WHEN
AN SUV CRASHED THROUGH THE
CEILING OF HER CLASSROOM.
>> I JUST COVERED MY BABIES.
I TRIED TO SAVE THEM.
IT CRUSHED MY ARM, BUT I'M OKAY
WITH THAT.
>> Reporter: THE NIGHTMARE SHE
ENDURED AND THE BRAVERY SHE
DISPLAYED, CAUGHT ON TAPE AT
BRIARWOOD WHERE OTHER TEACHERS
BATTLED DARKNESS, FEAR, FALLING
DEBRIS, AND PROTECTED CHILDREN.
[ SHOUTING AND CHAOS ]
TODAY MANY PARENTS EXPRESSED
THEIR GRATITUDE, AN ASSEMBLY FOR
ALL THE TEACHERS AND STUDENTS ON
WHAT SHOULD HAVE BEEN THE LAST
DAY OF SCHOOL.
>> SHE SHIELDED WITH HER OWN
BODY TO PROTECT MY DAUGHTER.
YOU KNOW THAT, I'M NEVER GOING
TO HAVE ANY WORDS TO REPAY HER
FOR WHAT SHE DID.
>> Reporter: THE FIRST OF 24
FUNERALS.
9-YEAR-OLD ANTONIA CANDELARIA
WAS LAID TO REST DURING A
VIOLENT THUNDERSTORM.
PARENTS LIKE ED KELLEY WRESTLE
WITH SURVIVOR'S GUILT.
>> I FEEL FORTUNATE, BUT IT
HURTS.
WHAT DO YOU SAY TO THOSE
PARENTS?
THEY DIDN'T GET TO BRING THEIR
KIDS HOME.
>> Reporter: ASHLYN AND THE
OTHERS WERE GIVEN BACKPACKS WITH
GOODIES FOR THE SUMMER.
HER SADNESS, HIDDEN BEHIND A
SMILE.
>> THREE OF MY FRIENDS HAD
SIBLINGS THAT DIED.
AND NONE OF THEM WERE THERE.
AND I REALLY WISH THEY WERE
THERE BECAUSE I WOULD LIKE TO
SEE THEM.
>> Reporter: AS FOR KINDERGARTEN
TEACHER JENNIFER SIMONS, JUST
HER SECOND YEAR IN THE
CLASSROOM, HER RIGHT ARM CRUSHED
BY THE TORNADO.
>> I DON'T THINK I'M A HERO.
I THINK IT'S WHAT ANYBODY WOULD
DO.
>> Reporter: A STORM COULD STEAL
HER SCHOOL, JENNIFER TOLD US,
NOT HER SPIRIT.
SHE'LL BE BACK IN THE CLASSROOM
NEXT FALL.
BYRON PITTS, ABC NEWS, MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
>> ANOTHER DIFFICULT DAY IN
MOORE.
>>> COMING UP HERE ON "WORLD
NEWS," YOU WILL NOT BELIEVE
THESE PICTURES.
THIS IS A PART OF A WING FROM A
747.
WHAT'S IT DOING ON THE FLOOR OF
A HOUSE?
A MYSTERIOUS DANGER IN THE SKY
AND ON THE GROUND, UP NEXT.
[ Female Announcer ] LOVE.
IT'S THE MOST POWERFUL THING
ON THE PLANET.
LOVE HOLDS US IN THE BEGINNING.
COMFORTS US AS WE GROW OLD.
LOVE IS THE REASON YOU CARE.
FOR ALL THE THINGS
IN YOUR LIFE...
THAT MAKE LIFE WORTH LIVING.
♪
♪ SWEET LOVE OF MINE
AS YOUR LIFE CHANGES,
FIDELITY IS THERE
FOR YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY,
HELPING YOU READJUST
ALONG THE WAY,
REFOCUS AS CAREERS CHANGE
AND KIDS HEAD OFF TO COLLEGE,
AND REVISIT YOUR INVESTMENTS
AS RETIREMENT GETS CLOSER.
WHEREVER YOU ARE TODAY,
FIDELITY'S GUIDANCE
CAN HELP YOU
FINE-TUNE
YOUR PERSONAL ECONOMY.
START TODAY WITH A FREE
ONE-ON-ONE REVIEW
OF YOUR RETIREMENT PLAN.
I WORKED A PATROL UNIT FOR 17
YEARS IN THE CITY OF BALTIMORE.
WHEN I FIRST STARTED
EXPERIENCING THE PAIN,
IT'S HARD TO DESCRIBE
BECAUSE YOU HAVE A NUMBNESS
BUT YET YOU HAVE THE PAIN
LIKE THOUSANDS OF NEEDLES
STICKING IN YOUR FOOT.
IT WAS PROGRESSIVELY
GETTING WORSE,
AND AT THAT POINT,
I KNEW I HAD TO DO SOMETHING.
WHEN I WENT BACK
TO MY HEALTH CARE PROFESSIONAL,
THAT'S WHEN SHE SUGGESTED
THE LYRICA.
ONCE I STARTED
TAKING THE LYRICA,
THE PAIN STARTED SUBSIDING.
[ Male Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYE SIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN, AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS, AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO'VE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
TO HEAR MORE OF TERRY'S STORY,
VISIT LYRICA.COM.
>>> TONIGHT, A MYSTERY IN THE
SKY.
WHAT IF YOU WERE SITTING IN YOUR
HOUSE ONE DAY AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN PART OF A JET CAME
CRASHING THROUGH YOUR ROOF?
INVESTIGATORS ARE NOW TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT HOW AND WHY THAT
EXACT SCENARIO PLAYED OUT IN
GEORGIA.
AN ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI IS ON
THE STORY.
>> Reporter: PAMELA WARE SAYS
SHE COULD HAVE DIED.
>> IF IT HAD LANDED IN HERE,
BECAUSE THAT'S JUST SHEET ROCK,
IT WOULD -- OH, BOY, I WOULDN'T
BE NO GOOD.
>> Reporter: SHE WAS WATCHING
TELEVISION IN HER BEDROOM WHEN
ALL OF A SUDDEN A HEAVY PIECE OF
AN AIRPLANE'S WING CAME BUSTING
THROUGH HER GEORGIA HOME AND
BOUNCED THROUGH THE HOUSE.
HERE'S WHAT THE PIECE LOOKS LIKE
COMPARED TO THE SIZE OF A DOOR.
>> IT'S JUST AUTOMATIC BECAUSE,
NOT THAT IT'S GOING TO STOP IT
IF IT HITS ME, BUT, YEAH, IT'S
JUST REACTION.
>> Reporter: THIS PLANE WAS
DROPPING PARTS FOR MORE THAN
FOUR MILES ABOVE NEIGHBORHOODS,
OUT OF THE SKY.
CHINA AIRLINES, 5254, A 747
CARGO PLANE WAS ABOUT TO LAND
SUNDAY AFTERNOON AT ATLANTA'S
INTERNATIONAL AIRPORT, WHEN ITS
RIGHT WING FLAP SUDDENLY BROKE
INTO TWO PIECES.
WITNESSES SAY A 20-FOOT CHUNK
LANDED IN THE PARKING LOT OF A
WALMART BEFORE THE PLANE LANDED
SUCCESSFULLY.
>> IN THE PAST, INVESTIGATIONS
HAVE REVEALED IT COULD BE A
MAINTENANCE ISSUE, OR COULD BE A
FATIGUE ISSUE, OR SOMETHING THAT
WAS OVERLOOKED, SUCH AS A LATCH
OR A COWLING WAS NOT SECURE
BEFORE TAKEOFF, OR SOMETHING OF
THAT NATURE.
>> Reporter: AS PLANES GET OLDER
EXPERTS EXPECT THIS TO HAPPEN.
LAST FALL, A REFRIGERATOR-SIZED
AIRPLANE DOOR FELL INTO A
SEATTLE SUBURB.
LAST SUMMER, DAGGER-SIZED PIECES
OF AN AIR CANADA JET THAT
CRASHED THROUGH CARS.
FEDERAL INVESTIGATORS IN ATLANTA
HAVE TORN THIS PLANE APART,
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT WHAT WENT
WRONG.
>> I KEEP THINKING WHAT COULD
HAVE HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: TODAY PAMELA SAYS
SHE CAN'T SLEEP RIGHT AND SAYS
THE AIRLINE NEEDS TO COME FIX
HER HOME.
STEVE OSUNSAMI, ABC NEWS,
ELLENWOOD, GEORGIA.
>> WE ARE GLAD SHE'S OKAY,
THOUGH.
>>> COMING UP ON THE BROADCAST,
A BIG SCARE FOR PRINCE CHARLES
AND CAMILLA.
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT IT COMING
UP IN OUR INSTANT INDEX.
AND CAMILLA.
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT IT COMING
UP IN OUR INSTANT INDEX.
CAMILLA,
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT IT IN OUR
INSTANT INDEX.
you can lie on one of those.
We provide the exact
individualization
that your body needs.
Oh, yeah!
Once you experience it
there's no going back.
Now save on the
closeout of our Classic
Special Edition bed set
just $1,299, a savings of $600
plus 36 month financing on all
beds through Memorial Day
Only at the Sleep Number store
Sleep Number,
Comfort individualized
HER LONG DAY OF PICK UPS
AND DROP OFFS
BEGINS WITH ARTHRITIS PAIN...
AND A CHOICE.
TAKE UP TO 6 TYLENOL IN A DAY
OR JUST 2 Aleve
FOR ALL DAY RELIEF.
ALL ABOARD.
♪
on my feet and exactly where
I needed more support.
Then, I got my number.
My tired, achy feet affected my
whole life.
Until I found my number.
I tried the free Dr. Scholl's
Foot Mapping Center.
In two minutes, I got my foot
map and custom number.
I'm a 440.
That matched up to the Dr.
Scholl's Custom Fit Orthotic
inserts with the right support
and cushioning I need.
I am a believer.
I'm a believer!
I'm a believer.
Go to DrScholls.com to
find your closest Walmart
with a Foot Mapping Center.
CHALKY...
NOT CHALKY.
TEMPORARY...
24 HOUR.
LOTS OF TABLETS...
ONE PILL.
YOU DECIDE.
PREVENT ACID
WITH PREVACID 24HR.
Hodoes your dog food have?s
30?
20?
New Purina ONE beyOnd has 9.
The simplified Purina ONE
beyOnd.
Learn more about these wholesome
ingredients at PurinaONE.com
SO YOU CAN CAPTURE
YOUR RECEIPTS, INK FOR
ALL BUSINESS PURCHASES.
AND MANAGE THEM
ONLINE WITH JOT,
THE LATEST APP FROM INK.
SO YOU CAN SPEND LESS
TIME DOING PAPERWORK.
AND MORE TIME DOING PAPERWORK.
INK FROM CHASE.
SO YOU CAN.
WITH THERMACARE HEATWRAPS.
THE ONLY WRAP WITH PATENTED
HEAT CELLS THAT PENETRATE DEEP
TO RELAX, SOOTHE,
AND UNLOCK TIGHT MUSCLES.
AND NOW, INTRODUCING
REUSABLE THERMACARE COLD WRAPS.
PAIN RELIEF
WITHOUT THE SHOCK OF ICE.
.
>>> OUR INSTANT INDEX BEGINS
TONIGHT WITH A CLOSE CALL FOR
PRINCE CHARLES AND CAMILLA.
THIS IS WHAT ROYALS LOOK LIKE
WHEN THEY'RE A LITTLE BIT
FRAZZLED.
HERE THEY ARE AFTER THEIR
HELICOPTER WAS FORCED TO MAKE AN
EMERGENCY LANDING FROM A
TECHNICAL FAULT.
THE PALACE DESCRIBED THE
INCIDENT AS, QUOTE, HAIRY.
THE TWO LATER ARRIVED AT THEIR
FESTIVAL BY CAR, EMBODYING THE
MOTTO, KEEP CALM AND CARRY ON.
>>> NOW TO A BIG SIDE OF BEING
THE AMERICAN PRESIDENT.
WHEN YOU ARE CHIEF EXECUTIVE,
PICTURES LIKE THIS TEND TO LEAK.
YOU ARE LOOKING AT SHOTS FROM
BARACK OBAMA'S SENIOR PROM,
CIRCA 1979.
THAT'S HIS DATE THERE IN THE
BLUE DRESS.
THESE PICTURES WERE RELEASED
EXCLUSIVELY BY "TIME" MAGAZINE,
ALONG WITH THIS INSCRIPTION IN
THE YEARBOOK.
PRESIDENT OBAMA CALLING ONE OF
THE WOMEN IN THAT PICTURE SWEET
AND FOXY, ADDING, YOU EVEN LAUGH
AT MY JOKES.
IN THE SPIRIT OF EQUAL TIME,
HERE'S A PICTURE OF THE FIRST
LADY'S PROM.
WE ALL HAVE OUR AWKWARD TEENAGE
PHOTOS.
>>> AND FOUR AMERICANS ON A TRIP
TO ICELAND HAD AN INTERESTING
IDEA.
ICELAND IS KNOWN FOR ITS ICY
LAGOONS.
SO WHY NOT HAVE A PICNIC AND
TAKE IN THE SCENERY?
TROUBLE IS, THIS HAPPENED.
THEY WERE STRANDED 32 FEET OFF
SHORE, SETTING UP A TABLE AND
CHAIRS ON THE ICE WHEN A GUST OF
WIND SET THEM ADRIFT.
THE TITANIC OF SUNDAY SUP ERDS.
ONE OF THEM JUMPED TO SHORE IN
TIME TO CALL THE ICELANDIC
EQUIVALENT OF 911.
BY THE TIME THE RESCUERS
ARRIVED, THEY HAD FINISHED THEIR
MEAL.
I AGREE WITH THEIR PRIORITY.
>>> COMING UP ON THE BROADCAST,
LOOK WHAT WE FOUND.
24 SETS OF TWINS, SAME TOWN,
SAME SCHOOL, SAME GRADE EVEN,
AND TONIGHT HOW THEY'RE MAKING
HISTORY.
GRADE, EVEN,
AND TONIGHT HOW THEY'RE MAKING
HISTORY.
MAKING
If you've got it, you know how
hard it can be to breathe
and man, you know
how that feels.
COPD includes emphysema
and chronic bronchitis.
SPIRIVA is a once-daily inhaled
COPD maintenance treatment
that helps open my obstructed
airways for a full 24 hours.
You know, SPIRIVA helps
me breathe easier.
SPIRIVA HandiHaler Tiotropium
Bromide Inhalation Powder
does not replace fast-acting
inhalers for sudden symptoms.
Tell your doctor if you
have kidney problems,
glaucoma, trouble urinating,
or an enlarged prostate.
These may worsen with SPIRIVA.
Discuss all medicines you
take, even eye drops.
Stop taking SPIRIVA and seek
immediate medical help
if your breathing
suddenly worsens,
your throat or tongue swells,
you get hives, vision changes
or eye pain, or problems
passing urine.
Other side effects include
dry mouth and constipation.
Nothing can reverse COPD.
SPIRIVA helps me
breathe better.
Does breathing with
COPD weigh you down?
Don't wait to ask your
doctor about SPIRIVA.
HOW OLD IS THE OLDEST PERSON
YOU'VE KNOWN?
WE GAVE PEOPLE A STICKER
AND HAD THEM SHOW US.
WE LEARNED A LOT OF US
HAVE KNOWN SOMEONE
WHO'S LIVED WELL INTO THEIR 90S.
AND THAT'S A GREAT THING.
BUT EVEN THOUGH
WE'RE LIVING LONGER,
ONE THING
THAT HASN'T CHANGED MUCH
IS THE OFFICIAL RETIREMENT AGE.
♪
THE QUESTION IS HOW DO YOU MAKE
SURE YOU HAVE THE MONEY YOU NEED
TO ENJOY ALL OF THESE YEARS.
♪
THE MIDDLE
OF THIS SPECIAL MOMENT
AND I NEED TO RUN OFF
TO THE BATHROOM.
♪
I'M FED UP WITH ALWAYS HAVING TO
PUT MY BLADDER'S NEEDS
AHEAD OF MY DAUGHTER.
♪
SO TODAY, I'M FINALLY
TALKING TO MY DOCTOR
ABOUT
OVERACTIVE BLADDER SYMPTOMS.
[ Female Announcer ]
KNOW THAT GOTTA GO FEELING?
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT PRESCRIPTION TOVIAZ.
ONE TOVIAZ PILL A DAY
SIGNIFICANTLY REDUCES
[ Female Announcer ]
KNOW THAT GOTTA GO FEELING?
SUDDEN URGES AND ACCIDENTS,
FOR 24 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE CERTAIN
STOMACH PROBLEMS OR GLAUCOMA,
OR CAN NOT EMPTY YOUR BLADDER,
YOU SHOULD NOT TAKE TOVIAZ.
GET EMERGENCY MEDICAL HELP
RIGHT AWAY
IF YOUR FACE, LIPS,
THROAT OR TONGUE SWELLS.
TOVIAZ CAN CAUSE
BLURRED VISION,
DIZZINESS, DROWSINESS
AND DECREASED SWEATING.
DO NOT DRIVE, OPERATE MACHINERY
OR DO UNSAFE TASKS
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW TOVIAZ AFFECTS YOU.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
ARE DRY MOUTH AND CONSTIPATION.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT TOVIAZ.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, TAKE A
MOMENT AND TRY TO THINK OF HOW
MANY SETS OF TWINS YOU KNOW?
THREE, FIVE, MAYBE TEN.
WHATEVER THE NUMBER IS, BEAR IT
IN MIND AS WE SHOW YOU WHAT WE
FOUND TODAY.
AT A MIDDLE SCHOOL OUTSIDE OF
CHICAGO.
THERE ARE THE BECKERS, THE
THOMASES, THE PICKETS, THE
RAMSEYS, THE HOMEBURGS, THE
MURKS, AND SOME.
AN ASTONISHING 24 SETS OF TWINS
ALL IN THE FIFTH GRADE IN THE
HIGHCREST MIDDLE SCHOOL IN
WILMETTE, ILLINOIS.
>> HELLO, "WORLD NEWS"!
>> Reporter: AS YOU MAY HAVE
NOTICED, MOST OF THEM ARE
FRATERNAL.
THERE ARE TWO SETS OF IDENTICAL.
BUT THIS STORY REALLY STARTS
WITH THESE TWINS, RYAN AND LUKE
NOVACEL.
THEY WERE THUMBING THROUGH THE
GUINNESS BOOK OF WORLD RECORDS
AND SAW THAT THE RECORD FOR MOST
TWINS IN A SINGLE CLASS, 16, IS
HELD BY A HIGH SCHOOL IN IOWA.
>> WOW, I THINK WE MIGHT HAVE A
WORLD RECORD.
>> Reporter: THEY CALLED
GUINNESS WHO HAVE ASKED FOR
DOCUMENTATION, INCLUDING BIRTH
CERTIFICATES AND A GROUP
PICTURE.
>> IT WAS PURE EXCITEMENT.
WHAT KID DOESN'T WANT TO BE IN
THE GUINNESS BOOK OF WORLD
RECORDS?
>> Reporter: TWINS HAVE LONG
THE SOURCE
THE SUBJECT OF VIRAL VIDEO, LIKE
THESE TWO BOYS, DEBATING NUCLEAR
THERMAL DYNAMICS IN THEIR OWN
SECRET LANGUAGE.
[ BABY JABBER ]
>> Reporter: THERE IS NO SCIENCE
TO SUGGEST TWINS HAVE ESP OR
ANYTHING LIKE THAT, BUT RESEARCH
DOES CONFIRM THEY HAVE POWERFUL
BONDS.
>> IT'S NICE TO KNOW THERE'S
SOMEONE OUT THERE WHO IS EXACTLY
LIKE YOU.
>> Reporter: IN THE PAST 30
YEARS, THERE'S BEEN A 75%
INCREASE IN TWINS, DRIVEN BY
FERTILITY TREATMENTS WHICH
INCREASE THE ODDS OF MULTIPLE
BIRTHS.
>> I THINK IT'S REALLY COOL
THERE'S SO MANY TWINS.
>> Reporter: DOCTORS ARE GETTING
BETTER AT ENSURING SINGLE
PREGNANCIES, SO THE TWIN RATE
IS LIKELY TO DROP.
WHICH MEANS THE KIDS HERE COULD
HOLD THE WORLD RECORD FOR A LONG
TIME.
>> VERY CUTE.
THEY'RE AWAITING THEIR OFFICIAL
RULING FROM THE PEOPLE AT
GUINNESS.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
WE'RE ALWAYS WORKING FOR YOU
ONLINE AT ABCNEWS.COM.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
>>> TONIGHT AMERICA'S CUP
RETURNED TO THE BAY UNDER A
CLOUD OF SAFETY CONCERNS CAN
THEY AGREE ON A SET OF RACING
RESTRICTIONS?
>> ONLY ON ABC 7 NEWS A
SURPRISE INSPECTION OF SAN
FRANCISCO'S GARBAGE TRUCK
FLEET AS WE LOOK INTO THE
COMPANY'S HISTORY OF
ACCIDENTS.
>> CRUISE PREPARE FR A MAJOR
REDO OF THEIR WORK ON THE NEW
BAY BRIDGE.
THE HE FIX NOW UNDERWAY.
>> FORGET WHAT YOU'VE HEARD
ABOUT OAKLAND.
IT'S AMONG THE TOP CITIES IN
THE COUNTRY FOR SOMETHING
OTHER THAN CRIME.
>> LET THE RACING RESUME.
TONIGHT DEFENDING CHAMPIONS
RETURNED TO THE BAY FOR THE
FIRST TIME SINCE THE FATAL
CATAMARAN CRASH.
>> GOOD EVENING.
>> FOR THE FIRST TIME EVER WE
SAW THREE 72 FOOT CATAMARANS
ON SAN FRANCISCO BAY OUT
PRACTICING JUST ONE DAY AFTER
DOZENS OF NEW RECOMMENDATIONS
WERE PROPOSED.
MARK MATTHEWS IS LIVE ALONG
THE EMBARK DARE CROW WITH THE
CHANGES.
MARK?
>> WE'RE OUTSIDE THE CITY
FRONT COMPOUND FOR ITALIAN
TEAM, LUNA ROSA AND NEW
ZEALAND TEAM.
ACTION STOD OUT THERE ON THE
BAY.
>> BEYOND THE GOLDEN GATE, THE
TEAM NEW ZEALAND JUST DID GET
UP HYDROPLAINING ON THE FOIL.
THE U.S. ORACLE TEAM REACH ADD
CROSS THE BAY GIVING AN IDEA
OF WHAT IS COMING UP THIS
SUMMER.
>> IT'S GREAT FOR THE CITY.
AND IT'S A BEAUTIFUL VENUE
FOR.
>> IT AN EXCITING EVENT TO
HAVE THAT CLOSE TO SHORE.
>> TODAY IS THE FIRST DAY OF
TEAMS HAVE BEEN OUT PRACTICING
SINCE ANNOUNCEMENT OF NEW
SAFETY RECOMMENDATIONS
FOLLOWING MAY 9th ACCIDENT
THAT TOOK THE LIFE OF ARTEMIS
TEAM'S STRATEGIST.
THE TEAMS APPEARED TO HAVE
THAT GEAR ALREADY.
BIGGEST CHANGE APPEARS TO BE A
MAXIMUM RELIABLE WIND SPEED.
THE MANAGING DIRECT SWRERZ THE
REACTION TO THE
RECOMMENDATIONS HAS BEEN GOOD.
>> SOMETHING HAPPENED AND
ARTEMIS WAS A TRAGEDY.
WE NEED TO SEE THE