FOR DREW AND RICK, THANKS FOR
INVITING US INTO YOUR HOMES.
SEE YOU BACK AT 6:00.
>>> WELCOME TO "WORLD NEWS
TONIGHT."
HOLY WEEK TERROR.
THE TWIN PALM SUNDAY ATTACKS
CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
SUICIDE BOMBERS TARGETING
CHRISTIAN CHURCHES ONE WEEK
BEFORE EASTER.
MORE THAN 40 KILLED.
ISIS CLAIMING RESPONSIBILITY,
VOWING MORE ATTACKS.
>>> SHOWDOWN WITH RUSSIA.
THE CRITICAL TEST FOR THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.
RUSSIA FURIOUS WITH THE U.S.
STRIKE ON SYRIA.
ACCUSATIONS THAT AMERICA CROSSED
RED LINES, AS OUR SECRETARY OF
STATE HEADS TO MOSCOW.
>>> HOT ZONE.
THOUSANDS OF ACRES BURNED AS NEW
BRUSH FIRES FLARE ACROSS
FLORIDA.
A GIRL SCOUT CAMP CLEARED OUT.
RESIDENTS FORCED TO EVACUATE.
>>> THE DEADLY SHOOTING INSIDE A
BUSY GYM.
A TRAINER FIRED FROM HIS JOB,
RETURNING WITH A GUN.
THREE PEOPLE DEAD.
TONIGHT, WHY AUTHORITIES SAY HE
MAY HAVE SNAPPED.
>>> AND, TO THE RESCUE.
THE DOG OWNER WHO WENT ALL-OUT,
EVEN RISKING HIS OWN LIFE, TO
SAVE HIS DEAR PET.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US ON THIS
SUNDAY.
I'M TOM LLAMAS.
AND WE BEGIN WITH A PAIR OF
SUICIDE BLASTS TARGETING
CHRISTIANS AT THE START OF HOLY
WEEK.
ONE OF THE ATTACKERS SEEN ON
SURVEILLANCE, DETONATING A
SUICIDE VEST AT A METAL DETECTOR
JUST OUTSIDE A CHRISTIAN CHURCH
IN HISTORIC ALEXANDRIA.
HOURS EARLIER, CHAOS IN THE CITY
OF TANTA, THE EXPLOSIVES TEARING
THROUGH A CHURCH.
THE AFTERMATH AT BOTH SCENES
CHILLING.
AT LEAST 44 KILLED, AND MORE
THAN 125 INJURED IN THE TWIN
BOMBINGS.
TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE
RESPONDING AS ISIS CLAIMS
RESPONSIBILITY.
ALEX MARQUARDT REPORTING TONIGHT
FROM THE REGION.
>> Reporter: ON ONE OF THE
HOLIEST DAYS OF THE YEAR, THIS
MASSIVE BLAST KILLING AT LEAST
17 AT ONE OF ALEXANDRIA'S MOST
FAMOUS CATHEDRALS.
SECURITY CAMERAS CAPTURING THIS
MAN, A SUICIDE BOMBER,
APPROACHING THE COPTIC CHURCH.
TOLD TO GO TO THROUGH A METAL
DETECTOR, HE PAUSES NEXT TO TWO
POLICE OFFICERS AND DETONATES
HIS EXPLOSIVES.
THE COPTIC POPE, THE HEAD OF THE
CHURCH, HAD BEEN INSIDE, BUT
ESCAPED UNHARMED.
THAT FOLLOWED ANOTHER SUICIDE
BLAST JUST HOURS EARLIER IN THE
MIDDLE OF PALM SUNDAY MASS IN
THE CITY OF TANTA.
THE VIDEO FEED CUTTING OUT AS
CHAOS ERUPTS.
CHURCHGOERS FRANTICALLY
SEARCHING FOR SURVIVORS.
"I GOT UP, AND SAW BODIES ALL
AROUND ME," THIS MAN SAID.
"I CLIMBED ONTO THE PEWS AND GOT
OUT USING A SIDE DOOR, THEN I
HEARD SCREAMS."
ALL TOLD, AT LEAST 44 WERE
KILLED IN THE TWIN BOMBINGS AND
MORE THAN 125 WOUNDED.
ISIS SOON CLAIMED
RESPONSIBILITY, AND WARNED OF
MORE ATTACKS TO COME ON EGYPT'S
CHRISTIANS.
BLOODIED FLOORS AND SHATTERED
PEWS MIXED WITH THE SHOCK, TEARS
AND SCREAMS OF WORSHIPPERS,
GIVING WAY TO ANGER AT SECURITY
FORCES.
"THE AUTHORITIES HAVE RECEIVED
WARNINGS BEFORE THAT THE CHURCH
IS BEING TARGETED," THIS MAN
SAID.
"WHY WEREN'T PROPER MEASURES
TAKEN?"
>> AND EGYPT'S PRESIDENT SISI IS
HEARING A LOT OF CRITICISM ABOUT
NOT GUARDING AGAINST THE TERROR
THREAT.
TONIGHT, NOW DECLARING A
THREE-MONTH STATE OF EMERGENCY.
>> Reporter: RIGHT, AND THAT
LIKELY MEANS A SIGNIFICANT
CRACKDOWN, IN A COUNTRY WITH
RAMPANT HUMAN RIGHTS ABUSES.
WE UNDERSTAND THAT JUST A SHORT
TIME AGO, PRESIDENT DONALD TRUMP
DID CALL PRESIDENT SISI TO
EXPRESS HIS CONDOLENCES.
AND HIS CONFIDENCE IN THE
ABILITY OF EGYPT TO CONFRONT
TERRORISM.
TOM?
>> ALEX, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, THE WHITE
HOUSE FACING A HIGH-STAKES
GLOBAL QUESTION.
PRESIDENT TRUMP RETURNING TO THE
WHITE HOUSE FROM MAR-A-LAGO, HIS
SYRIA AIR STRIKES FRONT AND
CENTER IN THE FOREIGN POLICY
DEBATE.
INFURIATING RUSSIA AS THE
SECRETARY OF STATE PREPARES TO
TRAVEL THERE.
DAVID WRIGHT WITH THE SIMMERING
NEW TENSIONS, AND THE
THREATENING STATEMENT TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, NEW IMAGES
OF SYRIA'S RUSSIAN-MADE
FIGHTER-BOMBERS TAKING OFF FROM
THE SAME AIR BASE STRUCK BY U.S.
MISSILES.
NGSIEAS. AND RUSSIA NOW
TODAY, AN OMINOUS WARNING FROM
MILITARY COMMANDERS DEFENDING
THE ASSAD REGIME, ECHOING THE
PRESIDENT'S OWN LANGUAGE.
"THE UNITED STATES CROSSED RED
LINES BY ATTACKING SYRIA," READS
THE JOINT STATEMENT FROM RUSSIA,
IRAN AND HEZBOLLAH.
THE COMMANDERS THREATEN TO
RETALIATE AGAINST ANY FUTURE
U.S. MILITARY ACTIONS.
ADDING, "RUSSIA AND IRAN WILL
NOT ALLOW THE UNITED STATES TO
BE THE ONLY SUPERPOWER IN THE
WORLD."
THAT WARNING COMES EVEN AS U.S.
OFFICIALS WORK OUT EXACTLY WHAT
THE ADMINISTRATION HOPES TO
ACCOMPLISH IN SYRIA.
TODAY, U.N. AMBASSADOR
NIKKI HALEY SUGGESTED REGIME
CHANGE MAY NOW BE THE GOAL.
>> WE DON'T SEE A PEACEFUL SYRIA
WITH ASSAD IN THERE.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT TRUMP, IN
HIS WEEKLY ADDRESS, WAS A BIT
MORE VAGUE.
>> OUR DECISIONS WILL BE GUIDED
BY OUR VALUES AND OUR GOALS AND
WE WILL REJECT THE PATH OF
INFLEXIBLE IDEOLOGY THAT TOO
OFTEN LEADS TO UNINTENDED
CONSEQUENCES.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT HAD
HOPED FOR CLOSER COOPERATION
WITH MOSCOW.
>> IF WE HAVE A GOOD
RELATIONSHIP WITH RUSSIA,
BELIEVE ME, THAT'S A GOOD THING,
>> Reporter: BUT HIS AIRSTRIKES
IN SYRIA HAVE PUSHED THE TWO
NATIONS EVEN FARTHER APART.
THIS WEEK, SECRETARY OF STATE
REX TILLERSON HEADS TO MOSCOW
HOPING TO MEND FENCES.
BUT BRITISH FOREIGN SECRETARY
BORIS JOHNSON CANCELLED HIS
PLANNED TRIP, AT THE U.S.'
REQUEST.
THAT PROMPTED THIS WITHERING
POST ON THE RUSSIAN FOREIGN
MINISTRY'S FACEBOOK PAGE.
UNDER AN UNFLATTERING PICTURE OF
JOHNSON, THE RUSSIANS ACCUSE
BRITAIN OF "FUNDAMENTAL
INCOMPREHENSION OR IGNORANCE OF
WHAT IS HAPPENING IN SYRIA, OF
RUSSIA'S EFFORTS TO RESOLVE THAT
CRISIS, AND OF THE POINT OF
DIPLOMACY IN GENERAL."
>> THE TENSION RISING.
DAVID, THERE HAS BEEN TOUGH TALK
ON BOTH SIDES.
BUT VLADIMIR PUTIN AND PRESIDENT
TRUMP HAVE YET TO CRITICIZE EACH
OTHER.
MUCH MORE MEASURED WITH THEIR
WORDS.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
IT'S A DELICATE DANCE AT THIS
POINT.
IT'S WORTH NOTING, THE KREMLIN
HAS CLEAR GOALS WHEN IT COMES TO
SYRIA.
THEY WANT ASSAD TO REMAIN IN
POWER.
THE WHITE HOUSE, NOT SO CLEAR ON
THE ISSUE.
IT'S A DIPLOMATIC CHALLENGE FOR
SECRETARY TILLERSON AS HE HEADS
TO MOSCOW.
TOM?
>> DAVID, THANK YOU.
>>> MEANTIME, ON ANOTHER FRONT,
AN AIRCRAFT CARRIER STRIKE GROUP
HEADING TO WATERS NEAR THE
KOREAN PENINSULA.
THE REPOSITIONING COMES AFTER
FOUR MISSILE LAUNCHES BY NORTH
KOREA THIS YEAR, AND CONCERNS
THE COUNTRY COULD CONDUCT AN
UNDERGROUND NUCLEAR TEST
ANYTIME.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT TO SOME
DANGEROUS WEATHER BACK HERE AT
HOME.
TINDERBOX CONDITIONS FUELING
BRUSH FIRES ACROSS FLORIDA, THIS
BLAZE NEAR ORLANDO FORCING
PEOPLE OUT OF THEIR HOMES.
HERE'S ROB MARCIANO ON THE FIRE
THREAT THAT CONTINUES TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: SMOKE BILLOWING
ACROSS THE FLORIDA SKY TONIGHT
AS FAST-MOVING BRUSH FIRES
CONTINUE TO FLARE UP ACROSS THE
STATE.
>> THERE'S ASHES FALLING FORM
THE SKY.
IT'S TIME TO GET OUT OF HERE.
>> Reporter: LIGHTNING BELIEVED
TO HAVE CAUSED THIS 650-ACRE
BLAZE NORTH OF TAMPA.
HELICOPTERS DUMPING WATER ON THE
INFERNO, WHICH TONIGHT IS ONLY
25% CONTAINED.
JUST OUTSIDE ORLANDO, A 165-ACRE
BRUSH FIRE FORCING THE
EVACUATION OF A GIRL SCOUT CAMP.
FIREFIGHTERS BATTLING GUSTY
WINDS, FIGHTING THE BLAZE FROM
ABOVE.
>> WE'RE RECEIVING MULTIPLE
CALLS FROM GIRL SCOUT OCCUPANTS
INSIDE THE CAMPGROUND.
WE ARE ADVISING THEM TO
EVACUATE.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN
TEN STRUCTURES DESTROYED.
THIS, JUST ONE OF 20 FIRES IN
THE ORLANDO AREA ALONE THIS
WEEKEND.
>> THE SMOKE AND THE SMELL, IT'S
REALLY BAD.
>> Reporter: AND NEAR MIAMI, A
BRUSH FIRE BURNING SINCE
WEDNESDAY.
GROWING TO NEARLY 7,000 ACRES.
A LACK OF RAINFALL CREATING
MODERATE TO SEVERE DROUGHT IN
PARTS OF THE SUNSHINE STATE,
ELEVATING FIRE DANGER LEVELS.
>> AND ROB JOINS US NOW.
I'M FROM FLORIDA, I KNOW IT'S
THE DRY SEASON RIGHT NOW, BUT
THIS IS A SERIOUS DROUGHT.
>> YES, FT. MYERS, NAPLES, ONLY
WITH ABOUT A THIRD OF THE RAIN
THEY USUALLY GET THIS YEAR.
EXTENDING TO TAMPA, ORLANDO, ALL
THE WAY TO DAYTONA.
RED FLAG WARNINGS EXTENDED UNTIL
TOMORROW.
AND THE COLD FRONT MOVING TO THE
EAST.
AND TOMORROW, CHICAGO AND
DALLAS, NOT A HUGE THREAT, BUT
CERTAINLY THERE.
AND AHEAD OF THE FRONT, VERY
WARM, TEN TO 20 DEGREES ABOVE
AVERAGE.
81 IN NASHVILLE.
NEW YORK CITY, 70s AND 80, IN
PHILADELPHIA AND D.C., IT WILL
FEEL LIKE JUNE.
>> JUST LIKE SUMMER.
ROB, THANK YOU.
>>> AND STORMS EARLIER THIS WEEK
IN ATLANTA STILL CAUSING
HEADACHES FOR AIR TRAVELERS.
DELTA CANCELLING MORE THAN 100
FLIGHTS TODAY, AFTER NEARLY 300
SATURDAY AND MORE THAN 3,000
CANCELLED SINCE WEDNESDAY.
THE AIRLINE SAYING IT REMAINS IN
RECOVERY MODE.
>>> AND NEXT TONIGHT, NEW
CONCERNS ABOUT A WISCONSIN MAN.
ALREADY ACCUSED OF STEALING
WEAPONS AND SENDING A MANIFESTO
TO THE PRESIDENT.
NOW, QUESTIONS ABOUT WHO MAY
HAVE FILMED HIM, AND CONCERNS
THIS DANGEROUS SUSPECT MAY BE
TARGETING CHURCHES.
HERE'S ADRIENNE BANKERT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, AS THE
MANHUNT INTENSIFIES FOR THAT
SELF-PROCLAIMED REVOLUTIONARY,
POTENTIAL NEW SIGHTINGS.
OFFICERS STEPPING UP PATROLS AT
PLACES OF WORSHIP AFTER THEY SAY
A MAN POSSIBLY MATCHING
JOSEPH JAKUBOWSKI'S DESCRIPTION
WALKED INTO THIS CHURCH ASKING
UNUSUAL QUESTIONS.
PARISHIONERS CANCELLING PALM
SUNDAY SERVICES.
WILL YOU HAVE EXTRA PATROLS
HEADING INTO EASTER SUNDAY?
>> WE HOPE TO HAVE HIM IN
CUSTODY BEFORE EASTER SUNDAY.
>> Reporter: THE 32-YEAR-OLD ON
THE RUN SINCE TUESDAY.
AUTHORITIES SAY HE STOLE
HIGH-POWERED HANDGUNS AND HE WAS
FILMED MAILING THIS MANIFESTO TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP, DETAILING HIS
HATRED FOR POLITICIANS AND
POLICE.
>> Y'ALL HAVE NO IDEA WHAT'S
ABOUT TO HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: DEPUTIES ALSO
QUESTIONING THE MAN WHO FILMED
THAT VIDEO.
YOU HEAR HIM TALKING THROUGHOUT
THE RECORDING BUT DON'T SEE HIM.
>> REMEMBER THIS FACE.
>> GAME TIME.
>> YOU'LL NEVER FORGET THIS
FACE.
>> Reporter: THE DUO WALKING
FROM INSIDE THE POST OFFICE TO
THE MAILBOX.
AGENTS INVESTIGATING MORE THAN
400 TIPS AND RELEASING THIS
PHOTO OF JAKUBOWSKI FROM A
WISCONSIN GAS STATION.
ASKING ANYONE WHO HAS SEEN HIM
TO CALL 911.
POLICE TELL US THE MAN WHO
FILMED THAT VIDEO IS NOT BEING
HELD NOR CHARGED WITH ANY CRIME.
WE'RE TOLD HE'S COOPERATING.
>> ADRIENNE, THANK YOU.
>>> WE HAVE AN UPDATE ON THE
TERROR ATTACK IN STOCKHOLM.
AUTHORITIES REVEALING NEW
INFORMATION ABOUT THE MAN WHO
ALLEGEDLY STOLE A TRUCK AND
TURNED IT INTO A DEADLY WEAPON.
RAISING QUESTIONS ABOUT WHETHER
WARNING SIGNS WERE MISSED.
HERE'S JENNIFER ECCLESTON.
>> Reporter: NEW DETAILS ABOUT
THE SUSPECTED DRIVER OF THIS
STOLEN DELIVERY TRUCK.
POLICE REVEALING THEY TRIED TO
DEPORT HIM JUST SIX WEEKS AGO.
>> HE WAS APPLYING FOR
RESIDENCE.
THAT WAS REJECTED.
>> Reporter: BUT WHEN POLICE
WENT TO HIS HOME TO DEPORT HIM,
THEY COULDN'T.
HE HAD GIVEN THEM THE WRONG
ADDRESS.
THE UNNAMED SUSPECT, ALSO KNOWN
TO INTELLIGENCE SERVICES IN THE
PAST.
DETERMINED A MARGINAL PLAYER.
BUT TONIGHT POLICE REVEALING HE
SHOWED ISIS SYMPATHIES.
THE SUSPECT, ARRESTED JUST HOURS
AFTER THE ATTACK.
ANOTHER SUSPECT ALSO IN CUSTODY.
POLICE BEEFING UP PATROLS ACROSS
THE CAPITAL.
OVER 500 QUESTIONED.
THOUSANDS TODAY GATHERED AT THE
SCENE OF THE ATTACK TO REMEMBER
THE FOUR KILLED.
FROM SWEDEN, BELGIUM, AND FROM
THE UK.
41-YEAR-OLD FATHER CHRIS
BEVINGTON.
A MUSIC EXECUTIVE BASED IN
STOCKHOLM.
QUESTIONS ABOUT SWEDEN'S
EXTREMIST MONITORING, AND HOW
THE SUSPECT SLIPPED THROUGH
THEIR NET BEFORE COMMITTING ONE
OF THE COUNTRY'S WORST ACTS OF
TERRORISM.
TOM?
>> JENNIFER, THANK YOU.
>>> BACK HERE IN THE STATES NOW
TO AN EXPLOSIVE SEX SCANDAL
INVOLVING THE GOVERNOR OF
ALABAMA.
ACCUSATIONS THAT THE GOVERNOR,
ROBERT BENTLEY, ABUSED POWER TO
COVER UP AN AFFAIR.
IMPEACHMENT PROCEEDINGS GETTING
UNDER WAY TOMORROW, WITH CALLS
FOR HIS RESIGNATION GROWING.
GLORIA RIVIERA REPORTS.
>> Reporter: ALABAMA'S GOVERNOR,
DEFIANT AND DETERMINED AS
IMPEACHMENT HEARINGS START
MONDAY.
>> I DO NOT PLAN TO RESIGN.
I HAVE DONE NOTHING ILLEGAL.
>> Reporter: REPUBLICAN GOVERNOR
ROBERT BENTLEY CAME UNDER FIRE
IN 2016 FOR HIS ALLEGED AFFAIR
WITH TOP ADVISER REBEKAH MASON.
>> I LOVE YOU, I LOVE TOUCHING
YOU.
>> Reporter: THIS AUDIO
RECORDING PROVIDED BY HIS FORMER
WIFE OF 50 YEARS.
TO INVESTIGATORS LOOKING INTO
WHETHER HE VIOLATED CAMPAIGN
FINANCE LAWS BY GIVING HIS
SUPPOSED MISTRESS STATE EMPLOYEE
PERKS AFTER SHE LEFT OFFICE.
A SCATHING 131-PAGE REPORT BY
THE HOUSE JUDICIARY COMMITTEE
DETAILED ALLEGATIONS OF
EXTENSIVE ABUSE OF POWER IN
COVERING HIS TRACKS.
AT ONE POINT ALLEGEDLY SENDING A
POLICE OFFICER TO HIS OWN SON'S
HOUSE TO TRY AND CONVINCE HIM TO
TURN OVER THE RECORDINGS MADE BY
HIS FORMER WIFE.
THE REPORT CONCLUDING THE
GOVERNOR WAS CLOUDED BY
"INCREASING OBSESSION AND
PARANOIA," SUBJECTING "CAREER
LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICERS TO
TASKS INTENDED TO PROTECT HIS
REPUTATION."
>> BABY, LET ME TELL YOU WHAT
WE'RE GONNA HAVE TO DO, WE'RE
GONNA START LOCKING THE DOOR.
>> Reporter: HIS EX-WIFE DIANE
CLAIMS HE ONCE SENT HER A TEXT
THAT SAID, I LOVE YOU REBEKAH.
GOVERNOR BENTLEY HAS REPEATEDLY
DENIED ACCUSATIONS OF AN AFFAIR,
CALLING THE ISSUE A PRIVATE
MATTER.
TOM?
>>> STILL MUCH MORE AHEAD ON
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT" THIS
SUNDAY.
THE PERSONAL TRAINER WHO
APPARENTLY SNAPPED.
WHY POLICE SAY HE STARTED
SHOOTING PEOPLE.
>>> PLUS, THE VIOLENT TAKEDOWN
CAUGHT ON CAMERA.
WAS THIS ARREST STANDARD
PROCEDURE?
>>> AND, A DOG OWNER'S HEROIC,
SPLIT-SECOND DECISION.
HIS NAME IS McGIVER.
COULD HE PULL OFF THIS ICY
RESCUE?
PLAYING OUT AS CAMERAS ROLL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
RESCUE?
PLAYING OUT AS CAMERAS ROLL.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
I put it on my back.
Ok, this is interesting.
There we go.
There's the little tingle.
I feel this electrical pulse
grabbing at my muscles.
Level 3. 5.
I'm pleasantly surprised.
It was more powerful
than I was expecting it to be.
It worked. What can I say?
I believe Aleve.
Learn more and read
Reviews at Aleve.com.
Bounty is more absorbent,Mom"
per roll
so the roll can last 50% longer
than the leading ordinary brand.
So you get more "Life" per roll.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker Upper
When it comes to heartburn...
trust the brand doctors trust.
Nexium 24HR is the #1 choice
of doctors and pharmacists
for their own frequent
heartburn.
For all day and all night
protection...
banish the burn...
with Nexium 24HR.
WHEN YOU'RE CLOSE TO
THE PEOPLE YOU LOVE,
DOES PSORIASIS EVER GET IN
THE WAY OF A TOUCHING MOMENT?
IF YOU HAVE MODERATE
TO SEVERE PSORIASIS,
YOU CAN EMBRACE
THE CHANCE
OF COMPLETELY CLEAR
SKIN WITH TALTZ.
TALTZ IS PROVEN TO GIVE YOU A
CHANCE AT COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
WITH TALTZ, UP TO
90% OF PATIENTS
HAD A SIGNIFICANT IMPROVEMENT
OF THEIR PSORIASIS PLAQUES.
IN FACT, 4 OUT OF 10 EVEN
ACHIEVED COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
DO NOT USE IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TALTZ.
BEFORE STARTING YOU
SHOULD BE CHECKED
FOR TUBERCULOSIS.
TALTZ MAY INCREASE YOUR
RISK OF INFECTIONS
AND LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT THEM.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF
YOU ARE BEING TREATED
FOR AN INFECTION
OR HAVE SYMPTOMS.
OR IF YOU HAVE RECEIVED
A VACCINE OR PLAN TO.
INFLAMMATORY BOWEL DISEASE
CAN HAPPEN WITH TALTZ.
INCLUDING WORSENING
OF SYMPTOMS.
SERIOUS ALLERGIC
REACTIONS CAN OCCUR.
NOW'S YOUR CHANCE AT
COMPLETELY CLEAR SKIN.
JUST ASK YOUR
DOCTOR ABOUT TALTZ.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW WITH A STORY
OF UNUSUAL VIOLENCE IN AN
UNEXPECTED PLACE.
POLICE SAY A PERSONAL TRAINER
WENT ON A SHOOTING SPREE,
ATTACKING COWORKERS IN AN
UPSCALE GYM IN SOUTH FLORIDA.
HERE'S EVA PILGRIM.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, NEW
DETAILS ON WHAT LED TO A DEADLY
WORKPLACE SHOOTING SPREE AT A
LUXURY HEALTH CLUB IN SOUTH
FLORIDA.
POLICE SAY A RECENTLY FIRED
EMPLOYEE GUNNED DOWN TWO OF HIS
FORMER BOSSES BEFORE TURNING THE
WEAPON ON HIMSELF.
>> I NOTICED HE WASN'T
CLEAN-SHAVEN, HE WASN'T LOOKING
HIS BEST.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES SAY
33-YEAR-OLD ABEKU WILSON, A
FORMER TRAINER AT THIS EQUINOX
GYM, WALKED INTO THE HEALTH CLUB
AROUND 1:00 YESTERDAY AFTERNOON
AND SHOT GENERAL MANAGER
JANINE ACKERMAN AND FITNESS
MANAGER MARIO ORTIZ.
THE GUNFIRE SENT PEOPLE RUNNING
FOR COVER.
SHUTTING DOWN THIS UPSCALE MALL
WHERE THE GYM IS LOCATED.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN THE ALARM
STARTED SOUNDING.
>> GET INSIDE, GET INSIDE, WE
RAN INSIDE AND THEY LOCKED THE
DOOR.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS SAY
WILSON WAS FIRED EARLIER IN THE
DAY FOR WORKPLACE VIOLENCE AND
ESCORTED OUT OF THE GYM.
POLICE SAY HE THEN WENT HOME AND
GOT A GUN BEFORE RETURNING.
>> OBVIOUSLY, EVERYBODY IS
CONNECTING THE DOTS, IT WAS HIS
FIRING THAT CAUSED HIM TO DO
WHAT HE DID.
>> Reporter: EQUINOX'S CHAIRMAN
RELEASING A STATEMENT ON
FACEBOOK, SAYING, "THERE IS
NOTHING I CAN SAY TO LESSEN THE
SEARING PAIN WE ALL FEEL AT THIS
TERRIBLE MOMENT."
HOMICIDE IS CURRENTLY THE FOURTH
LEADING CAUSE OF DEATH IN THE
WORKPLACE IN THE U.S.
2 MILLION REPORTED BEING THE
VICTIMS OF WORKPLACE VIOLENCE
EACH YEAR.
>> EVA, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THAT
DRAMATIC TAKEDOWN.
WHY POLICE ARRESTED THIS WOMAN.
>>> PLUS, YOU WON'T BELIEVE WHAT
TWO PEOPLE FOUND IN THEIR SALAD.
IT'S LED TO A FOOD RECALL
TONIGHT AT A MAJOR CHAIN YOU
NEED TO HEAR ABOUT.
STAY WITH US.
mple
off to Ancestry.
My Ancestry DNA results
are that I am 26% Nigerian.
I am just trying to
learn as much as I can
about my culture.
I put the Gele on my
head and I looked
into the mirror and I
was trying not to cry.
Because it's a hat,
but it's like the most
important hat I've
ever owned.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
Come close, come close.
I like that.
[ ALL SOUNDS COME TO A
CRASHING HALT ]
Ah.
When your pain reliever
stops working,
your whole day stops.
Awww.
Try this.
For minor arthritis pain,
only Aleve is FDA
approved to work
for up to 12 straight hours
with just one pill.
Thank you.
Come on everybody.
Aleve.
Live Whole.
Not Part.
I'm Val. The Orange Money
retirement squirrel from Voya.
I represent the money you save
for the future.
Who's he?
He's the green money you can
spend now. What's up?
Gonna pay some bills, maybe buy
a new tennis racket.
He's got a killer backhand.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement, it's time to get
Voya.
People spend less
time lying awake
with aches and
pains with Advil PM
than with Tylenol PM.
Advil PM combines the
number one pain reliever
with the number one sleep aid.
Gentle, non-habit
forming Advil PM.
For a healing night's sleep.
>>> TIME NOW FOR OUR "INDEX."
AND A POLICE TAKEDOWN.
FT. COLLINS POLICE SAYING THEY
USED STANDARD PROCEDURE WHEN
ARRESTING THIS WOMAN, SLAMMING
HER TO THE GROUND OUTSIDE A BAR.
POLICE RESPONDING TO A DISPUTE
BETWEEN TWO MEN WHEN SHE
ALLEGEDLY GOT INTO THE POLICE'S
WAY AND STRUCK AN OFFICER.
THE CASE NOW BEING REVIEWED.
>>> NOW TO FLORIDA AND THE
REVOLTING DISCOVERY.
THE CDC AND FDA INVESTIGATING
HOW A DEAD BAT MADE ITS WAY INTO
SOME LEAFY GREENS.
THE FRESH EXPRESS BRAND ORGANIC
MARKETSIDE SPRING MIX NOW UNDER
PRECAUTIONARY RECALL.
DISTRIBUTED EXCLUSIVELY TO
WALMART STORES IN THE SOUTHEAST.
>>> AND THE LIFE AND DEATH
DECISION FOR A MAN AND HIS DOG.
COSMO THE FRENCH BULLDOG FALLING
THROUGH THIN ICE.
THE OWNER JUMPING IN TO SAVE
HIM.
NAVIGATING FREEZING POND WATERS,
IN CANADA.
THE HERO'S LAST NAME, McGIVER.
McGIVER AND HIS SIDEKICK,
DRENCHED BUT OKAY TONIGHT.
>>> UP NEXT, A NEW MOM DIAGNOSED
WITH A BRAIN TUMOR.
DOCTOR AFTER DOCTOR TOLD HER NO,
SO SHE TURNED TO SOCIAL MEDIA.
THE INCREDIBLE CONNECTION,
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE, COMING UP.
,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
♪ She'll unease you
♪ All the better just
to please you ♪
♪ She's precocious,
and she knows just ♪
♪ What it takes to
make a pro blush ♪
♪ All the boys
think she's a spy, ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes
Ito treat your toughy
nasal allergies...
♪
...listen up.
Unlike pills that don't
treat congestion,
Clarispray covers 100 percent of
your nasal allergy symptoms.
Clarispray. From the
makers of Claritin.
Just Head & Shoulders?
(gasp)
I thought it was just
for, like, dandruff
New Head & Shoulders. Cleans,
protects and moisturizes to...
...get up to 100% flake-free and
unbelievably beautiful hair
It's not Head & Shoulders, it's
the new Head & Shoulders
Bburning of diabetic nerve pain
these feet...
jumped into city life
as a kid...
...raised two rough
and tumble boys...
...and kept my town moving.
But I couldn't bear my diabetic
nerve pain any longer.
So I talked to my doctor
and he prescribed LYRICA.
Nerve damage from diabetes
causes diabetic nerve pain.
LYRICA is FDA approved
to treat this pain.
LYRICA may cause serious
allergic reactions
or suicidal thoughts
or actions.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have these,
new or worsening depression,
or unusual changes in mood
or behavior.
Or swelling, trouble breathing,
rash, hives, blisters, muscle
pain with fever,
tired feeling or blurry vision.
Common side effects are
dizziness, sleepiness,
weight gain and swelling
of hands, legs, and feet.
Don't drink alcohol while
taking LYRICA.
Don't drive or use machinery
until you know how LYRICA
affects you.
Those who have had a drug or
alcohol problem
may be more likely
to misuse LYRICA.
Now I have less diabetic
nerve pain.
And I love keeping their little
feet safe and sound.
Ask your doctor about
LYRICA.
If you are eligible,
you could pay as little as $25
dollars a month.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, THE CHANCE
CONNECTION TRANSFORMING INTO A
SECOND CHANCE AT LIFE.
FOR THIS 28-YEAR-OLD MOM, IT ALL
STARTED WITH HEADACHES.
>> THERE WERE POINTS WHEN I JUST
LAID IN MY BED AND CRIED,
BECAUSE I WAS IN SO MUCH PAIN.
I WENT IN FOR AN MRI, THEY SAID
THAT THERE WAS A LESION IN MY
BRAIN, AND ABOUT A MINUTE LATER,
IT TRANSLATED TO A BRAIN TUMOR.
>> Reporter: THIS TOUGH MOM
STARTED BLOGGING ABOUT HER
FIGHT TO BEAT THIS TUMOR.
DOCTORS TOLD HER SURGERY WAS NOT
AN OPTION.
WHAT WAS THAT LIKE, TO BE
REJECTED BY DOCTOR AFTER DOCTOR?
>> A FEELING OF HOPELESSNESS, I
FEEL.
BUT IT GOT TO THE POINT WHERE,
WE WERE LIKE, OKAY, IF THIS IS
INOPERABLE, THIS IS IN GOD'S
HANDS.
>> Reporter: SO SHE KEPT
BLOGGING, AND PEOPLE KEPT
READING AND SHARING HER STORY ON
SOCIAL MEDIA.
IT CAUGHT THE EYE OF ONE DOCTOR,
NEARLY 1,000 MILES AWAY IN
OKLAHOMA, WHO TOLD HER HE WAS
WILLING TO TRY IF SHE WAS.
FOUR DAYS LATER, SHE WAS READY
FOR SURGERY.
IT WASN'T GOING TO BE A COMPLETE
FIX, BUT IT WOULD IMPROVE AND
PROLONG HER LIFE.
>> THE PATIENTS ARE A LOT BRAVER
THAN THEY GET CREDIT FOR.
>> Reporter: BUT FOR THAT
OPERATION, STEPHANIE GOT COLD
FEET.
WHAT IF IT DIDN'T WORK OUT?
SHE TOLD HER HUSBAND SHE NEEDED
A SIGN.
>> A CLEAR YES OR NO.
I WAS LOOKING ON WALLS,
BUILDINGS.
ABOUT FIVE MINUTES BEFORE I WAS
TAKEN INTO THE OPERATING ROOM,
ONE OF THE NURSES SAID, I'M JUST
GOING TO WRITE YES ON YOUR HEAD.
AND I SMILED AND SAID, THERE IT
IS.
>> Reporter: THAT WAS ONE MONTH
AGO.
SHE SAYS SHE FEELS BETTER.
SHE'S STILL GOING THROUGH
TREATMENT.
BUT SHE'S HAPPY SHE DIDN'T GIVE
UP AND THAT SHE FOUND A DOCTOR
THAT DIDN'T GIVE UP ON HER.
>> ALWAYS HAVE HOPE, AND NEVER
GIVE UP.
>> WE THANK STEPHANIE FOR
SHARING HER STORY, AND WE'RE ALL
ROOTING FOR HER COMEBACK.
THANKS SO MUCH FOR WATCHING.
I'M TOM LLAMAS IN NEW YORK.
"GMA" FIRST THING IN THE
MORNING.
DAVID MUIR RIGHT BACK HERE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
HAVE A GOOD EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
EVENING.
>>> A JOY RIDE ON THE BACKSIDE
OF A BUMPER TURNS DEADLY FOR A
CALIFORNIA TEENAGER.
AND THE UNWANTED GUEST WHO
CRAWLED OUT OF THE WOODS TO
TERRORIZE A CALIFORNIA FAMILY.
ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
>> ANNOUNCER:  LIVE WHERE YOU
LIVE, THIS IS ABC 7 NEWS.
>> A MARCH AGAINST MILITARY
ACTION IN THE MIDDLE EAST, THE
BAY AREA ACTIVISTS WEREN'T THE
ONLY ONES CALLING OUT THE RECENT
U.S. AIR STRIKES IN SYRIA.
GOOD EVENING, I'M ERIC THOMAS.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
PROTESTERS FIGURE WHAT COULD
HAPPEN NEXT FOLLOWING THE
ATTACKS ON A SYRIAN AIR BASE.
ABC 7 NEWS REPORTER CORNELL IS
LIVE IN THE STUDIO.
>> Reporter: ACTIVISTS CONCERNED
ABOUT THE AIRSTRIKES IN SYRIA.
SUPPORTERS AND CRITICS NOW
DEMANDING TO KNOW WHAT THE
LONG-TERM PLAN IS FOR DEALING
WITH THE REGION.
♪
>> Reporter: SONGS OF PEACE
FOLLOWED BY PROTEST.
ACTIVISTS WITH CODE PINK MARCHED
ACROSS THE GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE
HONKING FOR PEACE IN SYRIA.
AFTER THE U.S. LAUNCHED
AIRSTRIKES ON THE SYRIAN AIR
BASE IN RESPONSE TO LAST WEEK'S
HORRIFIC CHEMICAL ATTACK.
>> YOU CAN BOMB THE WORLD INTO
PIECES, BUT YOU CAN'T BOMB IT
INTO PEACE.
>> IT IS A COMPLEX PROBLEM I
DON'T THINK CAN BE SOLVED WITH
MORE AND MORE BOMBS.
>> Reporter: TODAY THE REGIME
BASHAR AL-ASSAD DEFIANT AFTER
THE AIRSTRIKES.
THE AIR FIELD STRUCK 59 AMERICAN
MISSILES BACK UP AND RUNNING.
FIGHTER BOMBERS ARMED FOR
BATTLE.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS THE U.S.
BOMBING WAS THE RIGHT MOVE.
>> WHAT HAPPENED THIS WEEK WAS
ONE OF THE PRESIDENT'S FINEST
HOURS.
HE WON'T STOP HERE.
IF HE NEEDS TO DO MORE, HE