JOIN US BACK HERE AT 6:00.
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, THE TRAIL OF TERROR.
NEW IMAGES AND FRESH DETAILS
FROM THE DRAMATIC CAPTURE OF THE
SECOND SUSPECT IN THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBINGS.
THE INFRARED CENSORS THAT
ACTUALLY SAW HIM INSIDE THAT
BOAT AND THE ROBOT THAT HELPED
FORCE HIM OUT.
TONIGHT, WE HAVE THE LATEST ON
THE SUSPECT'S CONDITION AND WHEN
WILL HE WILL BE ASKED THOSE
URGENT QUESTIONS?
WHAT WAS HIS ALLEGED MOTIVE, AND
WAS HE PART OF A LARGER PLOT?
PLUS, DID THE FBI MISS A CHANCE
TO STOP THE BOMBING WHEN THEY
QUESTIONED THE OTHER SUSPECT,
HIS OLDER BROTHER, TWO YEARS
AGO?
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, IN A CITY
THAT'S COMING BACK TO LIFE AFTER
AN EXTRAORDINARY DAY ON
LOCKDOWN, THE ONLINE EFFORTS TO
REWARD THE MAN WHO FOUND THE
SUSPECT IN HIS BOAT.
AND AT FENWAY PARK, THE PLAYERS
JOINED BY THE RUNNERS AND THE
FIRST RESPONDERS.
♪ SWEET CAROLINE
>> BOSTON IS BACK.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US ON A VERY
BUSY SATURDAY NIGHT.
ON THIS DAY WHEN A MILLIONS OF
BOSTONIANS EMERGED FROM THEIR
POLICE-ORDERED HIBERNATION, WE
ARE GETTING EXTRAORDINARY NEW
IMAGES FROM THE CAPTURE OF
SUSPECT NUMBER TWO.
TAKE A LOOK AT THIS SHOT FROM A
STATE POLICE HELICOPTER,
EQUIPPED WITH A THERMAL CAMERA.
THAT DARK FORM RIGHT THERE IN
THE BACK OF THE BOAT, THAT,
POLICE SAY, IS 19-YEAR-OLD
DZHOKHAR TSARNAEV.
HERE IT IS FROM ANOTHER ANGLE.
YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE THE SUSPECT
LYING DOWN IN THE BACK OF THE
BOAT.
LOOK AT THIS, THE POLICE SEND IN
A VOOK RIGGED WITH A ROBOT ARM
TO TEAR OFF THE COVER OF THE
BOAT.
TONIGHT TSARNAEV IS BEING
TREATED IN THE SAME HOSPITAL AS
MANY OF THE BOMBING VICTIMS
THEMSELVES.
WE HAVE TEAM COVERAGE FROM
BOSTON ALL THE WAY TO RUSSIA.
WE START WITH OUR CHIEF
INVESTIGATIVE CORRESPONDENT,
BRIAN ROSS.
HE'S OUTSIDE THE HOSPITAL.
BRIAN?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
THE HEADLINES SAY THE NIGHTMARE
IN BOSTON IS OVER.
THAT'S HARDLY THE CASE FOR THE
INVESTIGATION AS THE FBI NOW
SEEKS THE MOTIVE OF THE ACCUSED
SUSPECT AND HIS DEAD BROTHER.
WHETHER THEY WERE IN LEAGUE WITH
OTHERS HERE OR OVERSEAS.
AS POLICE AND FEDERAL AGENTS
CLOSED IN ON THE ACCUSED BOMBER
LAST NIGHT, WITH A HELICOPTER
BEAMING BACK THESE REMARKABLE
THERMAL IMAGES OF HIM HIDING IN
A BOAT.
>> WE HAVE MOVEMENT IN THE BOAT.
HE JUST SAT UP.
HE IS MOVING, AND FLAILING
ABOUT, QUITE A BIT OF MOVEMENT.
>> Reporter: THE ORDERS WENT OUT
TO DO EVERYTHING TO CAPTURE
19-YEAR-OLD DZHOKHAR TSARNAEV
ALIVE.
EVEN AFTER EXCHANGE OF GUNFIRE.
>> ALL UNITS, DO NOT RETURN
FIRE.
>> Reporter: FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE DOWN, THE PRIORITY NOW IS
TO LEARN THE MOTIVES OF THE TWO
BROTHERS WHO AUTHORITIES SAY ARE
RESPONSIBLE FOR THE SUCCESSFUL
TERROR ATTACK ON THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
>> WE WILL DETERMINE WHAT
HAPPENED.
WE WILL INVESTIGATE ANY
ASSOCIATIONS THAT THESE
TERRORISTS MAY HAVE HAD.
>> Reporter: TSARNAEV WAS TAKEN
TO THE HOSPITAL WITH SERIOUS
INJURIES.
BUT ONCE HE'S CONSCIOUS A
SPESHLT TEAM PLANS TO QUESTION
HIM UNDER WHAT IS KNOWN AS THE
PUBLIC SAFETY EXCEPTION.
TO REMAIN SILENT, OR TO HAVE A
LAWYER.
IN PREVIOUS CASES FOR A DURATION
OF ABOUT 50 MINUTES.
>> THERE'S A PUBLIC SAFETY
EXEMPTION IN CASES OF NATIONAL
SECURITY AND ACTS OF TERRORISM.
AND SO THE GOVERNMENT HAS THAT
OPPORTUNITY.
>> Reporter: THE DRAMATIC EVENTS
UNFOLDED LAST NIGHT AFTER
AUTHORITIES HAD LIFTED A
LOCKDOWN ON WATERTOWN, WHEN THE
MAN WHO LIVES IN THIS HOUSE,
DAVE HENNEBERRY, WAS FINALLY
ABLE TO GO OUTSIDE, HE SPOTTED
BLOOD ON HIS BOAT IN THE BACK
DRIVEWAY.
ACCORDING TO HIS NEIGHBOR --
>> HE STARTED TO OPEN UP THE
ZIPPER, LOOKED INSIDE AND HE SAW
BLOOD.
THEN HE LOOKED AND HIS DECK HAS
A BOX, THE ENGINE BOX IS UP
ABOVE THE DECK.
AND HE LOOKED AT WHAT HE THOUGHT
WAS A BODY RIGHT BEHIND THE BOX.
>> Reporter: FBI AND POLICE
S.W.A.T. TEAMS STORMED THE AREA
AND BEGAN A TWO-HOUR STANDOFF,
WITH GUNFIRE EXCHANGED AT ONE
POINT.
THE HELICOPTER BEAMED BACK THOSE
IMAGES SHOWING THE SUSPECT IN
THE BOAT.
>> WE HAVE MOVEMENT.
>> Reporter: A ROBOT WAS SENT IN
TO RIP THE TARP OFF THE TOP OF
THE BOAT.
>> IF THEY'RE ABLE TO
SUCCESSFULLY RIP THAT OFF, HE'LL
BE FULLY EXPOSED.
>> Reporter: TSARNAEV HAD BEEN
INJURED IN A GUNFIGHT WITH
POLICE THE NIGHT BEFORE AND
APPEARED WEAK AND NOT WEARING A
SUICIDE VEST AS HAD BEEN FEARED.
>> THE HOSTAGE RESCUE TEAM DID
WORK IN TRYING TO NEGOTIATE HIM
OUT OF THAT BOAT.
>> Reporter: AND THEN IT WAS
OVER.
>> THE SUSPECT'S IN CUSTODY.
>> Reporter: ACROSS THE STREET,
ACROSS BOSTON, AND ACROSS THE
NATION, THE CHEERS WENT UP.
TONIGHT TSARNAEV IS HERE UNDER
GUARD AT THE BETH ISRAEL MEDICAL
CENTER, ACCORDING TO THE
GOVERNOR, IN SERIOUS, STABLE
CONDITION, BUT STILL NOT ABLE TO
COMMUNICATE.
>> SO WHEN HE'S ABLE TO
COMMUNICATE, POLICE ARE GOING TO
HAVE A LIMITED PERIOD OF TIME,
MAYBE 50 MINUTES, TO INTERVIEW
THE SUSPECT BEFORE THEY HAVE TO
READ HIM HIS RIGHTS.
WHAT ARE THE KEY QUESTIONS
THEY'RE LIKELY TO ASK?
>> THERE'S TWO KEY QUESTIONS.
ARE THERE OTHERS WORKING WITH
HIM?
AND ARE THERE OTHER TARGETS THAT
STILL MIGHT BE HIT BY OTHERS
WORKING WITH HIM?
DAN?
>> HUGE QUESTIONS STILL
UNANSWERED.
BRIAN THANK YOU FOR LEADING OUR
COVERAGE ALL WEEK.
WE THANK YOU ONE AGAINST.
>>> NOW TO THE SUSPECTS, THERE
ARE NEW DETAILS TONIGHT ABOUT
WHO THEY ARE, ALSO NEW QUESTIONS
ABOUT WHAT EXACTLY THE OLDER
BROTHER DID ON A SIX-MONTH TRIP
TO RUSSIA AND WHY THE FBI
INVESTIGATED HIM TWO YEARS AGO
AND THEN CLEARED HIM.
ABC'S SENIOR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PIERRE THOMAS HAS
BEEN ON THAT ANGLE ALL DAY.
PIERRE, GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
>> GOOD EVENING, DAN.
WITH THE MANHUNT NOW OVER, THE
FBI IS LOOKING FOR A
MOTIVE BEHIND THE BOMBINGS?
WAS ANYONE ELSE INVOLVED?
WHERE DID THEY GET THAT
TRAINING?
IMMIGRANTS FROM THE RUSSIAN
CAUCUSES, THE BROTHERS CAME WITH
THEIR PARENTS TO THE U.S. AS
CHILDREN.
SEEKING REFUGEE STATUS.
THEY THRIVED ATTENDING TOP
BOSTON SCHOOLS.
OLDER BROTHER, TAMERLAN, 26,
STAR ATHLETE, GOLDEN GLOVE
BOXER, PIANIST.
YOUNGER BROTHER DZHOKHAR, 19,
HAD JUST BECOME A U.S. CITIZEN,
IRONICALLY, ON SEPTEMBER 11th OF
LAST YEAR.
ONCE A LIFEGUARD, HE WAS AN
ALL-STATE WRESTLER AND COLLEGE
STUDENT.
>> I CERTAINLY CAN'T PUT IT
TOGETHER THAT HE WAS A PERSON
FIRING A WEAPON AND POTENTIALLY
KILLING PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: LAST NIGHT THE FBI
ACKNOWLEDGED IT INTERVIEWED
TAMERLAN IN 2011 BASED ON A TIP
FROM THE RUSSIANS.
THE RUSSIANS SAID HE WAS A
RADICAL ISLAMIST, PREPARING TO
LEAVE THE U.S., POSSIBLY FOR A
TRIP TO THE CAUCUSES.
AFTER LOOKING INTO TAMERLAN'S
PHONE RECORDS, WEBSITES HE
VISITED AND ASSOCIATES, THE FBI
FOUND NO TIES TO TERRORISTS.
BY LAW, FBI OFFICIALS SAID,
MONITORING HAD TO STOP, BARRING
NEW NEGATIVE INFORMATION.
>> TOO MANY PEOPLE IN THIS
COUNTRY, JUST LIKE HIM, THAT ARE
TOUCHING EXTREMIST WEBSITES,
THAT ARE ESPOUSING THINGS THAT
AREN'T PARTICULARLY KIND TO
AMERICANS, BUT THAT'S NOT
AGAINST THE LAW HERE.
>> Reporter: TAMERLAN'S FATHER
SAID HIS SONS COULDN'T HAVE
PLANNED THE ATTACK, BECAUSE THEY
KNEW THE FBI WAS WATCHING THEM.
BUT THEY APPARENTLY WERE NOT.
AND NEVER KNEW THAT A DARK SIDE
OF THE TWO BROTHERS HAD BEGUN TO
EMERGE.
TAMERLAN WAS CHARGED IN
CAMBRIDGE WITH BEATING HIS
FORMER GIRLFRIEND.
HE STARTED POSTING VIOLENT
VIDEOS, URGING JIHAD.
ON HIS YOUTUBE CHANNEL.
AND DZHOKHAR BEGAN WRITING
BIZARRE TWEETS.
"A DECADE IN AMERICA ALREADY, I
WANT OUT."
AUTHORITIES NEVER SAW THIS
COMING.
TAMERLAN TRAVELED TO RUSSIA FOR
SIX MONTHS LAST YEAR.
THE FBI WANTS TO KNOW EXACTLY
WHO HE SAW AND WHAT HE WAS
DOING, DAN.
>> LET ME GET BACK TO THE FBI
INVESTIGATION INTO THE OLDER
BROTHER.
YOU'VE BEEN TALKING TO THE FBI
ALL DAY.
ARE THEY NOT EXPECTING ANY SENSE
OF FRUSTRATION OR REMORSE OVER
HAVING MISSED WHAT COULD HAVE
BEEN A REAL OPPORTUNITY HERE?
>> THEY'LL DO A POSTMORTEM,
WHICH IS NORMAL IN THESE CASES,
BUT THEY SAID THEY DID WHAT THE
LOU AND THE CONSTITUTION ALLOWS.
>> PIERRE, THANK YOU.
>>> AND IN ORDER TO DIG DEEPER
INTO THE LIVES OF THESE TWO
YOUNG SUSPECTS, WE SENT KIRIT
RADIA TO A ROUGH AND REMOTE
AREA WHERE THE FAMILY COMES
FROM.
HERE IS WHAT HE FOUND TODAY.
>> Reporter: IN A TEARFUL PHONE
CALL WITH ABC NEWS THIS EVENING,
THE MOTHER OF THE SUSPECTED
BOSTON BOMBERS SAID SHE AND HER
HUSBAND PLANNED TO TRAVEL TO THE
U.S. TO SEE THEIR YOUNG SON
CAPTURED FRIDAY NIGHT.
SHE INSISTS HER SONS WERE SET
UP, AND THAT HER ELDEST SON WAS
INVESTIGATED BECAUSE HE LOVED
ISLAM AND DIDN'T DO ANYTHING
BAD.
HER COMMENTS FEED THE MYSTERY
OVER WHAT HAPPENED TO TURN THE
TWO BROTHERS INTO TERRORISTS.
DAGESTAN IS A POOR AND DANGEROUS
REGION IN SOUTHERN RUSSIA.
HOME TO ISLAMIC MILITANT
UPRISING.
BUT FRIENDS AND FAMILY SAY THE
PARENTS REJECTED ISLAMIC
FUNDAMENTALISM.
E WASN'T TOO RELIGIOUS, THIS
NEIGHBOR IT IS ABOUT THE FATHER.
THERE WAS NO FANATICISM.
BUT IT WAS JUST A YEAR AGO ON A
TRIP HERE, THAT THE OLDER SON
SETOFF ALARM BELLS AMONGST THE
FAMILY.
ABC NEWS HAS LEARNED THAT HIS
UNCLE KICKED HIM OUT OF THE
HOUSE, UPSET ABOUT HIS
INCREASINGLY EXTREMIST VIEWS.
THE VILLAGE WHERE THE MOTHER'S
FAMILY LIVED, WE SEARCHED FOR
CLUES ABOUT THE BROTHERS.
FEW WERE WILLING TO TALK.
BUT IN HER CALL WITH ABC NEWS,
THE MOTHER SAID, I DON'T KNOW
HOW TO LIVE WITH THIS.
KIRIT RADIA, ABC NEWS, DAGESTAN.
>> THE VIEW FROM RUSSIA TONIGHT.
>>> AND TODAY, PRESIDENT OBAMA
HELD A MEETING IN THE SITUATION
ROOM TO GET AN UPDATE ON THE
INVESTIGATION.
THE HEADS OF THE FBI AND CIA
WERE THERE, AMONG OTHERS.
WHICH LEADS US TO ABC'S CHIEF
GLOBAL AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT,
MARTHA RADDATZ.
MARTHA, THANKS FOR COMING IN.
WE APPRECIATE IT.
LET'S TALK ABOUT THE OLDER
BROTHER'S TRIP TO RUSSIA.
WE KNOW THERE ARE ISLAMIC
MILITANTS IN THIS PART OF
RUSSIA, BUT DO THESE PEOPLE HAVE
ANY HISTORY OF ATTACKING
AMERICA?
>> NOT THE CHECHENS.
THEY HAVE NO HISTORY OF
ATTACKING THE AMERICA.
WHAT INVESTIGATORS WILL WANT TO
FIND OUT IS WHETHER HE WENT TO
SOME SORT OF TRAINING CAMP, SOME
RADICAL TRAINING CAMP THAT DID
HAVE A BEEF WITH AMERICA.
WHO FUNDED HIM, IF HE HAD ANY
SORT OF EXTRA FUNDING.
DID HE LEARN HOW TO BUILD THOSE
BOMBS THERE, OR DID HE BUILD
THEM ON THE INTERNET?
THAT'S WHAT THEY'LL BE LOOKING
AT AND THEY WILL INTERVIEW
EVERYBODY THEY POSSIBLY CAN TO
SEE WHERE THOSE DARK MONTHS LED.
>> IF THEY RULE OUT SOME SORT OF
FOREIGN PLOT, AND THAT'S A BIG
IF AT THIS POINT, IT WOULD MAKE
THESE TWO BROTHERS, ASSUMING
THEY'RE PROVEN TO BE GUILTY, IT
WOULD MAKE THEM LONE WOLVES,
WHICH AS I UNDERSTAND IT, HAS
BEEN KEEPING UP NATIONAL
SECURITY OFFICIALS IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT FOR YEARS NOW.
>> YES, BECAUSE IF YOU HAVE ONE
LONE WOLF, WHO THEY BELIEVE
PROBABLY CONVINCED HIS BROTHER
TO BE ANOTHER ONE, THEN YOU
DON'T KNOW WHERE THE REST OF
THEM ARE.
WHAT WILL INSPIRE THEM, HOW THEY
MIGHT GET RADICALIZED.
THAT'S A NIGHTMARE SCENARIO.
>> THANK YOU, MARTHA.
>>> I WANT TO SWITCH GEARS BACK
TO BOSTON, A CITY THAT AMERICA
FELL IN LOVE WITH THIS WEEK.
THE HEROISM, THE STOICISM,
COMMUNITY SPIRIT AND ALL OF THAT
EXPRESSED WITH THAT UNMISTAKABLE
ACCENT, A MIXTURE OF VINEGAR AND
MOLASSES.
AND AS BOSTON EMERGED FROM THE
EXTRAORDINARY POLICE LOCKDOWN,
ABC'S NEWEST ANCHOR BYRON PITTS
WAS OUT IN THE MIDDLE OF IT ALL.
>> Reporter: IN A CITY SO
PASSIONATE ABOUT ITS BASEBALL
TEAMS, SPORTS ARE THE THERAPY
TODAY.
>> HOTDOGS, SAUSAGES!
>> Reporter: HERE EVEN A HOTDOG
FELT LIKE A HUG.
>> CELEBRATING WITH SAUSAGES.
I FEEL LIKE I'M BREATHING.
I JUST FEEL LIKE WE HAVEN'T BEEN
BREATHING ALL WEEK.
>> Reporter: SINCE FRIDAY
NIGHT'S GAME WAS CANCELED FOR
SECURITY REASONS, THE EMOTIONS
RAN EVEN DEEPER THIS AFTERNOON.
>> WE DIDN'T THINK TWICE ABOUT
COMING.
>> FENWAY PARK IS A SPECIAL
PLACE.
IN THE HEARTS AND MINDS OF
PEOPLE OF BOSTON, THE PEOPLE OF
NEW ENGLAND, THIS IS A CIVIC
CATHEDRAL.
>> Reporter: FROM THE BALLPARK
TO THE HEART OF DOWNTOWN, BOSTON
WAS TRANSFORMED TODAY.
LIFE RETURNED TO A CITY THAT WAS
ON LOCKDOWN FRIDAY.
THE POLICEMANHUNT WAS
UNPRECEDENTED.
SO, TOO, THE COLLECTIVE SIGH THE
CITY TOOK INSIDE FENWAY.
♪
THE EMOTIONAL PREGAME CEREMONY
HONORED THE FIRST RESPONDERS,
SURVIVORS, AND VICTIMS OF
MONDAY'S ATTACK.
AND THE WHOLE STADIUM SANG THE
STAR SPANGLED BANNER.
♪ O SAY CAN YOU SEE
♪ BY THE DAWN'S EARLY LIGHT
>> I BRING LOVE FROM THE WHOLE
COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: EVEN NEIL DIAMOND
SHOWED UP TO SING HIS SIGNATURE
SONG.
THIS WEEK IT BECAME AMERICA'S
♪ SWEET CAROLINE
GOOD TIMES NEVER SEEMED SO
GOOD ♪
>> SO GOOD, SO GOOD, SO GOOD!
>> Reporter: THERE'S ALSO BEEN
PLENTY OF COMMERCE TODAY.
THAT'S IMPORTANT BECAUSE
FRIDAY'S SHUTDOWN REALLY COST
THIS CITY MONEY.
TODAY, MONEY AND GOODWILL HAVE
BEEN FLOWING ALL DAY LONG.
DAN?
>> YES, THEY WERE, BYRON PITTS,
THANK YOU, AND AGAIN, WELCOME TO
ABC NEWS.
>>> BOSTON, AS WE SAID, IS BACK.
COMING UP HERE ON "WORLD NEWS"
ON THIS SATURDAY NIGHT, TWO
DISASTERS IN ONE WEEK, ONE IN
BOSTON, AND ONE IN WEST, TEXAS.
SEPARATED BY 1,900 MILES, BUT
CONNECTED BY THIS MAN.
OUR CECILIA VEGA WITH THIS MAN'S
AMAZING, ONE IN A MILLION STORY.
ALSO TONIGHT, THE ONLINE
CAMPAIGN ON BEHALF OF A MAN
WHOSE BOAT WAS SHOT UP IN THE
CAPTURE OF THAT SUSPECTED
MARATHON BOMBER.
THE MAN WHO LED POLICE TO THEIR
SUSPECT MAY BE GETTING A VERY
BIG THANK-YOU GIFT.
AAAH!
AAAAAH!
THERES A GUY ON THE WINDOW!
DO SOMETHING, DAD!
AAAAH!
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
THEY'RE RATE SUCKERS.
THEIR BAD DRIVING
MAKES CAR INSURANCE
MORE EXPENSIVE
FOR THE REST OF US.
GOOD THING THERE'S SNAPSHOT
FROM PROGRESSIVE.
SNAP IT IN AND GET A DISCOUNT
BASED ON YOUR GOOD DRIVING.
STOP PAYING
FOR RATE SUCKERS.
TRY SNAPSHOT FREE
AT PROGRESSIVE.COM.
A BODY AT REST
TENDS TO STAY AT REST...
WHILE A BODY IN MOTION
TENDS TO STAY IN MOTION.
STAYING ACTIVE CAN ACTUALLY
EASE ARTHRITIS SYMPTOMS.
BUT IF YOU HAVE ARTHRITIS,
STAYING ACTIVE
CAN BE DIFFICULT.
PRESCRIPTION CELEBREX
CAN HELP RELIEVE ARTHRITIS PAIN
SO YOUR BODY
CAN STAY IN MOTION.
BECAUSE JUST ONE
200MG CELEBREX A DAY
CAN PROVIDE 24 HOUR RELIEF
FOR MANY WITH ARTHRITIS PAIN
AND INFLAMMATION.
PLUS, IN CLINICAL STUDIES,
CELEBREX IS PROVEN TO IMPROVE
DAILY PHYSICAL FUNCTION
SO MOVING IS EASIER.
CELEBREX CAN BE TAKEN
WITH OR WITHOUT FOOD.
AND IT'S NOT A NARCOTIC.
YOU AND YOUR DOCTOR
SHOULD BALANCE THE BENEFITS
WITH THE RISKS.
ALL PRESCRIPTION NSAIDS,
LIKE CELEBREX, IBUPROFEN,
NAPROXEN AND MELOXICAM
HAVE THE SAME
CARDIOVASCULAR WARNING.
THEY ALL MAY INCREASE
THE CHANCE
OF HEART ATTACK OR STROKE,
WHICH CAN LEAD TO DEATH.
THIS CHANCE INCREASES
IF YOU HAVE HEART DISEASE
OR RISK FACTORS
SUCH AS HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
OR WHEN NSAIDS ARE TAKEN
FOR LONG PERIODS.
NSAIDS, LIKE CELEBREX,
INCREASE THE CHANCE OF SERIOUS
SKIN OR ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR STOMACH AND INTESTINE
PROBLEMS,
SUCH AS BLEEDING AND ULCERS,
WHICH CAN OCCUR WITHOUT WARNING
AND MAY CAUSE DEATH.
PATIENTS ALSO TAKING ASPIRIN
AND THE ELDERLY
ARE AT INCREASED RISK FOR
STOMACH BLEEDING AND ULCERS.
DON'T TAKE CELEBREX
IF YOU HAVE BLEEDING
IN THE STOMACH OR INTESTINE,
OR HAD AN ASTHMA ATTACK, HIVES,
OTHER ALLERGIES TO ASPIRIN,
NSAIDS OR SULFONAMIDES.
GET HELP RIGHT AWAY IF YOU HAVE
SWELLING OF THE FACE OR THROAT,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
YOUR MEDICAL HISTORY.
AND FIND AN ARTHRITIS TREATMENT
FOR YOU.
VISIT CELEBREX.COM AND ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CELEBREX.
FOR A BODY IN MOTION.
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
>>> THIS HAS BEEN, LET'S BE
HONEST ABOUT IT, AN UNPLEASANT
WEEK IN AMERICA.
BOMBS, POISON S,
>> THIS HAS BEEN AN UNPLEASANT
WEEK IN AMERICA.
BOMBS, POISON LETTERS AND FLOODS
ALONG THE MISSISSIPPI AND THAT
EXPLOSION IN WEST, TEXAS.
SEPARATED BY 1,900 MILES, BUT
CONNECTED BY THIS MAN.
OUR CECILIA VEGA WITH THIS MAN'S
TONIGHT, FOR THE FIRST TIME,
WE'RE GETTING A CLOSE-UP LOOK AT
GROUND ZERO OF THE BLAST THAT
LEVELED AN ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOOD.
THE DEATH TOLL IS NOW AT 14,
WITH CLOSE TO 200 INJURED.
EXPERTS TELL US THE ODDS OF
HAVING TWO DISASTERS LIKE TEXAS
AND BOSTON IN THE SAME WEEK, ARE
ONE IN EVERY 4,800 YEARS.
SO WHAT, THEN, ARE THE ODDS OF
ONE MAN BEING AN EYEWITNESS TO
BOTH?
HERE'S ABC'S CECILIA VEGA.
>> Reporter: JOE BERTI FINISHED
THE BOSTON MARATHON IN THREE
HOURS AND 56 MINUTES FLAT.
AND THEN MINUTES LATER, THIS.
[ BLAST ]
>> I HEARD THE EXPLOSION AND IT
WAS LOUD.
SO I TURNED AROUND AND SAW THE
SMOKE COMING FROM THE FINISH
LINE.
SO AT THAT INSTANT I JUST FELT
LIKE, IT WAS A BOMB.
>> YOU THOUGHT RIGHT AWAY IT WAS
A BOMB?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
BECAUSE OF HOW LOUD IT WAS AND
WHERE IT WAS.
LITERALLY SECONDS LATER, THE
SECOND BOMB EXPLODED.
>> Reporter: BERTI'S WIFE AMY
WAS JUST TEN YARDS AWAY FROM THE
EXPLOSION.
A WOMAN STANDING NEXT TO HER
LOST A LEG.
BUT AMY WAS FINE.
TWO DAYS LATER, BACK HOME IN
TEXAS, BERTI WAS DRIVING FROM A
MEETING.
HE SAW A HUGE FIRE RAGING IN THE
DISTANCE AND THEN A FAMILIAR
SOUND.
THE BLAST FROM THE EXPLODED
FERTILIZER PLANT IN WEST, TEXAS,
SO STRONG IT ROCKED BERTI'S CAR.
>> I WAS TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT IT WAS, WAS IT A TERRORIST
ATTACK?
DID SOMEONE DROP A BOMB ON US?
THE SIZE OF IT WAS JUST
INCREDIBLE.
>> Reporter: ARE YOU THINKING,
WHAT?
AGAIN?
>> YEAH, I WAS JUST THINKING I
CAN'T BELIEVE THIS IS ING.
>> Reporter: MAYBE IT WAS LUCK,
PERHAPS FATE.
BERTI HAS ANOTHER WAY OF LOOKING
AT IT.
>> I FEEL BLESSED.
YOU KNOW, MY WIFE WAS TEN YARDS
FROM A MAJOR EXPLOSION.
AND HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE AROUND
HER ARE CRITICALLY INJURED, AND
SHE DOESN'T EVEN HAVE A SCRATCH
ON HER.
I WAS 30 SECONDS TO THE FINISH
LINE AND UNINJURED.
SO WE BOTH FEEL BLESSED.
>> Reporter: TWO EXPLOSIONS IN
ONE WEEK, IT SOUNDS PRETTY
UNLUCKY.
JOE BERTI WALKED AWAY WITHOUT A
SCRATCH, AND THOSE, DAN, ARE
SOME PRETTY GOOD ODDS.
>> INDEED THEY ARE.
WE'RE GLAD THEY'RE BOTH OKAY.
THANK YOU FOR THAT STORY.
>>> COMING UP HERE ON THE
BROADCAST, THE DESPERATE FLOOD
FEARS ALONG THE MISSISSIPPI, AND
THE SURPRISING ONLINE CAMPAIGN
TO HELP AMERICA'S MOST BELOVED
BOAT OWNER, THE GUY WHO HELPED
POLICE IN BOSTON NAB THEIR MAN.
DIGESTIVE BALANCE IN SYNC?
TRY ALIGN.
IT'S THE NUMBER ONE
GE RECOMMENDED PROBIOTIC
THAT HELPS MAINTAIN
DIGESTIVE BALANCE.
♪
STAY IN THE GROOVE WITH ALIGN.
NEED HELP KEEPING YOUR
DIGESTIVE BALANCE IN SYNC?
TRY ALIGN.
IT'S A PROBIOTIC THAT FORTIFIES
YOUR DIGESTIVE SYSTEM
WITH HEALTHY BACTERIA 24/7.
BECAUSE YOUR INSIDES
SET THE TONE.
STAY IN THE GROOVE WITH ALIGN.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS IS KAREN AND JEREMIAH.
THEY DON'T KNOW IT YET,
BUT THEY'RE GONNA FALL IN LOVE,
GET MARRIED,
HAVE A COUPLE OF KIDS,
[ children laughing ]
MOVE TO THE COUNTRY,
AND LIVE A LONG, HAPPY LIFE
TOGETHER
WHERE THEY ALMOST NEVER FIGHT
ABOUT MONEY.
[ dog barks ]
BECAUSE RIGHT AFTER
THEY GET MARRIED,
THEY'LL FIND
SOME RETIREMENT PEOPLE
WHO ARE PAID ON SALARY,
NOT COMMISSION.
THEY'LL GET
STRAIGHTFORWARD GUIDANCE
AND BE ABLE TO FOCUS ON OTHER
THINGS, LIKE EACH OTHER,
WHICH ISN'T ROCKET SCIENCE.
IT'S JUST COMMON SENSE.
FROM TD AMERITRADE.
OF MILD TO MODERATE
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE
IS EXELON PATCH.
NOW WITH
MORE TREATMENT OPTIONS,
EXELON PATCH MAY IMPROVE
OVERALL FUNCTION AND COGNITION.
YOUR LOVED ONE CAN GET
A FREE 30-DAY TRIAL.
AND YOU CAN HAVE
ACCESS TO NURSES.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE
HOW THE DISEASE PROGRESSES.
HOSPITALIZATION,
AND RARELY DEATH,
HAVE BEEN REPORTED FROM WEARING
MORE THAN ONE PATCH AT A TIME.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
ARE NAUSEA, VOMITING, DIARRHEA,
FALL, LOSS OF APPETITE
OR WEIGHT,
APPLICATION SITE REDNESS,
AND URINARY TRACT INFECTION.
THE LIKELIHOOD AND SEVERITY
OF THESE SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCREASE
AS THE DOSE INCREASES
OR IF PATIENTS
WEIGH LESS THAN 110 POUNDS.
PEOPLE AT RISK
FOR STOMACH ULCERS
WHO TAKE
CERTAIN OTHER MEDICINES
SHOULD TALK TO THEIR DOCTOR
AS SERIOUS STOMACH PROBLEMS
SUCH AS BLEEDING MAY WORSEN.
PATIENTS MAY EXPERIENCE
SLOW HEART RATE.
FREE TRIAL OFFER FOR THEM.
NURSES TO TALK TO FOR YOU.
VISIT EXELONPATCHOFFER.COM.
♪
>>> A LATE SEASON AVALANCHE IN
THE COLORADO ROCKIES TOOK A
DEADLY TOLL.
FIVE SNOWBOARDERS LOST THEIR
LIVES NEAR THE LOVELAND PASS.
ONE PERSON WAS PULLED OUT ALIVE.
THE OF GROUP WAS IN THE BACK
COUNTRY AND WE HAVE MORE.
>> IT WAS THE DEADLIEST
AVALANCHE IN 50 YEARS.
SIX SNOWBOARDERS TRAPPED UNDER
MONTH THAN EIGHT FEET OF SNOW
AND LOVELAND PASS 60 MILES WEST
OF DENVER.
LOCAL SHERIFF SAYS THE GROUP
VENTURED INTO AN OUT OF BOUNDS
AREA.
ONE SNOWBOARDER FOUND ALIVE, THE
BODIES OF THE OTHERS RECOVERED.
NEARLY 20 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
KILLED ACROSS THE COUNTRY THIS
YEAR.
>> VERY DIFFERENT KIND OF
NATURAL DISASTER, DEADLY
FLOODING IN THE MIDWEST.
STATES OF EMERGENCY AND DISASTER
DECLARATIONS IN AT LEAST HALF A
DOZEN STATES NOW AND ALILEX PER
HAS THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: MOTHER NATURE'S
WRATH ACROSS THE MIDWEST HAS
BEEN UNRELENTING.
NEAR INDIANAPOLIS TODAY ONE MAN
IS DEAD, ANOTHER MISSING, AFTER
THEIR CARS WERE SWEPT AWAY BY
FLOODWATERS.
IN ZIONSVILLE, INDIANA, FLOODED
HOMEOWNERS ARE BATTLING TO GET
THE WATER OUT --
>> IT'S IN OUR KITCHEN, DINING
ROOM, AND GOING UP THROUGH THE
REST OF THE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: HEAVY RAIN HAS
HAMMERED THE HEARTLAND ALL WEEK.
MANY FORCED TO EVACUATE THEIR
HOMES.
IN RIVER GROVE, ILLINOIS, CANOES
REPLACED CARS.
PARTS OF ILLINOIS SAW A RECORD
EIGHT INCHES OF RAIN ON
THURSDAY, COMPLETELY SUBMERGING
PARTS OF CHICAGO.
HERE AT THIS CITY PARK, THERE'S
SO MUCH WATER, YOU CAN'T TELL
WHERE THE POOL ENDS, OR WHERE
THE PARK BEGINS.
SANDBAG AFTER SANDBAG, ENTIRE
COMMUNITIES ARE WORKING TO KEEP
THE WATER OUT.
BUT WITH THE MISSISSIPPI AND AT
LEAST 17 OTHER RIVERS AT OR NEAR
FLOOD LEVELS, THIS FIGHT IS FAR
FROM OVER.
ALEX PEREZ, ABC NEWS, CHICAGO.
>>> AND UP NEXT HERE ON "WORLD
NEWS," THERE COULD BE A VERY BIG
THANK-YOU GIFT IN THE WORKS FOR
THE BOAT OWNER WHO HELPED POLICE
IN BOSTON GET THEIR SUSPECT.
THE SURPRISING ONLINE CAMPAIGN,
BREWING RIGHT NOW, KEEP IT HERE.
NEXIUM, THE PURPLE PILL,
HELPS PROVIDE MANY WITH
DAY AND NIGHT RELIEF
OF HEARTBURN SYMPTOMS CAUSED
BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE,
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE HEADACHE,
ABDOMINAL PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
CALL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY IF
YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF NEXIUM
IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
FIND OUT HOW YOU MAY BE ABLE TO
GET NEXIUM FOR JUST $18 A MONTH
AT PURPLEPILL.COM
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
WHEN I FIRST FELT
THE DIABETIC NERVE PAIN,
OF COURSE,
I HAD NO IDEA WHAT IT WAS.
I FELT LIKE
MY FEET WERE GOING TO SLEEP.
IT PROGRESSED FROM THERE
TO BURNING
LIKE I WAS WALKING ON HOT COALS
TO LIKE A THOUSAND BEES
THAT WERE JUST STINGING MY FEET.
I HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE FOUND LYRICA FOR ME.
[ Female Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYE SIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN, AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS, AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO'VE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
HAVING LESS PAIN...
IT'S A WONDERFUL FEELING.
[ Female Announcer ] ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
TO HEAR MORE OF PHYLLIS'S
STORY, VISIT LYRICA.COM.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, A NEW FOLK
HERO HAS EMERGED OUT OF BOSTON'S
TERRIBLE WEEK.
HIS NAME IS DAVE HENNEBERRY.
HE'S THE GUY WHO FOUND THE
SUSPECT IN HIS BOAT IN HIS
BACKYARD.
TONIGHT, THE INTERNET IS
CONSPIRING TO SEND MR.
HENNEBERRY A GIANT THANK-YOU
GIFT.
HERE'S ABC'S GIO BENITEZ.
>> Reporter: IT'S THE NOW-FAMOUS
LITTLE BOAT THAT KEPT A BIG
SECRET, THE UNLIKELY HIDEOUT FOR
AMERICA'S MOST WANTED MAN.
AND THIS IS THE BOAT'S OWNER,
DAVID HENNEBERRY, A MAN NOW
CALLED A HERO FOR FINDING THE
SUSPECTED MARATHON BOMBER LAST
NIGHT AND CALLING 911.
WATERTOWN'S CHIEF OF POLICE SETS
THE SCENE.
WHAT HAPPENED WHEN YOUR OFFICERS
ARRIVED?
>> THERE WAS A SHOOTOUT IN THE
BEGINNING.
>> Reporter: THAT SHOOTOUT SO
DAMAGED THE BOAT, HENNEBERRY'S
NEIGHBOR SAID --
>> HE'S COMPLETELY SHOCKED AND
HE SAYS, MY POOR BOAT, MY POOR
BOAT.
I MEAN, HE'S TAKEN CARE OF THAT
BOAT METICULOUSLY SINCE HE'S HAD
IT AND NOW IT'S FULL OF HOLES.
>> Reporter: NOW A DIGITAL SHOW
OF SUPPORT, PEOPLE FROM ALL OVER
THE NATION ARE TURNING TO SOCIAL
MEDIA SITES LIKE FACEBOOK,
RAISING MONEY TO BUY HENNEBERRY
A NEW BOAT.
EVEN THE CHIEF IS HEARING ABOUT
THIS CALL TO ACTION.
>> I GOT AN E-MAIL THIS MORNING,
SOME PERSON IN DETROIT,
MICHIGAN, WHO WANTS TO REPLACE
THE BOAT FOR THE WATERTOWN
RESIDENT THAT GOT SHOT UP.
I MEAN, IT'S JUST INCREDIBLE.
>> Reporter: INCREDIBLE BECAUSE
IT WAS HENNEBERRY'S QUICK
THINKING TO CALL POLICE THAT
TURNED A COMMUNITY'S TERROR INTO
A SIGH OF RELIEF.
GIO BENITEZ, ABC NEWS,
WATERTOWN, MASSACHUSETTS.
>> AND WE HOPE HE GETS A NEW
BOAT.
>>> THAT WILL DO IT FOR "WORLD
NEWS" ON THIS SATURDAY NIGHT.
FOR DAVID MUIR AND EVERYBODY
HERE AT ABC NEWS, I'M DAN
HARRIS.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING AND I'LL
SEE YOU RIGHT BACK HERE TOMORROW
MORNING ON "GMA."
>>> A STUNNING NEW IMAGES.
WHAT IT TOOK TO TAKE DOWN A
TERRORIST.
>> BOSTON COMES BACK TO LIFE NOW
THAT THE SECOND BOMBING SUSPECT
HAS BEEN CAPTURED.
I'M AMA DAETZ IN BOSTON WITH THE
STORY.
>> SECURITY AT BAY AREA SPORTING
EVENTSLE WHAT IS BEING DONE TO
PROTECT YOU.
ABC7 NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
♪ SWEET CAROLINE
♪ WOO WOO WOO
>> A STRO OF STRENGTH FOR BOSTON
TODAY AT FENWAY PARK AS THE CITY
AND NATION RECOVER FROM A
TERRORIST ATTACK.
AND TONIGHT WE'RE LEARNING MORE
ABOUT HOW AUTHORITIES CAUGHT THE
SECOND SUSPECT HIDING FOR HOURS
IN A BOAT.
I'M ON TO AMA DAETZ.
AMA DAETZ IS LIVE IN BOSTON
TONIGHT WHERE THE CITY IS SLOWLY
RECOVERING.
>> Ama: WE'RE BACK BY BOYLSTON
STREET TODAY, WHERE IS THERE A
MEMORIAL THAT HAS BEEN THERE FOR
DAYS NOW, AND ON THIS SATURDAY,
IT AS IF BOSTON IS SAYING, WE'RE
BACK, AFTER THE SECOND SUSPECT
HAS BEEN CAPTURED.
[CHEERING]
>> YOU CAN FEEL THE ENERGY IN
BOSTON AS THE CITY COMES ALIVE
ONE DAY AFTER LAW ENFORCEMENT
CAPTURED THE SECOND MARATHON
BOMBING SUSPECT.
>> ALL UNITED TO GET THIS ONE
IDIOT, WHATEVER, TO CAUSE THIS
MUCH PROBLEMS BETWEEN THESE
PEOPLE ON A SPECIAL DAY THAT ALL
COUNTRIES ARE UNITED.
SO I'M GLAD THEY GOT THIS GUY.
>> AT FENWAY PARK THE RED SOX
GAME BEGAN WITH A MOMENT TO
HONOR THE VICTIMS OF THE
BOMBINGS.
>> WON'T YOU JOIN US AS WE
OBSERVE A MOMENT OF SILENCE.
>> THIS FIRST HOME GAME SINCE
MONDAY'S BOMBINGS WAS A SPECIAL
ONE.
>> HAD A BIG