>> THANK YOU.
SEE YOU AGAIN AT 6:00.
>>> TONIGHT, WE'RE ON THE SCENE.
THE RACE AGAINST TIME.
AND THE STUNNING MOMENTS.
THE WOMAN VISIBLY SHAKEN, PULLED
THROUGH THE DEBRIS THROUGH A
HOLE IN THE CEILING.
THE CHILD PULLED FROM A CRUMBLED
SCHOOL.
OUR TEAM IN MEXICO CITY.
>>> ALSO BREAKING, FROM PUERTO
RICO, FOR THE FIRST TIME, ROB
MARCIANO TAKES US TO THE PART OF
THE ISLAND WHERE THE HURRICANE
MADE LANDFALL.
THE URGENT PLEA TONIGHT.
THE WOMAN WAVING OUR TEAM INSIDE
AND WHAT ROB FOUND.
>>> WE HAVE NEWS ON NORTH KOREA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP REVEALING
PUNISHING NEW SANCTIONS AND THAT
CHINA WILL NOW HELP.
>>> FACEBOOK'S FOUNDER MARK
ZUCKERBERG TONIGHT AND THE VIDEO
MESSAGE HE JUST PUT OUT.
THE RUSSIANS DID BUY THOUSANDS
OF ADS ON FACEBOOK DURING THE
ELECTION.
ATTACKING HILLARY CLINTON AND
PRAISING DONALD TRUMP.
HE'LL NOW GIVE THOSE ADS TO
CONGRESS.
>>> TWO PEOPLE TRAPPED IN THIS
BURNING CAR.
SEVERAL OFFICERS SMASHING
WINDOWS TO GET TO THEM.
>>> AND THE DISCOVERY TONIGHT.
DOCTORS REVEALING WHAT THEY
FOUND IN AARON HERNANDEZ'S
BRAIN.
THE, QUOTE, MOST SEVERE CASE
THEY'VE EVER SEEN.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A THURSDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN WITH THAT RACE
AGAINST TIME IN MEXICO CITY.
WE WITNESSED REMARKABLE MOMENTS
OF HEROISM TODAY.
THE RESCUE CREWS THAT HAVE NOT
GIVEN UP.
SOME HAVE BEEN ABLE TO PULL
PEOPLE TO SAFETY AMID SO MANY
COLLAPSED BUILDINGS.
THE DESPERATE SCRAMBLE NOW TO
FIND THE MISSING, WITH HOPE
BEGINNING TO FADE.
BUT THERE WAS THIS.
SOME OF THE SMALLEST SURVIVORS
BEING PULLED OUT ALIVE, WHICH IS
WHY THEY KEEP GOING TONIGHT.
ABC'S MATT GUTMAN IS IN MEXICO
CITY, WHERE THEY ARE AFRAID THE
BUILDING HE'S REPORTING FROM
COULD COME DOWN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, 48 HOURS
AFTER THE EARTH SHOOK AND THE
BUILDINGS HERE CAME DOWN, NEW
IMAGES OF SURVIVORS BEING PULLED
FROM TOMBS OF RUBBLE.
THESE MEXICAN FIREFIGHTERS
EASING THIS WOMAN OUT A HOLE IN
THE CEILING.
FIRST, THE LEGS, AND THEN
GENTLY, THE REST OF HER BODY.
SHE EMERGES WITH THAT LOOK OF
SHOCK, AND THOSE TEARS.
OVER 50 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN RESCUED
HERE SINCE THAT MASSIVE 7.1
MAGNITUDE QUAKE ON TUESDAY.
BUT TONIGHT, THERE ARE STILL
FAMILIES WAITING BY THE LISTS OF
THE MISSING.
DESPERATE FOR WORD OF LOVED
ONES.
THE L.A. COUNTY FIRE DEPARTMENT
RESCUE TEAM ARRIVING WITH
SPECIALIZED EQUIPMENT TO ASSIST
IN THE SEARCHES.
AMONG THE MOST DRAMATIC RESCUES,
THESE CHILDREN AT THE ENRIQUE
REBSAMEN SCHOOL.
BYSTANDERS PRYING AT THE
CONCRETE, COAXING THE TERRIFIED
CHILDREN THROUGH A GAP IN THE
WALL.
FINALLY SCOOPING THEM UP,
SCREAMING, BUT ALIVE.
AFTER MORE THAN 36 HOURS, THE
ENTIRE NATION WAS TRANSFIXED ON
THIS FLATTENED SCHOOL, HOPING TO
SEE ONE MORE CHILD RESCUED.
THE EDUCATION MINISTER TELLING
ME THEY BELIEVED A YOUNG GIRL
WAS INSIDE.
>> AS THE RESCUE TEAMS INSIDE
TOLD YOU, THEY MADE CONTACT WITH
HER.
>> Reporter: THEY HEARD HER
VOICE?
>> YES.
YES.
THE RESCUE TEAMS HEARD HER
VOICE.
>> Reporter: TEAMS OF THOUSANDS
OF RESCUERS AND VOLUNTEERS,
DOGS, THOSE SENSITIVE
MICROPHONES AND THE ENDLESS
BUCKET BRIGADES DIGGING THROUGH
THE RUBBLE.
WHAT BRINGS EVERYTHING HOME IS
SEEING WHERE THEY'VE DEPOSITED
ALL OF THE CHILDREN'S BELONGINGS
HERE.
BOOKBAGS, NOTEBOOKS AND TOYS.
AND THOSE DESPERATE DEMANDS FOR
SILENCE.
>> SILENCIO TOTAL.
SILENCIO TOTAL POR FAVOR.
>> Reporter: BUT LATE TODAY, THE
STUNNING ANNOUNCEMENT.
OFFICIALS ANNOUNCING THERE WAS
NO GIRL AFTER ALL.
ALL THE STUDENTS ARE ACCOUNTED
FOR, 19 LOSING THEIR LIVES HERE.
WHAT YOU'RE CERTAIN IS, THERE
ARE NO KIDS FROM THIS SCHOOL
STILL IN THE RUBBLE.
>> NO, FOR CERTAIN.
>> Reporter: AND MATT GUTMAN
REPORTING IN NOW.
AND I UNDERSTAND THEY'RE WORRIED
THAT BUILDING RIGHT THERE BEHIND
YOU COULD COME DOWN?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
YOU CAN SEE THE CHAOS BEHIND ME.
EVERYBODY HERE IS BEING
EVACUATED.
THE CONCERN IS FOR THE OTHER
SIDE OF THE BUILDING.
NOW, THE BUILDING YOU SEE BEHIND
ME, THAT IS THE SCHOOL THAT
COLLAPSED, WHERE THOSE CHILDREN
WERE KILLED.
AND NOW THEY'RE LITERALLY
PUSHING US OUT OF THIS PLACE,
BECAUSE IT'S SIMPLY TOO
DANGEROUS.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, MATT GUTMAN WITH
US AGAIN TONIGHT FROM MEXICO
CITY.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT HERE TO THE
CATASTROPHIC DAMAGE IN PUERTO
RICO.
HOME TO 3.5 MILLION AMERICAN
CITIZENS.
HURRICANE MARIA, THE WORST STORM
TO BATTER THAT ISLAND IN NEARLY
A CENTURY.
AND FOR THE FIRST TIME, RIGHT
HERE TONIGHT, OUR ROB MARCIANO
TAKES US TO THE PART OF THE
ISLAND WHERE THE HURRICANE MADE
LANDFALL.
THERE WAS A WOMAN WHO WAVED HIM
IN, AND WHAT HE SAW WHEN HE WENT
INSIDE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, IN
PUERTO RICO, THE FIRST LOOK AT
HURRICANE MARIA'S WRATH, AS
THOUSANDS OF FAMILIES FACE A
DIFFICULT NIGHT AND AN UNCERTAIN
FUTURE.
AS THE STORM BORE DOWN ON THE
ISLAND, MANY HAD NO SAFE PLACE
TO GO.
THOSE FEROCIOUS
155-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS, THE
MOST POWERFUL SEEN HERE IN
GENERATIONS.
THE ENTIRE ISLAND STILL WITHOUT
POWER.
WE HEADED SOUTH TO WHERE MARIA
MADE LANDFALL.
NOW THAT WE'RE SOUTH OF TOWN,
WE'RE SEEING SOME DAMAGE THAT
ACTUALLY LOOKS ALMOST LIKE A
TORNADO CAME THROUGH.
CLEARLY, THIS IS THE PATH OF THE
EYE WHEN IT CAME THROUGH.
MILLIONS OF TREES OBLITERATED.
IN YOBACOA, THE TOWN DECIMATED
BY A DIRECT HIT, WE FIND
DESPERATE RESIDENTS LINING UP
FOR WATER THAT'S BEEN TRUCKED
IN.
>> WE NEED DIESEL FOR THE
GENERATOR.
WE NEED LIGHT.
WE NEED WATER.
>> Reporter: CAREGIVER MARIA
ORTEZ FLAGGED US DOWN.
>> WE CAN'T LET THEM DIE.
WE CAN'T LET THEM DIE.
WE NEED HELP, WE NEED ALL THE
HELP WE CAN GET.
>> Reporter: SHE TAKES US TO HER
NURSING HOME, NOW ON THE BRINK.
HARROWING SCENES INSIDE.
THIS MAN, CLINGING TO LIFE.
NOW I SEE, WHEN THAT GENERATOR
RUNS OUT --
>> WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
WHAT ARE WE GOING TO DO?
>> Reporter: 11 PATIENTS, ALL
FRAIL, DEHYDRATING IN THE
SWELTERING ROOMS.
SOME WITH ALZHEIMER'S.
>> THAT'S ALL THEY HAVE NOW IS
ME.
THAT'S ALL THEY HAVE.
>> Reporter: COMMUNITIES ALL
AROUND PUERTO RICO IN DIRE
CONDITIONS.
THE GOVERNOR OUT WITH THE
NATIONAL GUARD OVERNIGHT OUTSIDE
SAN JUAN RESCUING THE STRANDED.
AND BACK AT THE NURSING HOME,
MARIA WITH A MESSAGE FOR HER
DAUGHTER BACK IN FLORIDA.
>> I JUST WANT TO SAY, DANEESA,
I LOVE YOU.
DANEESA, I'M HERE, WE'RE ALIVE,
>> AND ROB MARCIANO REPORTING IN
FROM SAN JUAN NOW.
AND ROB, I WANT TO GET BACK TO
WHAT THE CAREGIVER PLEADED FOR
AT THE NURSING HOME.
WATER, DIESEL, FOOD.
ANY IDEA TONIGHT IF AUTHORITIES
HAVE HEARD HER CALLS FOR HELP?
>> Reporter: WELL, OUR HEARTS
JUST GO OUT FOR HER.
SHE ALSO NEEDS OXYGEN, SO,
OXYGEN AND DIESEL ARE NOT
SOMETHING WE CARRY, SO, OUR TEAM
CONTACTED THE OFFICE OF
EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT, AND THEY
ARE AWARE OF HER DESPERATE PLEA
AND HOPEFULLY CAN GET HER THE
HELP SHE NEEDS HERE IN THE
COMING DAYS, DAVID.
>> JUST A DIRE SITUATION THERE.
IN THE MEANTIME, ROB, WHERE IS
THE HURRICANE TONIGHT, AND ARE
THOSE MODELS NOW IN AGREEMENT
WHEN IT COMES TO THE EAST COAST
OF THE U.S.?
>> Reporter: WELL, WE'RE FEELING
A LITTLE BIT BETTER ABOUT THE
EAST COAST OF THE U.S. RIGHT
NOW.
IT'S ABOUT 90 MILES
EAST-SOUTHEAST OF GRAND TURK
ISLAND.
HURRICANE WARNINGS ARE UP THERE.
AND IT'S BACK UP TO CATEGORY 3
STATUS, SO, FORMIDABLE STORM.
AND YOUR FORECAST TAKES IT A LOT
FARTHER NORTH AND INTO THE OPEN
OCEAN, AND LIKELY KEEPS IT
THERE.
WEAKENS IT AS IT GETS INTO
COOLER WATER.
AND THERE ARE THE MODELS.
WE'RE MORE CONFIDENT IT WILL GO
OUT TO SEA.
CERTAINLY HOPE THAT FORECAST
HOLDS, DAVID.
>> ALL RIGHT, ROB MARCIANO.
AND WE WILL STAY ON THE STORY OF
THAT NURSING HOME.
ROB, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE WAS ALSO GREAT CONCERN
FOR SO MANY AMERICAN MEDICAL
STUDENTS ON DOMINICA.
TONIGHT, WHAT WE'VE LEARNED
ABOUT THOSE AMERICANS, AS WE NOW
SEE THE CATASTROPHIC IMAGES
COMING IN.
AN ISLAND WIPED OUT.
ABC'S VICTOR OQUENDO IN THE
STORM ZONE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, A LOOK AT
THE WORST OF MARIA'S WRATH.
THE HARD-HIT ISLAND OF
DOMINICA -- TOTAL DEVASTATION.
NEARLY EVERYTHING DESTROYED.
ROADS RIPPED, HUGE TREES
UPROOTED, DEBRIS LITTERING THE
STREET.
AT LEAST 15 PEOPLE ARE DEAD, BUT
MANY OTHERS ARE MISSING IN
COMMUNITIES THAT ARE COMPLETELY
CUT OFF.
AND LATE TODAY, WORD THAT 1,000
MEDICAL STUDENTS, MANY OF THEM
AMERICAN, WHOSE CONDITION WAS
UNKNOWN, HAVE BEEN REACHED AND
ARE CONFIRMED SAFE.
IN PUERTO RICO, MARIA'S WINDS
GAVE WAY TO MORE THAN 30 INCHES
OF RAIN.
OVERWHELMING RIVERS IN
LEVITTOWN.
THE POWER COMPANY USED CHERRY
PICKERS TO PLUCK RESIDENTS FROM
THEIR ROOFTOPS, FORCED TO WAIT
UNTIL THE FLOODWATERS RECEDED.
DAVID, THE RESIDENTS WHO WERE
RESCUED FROM HERE ARE BEING
TAKEN BY A NEARBY SCHOOL, WHERE
THEY HAVE SET UP A SHELTER.
THE CLEANUP PROCESS WILL LIKELY
TAKE WEEKS.
MAYBE EVEN MONTHS.
DAVID?
>> VICTOR OQUENDO REPORTING IN
FROM THE STORM ZONE.
VICTOR, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS ALSO BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT INVOLVING NORTH KOREA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WITH TOUGH NEW
SANCTIONS AGAINST NORTH KOREA,
AND WITH THE PROMISE OF HELP
FROM CHINA.
WHAT WOULD BE A MAJOR VICTORY
FOR THIS WHITE HOUSE.
AND JUST IN THIS EVENING, NORTH
KOREA'S FIERY NEW RESPONSE.
ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL.
>> Reporter: AFTER THREATENING
TO ANNIHILATE THE ENTIRE NATION
OF NORTH KOREA, PRESIDENT TRUMP
TODAY PUT ASIDE WAR TALK IN
FAVOR OF DIPLOMACY, ANNOUNCING A
NEW ROUND OF ECONOMIC SANCTIONS.
>> A NEW EXECUTIVE ORDER WILL
CUT OFF SOURCES OF REVENUE THAT
FUND NORTH KOREA'S EFFORTS TO
DEVELOP THE DEADLIEST WEAPONS
KNOWN TO HUMAN KIND.
>> Reporter: TRUMP ALSO
ANNOUNCED THAT CHINA IS NOW
TAKING NEW STEPS TO ISOLATE KIM
JONG-UN.
>> CHINA, THEIR CENTRAL BANK,
HAS TOLD THEIR OTHER BANKS --
THAT'S A MASSIVE BANKING
SYSTEM -- TO IMMEDIATELY STOP
DOING BUSINESS WITH NORTH KOREA.
>> Reporter: IT'S A STRIKING
DIFFERENCE IN TONE FROM EARLIER
THIS WEEK.
>> THE UNITED STATES HAS GREAT
STRENGTH AND PATIENCE, BUT IF IT
IS FORCED TO DEFEND ITSELF OR
ITS ALLIES, WE WILL HAVE NO
CHOICE BUT TO TOTALLY DESTROY
NORTH KOREA.
>> Reporter: TODAY, I ASKED U.N.
AMBASSADOR NIKKI HALEY ABOUT
THAT.
WHAT EXACTLY DID HE MEAN?
UNDER WHAT CIRCUMSTANCES WOULD
HE CONSIDER TOTALLY DESTROYING
NORTH KOREA?
>> WELL, I THINK THAT'S JUST
COMMON SENSE.
IF, FOR ANY REASON, NORTH KOREA
ATTACKS THE UNITED STATES OR OUR
ALLIES, THE U.S. WILL RESPOND.
PERIOD.
>> JON KARL WITH THE QUESTION
FOR NIKKI HALEY TODAY.
AND JON, WE HAVE A RESPONSE
TONIGHT FROM NORTH KOREA.
KIM JONG-UN RESPONDING?
>> Reporter: WE DO.
HE CALLED THE PRESIDENT MENTALLY
DERANGED AND SAID THAT HE WILL
MAKE HIM PAY DEARLY, THOSE WERE
HIS WORDS, FOR HIS SPEECH AT THE
U.N.
AND I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU,
THERE'S A REAL EFFORT BY THE
ADMINISTRATION TO TURN THE
TEMPERATURE DOWN HERE.
NIKKI HALEY MADE IT CLEAR,
THERE'S A LOT MORE STILL TO BE
DONE DIPLOMATICALLY.
>> JON KARL WITH US AGAIN
TONIGHT.
JON, THANK YOU.
>>> NEXT, TO A STUNNING PUBLIC
ADMISSION FROM FACEBOOK TONIGHT.
A VIDEO MESSAGE RELEASED LATE
TODAY, MARK ZUCKERBERG
ACKNOWLEDGING RUSSIAN AGENTS
DID, IN FACT, BUY THOUSANDS OF
ADS DURING THE ELECTION,
ATTACKING HILLARY CLINTON, OR
PRAISING DONALD TRUMP.
TONIGHT, FACEBOOK SAYS IT WILL
NOW TURN THOSE ADS OVER TO
CONGRESS.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: AFTER MONTHS OF
STONEWALLING CONGRESS, TODAY
FACEBOOK GAVE IN.
ITS FOUNDER, MARK ZUCKERBERG,
AGREEING TO TURN OVER MORE THAN
3,000 RUSSIAN-LINKED POLITICAL
ADS THAT RAN DURING LAST YEAR'S
ELECTION CAMPAIGN.
>> I DON'T WANT ANYONE TO USE
OUR TOOLS TO UNDERMINE
DEMOCRACY.
THAT'S NOT WHAT WE STAND FOR.
>> Reporter: RUSSIAN COMPANIES
SPENT MORE THAN $100,000 ON THE
ADS, MANY OF THEM PRAISING
DONALD TRUMP OR ATTACKING
HILLARY CLINTON.
MILLIONS OF AMERICANS SAW THEM,
AND JUST THIS WEEK, CLINTON SAID
FACEBOOK HAS TO OWN UP TO THE
PROBLEM.
>> I DON'T THINK ANYBODY CAN
WITH A STRAIGHT FACE SAY THAT
THE RUSSIANS DID NOT SET OUT TO
INFLUENCE OUR ELECTION, AND THEY
DID SO.
THIS LATEST REVELATION ABOUT THE
WAY THEY BOUGHT ADS ON FACEBOOK,
AND TARGETED THEM -- WE'RE GOING
TO FIND OUT A LOT MORE.
>> Reporter: UNTIL TODAY,
FACEBOOK REFUSED TO REVEAL WHO
PAID FOR POLITICAL ADS.
ZUCKERBERG SAYS THAT WILL NOW
CHANGE.
>> WE CAN DO BETTER.
>> Reporter: FACEBOOK AT FIRST
HAD DENIED TO CONGRESS THEY HAD
POSTED ANY ADS PAID BY THE
RUSSIANS.
>> WHEN I RAISED THESE ISSUES
LAST WINTER, COULDN'T HAPPEN,
AND THEY PRIVATELY SAID, YOU
KNOW, IT WAS A CRAZY IDEA, AS
WELL.
THEY WEREN'T CRAZY IDEAS.
>> Reporter: IT WAS NOT JUST
ADS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY HAVE ALSO
FOUND HUGE NUMBERS OF FAKE
FACEBOOK PAGES LINKED TO THE
RUSSIANS, LIKE THIS ONE
DISCOVERED BY "THE NEW YORK
TIMES," SUPPOSEDLY AN
ANTI-CLINTON FATHER LIVING IN
PENNSYLVANIA.
BUT HE DIDN'T EXIST.
THE PICTURE WAS ACTUALLY OF
SOMEONE IN BRAZIL.
>> THAT'S JUST INCREDIBLE.
ALL RIGHT, BRIAN ROSS WITH US
NOW.
THOUSANDS OF ADS BOUGHT BY THE
RUSSIANS, FACEBOOK ACKNOWLEDGING
THIS.
THEY'RE GOING TO GIVE IT TO
CONGRESS.
BUT YOU'VE BEEN DIGGING INTO
THIS.
DO WE KNOW WHICH STATES, WHICH
VOTERS THEY WERE TRYING TO
TARGET HERE?
>> Reporter: WELL, DAVID, ONLY
FACEBOOK KNOWS THE ANSWER TO
THAT, AND SO FAR, THEY HAVE KEPT
IT SECRET.
BUT ONE NEW STUDY SHOWS A
DISPROPORTION NATE
RUSSIAN-DIRECTED FAKE NEWS POSTS
WERE SQUARELY AIMED AT THE SWING
STATES IN THE LAST ELECTION.
>> BRIAN ROSS, YOU'LL STAY ON
TOP OF THIS.
BRIAN, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT HERE TO CAPITOL
HILL, AND THE NEW EFFORT TO KILL
OBAMACARE.
THE SENATE HAS UNTIL NEXT WEEK
TO PULL OFF THIS NEWEST ATTEMPT.
OUR TEAM TODAY CALLING THE
SENATORS OFFICES, THE KEY
SENATORS ON THE FENCE, AND WHAT
WE'VE LEARNED TONIGHT.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE BACK ON THE
HILL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE
PRESSURE IS ON FOR THE
REPUBLICAN SENATORS WHO WILL
MAKE OR BREAK THE NEW HEALTH
CARE BILL.
WATCHING CLOSELY FROM VIRGINIA,
MOM SAMANTHA McGOVERN.
HER DAUGHTER, JOSEPHINE, WAS
BORN AT JUST 24 WEEKS.
THAT'S CONSIDERED A PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION.
HER MOSTLY HEALTH CARE COSTS
$27,000.
SAMANTHA'S WORRIED WHAT HAPPENS
IF INSURANCE STOPS COVERING THAT
BILL.
>> I WANT THEM TO FIND A WAY TO
COVER ME AND PUT IT IN THE BILL.
DON'T LEAVE IT UP TO CHANCE.
DON'T LEAVE IT UP TO STATES.
DON'T ROLL THE DICE AND TAKE THE
RISK AND TAKE THE GAMBLE ON MY
CHILD'S LIFE.
>> Reporter: THE BILL DOES
REQUIRE STATES PROVIDE ACCESS TO
ADEQUATE AND AFFORDABLE HEALTH
INSURANCE, BUT THOSE TERMS ARE
NOT DEFINED OR GUARANTEED.
STATES COULD ALLOW INSURERS TO
CHARGE SOME PEOPLE WITH
PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS MORE.
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE THE MONEY
THAT WE WOULD HAVE SPENT ON
OBAMACARE IN WASHINGTON AND SEND
IT BACK HOME AND LET US DO A
BETTER JOB WITH IT.
>> Reporter: BUT WITH FAR LESS
MONEY.
BY ONE NEW ESTIMATE, $160
BILLION LESS.
TONIGHT, THE OPPOSITION FROM
MEDICAL GROUPS, PATIENT
ADVOCATES AND INSURERS IS PILING
UP.
WHAT COMES NEXT IS LARGELY UP TO
THESE FOUR REPUBLICANS.
>> I'M A PRODUCER WITH ABC NEWS.
>> Reporter: WITH THE SENATE OUT
OF SESSION, TODAY, OUR TEAM
WORKED THE PHONES.
>> I WAS JUST WONDERING IF
SENATOR PAUL IS A YES OR NO.
>> CALLING TO SEE IF THERE'S ANY
UPDATE ON THE HEALTH CARE VOTE.
>> Reporter: THEIR DEADLINES
LOOMING AT THE END OF NEXT WEEK.
>> AND MARY BRUCE WITH US AGAIN
FROM CAPITOL HILL TONIGHT.
OUR POLITICAL TEAM, WE SEE THEM
THERE MAKING THE CALLS, AS THEY
ALWAYS DO.
WHERE DO THOSE SENATORS STAND
TONIGHT, MARY?
>> Reporter: DAVID, REPUBLICANS
CAN AFFORD TO LOSE JUST TWO
VOTES HERE, AND RIGHT NOW, NONE
OF THOSE FOUR ARE ONBOARD.
PAUL IS A NO, COLLINS IS LEANING
NO, MURKOWSKI IS UNDECIDED, AND
McCAIN STILL WON'T SAY WHERE HE
STANDS, AND HE WANTS US TO STOP
ASKING.
DAVID?
>> MARY BRUCE WITH OUR POLITICAL
COVERAGE FOR TONIGHT.
MARY, THANK YOU.
>>> WE TURN NEXT HERE TO
OKLAHOMA CITY.
QUESTIONS ABOUT POLICE USE OF
FORCE.
OFFICERS INVESTIGATING A HIT AND
RUN ACCIDENT, ENCOUNTERING A MAN
THEY SAY WAS HOLDING A METAL
PIPE.
THEY TOLD HIM TO DROP IT, BUT HE
WAS DEAF.
HE WAS THEN SHOT AND KILLED.
ABC'S KENNETH MOTON FROM THE
SCENE TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, AN
INVESTIGATION INTO THE DEADLY
POLICE SHOOTING OF A DEAF MAN IN
OKLAHOMA CITY.
>> OFFICER INVOLVED SHOOTING.
OFFICERS ARE FINE.
SOUTHEAST 57th AND SHIELDS.
>> Reporter: IT ALL BEGAN
MOMENTS EARLIER.
THE STUNNING HIT AND RUN
CAPTURED ON SURVEILLANCE VIDEO.
INVESTIGATORS SAY A GREEN PICKUP
TRUCK HIT A CAR, FLIPPED AND
LANDED UPRIGHT.
THE DRIVER TOOK OFF.
POLICE SAY THEY TRACKED DOWN THE
TRUCK, BUT WAS CONFRONTED BY HIS
SON, MAGDIEL SANCHEZ.
THEY SAY HE WAS HOLDING A METAL
PIPE.
>> MYSELF AND MY DAUGHTER WERE
ACTUALLY SCREAMING AT THEM
NOT -- YOU KNOW, THAT HE WAS
DEAF, THAT HE COULDN'T HEAR
ANYTHING.
AND THEY PROCEEDED ON SHOOTING
HIM.
>> Reporter: ONE OFFICER USED A
TASER.
THE OTHER FATALLY SHOOTING
SANCHEZ WITH HIS GUN.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE A WEAPON OUT,
YOU CAN GET WHAT THEY CALL
TUNNEL VISION, OR YOU CAN LOCK
INTO JUST THE PERSON THAT HAS
THE WEAPON THAT WOULD BE A
THREAT AGAINST YOU.
>> Reporter: THE OFFICERS WERE
NOT WEARING BODY CAMERAS.
DAVID, THE POLICE CHIEF SAYS
SANCHEZ COULDN'T HEAR, BUT HE
COULD SEE THAT HIS OFFICERS WERE
IN UNIFORM AND MARKED PATROL
CARS.
THAT OFFICER WHO FIRED THE FATAL
SHOTS IS ON LEAVE DURING THE
INVESTIGATION.
DAVID?
>> KENNETH MOTON TONIGHT.
KENNETH, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS THURSDAY.
THE MYSTERY EXPLOSION, MULTIPLE
HOMES DAMAGED OR DESTROYED IN AN
AMERICAN NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU'LL SEE THE PICTURES.
>>> ALSO, THE FIERY CAR RESCUE.
TWO PEOPLE TRAPPED INSIDE THIS
CAR.
SEVERAL OFFICERS SMASHING
WINDOWS TO GET TO THEM.
>>> THE NEW DISCOVERY TONIGHT.
DOCTORS REVEALING WHAT THEY
FOUND IN AARON HERNANDEZ'S
BRAIN, CALLING IT THE, QUOTE,
MOST SEVERE CASE THEY'VE EVER
SEEN.
>>> AND THERE'S ALSO A NEW
HEADLINE TONIGHT ABOUT TOM
CRUISE AND HIS NEW MOVIE.
THE PRODUCERS BEING SUED FOR A
DEADLY ACCIDENT.
AND WHY THE PLAINTIFFS SAY THAT
CRUISE IS PARTIALLY TO BLAME.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
Ever
ar we take
a girl's trip.
Remember Nashville?
Kimchi BBQ.
Amazing Honky Tonk??
I can't believe
you got us tickets.
I did.
I didn't pay for anything.
You never do.
Send me what I owe.
I've got it.
I mean, You did find money
to buy those boots.
Are you serious?
Is that why
you don't like them?
Those boots could
make a unicorn cry.
Yeah, tears of joy.
The Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
The fast, secure and
simple way to send money.
it can seem like triggers
pop up everywhere.
Luckily there's Powerful,
24-hour, non-drowsy Claritin.
It provides relief
of symptoms
that can be triggered by over
200 different allergens.
Live Claritin Clear.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
Before I hadburning,oting,
pins-and-needles
of diabetic nerve pain,
these feet...
Grew into a free-wheeling kid...
Loved every step
of fatherhood...
And made old cars
good as new.
But I couldn't bear
my diabetic nerve pain
any longer.
So I talked to my doctor
and he prescribed LYRICA.
Nerve damage from diabetes
causes diabetic nerve pain.
LYRICA is FDA approved
to treat this pain,
from moderate
to even severe
diabetic nerve pain.
LYRICA may cause serious
allergic reactions,
suicidal thoughts or actions.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have these,
new or worse depression,
unusual changes
in mood or behavior,
swelling,
trouble breathing,
rash, hives, blisters,
muscle pain with fever,
tired feeling or blurry vision.
Common side effects:
dizziness, sleepiness,
weight gain,
swelling of hands,
legs, and feet.
Don't drink alcohol
while taking LYRICA.
Don't drive or use machinery
until you know how
LYRICA affects you.
Those who've had a
drug or alcohol problem
may be more likely
to misuse LYRICA.
Now I have less
diabetic nerve pain.
And I love smoothing the road
ahead for others.
Ask your doctor about LYRICA.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, THE FIERY
CAR RESCUE IN ATLANTA.
POLICE BATTLING FLAMES, SMASHING
WINDOWS TO FREE VICTIMS TRAPPED
INSIDE.
HERE'S ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI.
>> Reporter: THE TWO PEOPLE
TRAPPED INSIDE THIS CRASHED AND
BURNING VEHICLE ARE ALIVE
TONIGHT --
>> GET OUT!
>> Reporter: -- THANKS TO THE
QUICK WORK OF THESE ATLANTA
POLICE OFFICERS.
>> PEOPLE IN THERE?
ARE THERE PEOPLE IN THERE?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: IN THEIR POLICE
BODY CAM VIDEOS FROM YESTERDAY,
YOU SEE THEM RUNNING WITH SMALL
FIRE EXTINGUISHERS, TRYING TO
PUT OF THE FIRE BEFORE THE CAR
EXPLODES.
>> OH, MY GOD.
CAR'S IN FLAMES.
OH, MY GOD.
>> OKAY, IS EVERYBODY OUT OF THE
CAR?
>> NO, NO, THEY CAN'T GET OUT.
>> Reporter: THE DOORS ARE
LOCKED.
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT IS STILL ON
THE WAY.
AND THE VICTIMS HAVE BROKEN
BONES AND ARE SCREAMING.
THE OFFICERS TRIED BREAKING
WINDOWS.
OFFICERS DANIEL, McCALL,
SKILLMAN, BROOKS AND VALENTINE
WERE ABLE TO PUT OUT THE FIRE IN
TIME.
THIS WAS THE CAR AFTER THE FIRE
DEPARTMENT USED THEIR EQUIPMENT
TO REMOVE THE TWO VICTIMS.
>> I SIGNED UP FOR THIS JOB TO
HELP PEOPLE.
I NEVER SECOND GUESS.
>> Reporter: THE CITY TONIGHT IS
CELEBRATING THESE POLICEMEN.
THE TWO VICTIMS ARE STILL
HOSPITALIZED THIS EVENING IN
SERIOUS CONDITION.
DAVID?
>> INCREDIBLE WORK FROM POLICE
THERE.
STEVE, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, TOM
CRUISE, HIS NEW MOVIE, AND THE
LAWSUIT AFTER A DEADLY ACCIDENT
AGAINST THE PRODUCERS.
THE PLAINTIFFS CLAIM CRUISE IS
PARTLY TO BLAME.
>>> ALSO, THE POWERFUL HOUSE
EXPLOSION.
SEVERAL HOMES DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED.
THE NEW SURVEILLANCE.
>>> AND THE DISCOVERY INVOLVING
AARON HERNANDEZ AND HIS BRAIN.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
help you reach your goals.
It's having the confidence
to create the future
that's most meaningful to you.
It's protection for generations
of families,
and 150 years of strength
and stability.
And when you're able to
harness all of that,
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask a financial advisor
about Pacific Life.
my doctor recommended I
switch laxatives.
Stimulant Laxatives
make your body go
by forcefully stimulating the
nerves in your colon.
MiraLAX is different.
It works with the
water in your body
to hydrate and soften.
Unblocking your
system naturally.
MiraLAX.
My friI say not if you this
protect yourself.ary.
What is scary?
Pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's a serious disease.
My doctor said the risk is
greater now that I'm over 50!
Yeah...ya-ha...
Just one dose of the PREVNAR 13®
vaccine can help protect you
from pneumococcal pneumonia-
an illness that can cause
coughing, chest pain,
difficulty breathing,
and may even put you
in the hospital.
PREVNAR 13® is approved for
adults 18 and older to help
prevent infections from
13 strains of the bacteria that
cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
You should not receive
PREVNAR 13® if you have had
a severe allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
If you have a weakened
immune system,
you may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects
were pain, redness,
and swelling at
the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Get this one done!
Ask about PREVNAR 13®
at your next visit to your
doctor's office or pharmacy.
83% try to eat healthy,
yet up to 90% fall short
on getting key nutrients.
Let's do more.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
Complete with 100% daily value
of more than 15 key nutrients.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis?
How do you chase what you love
Do what I did.
Ask your doctor about HUMIRA.
It's proven to help relieve pain
and protect joints
from further irreversible damage
in many adults.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to block
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes to RA symptoms.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 20 years.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
Ready for a new chapter?
Talk to your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA at work.
>>> TO THE INDEX.
THE HOUSE EXPLOSION IN
CALIFORNIA.
THE BLAST IN WEST HILLS.
TWO PEOPLE INSIDE AT THE TIME.
THEY'RE OKAY.
BUT NEW SURVEILLANCE SHOWS THE
MOMENT THE BLAST ROCKED THE
ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOOD.
INVESTIGATORS ARE LOOKING FOR A
CAUSE.
>>> THERE IS NEWS TONIGHT ABOUT
AARON HERNANDEZ.
HIS LAWYER REVEALING TESTS SHOW
THE FORMER PATRIOTS PLAYER HAD
THE BRAIN DISEASE CTE.
DOCTORS CALLING IT, QUOTE, THE
MOST SEVERE CASE THEY HAD EVER
SEEN IN SOMEONE HIS AGE.
HERNANDEZ WAS SERVING A LIFE
SENTENCE FOR MURDER WHEN HE
COMMITTED SUICIDE.
>>> THE MAJOR LAWSUIT TONIGHT
INVOLVING TOM CRUISE.
THE ACTOR ACCUSED OF NEGLIGENCE
FOR A DEADLY PLANE CRASH DURING
FILMING OF HIS NEW MOVIE.
TWO PILOTS KILLED, INCLUDING
ALAN PURWIN, SEEN WITH CRUISE IN
THIS PHOTO.
THEIR ESTATES NOW SUING
PRODUCERS, CLAIMING CRUISE AND
HIS FLYING DEMANDS PUT PILOTS IN
DANGER.
CRUISE IS NOT NAMED AS A
DEFENDANT.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, FOOTBALL
SEASON IS HERE.
BUT WHAT HAPPENED IN ONE STADIUM
THAT SUDDENLY HAD EVERYONE
LOOKING UP.
Growing up, we were German.
We danced in a German dance
group. I wore lederhosen.
When I first got on Ancestry
I was really surprised that
I wasn't finding all of
these Germans in my tree.
I decided to have my DNA
tested through Ancestry DNA.
The big surprise was
we're not German at all.
52% of my DNA comes from
Scotland and Ireland.
So, I traded in my
lederhosen for a kilt.
Ancestry has many paths
to discovering your story.
Get started for free
at Ancestry.com.
I tabut with my back paines,
I couldn't sleep
and get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
(Con artists...)
They'll try anything to get your
Medicare card number.
So they can steal your identity,
commit Medicare Fraud.
What can you do?
Guard your Card?
Just like your credit card.
Nobody gets my number, unless I
know they should have it.
To protect your identity,
new Medicare cards without
Social Security numbers
will be mailed next year.
Visit Medicare.gov/Fraud
Stay sharp people!
When this bell rings...
...it starts a chain
reaction...
...that's heard throughout the
connected business world.
AT&T network security helps
protect business,
from the largest financial
markets to the smallest
transactions,
by sensing cyber-attacks in near
real time
and automatically deploying
countermeasures.
Keeping the world of business
connected and protected.
That's the power of and.
and life's beautiful moments.ns
get between you
Flonase outperforms the #1
non-drowsy allergy pill.
It helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause symptoms.
Pills block one
and 6 is greater than 1.
Flonase changes
everything.
that goes beyond assuming
Beingredients are safe...ood
to knowing they are.
Going beyond expectations...
Because our pets deserve it.
Beyond. Natural Pet Food.
Steve chooses to walk
Over the26.2 miles,9 days...
that's a marathon.
And he does it with
Dr. Scholl's.
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel insoles
that provide all-day comfort to
keep him feeling more energized.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
>>> AMERICA STRONG.
AND A NEW TRADITION IN COLLEGE
FOOTBALL.
WE LOVE IT.
IT WAS THE UNIVERSITY OF IOWA
HAWKEYES AGAINST THE WYOMING
COWBOYS.
THE FANS IN THE STADIUM READY.
BUT IT WASN'T JUST THOSE TEAMS
ON THE FIELD THEY WERE ABOUT TO
CHEER FOR.
THEIR EYES TRAINED ABOVE, TO THE
HOSPITAL LOOKING OVER THE
STADIUM.
THE NEWLY COMPLETED UNIVERSITY
OF IOWA STEAD FAMILY CHILDREN'S
HOSPITAL.
THE CHILDREN AND THEIR FAMILIES
WATCHING.
THE TEAM ON THE FIELD ALREADY
KNOWS THEM.
CHEERLEADERS PASSING THE BALL
TO THE KIDS.
AND NOW THE NEW TRADITION.
BETWEEN THE FIRST AND SECOND
QUARTERS, THAT HOMETOWN CROWD
ALWAYS LOOKS UP.
TO LET THOSE KIDS KNOW THEY'RE
ROOTING FOR THEM, TOO.
AMONG THEM, 4-YEAR-OLD
WYATT HEMPHILL IN HIS HOSPITAL
BED.
WYATT WAVING AS HE FIGHTS A RARE
IMMUNE DEFICIENCY DISORDER.
THAT LITTLE FIGHTER, FUELED BY
THOSE FANS, RUNNING TO THE END
ZONE IN THAT HOSPITAL HALLWAY,
LAUGHTER AND ALL.
WYATT AND HIS DAD WAVING TO US
TONIGHT.
>> HI, DAVID.
>> WE'RE WAVING RIGHT BACK,
ALONG WITH THE FANS IN THAT
STADIUM.
WE'RE PULLING FOR YOU, WYATT.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW.
UNTIL THEN, GOOD NIGHT.
>>> MIXED MESSAGES FROM MEXICO.
CONFUSION, HOPE AND DESPAIR.
AND BAY AREA FINDS A UNIQUE WAY
TO HELP OUT.
>> I'M WAYNE FREEDMAN IN
LAFAYETTE AT ICONIC TOWER AND
RESERVOIR.
NEW REPORTS SAYS IT COULD BE A
PROBLEM IN AN EARTHQUAKE.
THAT'S COMING UP.
>>> ALSO WALK THROUGH PUERTO
RICO TO SEE FIRSTHAND THE DAMAGE
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE ARE DEALING
WITH, RESULT OF HURRICANE MARIA.
>> AND SNOWING IN CALIFORNIA ON
THE LAST DAY OF SUMMER.
FORECAST FOR THE FIRST DAY OF
FALL.
>> AMERICA IS SKMCOMMITTED TO
STANDING SHOULDER TO SHOULDER
WITH PEOPLE IN THEIR HOUR OF
NEED.
IT IS WHO WE ARE AS AMERICANS.
>> DOZENS OF AMERICAN EXPERTS
ARRIVE IN MEXICO, HELPING WITH
DESPERATE SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS
MORE THAN TWO DAYS AFTER 7.1
EARTHQUAKE.
I'M LARRY.
>> AND I'M KRISTEN SZE, THE
DEATH TOLL RISEN TO 273.
TOURING THE DAMAGE SOUCHLK
MEXICO CITY, 73 DEATHS REPORTED
THERE.
67 PEOPLE AND FIVE HIGHLY
TRAINED DOGS FROM THE LOS
ANGELES COUNTY FIRE DEPARTMENT
URBAN SEARCH AND RESCUE TEAM
ARRIVED IN MEXICO CITY.
THE MEXICAN GOVERNMENT REQUESTED
THE HELP.
>> TEAMS ARRIVED WITH TOOLS AND
MEDICAL EQUIPMENT TO CONDUCT
AROUND THE CLOCK SEARCH AND
RESCUE OPERATIONS.
>> MORE THAN 50 BUILDINGS
CLAPGSED IN MEXICO CITY ALONE.
ARMED SOLDIERS GUARDING MORE AT
RISK OF COLLAPSING.
>> SEEN PEOPLE IN MEXICO CITY
PERFORM HUMAN CHEFS TO REMOVE
RUBBLE.
ONE SAN FRANCISCO CHEF IS DOING
HER PART TO FEED VOLUNTEERS AND
RESCUE WORKERS IN DEVASTATED
AREAS.
GABR