THERE.
THE COMMERCIALS WILL BE TAPED
NEXT MONTH.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, YOSEMITE ON FIRE.
MONSTER WILDFIRE NOW BURNING ITS
WAY THROUGH THE GREAT AMERICAN
PARK.
WE'RE LIVE ON THE FRONT LINES
TONIGHT AND OUR CAMERAS JUST
FEET FROM THE FLAMES.
THIS VIEW FROM THE SKY THIS
EVENING, THE ALL-OUT BATTLE TO
GET CONTROL.
>>> THIS IS SUMMER.
HAIL TWO FEET DEEP.
THE SNOWPLOWS BACK IN ACTION
TONIGHT.
ABC'S GINGER ZEE RIGHT HERE WITH
THE EXTREME WEATHER COMING THIS
WEEKEND.
>>> THE GREAT ESCAPE.
CAUGHT ON TAPE, THE BRAZEN
PRISON BREAK.
TONIGHT WHAT POLICE HAVE JUST
ANNOUNCED IN THE CASE.
>>> AND GETTING OUT ALIVE.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THOSE STORMS
DROP POWER LINES ON THE STREET
ON YOUR CAR?
HOW TO GET OUT AND THE EXPERTS
WHO SAY YOUR FLOOR MAT COULD
SAVE YOUR LIFE.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
DIANE HAS THE EVENING OFF.
WE DO BEGIN WITH THAT PART OF
THE GREAT NATIONAL PARK BURNING
TONIGHT.
THE WILDFIRE RACING INTO
YOSEMITE.
GROWING AT A BREAK-NECK PACE AND
JUST LOOK, TONIGHT, FIREFIGHTERS
RIGHT THERE ON THE FRONT LINES,
BATTLING THE BLAZE FROM THE
GROUND.
PART OF THE FOREST UP IN FLAMES
TONIGHT.
LOOK AT THIS, ANOTHER VIEW FROM
THE SKY.
THE NATIONAL GUARD LIFTING WATER
FROM A NEARBY LAKE AND DROPPING
IT FROM THE AIR TO DRY TO DOUSE
-- TRY TO DOUSE THE FLAMES.
ONE MORE IMAGE OF THE SCOPE
TONIGHT, A WALL OF SMOKE FILLING
THE SKY AND WORD THIS EVENING
THAT THAT SMOKE NOW SETTING OFF
A RED ALERT FOR AIR QUALITY.
150 MILES AWAY IN RENO.
OUR TEAM IS LIVE INSIDE THE FIRE
ZONE AGAIN TONIGHT AND ABC'S
NEAL KARLINSKY LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: A VIEW OF THE
SURREAL WAR ABOVE YOSEMITE OF A
FIRE THAT IS NOW SO BIG AND SO
FAST-MOVING, VETERAN PILOTS ARE
STUNNED BY THE SIGHT.
>> THAT IS UNREAL.
>> Reporter: FROM THE COCKPIT,
LOOK CLOSELY, THAT SPECK IS A
SPOTTER PLANE, IT UNLEASHES SOME
SMOKE TO MARK THE TARGET,
SECONDS LATER THAT'S WHERE
PILOTS DROP THEIR FLAME
RETARDANT.
>> READY?
DROP.
>> Reporter: THE LAND IS
TORCHING WITH EXTREME FIRE
BEHAVIOR.
YOU CAN CLEARLY SEE TREES IGNITE
AND BE SWALLOWED UP IN SECONDS.
THE PARK, BIGGER THAN THE STATE
OF VERMONT, IS ONLY BEING
TOUCHED BY FIRE ON THE WEST SIDE
RIGHT NOW.
FAR FROM THE CAMP GROUNDS AND
MOUNTAINS THAT MAKE IT SO
FAMOUS.
>> I GOT TO KNOW WHERE PEOPLE
ARE.
>> Reporter: WE CAUGHT UP WITH
HOT SHOT FIRE TEAMS CONCERNED
ABOUT CONDITIONS.
>> YOU GUYS GOT TO -- [ BLEEP ].
>> IF YOU GUYS PULL OUT, I HAVE
TO KNOW.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
>> YOUR JOB HERE IS HOLD THE
LINE.
>> EXACTLY.
>> ARE YOU SURPRISED THE
BEHAVIOR OF THIS FIRE?
>> NEVER SEEN A FIRE MOVE THIS
FAST.
>> REALLY?
>> AND IT'S IN DIFFERENT
DIRECTIONS.
>> Reporter: ALONG THE OTHER
FRONT LINES, HOMES WITH VIEWS OF
THE FIRE BURNING STRAIGHT AT
THEM.
TEAMS OF FIREFIGHTERS ARE
ACTUALLY SLEEPING HERE NOW.
>> I JUST HOPE TO GOD THAT IT
DOESN'T GET PAST THIS POINT.
I HOPE IT DOESN'T BURN ANY OF
THESE HOUSES ON THIS SIDE.
>> Reporter: BACK OUT HERE LIVE,
THIS IS AN AREA THE FIRE JUST
BURNED THROUGH.
YOU GET A SENSE OF THE
DEVASTATION.
THERE ARE STILL HOT SPOTS HERE.
THE FIRE IS BURNING ON TWO
FRONTS RIGHT NOW, ONE NEAR
YOSEMITE, THE OTHER NEAR HOMES
AND THERE'S VERY LITTLE
CONTAINMENT ON EITHER.
>> JUST A STUNNING SCENE.
NEIL, THANK YOU.
THE IMAGES FROM YOSEMITE FOR
TONIGHT.
>>> THE EXTREME WEATHER ALSO THE
STORY SOME 1,100 MILES EAST OF
THERE IN COLORADO THIS EVENING.
SOMETHING WE NEVER THOUGHT WE'D
SEE.
LOOK AT THIS.
IS IT REALLY A SUMMER STORM?
STAGGERING AMOUNTS OF HAIL IN
AUGUST, SNOWPLOWS OUT IN FORCE.
AND GINGER ZEE HERE WITH THE
IMAGES AND THE NEXT THREAT ON
THE WAY THIS WEEKEND.
>> HAIL, AND WATER.
>> Reporter: SO MUCH HAIL AND SO
MUCH WATER, FILLING THE STREETS
OF COLORADO SPRINGS, GROWING TO
GOLF BALL SIZE NEAR DENVER.
HAIL, HALTING TRAFFIC, CLOSING
SEVERAL ROADS, FILLING CARS AND
YARDS AND PLOWS.
YES, PLOWS BUSY CLEARING IT ALL.
THEN THERE WAS THIS ON A
COLORADO HIGHWAY.
>> YOU CAN'T SEE.
>> A COUPLE TRYING TO GET HOME.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN FOUR
INCHES OF RAIN FALLING IN JUST
OVER AN HOUR.
>> IT'S STILL NOT LETTING UP.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, FLASH
FLOODING IN IDAHO, MORE THAN AN
INCH OF RAIN IN LESS THAN 45
MINUTES.
>> WOW, JUST WON'T LET UP.
JINGEER Z
GINGER ZEE IS WITH US NOW.
YOU SAY MORE RAIN THIS WEEKEND
AND POTENTIAL FOR MORE FLOODING?
>> YES AND I HAVE TO INTRODUCE
YOU TO TROPICAL STORM IVO.
THIS WILL BE THE CULPRIT.
THE DESERT AND SOUTHWEST WILL
GET HIT BY CHUNKS OF THE
TROPICAL MOISTURE, NOT ACTUALLY
THE STORM ITSELF.
THAT'S A DIFFERENT COMPUTER
MODEL FROM THE PAST.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU HOW MUCH RAIN
WE'RE TALKING.
SOME OF THE MODELS ARE PRINTING
SCARY NUMBERS, ANYWHERE FROM LAS
VEGAS TO PHOENIX.
YOU SEE THAT BULL'S EYE OF TWO
TO THREE INCHES, COULD BE
LOCALIZED FLOODING AS A BIG
ISSUE GOING INTO SUNDAY AND
MONDAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, GINGER, THANK YOU.
>>> WE DO MOVE ON THIS EVENING
TO WHAT COULD BE A TURNING POINT
FOR AMERICA AND OUR INVOLVEMENT
IN SYRIA.
TONIGHT, VIOLENT NEW CLASHES
ERUPTING RIGHT WHERE THE ALLEGED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACKS TOOK
PLACE THIS WEEK.
AND THIS EVENING A HAUNTING NEW
NUMBER.
ONE MILLION CHILDREN SENT
FLEEING FROM THE VIOLENCE,
WITHOUT HOMES, SOME OF THEM
RIPPED FROM THEIR PARENTS.
THAT'S THE EQUIVALENT OF ALL THE
CHILDREN IN BOSTON AND LOS
ANGELES COMBINED.
TONIGHT IT'S WHAT THE PRESIDENT
IS NOW SAYING ABOUT THOSE
ALLEGED CHEMICAL ATTACKS THAT
SIGNALS AMERICA MIGHT SOON BE
INVOLVED.
ABC'S MARTHA RADDATZ IN THE
REGION ON WHAT IT WAS THE
PRESIDENT SAID.
>> Reporter: THESE ARE THE
IMAGES THAT HAVE HAD THE WHITE
HOUSE HUDDLED IN MARATHON
MEETINGS.
THE SUSPECTED CHEMICAL ATTACK,
SYRIAN WOMEN, CHILDREN,
ESTIMATES RANGING UPWARD OF
1,000 KILLED.
>> WHAT WE'VE SEEN INDICATES
THIS IS CLEARLY A BIG EVENT OF
GRAVE CONCERN.
>> Reporter: SPEAKING TO CNN,
THE PRESIDENT RAISING THE
STAKES.
>> THAT STARTS GETTING TO SOME
CORE NATIONAL INTERESTS THAT THE
UNITED STATES HAS.
>> Reporter: SYRIA'S CHAOS.
ITS CHEMICAL WEAPONS AND ITS
BREEDING OF TERROR, A THREAT TO
THE ENTIRE REGION AND OUR KEY
ALLY, ISRAEL.
ALL OF WHICH COULD MEAN A THREAT
TO AMERICA.
ON THE TABLE, EVERYTHING FROM
MISSILE STRIKES, ON DOWN TO THE
FORMAL ARMING OF THE REBELS,
WHICH AMERICA HAS COMMITTED TO,
BUT STILL HAS NOT DONE.
BUT THOSE IMAGES OF THE
SUSPECTED ATTACK AND THAT
STUNNING MILESTONE OF A MILLION
CHILDREN FLEEING THEIR HOMES HAS
NATIONS ACROSS THE GLOBE SAYING
NOW IS THE TIME TO ACT.
DAVID, THE PRESIDENT DOES NOT
WANT TO GO TO WAR WITH SYRIA.
AMERICA DOES NOT WANT TO GO TO
WAR.
BUT HIS WORDS, THAT THIS IS
IMPACTING AMERICA'S CORE
INTERESTS, ARE CRITICAL.
AND MAKE IT EXTREMELY DIFFICULT
TO JUST STAND BY ANY LONGER.
DAVID?
>> MARTHA, THANK YOU.
WE KNOW YOU'LL BE ANCHORING
ABC'S "THIS WEEK" FROM THE
REGION AND WE'LL ALL BE
WATCHING.
SUNDAY MORNING ON "THIS WEEK".
>>> IN THE MEANTIME TONIGHT, TWO
MAJOR VERDICTS BREAKING THIS
EVENING.
FIRST THE FORT HOOD SHOOTER.
NADAL HASSAN CONVICTED ON ALL
COUNTS IN THE SHOOTING RAMPAGE.
NEARLY FOUR YEARS AGO NOW,
OPENING FIRE ON HIS FELLOW
SOLDIERS, KILLING 13 PEOPLE.
HASSAN DID NOT FLINCH AS THE
VERDICT WAS READ.
HE COULD NOW FACE THE DEATH
PENALTY.
AND ROBERT BALES BEHIND ONE OF
THE WORST ATROCITIES IN THE WAR
IN AFGHANISTAN, THAT MASS
KILLING.
SENTENCED TO LIFE WITHOUT PAROLE
TODAY.
THE FATHER OF TWO CONFESSED TO
KILLING 16 VILLAGERS, MOSTLY
WOMEN AND CHILDREN IN MARCH OF
2012.
THE FAMILIES TRAVELING 7,000
MILES TO TESTIFY AGAINST THE
AMERICAN STAFF SERGEANT.
HE PLEADED GUILTY TO THE
MASSACRE IN ORDER TO AVOID THE
DEATH PENALTY.
>>> NOW TO LAS VEGAS TONIGHT AND
A MAJOR PLOT THWARTED.
AN UNDERCOVER STING THAT BUSTED
A SINISTER PLAN WELL UNDER WAY.
TONIGHT THESE TWO SUSPECTS IN
CUSTODY.
ONE A GRANDMOTHER, BOTH CHARGED
WITH PLANNING TO KIDNAP,
TORTURE, AND KILL A COP, ALL IN
THE SHADOW OF THE SUNSET STRIP.
WHY DID THEY ALLEGEDLY HATCH
THIS PLAN?
HERE'S ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI NOW.
>> Reporter: ON THE GLITTERY
STREETS OF LAS VEGAS, POLICE
WORKING UNDER COVER SINCE APRIL,
SAY THEY EARNED THE TRUST OF
ALLEGED ANTI-GOVERNMENT
SOVEREIGN CITIZENS AND WERE ABLE
TO FOIL THEIR ALLEGED PLANS TO
KILL COPS.
42-YEAR-OLD DAVID BRUTSCHE WAS
ARRESTED TUESDAY WITH
67-YEAR-OLD DEVON NEWMAN, A
GRANDMOTHER LIVING IN A SENIOR
CENTER.
>> I OBJECT.
I'VE HURT NO ONE.
>> Reporter: IN COURT THIS
MORNING, THEY WERE ALL MOUTH.
>> SIR, ONE MORE WORD AND IT'S
CONTEMPT.
>> I OBJECT TO THE ENTIRE
PROCEEDINGS OF THIS COURT.
>> Reporter: PROSECUTORS SAY
THEY PLANNED TO KIDNAP POLICE,
AT ROAD STOPS, SHACKLE THEM WITH
CHAINS, DRAG THEM TO A MAKESHIFT
JAIL AND COURT AND THEN TRY THEM
FOR TREASON.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY WERE
GOING TO EXECUTE THE OFFICERS
AND DUMP THEIR BODIES IN THE
DESERT.
POLICE HAVE LEARNED TO TAKE
SOVEREIGN CITIZENS SERIOUSLY.
IN 2010, TWO OFFICERS WERE
KILLED IN ARKANSAS WHEN THEY
PULLED TWO OF THEM OVER.
THE FBI CALLING EXTREMISTS IN
THE MOVEMENT DOMESTIC
TERRORISTS.
IN A JAIL HOUSE INTERVIEW,
NEWMAN KEPT ON PREACHING,
TELLING AMERICANS TO WAKE UP.
>> I WANT THEM TO REALIZE THAT
OUR FREEDOMS ARE BEING ERODED.
>> Reporter: STEVE OSUNSAMI, ABC
NEWS, ATLANTA.
>> STEVE, THANK YOU.
>>> TO ONE MORE CASE, TONIGHT, A
REAL-LIFE BONNIE AND CLYDE,
PULLING OFF THAT JAIL BREAK.
A MAJOR DEVELOPMENT IN THE CASE.
YOU'LL REMEMBER THESE IMAGES,
THE INMATE RUNNING TO ESCAPE,
HIS GIRLFRIEND WAITING IN THE
GET-AWAY CAR, THE POLICE THEN IN
HOT PURSUIT.
THE TWO ON THE RUN FOR WEEKS,
BUT TONIGHT THEIR RUN SUDDENLY
CUT SHORT.
ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS NOW ON THE
JUMP TO FREEDOM THAT STARTED IT
ALL.
>> Reporter: DEREK ESTELLE SEEN
HERE SQUATTING ON THE FLOOR ON
THE PHONE JUST BEFORE JUMPING ON
TO THE COUNTER, SLITHERING
THROUGH THE WINDOW AND RUNNING
ACROSS THE PARKING LOT WITH
POLICE IN HOT PURSUIT IS TONIGHT
FINALLY BACK IN CUSTODY.
>> IT'S HARD TO TELL OUR
EXCITEMENT TODAY, BUT IF YOU HAD
BEEN HERE LAST NIGHT, YOU WOULD
HAVE SEEN JUMPING UP AND DOWN,
SHAKING HANDS, PATTING EACH
OTHER ON THE BACK.
>> ESTELLE AND HIS GIRLFRIEND,
WHO ALLEGEDLY DROVE THE GET-AWAY
CAR, WERE ON THE RUN FOR 26
DAYS, POLICE HOT ON THEIR TAIL,
EVEN ARRESTING ESTELLE'S MOTHER
FOR HER ALLEGED ROLE IN THE JAIL
BREAK.
LAST NIGHT A TIP TO ARKANSAS
AUTHORITIES LED POLICE TO AN
ABANDONED HOME IN SANTA ROSA
COUNTY, FLORIDA.
WHERE THE COUPLE WAS HIDING OUT.
THEY WERE SURROUNDED AND
ARRESTED WITHOUT INCIDENT.
>> WE'VE TAKEN EXTRA STEPS TO
MAKE SURE IT DOESN'T HAPPEN
AGAIN.
LOCKING MECHANISMS ON THE
DETENTION CENTER DOORS.
THE SLIDING WINDOW THAT HE WAS
ABLE TO GET THROUGH HAS NOW BEEN
SEALED.
>> Reporter: THEIR HOPE NOW, HIS
HOUDINI-LIKE ESCAPE WILL BE HIS
LAST.
LINSEY DAVIS, ABC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> AND TO THE STAND-OFF PLAYING
OUT ALL WEEK IN SAN DIEGO.
SO MANY OF THE PEOPLE THERE
TELLING THEIR MAYOR IT'S TIME TO
GO.
TONIGHT HE IS GONE.
AFTER THOSE STORIES OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT FROM YOUNG WOMEN TO
GRANDMOTHERS COMING FORWARD.
THAT 1-800 HOTLINE SET UP WITH
THE NUMBERS GROWING.
RYAN OWENS IS THERE WITH THE
NEWEST TURN.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING TO
YOU, MAYOR BOB FILNER IS OUT
AFTER SIX WEEKS OF SCANDAL.
HIS LAST DAY IS AT THE END OF
THIS MONTH.
THE CITY COUNCIL HERE LATE TODAY
UNANIMOUSLY ACCEPTED HIS
RESIGNATION.
MINUTES AFTER THROWING IN THE
TOWEL, THE EMBATTLED MAYOR SPOKE
TO HIS SUPPORTERS, SPECIFICALLY
TO THE 18 WOMEN WHO HAVE ACCUSED
HIM OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT.
>> TO ALL THE WOMEN THAT I
OFFENDED, I HAD NO INTENTION TO
BE OFFENSIVE.
I HAVE NEVER SEXUALLY HARASSED
ANYONE.
BUT THIS HYSTERIA HAS BEEN
CREATED AND MANY OF YOU HELPED
DEFEAT IS THE HYSTERIA OF A
LYNCH MOB.
>> THAT FIERY DENIAL FROM A
70-YEAR-OLD MAN WHO CRITICS SAY
HAS BROUGHT EMBARRASSMENT TO
AMERICA'S EIGHTH LARGEST CITY.
MANY MAY BE RELIEVED TO SEE HIM
GO, BUT THE CONSUMMATE
POLITICIAN SEEMS DETERMINED TO
CLEAR HIS NAME.
>> I CAN'T AFFORD TO CONTINUE
THIS BATTLE, EVEN THOUGH I KNOW,
IF GIVEN DUE PROCESS, I WOULD BE
VINDICATED.
>> THE CITY OF SAN DIEGO AGREED
TO PAY AT LEAST SOME OF HIS
LEGAL EXPENSES.
DAVID?
>> RYAN OWENS, THANK YOU.
>>> PAULA DEEN IS BACK IN THE
NEWS TONIGHT.
A JUDGE DISMISSING THE LAWSUIT
THAT LED TO THE CHAOS WITHIN HER
FOOD AND TV EMPIRE.
A FORMER EMPLOYEE ACCUSED DEEN
AND HER BROTHER OF RACIAL
DISCRIMINATION AND SEXUAL
HARASSMENT.
THE TWO SIDES AGREE TO A
SETTLEMENT WITHOUT MONEY
CHANGING HANDS.
DEEN HAS ALREADY LOST MILLIONS
OF DOLLARS WHEN COMPANIES
SEVERED TIES WITH HER, INCLUDING
THE FOOD NETWORK AND WALMART.
>>> AND WORD TONIGHT OF A NEW
ARRIVAL AT THE NATIONAL ZOO IN
WASHINGTON.
A GIANT PANDA GAVE BIRTH TO A
CUB THIS AFTERNOON.
NO NAME YET.
BUT MAMA PICKED UP HER CUB
IMMEDIATELY AND STARTED CRADLING
IT.
TODAY'S BIRTH COMES AS MATT
GUTMAN GOT A LOOK AT THE TWIN
PANDAS IN THE ATLANTA ZOO, THE
FIRST TWIN PANDAS BORN IN THE
U.S. IN 26 YEARS.
"PANDAMONIUM" TONIGHT.
I HAD TO.
>>> SO MUCH MORE AHEAD HERE ON
"WORLD NEWS" THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
COMING UP WITH THE EXTREME
STORMS ON THE WAY THIS WEEKEND,
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN POWER LINES
COME DOWN ON YOUR HOME, ON YOUR
CAR.
TONIGHT, HOW TO GET OUT ALIVE,
AND GET THIS, THE FLOOR MAT IN
YOUR CAR COULD SAVE YOUR LIFE.
>>> AND LATER TONIGHT HERE THE
LITTLE BOY ON THE SIDELINES
GETTING A TALKING TO.
WHAT WE LEARNED LATE TODAY ABOUT
THE MAJOR LEAGUE COACH IN HIS
FACE AND WHY SO MANY MOMS AND
DADS OUT THERE WILL BE NODDING
THEIR HEADS WHEN YOU HEAR WHAT
HE HAS TO SAY.
[ Male Announcer ]
WHAT'S IMPORTANT TO YOU?
AT HUMANA, OUR MEDICARE AGENTS
SIT DOWN WITH YOU AND ASK.
HANGING OUT WITH THIS GUY.
HE'S JUST THE LOVE OF MY LIFE.
[ Male Announcer ]
GETTING TO KNOW YOU
IS HOW WE HELP YOU CHOOSE
THE HUMANA MEDICARE PLAN
THAT WORKS BEST FOR YOU.
MI FAMILIA.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
WE WANT TO HELP YOU ACHIEVE
YOUR BEST HEALTH,
SO YOU CAN KEEP DOING
THE THINGS
THAT ARE IMPORTANT TO YOU.
KEEPING UP WITH THEM.
I LOVE IT!
[ Male Announcer ]
HELPING YOU --
NOW THAT'S WHAT'S IMPORTANT
TO US.
does your dog food have?
[ Male Announcer ]
HELPING YOU --
18 percent?
20?
New Purina ONE True Instinct
has 30.
Active dogs crave nutrient-dense
food.
So we made Purina ONE True
Instinct.
Learn more at PurinaONE.com
[ CRASHING ]
[ Male Announcer ] WHEN YOUR
FAVORITE FOOD STARTS A FIGHT,
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
AND GOES TO WORK IN SECONDS.
♪ TUM, TUM TUM TUM TUMS!
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS
TO MAKE THE CALL.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE,
MY DOCTOR AND I
WENT WITH AXIRON,
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT THE
ONLY UNDERARM LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
>>> YOU LIKELY HEARD GINGER
MENTIONING EARLIER THE STORMS ON
THE WAY THIS WEEKEND.
WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THAT EXTREME
WEATHER BRINGS DOWN THE POWER
LINES?
TONIGHT ABC'S GIO BENITEZ INSIDE
A CAR AND IT TURNS OUT THE FLOOR
MAT COULD BE THE KEY TO GETTING
OUT ALIVE.
>> Reporter: THEY ARE THE
SPLIT-SECOND DECISIONS IN
EXTREME WEATHER THAT COULD MEAN
LIFE OR DEATH.
>> WHAT IS HE DOING?
>> Reporter: HOW DO YOU SURVIVE
UNTIL HELP ARRIVES?
>> IF YOU THINK AND ACT LIKE A
NAVY SEAL, YOU CAN SURVIVE
ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: WE ASKED A FORMER
NAVY SEAL WHO WROTE THE SEAL
SURVIVAL GUIDE.
WHEN DISASTER STRIKES IN THE
CAR, DO YOU ABANDON SHIP OR DO
YOU STAY PUT?
>> IT DEPENDS ON THE SITUATION.
>> Reporter: ONE OF THE MOST
COMMON DISASTERS, A DOWNED POWER
LINE ON TOP OF A CAR.
A HAZARD IN ANY STORM.
IF YOU'RE NOT IN IMMEDIATE
DANGER, STAY PUT.
BUT WHAT IF YOUR CAR'S ON FIRE
AND YOU HAVE TO GET OUT?
>> MOST FLOOR MATS ARE MADE OF
RUBBER.
OPEN YOUR DOOR, GRAB THAT MAT,
PUT IT OUT A FOOT AND A HALF,
TWO FEET OUTSIDE.
KEEPING YOURSELF -- OH, YOU JUST
KILLED YOURSELF.
BECAUSE YOU ALLOWED AN ARC TO
COME THROUGH ONE LEG THAT WAS
SEPARATED AND KILLED YOURSELF.
IF YOU KEEP YOUR FEET TOGETHER
ON THE MAT AND WITHOUT TOUCHING
THE EXTERIOR OF THE VEHICLE,
USE THE SEAT, GO AHEAD AND PUSH
YOURSELF UP.
KEEP YOUR FEET TOGETHER AND PULL
YOURSELF HOP, NOW WITH FEET
TOGETHER, SLOWLY HOP AWAY FROM
THE CAR.
THAT'S YOUR BEST BET FOR GETTING
OUT OF THIS.
>> BUT AGAIN, YOU ONLY WANT TO
GET OUT IF YOU HAVE TO.
OTHERWISE EXPERTS SAY, STAY IN
YOUR CAR IF A POWER LINE FALLS
ON IT.
>> THE FLOOR MAT, WHO KNEW?
YOU'LL HAVE MUCH MORE TONIGHT, I
KNOW.
ALSO TONIGHT ON "20/20," WE
REVEAL THE TEN MOST DANGEROUS
ROADS IN AMERICA.
IS ONE OF THEM IN YOUR HOMETOWN?
TONIGHT ON A SPECIAL "20/20" AT
10:00 P.M. EASTERN.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
DEBATE OVER THE NEW BATMAN.
WE WANT YOU TO WEIGH IN.
AND LATER, THE MAJOR LEAGUE
COACH GIVING THE TINY FAN A
TALKING TO.
MOMS AND DADS CHEERING.
TONIGHT WE LEARN ABOUT WHAT HE
DOES BEFORE HE WALKS AWAY.
[ Male Announcer ]
NOBODY KNOWS WHERE OR WHEN
THE NEXT POWERFUL STORM
IS GOING TO HIT...
BUT IT WILL...
THAT'S WHY
THERE'S A NEW DURACELL BATTERY.
INTRODUCING DURACELL QUANTUM.
WITH ITS HIGH DENSITY CORE,
IT'S A QUANTUM LEAP
IN BATTERY POWER.
THE NEXT STORM IS OUT THERE.
BUT SO ARE THE HEROES.
SO WE'RE GIVING
A MILLION DURACELL QUANTUM
TO FIRST RESPONDERS EVERYWHERE.
POWER. IN THE HANDS
OF THE MOST POWERFUL.
DURACELL.
TRUSTED EVERYWHERE.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
HAVING SOME FIBER!
WITH NEW Phillips'
Fiber Good Gummies.
THEY'RE FRUITY DELICIOUS!
JUST TWO GUMMIES
HAVE 4 GRAMS OF FIBER!
TO HELP SUPPORT
REGULARITY!
I WANT SOME...
[ Woman ] HOP ON OVER!
[ Marge ] FIBER THE FUN WAY,
FROM Phillips'.
[ Male Announcer ] EVER WONDER
WHY NO OTHER MOUTHWASH
FEELS LIKE LISTERINE®?
BECAUSE NO OTHER MOUTHWASH
WORKS LIKE LISTERINE®.
IN YOUR MOUTH,
BACTERIA FORMS IN LAYERS.
LISTERINE® PENETRATES
THESE LAYERS
DEEPER THAN OTHER MOUTHWASHES,
KILLING BACTERIA ALL THE WAY
DOWN TO THE BOTTOM LAYER.
SO FOR A CLEANER,
HEALTHIER MOUTH,
GO WITH THE MOUTHWASH
DENTISTS RECOMMEND
MORE THAN ALL OTHERS COMBINED.
#1 DENTIST RECOMMENDED
LISTERINE®...
POWER TO YOUR MOUTH™.
#1 DENTIST RECOMMENDED
SHE'AND YOU LOVE HER FOR IT.IDE.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A
QUESTION OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY ANYTIME
THE MOMENT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS
THE ONLY DAILY ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED
AND SYMPTOMS OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL YOUR MEDICAL
CONDITIONS AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN 4 HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC
REACTIONS SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
with freshly bakedeve in
whole grain bread.right
Then we add
all-natural eggs...
lean antibiotic-free ham...
and Vermont white cheddar.
Get 16 grams of protein
and 23 grams
of whole grain
in the Breakfast
Power Sandwich.
>>> OUR "INSTANT INDEX" ON A
FRIDAY NIGHT, EVERYONE DEBATING
THE NEW PIC TONIGHT.
YOU KNOW THE THEME.
♪ BATMAN
>> WELL, THE NEW BATMAN TONIGHT,
BEN AFFLECK, WHO JOINS A LONG
LINE OF CAPED CRUSADERS ON THE
BIG SCREEN -- KEATON, CLOONEY,
KILMER, CHRISTIAN BALE, OF
COURSE.
BUT NOT EVERYONE IS SURE HE'S
THE RIGHT CHOICE.
TWEET AND LET ME KNOW WHAT YOU
THINK.
>>> AND THE MAJOR LEAGUE PEP
TALK GOING VIRAL.
A TINY FAN AT THE ROCKIES GAME,
WE FIRST SHOWED IT ON GMA.
CORNERED BY FIRST BASE COACH
RENE LACHEMANN, IT HAS MOMS AND
DADS CHEERING.
SEE IF YOU CHEER TOO.
HE STARTS ABOUT THE VIRTUES OF
TAKING OUT THE TRASH.
>> WHEN YOUR DAD TELLS YOU TO
TAKE OUT THE TRASH, YOU TAKE IT
OUT.
WHEN YOUR MOTHER TELLS YOU TO
CLEAN YOUR ROOM UP, YOU CLEAN IT
UP.
YOU COME HOME FROM SCHOOL, THE
FIRST THING YOU DO IS DO YOUR
HOMEWORK.
YOU UNDERSTAND THAT?
YOU EAT YOUR DINNER AND YOUR
VEGETABLES.
YOU GOT A BROTHER AND SISTER?
>> YEP.
>> DON'T BE FIGHTING WITH THEM.
>> WE LOVE THIS GUY.
WE ALSO LEARNED SOMETHING ELSE.
HE'S MADE IT A TRADITION TO GIVE
A SOUVENIR BASEBALL AFTER THAT
PEP TALK.
HE ALSO SAYS, "SANTA'S
WATCHING," BY THE WAY.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE YOUNG
-- THE BOLD MOVE FROM THE YOUNG
MOTHER WHOSE VOICE AND MUSIC YOU
KNOW.
♪ CONCRETE JUNGLE WHERE DREAMS
ARE MADE OF ♪
>> TONIGHT WHAT ALICIA KEYS DID
THIS WEEK AS THE CAMERAS WERE
ROLLING AND WHO SHE'S OUT TO
SAVE TONIGHT.
IF YOU'RE LOOKING FOR HELP
RELIEVING HEARTBURN,
CAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES
24-HOUR HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL
PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
YOU KNOW, FROM OUR 4,000
TELEVISION COMMERCIALS.
YEP, THERE I AM WITH FLO.
HOO-HOO! WATCH IT!
[Chuckles] ANYHOO, 3 MILLION
PEOPLE SWITCHED TO ME LAST YEAR,
SAVING AN AVERAGE
OF $475.
[Sigh] IT FEELS GOOD
TO HELP PEOPLE SAVE...
WITH GREAT DISCOUNTS LIKE
SAFE DRIVER, MULTICAR,
AND MULTIPOLICY.
SO CALL ME TODAY.
YOU'LL BE GLAD YOU DID.
CANNONBOX!
[SPLASH!]
A BODY AT REST
TENDS TO STAY AT REST...
WHILE A BODY IN MOTION
TENDS TO STAY IN MOTION.
STAYING ACTIVE CAN ACTUALLY
EASE ARTHRITIS SYMPTOMS.
BUT IF YOU HAVE ARTHRITIS,
STAYING ACTIVE
CAN BE DIFFICULT.
PRESCRIPTION CELEBREX
CAN HELP RELIEVE ARTHRITIS PAIN
SO YOUR BODY
CAN STAY IN MOTION.
BECAUSE JUST ONE
200MG CELEBREX A DAY
CAN PROVIDE 24 HOUR RELIEF
FOR MANY WITH ARTHRITIS PAIN
AND INFLAMMATION.
PLUS, IN CLINICAL STUDIES,
CELEBREX IS PROVEN TO IMPROVE
DAILY PHYSICAL FUNCTION
SO MOVING IS EASIER.
CELEBREX CAN BE TAKEN
WITH OR WITHOUT FOOD.
AND IT'S NOT A NARCOTIC.
YOU AND YOUR DOCTOR
SHOULD BALANCE THE BENEFITS
WITH THE RISKS.
ALL PRESCRIPTION NSAIDS,
LIKE CELEBREX, IBUPROFEN,
NAPROXEN AND MELOXICAM
HAVE THE SAME
CARDIOVASCULAR WARNING.
THEY ALL MAY INCREASE
THE CHANCE
OF HEART ATTACK OR STROKE,
WHICH CAN LEAD TO DEATH.
THIS CHANCE INCREASES
IF YOU HAVE HEART DISEASE
OR RISK FACTORS
SUCH AS HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
OR WHEN NSAIDS ARE TAKEN
FOR LONG PERIODS.
NSAIDS, LIKE CELEBREX,
INCREASE THE CHANCE OF SERIOUS
SKIN OR ALLERGIC REACTIONS,
OR STOMACH AND INTESTINE
PROBLEMS,
SUCH AS BLEEDING AND ULCERS,
WHICH CAN OCCUR WITHOUT WARNING
AND MAY CAUSE DEATH.
PATIENTS ALSO TAKING ASPIRIN
AND THE ELDERLY
ARE AT INCREASED RISK FOR
STOMACH BLEEDING AND ULCERS.
DON'T TAKE CELEBREX
IF YOU HAVE BLEEDING
IN THE STOMACH OR INTESTINE,
OR HAD AN ASTHMA ATTACK, HIVES,
OTHER ALLERGIES TO ASPIRIN,
NSAIDS OR SULFONAMIDES.
GET HELP RIGHT AWAY IF YOU HAVE
SWELLING OF THE FACE OR THROAT,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
YOUR MEDICAL HISTORY.
AND FIND AN ARTHRITIS TREATMENT
FOR YOU.
VISIT CELEBREX.COM AND ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CELEBREX.
FOR A BODY IN MOTION.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE, OUR
PERSON OF THE WEEK.
YOU KNOW HER VOICE ON STAGE, BUT
HAVE YOU HEARD IT BEHIND THE
SCENES TOO?
SAVING LIVES.
TONIGHT ALICIA KEYS USING THE
POWER OF HER VOICE RIGHT HERE AT
HOME.
♪ SHE'S JUST A GIRL AND SHE'S ON
FIRE ♪
>> YOU ALREADY KNOW ALICIA KEYS
AND THAT SINGULAR VOICE.
♪
>> BUT FOR THE LAST DECADE SHE'S
BEEN QUIETLY USING THAT VOICE TO
SAVE OTHERS.
♪
>> TEACHING PREVENTION AND
TREATMENT FOR HIV.
HER ORGANIZATION, KEEP A CHILD
ALIVE.
♪
>> AND THE CHILDREN IN THOSE
TOWNS AND VILLAGES IN AFRICA,
SHE'S HELPED TO SAVE.
THEY NOW SING TO HER.
♪
>> AND THIS WEEK, SHE CAME HOME
TO NEW YORK TO SIT DOWN WITH US.
SHE ALSO DID SOMETHING ELSE.
AS CAMERAS WERE ROLLING, SHE
TOOK A TEST.
A RAPID HIV TEST, TO REIGNITE
THE CONVERSATION HERE IN
AMERICA.
>> YOU SAY THAT A LOT OF US MAKE
THE MISTAKE OF THINKING IT'S
JUST HAPPENING OVER THERE.
>> I REALIZE, I MYSELF EVEN,
WE'RE JUST NOT TALKING ABOUT IT
IN AMERICA.
THERE'S SO MANY PEOPLE WHO ARE
FINDING THEMSELVES NEWLY
INFECTED.
THE INFECTION RATE IS JUST
REMAINING THE SAME.
IT'S NOT GOING DOWN HERE IN
AMERICA.
>> AND TONIGHT SHE'S BEHIND A
BRAND NEW PROJECT, EMPOWERED.
SITTING DOWN WITH WOMEN FROM ALL
OVER AMERICA LIVING WITH HIV AND
SURVIVING.
JEN IS A WIFE AND A MOTHER.
>> PRETTY MUCH EVERYONE WHO ENDS
UP HIV-POSITIVE SAYS, I DIDN'T
THINK IT COULD HAPPEN TO ME.
AND THEN IT HAPPENED TO ME.
>> ALICIA WANTS THESE WOMEN TO
KNOW THEY HAVEN'T BEEN
FORGOTTEN.
SHE WANTS TO WIPE OUT HIV FOR
THE NEXT GENERATION.
HER SON NOW 2 YEARS OLD, NOW
WITH HER ON TOUR, BUT HE DOESN'T
GET TO STAY UP WITH HER FOR THE
WHOLE CONCERT.
BUT KNOWS EVERY WORD.
♪ NEW YORK, CONCRETE JUNGLE
WHERE DREAMS ARE MADE OF ♪
>> THAT'S BECOME THE THEME SONG
FOR NEW YORK CITY.
FOR THE WORLD.
THE WORLD NOW SINGS THAT SONG.
>> IT'S THE ONE THING WE CAN ALL
SAY WE CAN TOTALLY CONNECT WITH
AND THAT WOULD DRIVE US ALL TO
HAVE A CHANCE.
AND THAT SONG IS ALL ABOUT THAT.
>> HAVING A CHANCE.
THE SINGER LOOKING OUT FOR THOSE
CHILDREN ALL OVER THE WORLD AND
FOR HER LITTLE ONE WHEN HE NEEDS
IT MOST.
>> TAKE HIM AND ROCK HIM IN MY
ARMS, SAY IT'S OKAY, YOU WANT
MOMMY TO SING ME A SONG?
HE SAYS, SING BRAND NEW ME.
>> CAN YOU GIVE US A BAR?
♪ IT'S BEEN A WHILE
I'M NOT WHO I WAS BEFORE
♪ YOU LOOK SURPRISED
BEEN MEANING TO TELL YOU ♪
♪ BUT I GUESS IT'S CLEAR TO SEE
♪ DON'T BE MAD
♪ IT'S JUST A BRAND NEW KIND OF
ME ♪
>> THAT'S FOR THE LITTLE GUY AND
FOR ME.
THANK YOU.
>> AND SO WE CHOOSE ALICIA KEYS
WORKING TOWARDS AN AIDS FREE
GENERATION.
WHAT A VOICE.
SEE YOU LATER TONIGHT ON
"20/20."
DIANE SAWYER RIGHT BACK HERE
MONDAY NIGHT.
>>> TONIGHT LIVE TEAM COVERAGE
ON THE RIM FIRE NEAR YOSEMITE
FORCING HUNDREDS OUT.
>> FROM A SAN FRANCISCO
COMMAND CENTER TONIGHT HOW THE
FIRE CUTOFF POWER SUPPLY TO
MUNI WHAT IT COULD DO TO
WATERS.
>> ONLY ON 7 TONIGHT A PEEK
INSIDE OF THE NEW CALDECOTT
TUNNEL.
THE OTHER BIG HIGHWAY PROJECT
ALMOST READY TO GO AND HOW
GOOGLE'S GADGET OF THE FUTURE
HAS BECOME A GAME CHANGER FOR
A LOCAL WOMAN WHO HAS DOUM
DEPEND ON IT.
>> WE HAVE EVERYTHING LOADED
AND READY ON TRAILERS AND
STUFF TO GO IF WE NEED TO GO.
EVERYBODY IS ON HIGH ALERT.
>> VAC WAIGSS ARE NOW
MANDATORY IN SOME
NEIGHBORHOODS NEAR YOS STIM
WHERE THE FIRE MAY QUICKLY
BECOME ONE OF THE BIGGEST IN
CALIFORNIA HISTORY.
GOOD EVENING, I'M CHERYL
JENNINGS.
>> MORE THAN 100,000 ACRES THE
RIM FIRE IS THE 20th LARGEST
WILDFIRE ON RECORD DATING BACK
TO 1932.
WITH JUST 2% CONTAINMENT IT'S
CERTAIN TO CERTAIN TO RISE ON
THAT LIST.
NOW, IT KURNS AN AREA BESIDE
THE CITY OF SAN JOSE.
EVACUATIONS ARE MANDATORY FOR
HUNDREDS ON THE WESTERN FLANK
OF THE FIRE AND RECOMMENDED
FOR PEOPLE ABOUT FIVE MILES
FROM THE FIRE LINES.
NANNETTE?
>> THERE SEEMS TO BE NO END IN
SITE.
THE FIRE BURNED AN AREA THREE
TIMES THE SIZE OF SAN
FRANCISCO IN SIX DAYS.
>> IT'S JUST PEERING NORTH.
>> LARGE PLUMES OF SMOKE ARE
THE SIGNS THE RIM FIRE IS NOW
BURNING OUT OF CONTROL.
105,000 ACRES HAVE BURNED.
>> FIRE BEHAVIOR IS EXTREME.
DRY FUELS.
SECOND IS A TINDER DRY.
>> FROM GROUND CREWS WHAT THAT
HAD TO WORK HARDER.