HOW YOU LIKE IT.
>>> TONIGHT, BREAKING NEWS AS WE
COME ON THE AIR.
HURRICANE MARIA'S DIRECT HIT,
SLAMMING INTO PUERTO RICO AS A
CATEGORY 4.
ONE EMERGENCY OFFICIAL TONIGHT
SAYING THE ISLAND IS DESTROYED.
THE ENTIRE ISLAND WITHOUT POWER.
A CURFEW IN PLACE.
AND THE NEW MODELS TONIGHT.
THE TRACK AS HURRICANE MARIA
THEN GETS CLOSER TO THE EAST
COAST, AND THE TIMING.
>>> ALSO BREAKING, WE ARE ON THE
SCENE OF A FRANTIC RESCUE
OPERATION RIGHT NOW IN MEXICO
CITY.
CHILDREN TRAPPED IN A SCHOOL.
THE CATASTROPHIC EARTHQUAKE.
BUILDINGS COLLAPSING.
THE EXPLOSION.
THE DEATH TOLL RISING TONIGHT.
>>> JUST IN THIS EVENING.
NORTH KOREA NOW RESPONDING TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP, REFERRING TO
KIM JONG-UN AS ROCKET MAN.
WHAT THEY'RE SAYING NOW.
>>> THE HORROR LATE TODAY AT
YANKEE STADIUM.
THE FOUL BALL AND THE LITTLE
GIRL.
THE PLAYERS SHAKEN AND IN TEARS
ON THE FIELD.
>>> AND STRUCK BY LIGHTNING.
THE FATHER AND TWO CHILDREN
VISITING A NATIONAL PARK.
THEIR FIRST CAMPING TRIP.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND IT'SREAT THAVE YOU WITH
US HERE ON A WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
AND WE BEGIN WITH THE FIRST
PICTURES NOW COMING IN FROM
PUERTO RICO, AFTER TAKING A
DIRECT HIT.
HURRICANE MARIA SLAMMING INTO
THE ISLAND, AND AS YOU HEARD,
ONE OFFICIAL SAYING, THE ISLAND
IS DESTROYED.HE FIRST CATEGORY O
HIT THERE IN NEARLY A CENTURY.
150-MILE-AN-HOUR WINDS RIPPING
BUILDINGS APART, KNOCKING OUT
POWER EVERYWHERE.
ALL OF THE ELECTRICITY IS OUT
TONIGHT.
PEOPLE ORDERED TO STAY INSIDE
UNTIL AT LEAST TOMORROW AMID
FEARS OF MORE MASSIVE FLOODING
TO COME.
AND THE SATELLITE IMAGE TONIGHT
DWARFING THE ISLAND.
NO PART OF IT WAS SPARED.
ABC'S VICTOR OQUENDO LEADING US
OFF FROM SAN JUAN TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, MARIA'S
DIRECT HIT, DEVASTATING PUERTO
RICO.
THE FIRST CATEGORY 4 STORM TO
STRIKE PUERTO RICO IN 85 YEARS,.
>> WE ARE BACK HERE ON THE
NORTHERN SIDE OF SAN JUAN HERE.
I CAN ONLY IMAGINE WHAT WENT
DOWN WHEN THIS THING MADE
LANDFALL ON THE SOUTHEAST CORNER
OF THIS ISLAND.
OBVIOUSLY, THE EYE GETTING
CLOSER AND CLOSER TO US, THAT
EYE WALL NOW SCRAPING THE
NORTHERN BEACHES THERE.
>> Reporter: ROOFS PEELED FROM
BUILDINGS.
DEBRIS FLYING.
STRUCTURES COLLAPSING.NCHES OF
AREAS, ENGULFING WHOLE
NEIGHBORS.
MICHELLE TORRES USING EVERYTHING
SHE CAN TO KEEP THE WATER OUT.
>> THE WIND HOWLED AND
SCREECHED.
THE DOORS RATTLED.
>> Reporter: WE ARE OUTSIDE OF
SAN JUAN, AND IT WAS HIT VERY
HARD.
A LOT OF DESTRUCTION TO HOMES,
DOWNED TREES AND POWER LINES, AS
WELL.
AND NOW, THEY'RE DEALING WITH
THIS.
FLOODING IN EVERY DIRECTION.
THE EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT
DIRECTOR SAYING THE ENTIRE
ISLAND IS DESTROYED.
MANY OF THESE HOMES NOT BUILT TO
WITHSTAND ANY HURRICANE, LET
ALONE A CATEGORY 4.
>> IT TOOK MY HOUSE.
>> Reporter: IS THAT ALL WIND
DAMAGE, IS THAT WHAT HAPPENED
HERE?
>> WIND DAGEMA.
>> Reporter: HOSPITALS DAMAGED,
RUNNING ON GENERATOR POWER.
WE'RE STANDING ON ONE OF THE
BUSIEST THOROUGHFARES IN ALL OF
SAN JUAN, PUERTO RICO.
THE JOHN K. KENNEDY EXPRESSWAY.
NOT A SINGLE CAR IN SIGHT.
WE'RE THE ONLY ONES OUT HERE.
EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT NOW
CONFIRMS, 100% OF PUERTO RICO
NOW WITHOUT POWER.
EVERYWHERE YOU LOOK, DOWNED
POWER LINES LIKE THESE, WHICH
STRETCH RIGHT ACROSS THE
EXPRESSWAY.
12,000 PEOPLE HEEDING THE CALL
TO GET TO SHELTERS, INCLUDING
OUR HOTEL'S BALLROOM.
EVACUEES MOVED OFF THIS ARENA
FLOOR, DUE TO SAFETY CONCERNS.
THE HOWLING WIND PIERCING THE
DARKNESS.
♪
TERRIFIED RESIDENTS SINGING
ABOUT STRENGTH DURING TRYING
TIMES TO EASE THE FEAR.
♪
DAVID, YOU CAN SEE THE DAMAGE
RIGHT HERE BEHIND ME.
THIS IS WHAT SO MANY STREETS
ACROSS SAN JUAN LOOK LIKE
TONIGHT.
OFFICIALS SAYING MANY AREAS WILL
BE UNINHABITABLE FOR WEEKS,
MAYBE EVEN MONTHS.
THEY'RE URGING PEOPLE TO SHELTER
IN PLACE.
THEY'VE ISSUED A CURFEW AND THE
GOVERNOR NOW SAYING HE IS
LAUNCHING SEARCH AND RESCUE
TEAMS AS WE SPEAK.
DAVID?
>> VICTOR OQUENDO LEADING US OFF
FROM SAN JUAN.
VICTOR, THANK YOU.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO SENIOR
METEOROLOGIST ROB MARCIANO LIVE
IN SAN JUAN, AS WELL.
ROB, WHERE IS THIS HURRICANE
TONIGHT?
AND YOU HAVE THE NEW MODELS, THE
TIMING, AS IT GETS CLOSER TO THE
EAST COAST.
>> Reporter: VERY IMPORTANT
FORECAST, DAVID.
FIRST OF ALL, THE CENTER OF THIS
THING IS NOW OFF THE COAST,
ABOUT 75 MILES EAST OF THE
DOMINICAN REPUBLIC.
THE MOUNTAINS OF PUERTO RICO
TOOK A LITTLE STEAM OUT OF IT.
IT'S A CATEGORY 2 NOW,
110-MILE-AN-HOUR WINDS.
IT MAY VERY WELL STRENGTHEN
AGAIN AS IT HEADS TOWARDS THE
TURKS AND CAICOS.
SHOULD STAY AWAY FROM THE MOST
POPULATED AREAS THERE.
GETTING UP TOWARDS THE CAROLINAS
COME MONDAY.
WHAT IT DOES AFTER THAT,
CERTAINLY SOME QUESTION MARKS,
BUT OUR LONGER TERM MODELS, AS
YOU MENTIONED, DO HAVE IT COMING
A LITTLE BIT CLOSER TO THE
COASTLINE, MAYBE COMING UP
TOWARDS NEW ENGLAND, MAYBE
TAKING A VERY JOSE-LIKE TRACK.
TOO SOON TO TELL WHETHER IT WILL
IMPACT THE U.S. DIRECTLY.
BUT SOMETHING WE'LL BE WATCHING
VERY, VERY CLOSELY IN THE COMING
DAYS.
DAVID?
>> AS WE ALL THINK OF THE PEOPLE
OF PUERTO RICO TONIGHT.
ROB, IN THE MEANTIME, OUR THANKS
TO YOU AND TO VICTOR.
>>> WE TURN NEXT TO THE OTHER
DEVASTATING SCENE UNFOLDING
RIGHT NOW.
THE CATASTROPHIC EARTHQUAKE IN
MEXICO.
BUILDINGS COMING DOWN.
PEOPLE TRAPPED.
SO MANY OF THEM CHILDREN.
TONIGHT, WE'RE ON THE SCENE OF A
SCHOOL COLLAPSE.
SOME OF THE CHILDREN HAVE BEEN
PULLED OUT.
AND RESCUE CREWS SHOUTING
"SILENCE" SO OFTEN TODAY, IN THE
MOMENTS THEY THOUGHT THEY COULD
HEAR THE CHILDREN.
ABC'S MATT GUTMAN IS ON THE
SCENE TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, AT THAT
SCHOOL, RESCUERS PEERING INTO A
HOLE.
SUDDENLY YELLING, "THERE ARE
CHILDREN HERE, THERE ARE
CHILDREN HERE."
THEN, PULLING A SMALL CHILD OUT.
DUSTY, MISERABLE, BUT ALIVE.
HUNDREDS STILL PRYING AWAY AT
THE DEBRIS, HOPING TO UNCOVER A
SIGN OF LIFE.
A LITTLE GIRL, BELIEVED TO BE
ENTOMBED IN THE RUBBLE THAT WAS
ONCE HER SCHOOL, POSSIBLY
COMMUNICATING WITH LOVED ONES BY
TEXT MESSAGES.
TONIGHT, POLICE ESCORTING US
INTO A SEARCH BOTH FRANTIC AND
EERILY QUIET.
FIRST RESPONDERS CRANING IN TO
LISTEN FOR A SIGN OF LIFE.
YOU SEE THOSE HANDS UP IN THE
AIR.
THEY'VE JUST CALLED FOR SILENCE.
THAT MEANS THEY'RE TRYING TO
LISTEN TO SEE IF THEY CAN
ACTUALLY HEAR THE PERSON THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR INSIDE STILL.
THAT SCENE REPEATING ITSELF ALL
AFTERNOON.
BUT SO FAR, THAT MISSING GIRL
HAS NOT BEEN FOUND.
YOU CAN SEE THE DESTRUCTION FROM
OVERHEAD.
"SILENCE" WRITTEN IN HUGE
LETTERS.
THROUGH A WINDOW, CHILDREN'S
BACKPACKS STILL HANGING ON THEIR
HOOKS.
13-YEAR-OLD RODRIGO NARROWLY
PICAESNG
HE SAYS, "WE HAD TO BE EVACUATED
BY CRAWLING OVER A WALL."
THE SCHOOL, ONE OF DOZENS OF
BUILDINGS THAT COLLAPSED IN
CENTRAL MEXICO WHEN THE MASSIVE
7.1 QUAKE STRUCK.
SENDING MILLIONS INTO THE
STREETS.
PEOPLE POSTING TO SOCIAL MEDIA
TO SHOW THE DEVASTATION.
FACADES CRUMBLING.
ACROSS MEXICO CITY, THE
DESPERATE SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS
STARTING IMMEDIATELY, CONTINUING
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
AND AT THE SCHOOL, NEIGHBO
LIKE JESUS AMONG THE FIRST TO
RUSH INTO THE RUBBLE, HEARING
SCREAMING FROM THE INSIDE.
THEN, MAKING A GRIM DISCOVERY.
>> WE PULLED OUT A KID AND I
SAW -- AND THEY PUT HIS OWN
SWEATER ON HIS FACE AND THEY
PULLED HIM OUT ON THE STRETCHER.
>> Reporter: WAS HE ALIVE?
>> NO.
I DON'T THINK HE WAS.
>> Reporter: SO FAR, AT LEAST 25
DEAD IN THE SCHOOL ALONE.
11 RESCUED.
THESE HANDWRITTEN PAGES WITH THE
NAMES OF THE WOUNDED AND THEIR
HOSPITALS.
OTHER NOTES LISTING THE MISSING.
DAVID, AN ENTIRE NATION IS
FIXATED ON THE DRAMA PLAYING OUT
JUST BENEATH ME.
NOW, WE'VE BEEN HERE FOR EIGHT
HOURS WATCHING RESCUERS GET
CLOSERND CLOSER TO THAT LITTLE
GIRL.
RIGHT NOW, THEY SEEM
TANTALIZINGLY CLOSE, BUT ONE
THING THEY ALL SAY, THEY ARE NOT
LEAVING HERE UNTIL THEY PULL THE
LAST PERSON OUT OF THAT SCHOOL.
DAVID?
>> MATT GUTMAN RIGHT THERE IN
MEXICO CITY.
MATT, THANK YOU.
>>> TO THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT,
AND NEW REPORTING HERE ON THE
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION.
SPECIAL COUNCIL ROBERT MUELLER
AND HIS NEW STEPESTING ESENT TR
ARE NOW UNDER SCRUTINY,
INCLUDING HIS FIRING OF FBI
DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY.
AND THE MEETING WITH RUSSIAN
OFFICIALS IN THE OVAL OFFICE THE
VERY NEXT DAY.
ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL WITH
WHAT HE'S LEARNED TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE
CLEAREST INDICATION YET SPECIAL
COUNBEG ROL TOUE T MRTHE ACTION
PRESIDENT TRUMP HIMSELF.
AS "THE NEW YORK TIMES" FIRST EE
PO
WHITE HOUSE DOCUMENTS
SURROUNDING THE PRESIDENT'S OVAL
OFFICE MEETING WITH RUSSIA
OFFICIALS THE DAY AFTER HE FIRED
FBI DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY.
TRUMP REPORTEDLY TOLD THE
RUSSIANS, QUOTE, "I FACED GREAT
PRESSURE BECAUSE OF RUSSIA.
THAT'S TAKEN OFF."
THE NEXT DAY, HE PUBLICLY
ACKNOWLEHE TEDSIUS R
INVESTIGATION WAS ON HIS MIND
WHEN HE FIRED COMEY.
>> WHEN I DECIDED TO JUST DO IT,
I SAID TO MYSELF, I SAID, YOU
KNOW, THIS RUSSIA THING WITH
TRUMP AND RUSSIA IS A MADE-UP
STORY.
>> Reporter: MUELLER ALSO WANTS
DOCUMENTS CONCERNING THE
RESPONSE TO THE NEWS THAT THE
PRESIDENT'S SON, DON JR., MET
WITH RUSSIAN OPERATIVES DURING
THE CAMPAIGN.
AT THE TIME, THE WHITE HOUSE
INSISTED THE MEETING WAS ONLY
ABOUT RUSSIAN ADOPTIONS AND THE
PRESIDENT PUBLICLY DEFENDED HIS
SON.
>> MY SON IS A WONDERFUL YOUNG
MAN.
>> Reporter: BUT E-MAILS SHOW
THE MEETING WAS SET UP, QUOTE,
"TO PROVIDE THE TRUMP CAMPAIGN
WITH SOME OFFICIAL DOCUMENTS AND
INFORMATION THAT WOULD
INCRIMINATE HILLARY."
WE LATER LEARNED THE PRESIDENT
WAS DIRECTLY INVOLVED IN
CRAFTING THAT FIRST MISLEADING
RESPONSE.
>> AND JON KARL WITH US HERE IN
NEW YORK TODAY.
AND WE LEARNED SOMETHING ELSE
TODAY, THAT THE LEGAL BILLS FOR
THE PRESIDENT AND HIS SON ARE
BEING PAID FOR BY DONATIONS MADE
BY EVERYDAY AMERICANS TO THE
REPUBLICAN NATIONAL COMMITTEE.
HOW UNUSUAL IS THAT?
>> Reporter: WELL, IT'S
PERFECTLY LEGAL, BUT IT IS
HIGHLY UNUSUAL, IF NOT
UNPRECEDENTED, FOR A POLITICAL
PARTY TO PAY THE PERSONAL LEGAL
BILLS OF A PRESIDENT AND HIS
FAMILY.
AND WE'RE TALKING ABOUT $230,000
FOR DONALD TRUMP'S LAWYERS, AND
ANOTHER $200,000, NEARLY
ALL THE MORE NOTABLE, DAVID,
BECAUSE IN THIS CASE, THE
PRESIDENT IS A BILLIONAIRE.N NE
YORK.
JON, THANKS, AS ALWAYS.
>>> IN THE MEANTIME, NEXT, TO
CAPITOL HILL TONIGHT, AND THE
SENATE'S HAIL MARY PUSH TO KILL
OBAMACARE.
THEIR NEW REPLACEMENT PLAN
TURNING OVER MUCH OF THE
RESPONSIBILITY TO THE STATES.
BUT IT IS RUNNING INTO A LOT OF
OPPOSITION TONIGHT, INCLUDING
FROM LATE NIGHT TV HOST JIMMY
KIMMEL, MAKING HIS PERSONAL
STORY A POLITICAL ONE.
ABC'S MARY BRUCE WITH THE TALLY,
REPUBLICAN SENATORS CAN ONLY
AFFORD TWO "NO" VOTES.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, JIMMY
KIMMEL IS TAKING ON THE
ARCHITECT OF THE NEW REPUBLICAN
HEALTH CARE BILL.
>> AND THIS GUY, BILL CASSIDY,
JUST LIED RIGHT TO MY FACE.
>> Reporter: LAST SPRING, KIMMEL
HIS INFANT SON'S HEART
CONDITION.
>> NO PARENT SHOULD EVER HAVE TO
DECIDE IF THEY CAN AFFORD TO
SAVE THEIR CHILD'S LIFE.
IT JUST SHOULDN'T HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: IN RESPONSE,
SENATOR CASSIDY PROMISED HE
WOULD DEFEND PROTECTIONS FOR
PEOPLE WITH PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS.
BUT NOW, KIMMEL SAYS HE'S NOT
LIVING UP TO HIS WORD.
YOU CAN PROMISE THOSE PEOPLE
WITH PRE-EXISTING CONDITIONS
THAT THEY WILL NOT BE CHARGEMOR
DISCRIMID NATED AGAINS
T, THEY
WON'T BE DENIED CARE?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S IN THE LEGISLATION.
>> Reporter: BUT EXPERTS TELL US
THERE'S NO GUARANTEE.
IN THE NEW BILL, STATES COULD
ALLOW INSURERS TO CHARGE MORE TO
PEOPLE WITH SOME PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS.
STATES STILL HAVE TO PROVIDE
ADEQUATE AND AFFORDABLE
COVERAGE, BUT THOSE TERMS ARE
NOT DEFINED OR ENFORCED.
>> OPTIONAL PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION?
>> Reporter: THE BUDGET OFFICE
IS EXPECTED TO RELEASE A
PRELIMINARY REPORT NEXT WEEK,
OUTLINING HOW MUCH THE BILL
COSTS, BUT NOT HOW MANY
AMERICANS COULD STAND TO LOSE
COVERAGE.
FOR THAT, THEY NEED MORE TIME.
>> MARY BRUCE WITH US LIVE
TONIGHT.'R
STILL WAITING FOR THE CBO SCORE,
WHICH WOULD ESTIMATE HOW MANY
FEWER AMERICANS WOULD BE
INSURED.
IN THE MEANTIME, WE KNOW THAT
REPUBLICANS CAN ONLY AFFORD TO
LOSE TWO VOTES.
FOUR KEY SENATORS TONIGHT, RAND
PAUL, JOHN McCAIN, SUSAN
COLLINS, LISA MURKOWSKI, THEY
COULD ALL BE PIVOTAL HERE.
WHAT DO YOU KNOW, MARY?
>> Reporter: DAVID, HERE'S THE
STATE OF PLAY.
PAUL TELLS ME HE'S A NO.
COLLINS IS LEANING NO.
MURKOWSKI SAYS SHE'S STUDYING
THE BILL.
AND McCAIN WON'T SAY WHERE HE
STANDS.
REPUBLICANS DO NOT HAVE THE
VOTES YET.
BUT THEY INTEND TO HOLD A VOTE
NEXT WEEK.
DAVID?
>> MARY BRUCE LIVE ON THE HILL
AGAIN TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, MARY.
>>> NEXT, NORTH KOREA REACTING
THIS EVENING TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S FIERY ADDRESS AT THE
U.N.
THE PRESIDENT SAYING THE U.S.
MAY HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO
TOTALLY DESTROY NORTH KOREA,
CALLING ITS LEADER KIM JONG-UN A
ROCKET MAN ON A SUICIDE MISSION.
TONIGHT, NORTH KOREA'S FOREIGN
MINISTER CALLING THOSE REMARKS,
QUOTE, THE SOUND OF A DOG
BARKING, AND THAT NORTH KOREA IS
NOT SCARED.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO THE HORROR
UNFOLDING RIGHT NOW IN MYANMAR.
VICE PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE JUST
TODAY TELLINSETYNCO  SG SWG T A
THE ROHINGYA ARE CONSIDERED ONE
OF THE MOST PERSECUTED
MINORITIES ON EARTH.
OUR CAMERAS THERE AS THEY ESCAPE
THEIR HOMES AMID REPORTS OF
TORTURE, RAPE AND ETHNIC
CLEANSING BY THEIR OWN COUNTRY'S
MILITARY.
MYANMAR'S DE FACTO LEADER, ANG
SAN SUU KYI, A NOBEL LAUREATE,
ADDRESSING THE ROHINGYA CRISIS
FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE REPORTS
MORE THAN 400,000 HAVE NOW FLED
IN FEAR.
AND ABC'S BOB WOODRUFF TONIGHT,
ON THE FRONT LINES IN MYANMAR.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE WHAT BOB
WITNESSED FIRST-HAND.
>> Reporter: THEY ARE RUNNING
FOR THEIR LIVES, HOPING TO
ESCAPE WHAT THEY BELIEVE IS
CERTAIN DEATH.
RISKING IT ALL TO CROSS
ILLEGALLY FROM MYANMAR INTO
BANGLADESH.
>> Translator: WE ARE BEING
PERSECUTED.
WE ARE SCARED.
THERE HAVE BEEN KILLINGS.
>> Reporter: DISTURBING REPORTS
EMERGING OF A NEW WAVE OF
ATTACKS UNLEASHED BY GOVERNMENT
FORCES IN MYANMAR ON THE
ROHINGYA, A MUSLIM MINORITY.
THERE ARE REPORTS OF VILLAGES
SURROUNDED, HOMES BURNED TO THE
GROUND, TORTURE, EXECUTIONS AND
RAPE.
SO, WE TRAVELED TO BANGLADESH TO
SPEAK WITH SURVIVORS OF
GOVERNMENT ATTACKS.
ATTACKS SUCH AS THIS ONE.
ROHINGYA VILLAGERS SEEN HERE
STRUCK REPEATEDLY BY POLICE.
EVERYONE WE ENCOUNTER WANTS TO
SHARE THEIR STORY.
DID YOU SEE GUN FIRE?
DID YOU SEE ATTACKS FROM THE
GOVERNMENT?
WHAT EXACTLY HAPPENED?
THIS IS THE NAF RIVER,
SEPARATING MYANMAR FROM
BANGLADESH.
JUST ACROSS THE WATER THERE IN
RAKHINE IS WHERE THE ATTACKS
AGAINST THE ROHINGYA ARE
REPORTED TO BE UNFOLDING.
>> MYANMAR AUTHORITIES ARE NOT
HOLDING ANYBODY ACCOUNTABLE FOR
THE CRIMES THAT ARE BEING
PERPETRATED AGAINST THE CIVILIAN
POPULATION.
S LIMIE  ERYTA
>> AND BOB WOODRUFF IS WITH US
NOW.
AND BOB, WE MENTIONED THEIR DE
FACTO LEADER, ANG SAN SUU KYI,
>> Reporter: SHE HAS NOT
CONDEMNED IT YET.
THERE'S A LIST OF LEADERS AROUND
THE WORLD THAT ARE CRITICIZING
FOR THIS, INCLUDING THE POPE.
THE STRONGEST WORDS SO FAR,
REALLY, ARE FROM VICE PRESIDENT
PENCE TODAY, WHERE HE CALLED ON
MYANMAR TO, QUOTE, END THEIR
VIOLENCE IMMEDIATELY AND SUPPORT
DIPLOMATIC EFFORTS FOR A
LONG-TERM SOLUTION.
DR,F REPORTING
TONIGHT.
BOB, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT"
THIS WEDNESDAY.
THE FRIGHTENING SCENE AT YANKEE
STADIUM.
THE GAME DELAYED LATE TODAY.
THE FOUL BALL, THE LITTLE GIRL.
THE PLAYERS SHAKEN AND IN TEARS
ON THE FIELD.
WE'LL HAVE MORE IN A MOMENT
HERE.
>>> DRAMATIC IMAGES.
THE FAMILY STRUCK BY LIGHTNING
DURING A CAMPING TRIP.
WE HAVE NEWS ON THEIR CONDITION
TONIGHT.
>>> AND THEN, THE COAST GUARD
DISCOVERY THIS EVENING, RIGHT
OFF THE AMERICAN COAST.
THE SUBMARINE-LIKE VESSEL
DETECTED, AND WHAT THEY HAVE NOW
DISCOVERED IN THAT SUB.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
DETECTED, AND WHAT THEY HAVE NOW
DISCOVERED IN THAT SUB.
When a critical patient is far
from the hospital,
the hospital must come to the
patient.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
The AT&T network is helping
first responders
connect with medical teams in
near real time...
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
...Saving time when it matters
most.
Stay with me, Mrs. Parker.
That's the power of and.
But he hasoke up
wwork to do.in.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
My friI say not if you this
protect yourself.ary.
What is scary?
Pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's a serious disease.
My doctor said the risk is
greater now that I'm over 50!
Yeah...ya-ha...
Just one dose of the PREVNAR 13®
vaccine can help protect you
from pneumococcal pneumonia-
an illness that can cause
coughing, chest pain,
difficulty breathing,
and may even put you
in the hospital.
PREVNAR 13® is approved for
adults 18 and older to help
prevent infections from
13 strains of the bacteria that
cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
You should not receive
PREVNAR 13® if you have had
a severe allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
If you have a weakened
immune syste
you may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects
were pain, redness,
and swelling at
the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Get this one done!
Ask about PREVNAR 13®
at your next visit to your
doctor's office or pharmacy.
>>> TO THE SCARE TODAY AT YANKEE
STADIUM.
A LITTLE GIRL STRUCK BY A LINE
DRIVE FOUL BALL.
PLAYERS ON THE FIELD VISIBLY
SHAKEN.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> Reporter: A SPLIT-SECOND
AFTER THE CRACK OF THAT BAT --
>> LOOK OUT.
OH MY GOODNESS.
>> Reporter: IT'S CLEAR A FAN IS
HURT.
YANKEES HITTER TODD FRAZIER
IMMEDIATELY SHOWS CONCERN.
PLAYERS ON BOTH SIDES LOOK
DISTRAUGHT, BOWING THEIR HEADS.
SOME EVEN CRYING.
>> A LITTLE TOO GRAPHIC FOR US
TO SHOW YOU.epter: THAT INJUREDA
LITTLE GIRL.
THE CROWD CALLS FOR HELP.
A MEDICAL TEAM TENDS TO THE GIRL
WHO IS RUSHED FROM THE STANDS TO
THE HOSPITAL.
TONIGHT, HER CONDITION IS
UNKNOWN.
A SIMILAR SCENE PLAYED OUT AT
YANKEE STADIUM IN JULY WHEN A
FOUL BALL HIT A FAN IN THE HEAD.
AND A YOUNG BOY WAS STRUCK BY
PART OF A BROKEN BK AC B IN
SHATTERED BATS AND FOUL BALLS
INJURING FANS IN RECENT YEARS
HAVE PROMPTED SOME TEAMS TO
EXTEND PROTECTIVE NETTING.
AFTER THAT INCIDENT IN JULY, THE
YANKEES SAID THEY WERE SERIOUSLY
EXPLORING EXTENDING THE NETTING
NEXT SEASON.
DAVID?
>> LINSEY DAVIS, THANK YOU.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
FAMOUS STAR BEHIND "RAGING
BULL", AND HIS TRIBUTE TONIGHT
TO THE LEGENDARY BOXER.
>>> ALSO, THAT FAMILY ON A
CAMPING TRIP, STRUCK BY
LIGHTNING.
>>> AND THE COAST GUARD
DISCOVERY RIGHT OFF THE COAST.
WHAT WAS IN THAT SUBMARINE?
degeneration, AMD,
ular
he told me to look at this
grid every day.
And we came up with a plan
to help reduce
my risk
of progression,
including PreserVision
AREDS 2.
My doctor said
PreserVision
AREDS 2
has the exact
nutrient formula
the National Eye
Institute recommends
to help reduce
the risk of progression of
moderate to advanced AMD
after 15 years
of clinical studies.
PreserVision
AREDS 2.
Because my eyes
are everything.
I NEEDED SOMETHING MORE TO HELP
CONTROL MY TYPE 2 DIABETES.
MY A1C WASN'T WERE
IT NEEDED TO BE.
SO I LIKED WHEN
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
THAT I MAY REACH MY BLOOD
SUGAR AND A1C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE MY BODY TO
DO WHAT IT'S SUPPOSE TO DO,
RELEASE ITS OWN INSULIN.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE A LUMP OR
SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
YO STOMACH,
OR SYMPTOMS SUCH AS ITCHING,
RASH, OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
E WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN,
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS E.RSWO
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY MAY HELP
ME REACH MY BLOOD SUGAR GOALS.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING
YOUR A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR,
ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
Our first concentrated pill
that rushes powerful relief.
A small new size that's fast,c.
Woohoo!
You'll ask, what pain?
New Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
What are the ingredients
Is it the places you go?
The things you own?
Or the people that fill it
with meaning?
For 150 years,
generations of families
have chosen Pacific Life
for retirement and
life insurance solutions.
Protecting what's most
important to you.
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask a financial advisor
about Pacific Life.
>>> TO THE INDEX.
AND THE FAMILY STRUCK BY
LIGHTNING IN CALIFORNIA.
FRIGHTENING MOMENT LIGHTNING HIT
IN SEQUOIA NATIONAL FOREST.
CHRISTOPHER LAVERA AND HIS TWO
YOUNG CHILDREN UNDER A TREE.
THEY WERE KNOCKED UNCONSCIOUS.
ALL THREE ARE RECOVERING FROM
SEVERE BURNS TONIGHT, BUT THEY
ARE EXPECTED TO BE OKAY.
THAT'S THE GOOD NEWS.
>>> THE MAJOR DRUGOFF
CALIFORNIA. BUST
THE COAST GUARD CHASING DOWN
THAT GRAY OBJECT IN THE PACIFIC.
THE SUBMARINE-LIKE VESSEL TRYING
TO AVOID DETECTION.
AUTHORITIES ARRESTING SEVERAL
SUSPECTS.
MORE THAN THREE TONS OF COCAINE
FOUND ONBOARD WORTH MILLIONS.
>>> AND LEGENDARY BOXER JAKE
LaMOTTA HAS DIED.
THE FORMER MIDDLEWEIGHT CHAMP
REMEMBERED AS ONE OF THE
TOUGHEST.
HE WAS THE SUBJECT OF THE FILM
"RAGING BULL," STARRING ROBERT
DE NIRO.
AND THE ACTOR TONIGHT SAYING,
"REST IN PEACE, CHAMP."
LaMOTTA WAS 95.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK TONIGHT,
CELEBRATING A MAJOR MILESTONE
FOR A MEMBER OF OUR OWN FAMILY
TODAY.AT
PLAYED OUT ON LIVE TV.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
and life's beautiful moments.ns
get between you
Flonase outperforms the #1
non-drowsy allergy pill.
It helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause symptoms.
Pills block one
and 6 is greater than 1.
Flonase changes
everything.
Adult 7+ promotes alertness and
mental sharpness in dogs
7 and older.
(Ray) The difference has been
incredible.
She is much more aware. She
wants to learn things.
(VO) Purina Pro Plan Bright
Mind. Nutrition that performs.
You don't let anything
Lkeep you sidelined.
Come on!
That's why you drink Ensure.
With 9 grams of protein, and
26 vitamins and minerals...
For the strength and energy,
to get back to doing
what you love.
Ensure, always be you.
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis?
How do you chase what you love
Do what I did.
Ask your doctor about HUMIRA.
It's proven to help relieve pain
and protect joints
from further irreversible damage
in many adults.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to block
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes to RA symptoms.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 20 years.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
Ready for a new chapter?
Talk to your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA at work.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, AMERICA
STRONG.
WE CELEBRATED A MILESTONE TODAY
FOR A MEMBER OF OUR OWN FAMILY.
ROBIN ROBERTS, MARKING HER FIFTH
ANNIVERSARY OF HER LIFE-SAVING
BONE MARROW TRANSPLANT.
HER FIFTH BIRTHDAY.
ROBIN'S MATCH, HER SISTER, SALLY
ANN.
BUT 70% OF THOSE PEOPLE WHO NEED
A BONE MARROW TRANSPLANT DON'T
FIND IT IN THEIR OWN FAMILY, AND
THAT'S WHERE BE THE MATCH COMES
IN.
AND THIS MORNING, A BOY NAMED
A.J. MEETING THE STRANGER WHO
SAVED HIM.
>> HE WAS A REALLY HEALTHY BOY.
ALL OF A SUDDEN, IN THE MIDDLE
OF THE NIGHT, HE WOKE UP WITH
LEG PAIN.
AND THE FOLLOWING DAY, WE HAD TO
TAKE HIM TO THE E.R.
>> Reporter: ON HIS FOURTH
BIRTHDAY, A.J. AND HIS FAMILY
IVCEED L AIFE-
>> WE FOUND OUT THAT IT WAS
ACTUALLY LEUKEMIA.>> Reporter:
WHILE DAD JEFF SERVED IN THE
MILITARY, A.J. AND HIS FAMILY
IMMEDIATELY FLEW BACK TO THE
STATES FOR TREATMENT.
>> A.J. WAS SO SICK.
THE TREATMENT WAS SO INTENSE.
>> Reporter: UNFORTUNATELY, IN
THE SUMMER OF 2015, A.J.
RELAPSED.
>> AT THAT POINT, WE KNEW THAT A
TRANSPLANT WAS REALLY HIS ONLY
OPTION.
>> Reporter: THE FAMILY TURNED
TO BE THE MATCH.
AND THANKFULLY, THEY FOUND A.J.
A MATCH.
A 22-YEAR-OLD WOMAN.
THAT'S ALL THE FAMILY KNEW AT
THE TIME.
LIKE A TYPICAL KID, A.J. FOUND
SMALL MOMENTS OF JOY IN HIS TOYS
AND EVEN DANCING.
A.J.'S MOM, WRITING TO HER SON'S
DONOR.
>> I THANK YOU FROM THE VERY
DEPTHS OF MY HEART.
>> Reporter: THE TRANSPLANT
WORKED.
A.J. WAS CANCER FREE.
AND NOW, MEETING HIS DONOR FOR
THE FIRST TIME, FACE TO FACE.
>> A.J.'S MATCH, ALEX.
>> SOMETHING YOU WANT TO SAY TO
HER?
>> THANK YOU FOR SAVING MY LIFE.
>> NOT A DRY EYE FOR ANY OF US
WATCHING THIS MORNING.
WE'RE ROOTING FOR A.J.
AND ROBIN, HAPPY FIFTH BIRTHDAY.
I'M DAVID MUIR.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW NIGHT.
UNTIL THEN, HAVE A GOOD EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> SOME OF THE FAMILIES SHARED
THEIR EXPERIENCE SHORTLY AFTER
LANDING AT SFO STOOD.
>>> HURRICANE MARIA HITS
HURRICANE LEAFING THE ENTIRE
ISLAND WITHOUT POWER.
MORE ON WHERE THIS STORM IS
HEADING NEXT.
>> A FRANTIC SEARCH FOR
SURVIVORS AFTERTHA T
7.1 EARTHQUAKE.
THANK FOR JOINING US.
I'M CHRISTINE ZEE.
MORE THAN TWO DOZEN BODIES HAVE
BEEN RECOVERED FROM THE SCHOOL'S
WRECKAGE.
>> THE DEATH TOLL IS 230 IS THE
MEXICAN'S PRESIDENT DECLARED A
DAY OF MOURNING.
MORE THAN 200 ARE DEAD AND MORE
REMAINED TRAPPED FOLLOWING A 7.1
MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE THAT HIT
HEAVILY POPULATED SECTIONS OF
MEXICO TUESDAY.
SURR CRUMBLE.CRIBED WATCHING
>> IT WAS CROWDING EVERYTHING,
THE STREET MAKING SURE WE WERE
AWAY FROM TREES.
>> WE PRETTY MUCH TRIED TO BE
NEXT TO THE WALL AND LIKE, JUST
LIKE -- BUT IT WAS --
>> THERE IS THE SECOND MAJOR
EARTHQUAKE TO HIT MEXICO IN THE
PAST TWO WEEKS.
PRESIDENT ENRIQUE PENA NEATO IS
CALLING A NEW NATIONAL
EMERGENCY.
TRN UNFORTUNATELY SEVERAL PEOPLE
HAVE LOST THEIR LIVES INCLUDING