FOR WATCHING.
WE'LL SE
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, TWO FAST-MOVING
STORIES.
IN BOSTON, THE BREAKING NEWS.
THE FBI SAYS THEY WANT EVERYBODY
TO HELP FIND THESE TWO MEN ON
THE SURVEILLANCE TAPE.
PERSONS OF INTEREST IN THE
BOSTON MARATHON BOMBING.
WE'LL TAKE YOU FRAME BY FRAME
THROUGH THE VIDEO.
WHY THE FBI SAYS, LOOK AT EVERY
DETAIL.
AND THE BREAKTHROUGH COMES AS AN
EMOTIONAL PRESIDENT TONIGHT HAS
A MESSAGE FOR THE BOMBERS.
>> WE WILL FIND YOU.
AND, YES, YOU WILL FACE JUSTICE.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, THAT TEXAS
DISASTER.
WHAT CAUSED THE GIANT TANK AT A
FERTILIZER PLANT TO EXPLODE AND
SHATTER AN ENTIRE TOWN?
THE TREMORS FELT MILES AWAY AS
TRUE HEROES RUSHED IN TO HELP.
>>> IN OTHER NEWS, WATER WORLD.
KAYAKING DOWN THE STREETS OF
CHICAGO.
FLOODS, CARS SWALLOWED IN A BIG
HOLE.
THE EARTH NO MATCH FOR THE
DELUGE.
>>> AND THE HEART OF A HERO.
FROM BOSTON TO TEXAS, THE
ORDINARY AMERICANS WHO RUSHED
TOWARD DANGER.
IS THERE A SUPER HERO IN EVERY
ONE OF US?
>>> GOOD EVENING TO YOU, AND
TONIGHT FROM TEXAS TO BOSTON, WE
ARE A NATION IN PURSUIT OF
ANSWERS.
AND AS WE COME ON THE AIR
TONIGHT, THERE IS STUNNING NEWS
OUT OF BOSTON.
THE FBI RELEASING SURVEILLANCE
TAPES.
TWO PEOPLE CALLED PERSONS OF
INTEREST IN THE MARATHON-DAY
BOMBINGS.
THE FBI CONSIDERS THEM ARMED,
DANGEROUS, ASKED THAT NO ONE
APPROACH THEM.
BUT THEY ASK ALL MEMBERS OF THE
PUBLIC TO LOOK AT THESE TAPES,
TO STUDY THEM IN DETAIL AND
HELP.
ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT, BRIAN ROSS, WILL
TAKE US FRAME BY FRAME THROUGH
THE CLUES.
BRIAN?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
FEDERAL AUTHORITIES NOW BELIEVE
THAT A TEAM OF AT LEAST TWO MEN
WAS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE BOMBINGS
HERE.
AS YOU SAY, DESCRIBED AS ARMED
AND EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
THE FBI IS BASING ITS TWO-BOMBER
THEORY ON THESE SURVEILLANCE
CAMERA VIDEOS AND STILL PICTURES
MADE PUBLIC LATE TODAY.
TWO WHITE MEN IN THEIR 20s,
ACCORDING TO THE FBI.
ONE WITH A BLACK CAP, THE SECOND
WITH A WHITE CAP WORN BACKWARDS.
BOTH WEARING BACKPACKS THAT THE
FBI BELIEVE HELD THE BOMBS.
OFF TO THE SIDE OF THIS VIDEO,
RUNNERS CAN BE SEEN HEADING TO
THE FINISH LINE AND TIME CODE
MARKERS INDICATE THE FOOTAGE WAS
MADE ABOUT 13 MINUTES BEFORE THE
FIRST BOMB WENT OFF.
THE FBI SAYS ONLY ONE OF THE TWO
POTENTIAL SUSPECTS, THE ONE WITH
THE WHITE CAP, WAS ACTUALLY SEEN
PLACING HIS BACKPACK AT THE
SCENE OF AN EXPLOSION.
>> WE ARE RELEASING PHOTOS OF
THESE TWO SUSPECTS.
RE IDENTIFT O.
THEY APPEAR TO BE ASSOCIATED.
>> Reporter: OFFICIALS SAY THEY
MADE THE IMAGES PUBLIC NOW
BECAE THEY ND
THE FACES TO NAMES.
BUT THEY WARN THESE ARE
DANGEROUS MEN.
>> WE CONSIDER THEM TO BE ARMED
AND EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
>> Reporter: THERE WERE NEW
DEVELOPMENTS TODAY BASED ON THE
SOME 300 PIECES OF EVIDENCE
RECOVERED FROM THE CRIME SCENE.
SOME OF THE COMPONENTS,
INCLUDING THIS BATTERY, AND THIS
CIRCUIT BOARD, WERE RECOGNIZED
BY HOBBYISTS AS PARTS OF A TOY
REMOTE CONTROL CAR, SIMILAR TO
THIS ONE SEEN IN AN ONLINE
VIDEO.
THE OWNER OF ONE HOBBY STORE
OUTSIDE BOSTON SAID FBI AGENTS
INTERVIEWED HIM LAST NIGHT AND
LEFT LITTLE DOUBT THAT A REMOTE
CONTROLLED UNIT HAD BEEN USED IN
THE BOMBS.
>> IT LOOKED TO ME THAT ONE OF
THE COMPONENTS WAS A RADIO
RECEIVER.
THE RESPONSE I GOT WAS DEAD ON.
>> Reporter: THERE ARE
INSTRUCTIONS ON THE INTERNET
ABOUT HOW TO USE A REMOTE
CONTROLLED TOY CAR TO SET OFF A
BOMB, BOTH FROM "THE ANARCHIST
COOKBOOK" AND SEVERAL JIHADIST
SITES AS WELL.
THERE IS STILL NO INDICATION OF
WHETHER THERE WAS AN ACT OF
FOREIGN OR DOMESTIC TERRORISM,
BUT THE PRESIDENT VOWED TODAY
THE BOMBERS, WHOEVER THEY ARE,
WILL NOT ESCAPE.
>> YES, WE WILL FIND YOU.
AND, YES, YOU WILL FACE JUSTICE.
>> Reporter: WHAT HAPPENS NEXT
IS WHAT ONE OFFICIAL CALLED AN
ELECTRONIC DRAGNET, PUSHING
THESE IMAGES FAR AND WIDE TO
ENGAGE THE PUBLIC IN THE HUNT.
DIANE?
>> ALL RIGHT, BRIAN.
THANK YOU.
I WANT TO BRING IN ABC'S PIERRE
THOMAS WHO HAS LEARNED NEW
DETAILS SINCE THE BRIEFING TODA.
>> A SENIOR LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIAL TELLS ME E WO
SUSPECTS IS SEEN IN ANHER
VIO MAKING A CELLPHONE CALL
AROUND THE TIME OF THE
EXNS.
THEY BELIEVE THAT THE CELLPHONE
WAS USED TO TRIGGER ONE OF THE
EXPLOSIONS.
THE OFFICIALS SAID A MASSIVE
EFFORT IS UNDER WAY TO CAPTURE
EVERY CELLPHONE CALL IN THAT
LOCAL AREA AT THE TIME OF THE
BOMBINGS, TO SEE IF THEY CAN
TRACE IT BACK TO THE BOMBER.
THE SOURCE SAID IT'S A
TIME-CONSUMING PROCESS BUT A TOP
PRIORITY.
>> AS YOU WATCH THE TAPES GO BY
PIERRE, AND YOU'VE STUDIED THESE
SO OFTEN, TELL US THE KIND OF
DETAIL THE FBI IS ASKING
EVERYONE TO NOTICE.
>> ONE OF THE THINGS YOU CAN SEE
AS YOU LOOK AT THE TAPE IS THAT
THE BLACK BACKPACK IS ONE
CRITICAL PIECE OF EVIDENCE.
MY SOURCES ARE TELLING ME THAT
BACKPACK IS THE ONE THAT THEY
RECOVERED THE MOST MATERIAL
FROM.
THE OTHER THING IS THAT EVERY
PIECE OF EVIDENCE IN THAT FRAME,
THE HAT, THE COAT, THE PANTS,
THEY WANT THE PUBLIC TO LOOK AT
THAT BECAUSE THERE MIGHT BE
SOMETHING THAT SOMEONE WOULD
NOTICE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
AND TO LOOK OVER EVERY FRAME BY
FRAME, THEY SENT EVERYONE TO THE
WEBSITE, FBI.GOV TO CHECK IT
OUT.
AND I KNOW YOU'LL BE GETTING
BACK TO THE PHONES AS WELL,
PIERRE.
THANK YOU.
>>> AS WE SAID, THE PRESIDENT
TODAY DELIVERED A SUMMONS, A
PROMISE, AND A BLAZING TRIBUTE
IN BOSTON.
AND ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS TELLS US
MORE.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT CAME
WITH A SIMPLE MESSAGE.
>> IF THEY SOUGHT TO INTIMIDATE
US, TO TERRORIZE US, IT SHOULD
BE PRETTY CLEAR BY NOW THAT THEY
PICKED THE WRONG CITY TO DO IT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> NOT HERE IN BOSTON,
NOT HERE IN BOSTON.
>> Reporter: AT TIMES, HE
BROUGHT THEM TO THEIR FEET.
AT OTHERS, HE BROUGHT THEM TO
T THSSE WAS ALWAYS TO
>> AS YOU BEGIN THIS LONG
JOURNEY OFECER AY, WLLITYOU AS T
STAND AND WALK AND, YES, RUN
AGAIN -- OF THAT I HAVE NO
DOUBT, YOU WILL RUN AGAIN.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Reporter: FOR THOSE WHOSE
CHEERS WERE ABRUPTLY SILENCED
MARATHON DAY, THE PRESIDENT
TODAY ROUSED THEM ONCE AGAIN.
AMONG THEM FAMILIES OF THE
VICTIMS.
AND RUNNERS, IN THOSE SIGNATURE
MARATHON JACKETS.
>> WE MAY BE MOMENTARILY KNOCKED
OFF OUR FEET, BUT WE'LL PICK
OURSELVES UP.
WE'LL KEEP GOING.
WE WILL FINISH THE RACE.
>> Reporter: AMID THE APPLAUSE,
THE ANGUISH, STILL SO FRESH FROM
THE PARISHIONERS TO THE
PRESIDENT HIMSELF.
THE HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE WHO LINED
THE STREETS OUTSIDE OF THE
CHURCH HERE TODAY, THEY COULDN'T
HEAR PRESIDENT OBAMA OR ANYONE
ELSE INSIDE.
THEY SIMPLY STOOD SILENTLY IN A
SHOW OF SUPPORT.
DIANE?
>> AND AGAIN THE PRESIDENT
QUOTING A POEM THAT BOSTON IS
NOT A PLACE, IT IS A STATE OF
GRACE.
THANKS SO MUCH, LINSEY DAVIS
FROM BOSTON FOR US TONIGHT.
>>> NOW WE TURN FROM BOSTON TO
THE OTHER AMERICAN REGION IN
CRISIS, REELING TONIGHT AND
ASKING THE NATION'S PRAYERS
AFTER A MASSIVE AND MYSTERIOUS
EXPLOSION AT A FERTILIZER PLANT.
THE IMAGE CAUGHT ON TAPE.
THE AIR THICK WITH THE SMELL OF
AMMONIA.
VOLUNTEER FIREFIGHTERS
OVERWHELMED.
THE BLAST HAD THE FEROCITY OF A
2.1 EARTHQUAKE AND THE
THUNDEROUS SHOCK COULD BE HEARD
45 MILES AWAY.
TONIGHT, THE SMALL TOWE
WACO, CALLED WEST, HAS BEEN
FLATTENED.
ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI HAS BEEN
THERE THROUGH THE NIGHT.
>> Reporter: THEIR MOMENT OF
CRISIS FOR FAMILIES IN A SMALL
TOWN OF WEST, TEXAS, CAME AT
7:29 P.M., WITH A FIRE RAGING AT
THEIR GIANT FERTILIZER DEPOT.
>> EVERYBODY NEEDS TO GET AWAY
FROM THERE.
BACK ALL TRUCKS AWAY FROM THE
PLANT.
>> Reporter: A SMALL TEAM OF
FIREFIGHTERS ANSWERING THE CALL,
WORRIED THE WHOLE THING COULD
BLOW.
THEN AT 7:53, THE SOUND NO ONE
HERE WILL SOON FORGET.
[ BLAST ]
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> I CAN'T HEAR.
GET OUT OF HERE, PLEASE GET OUT
OF HERE!
>> Reporter: THE PLANT BLEW TO
PIECES.
>> WE NEED EVERY AMBULANCE WE
CAN GET.
A BOMB JUST WENT OFF INSIDE
HERE.
IT'S PRETTY BAD.
>> Reporter: A MUSHROOM CLOUD OF
SMOKE FILLED THE SKY.
>> WHAT IS IT?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
>> IT LOOKED LIKE, YOU REMEMBER
SEEING ATOMIC BOMB, YOU KNOW,
THAT PLUME.
WELL, THERE IT WAS.
>> Reporter: BY 8:15 THERE WERE
FIVE FIREFIGHTERS MISSING, TWO
>> WE GOT A LOT OF FIREMEN DOWN.
>> Reporter: THE NURSING HOME
ACROSS THE STREET, BLASTED.
A NEARBY APARTMENT BUILDING
DESTROYED.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Reporter: AT 8:30, BETTY
TUCKER, THREE BLOCKS DOWN WAS
TRAPPED AND SAYS A NEIGHBOR
HELPED PULL HER OUT FROM UNDER
HER CRUMBLED WALLS.
>> THE MOST HORRIBLE NOISE I'VE
HEARD IN MY LIFE.
>> Reporter: SHE WALKED TO
FIND WOUNDED NEIGHBORS STU
THROUGH THE STREETS.
DOCTORS SET UP A MAKESHIFT
TRIAGE IN A NEARBY FIELD.
>> DID YOU KNOW ANYONE WHO WAS
KILLED IN THIS?
>> YES, I DO.
THIS IS A SMALL, PRIVATE
COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
INVESTIGATORS ARE TRYING TO
DETERMINE WHAT STARTED THE FIRE
AT THE PLANT WITH ITS HUGE TANKS
OF HIGHLY FLAMMABLE ANHYDROUS
AMMONIA, USED TO TREAT
FERTILIZER.
>> WE'RE WAY TOO EARLY IN THE
INVESTIGATION TO SPECULATE ON
CAUSES OR WHAT MAY HAVE
OCCURRED.
>> Reporter: BUT THE TIMING OF
THE DISASTER IS HAUNTING.
20 YEARS AGO THIS WEEK, THE
COMPOUND OF THE BRANCH DAVIDIAN
CULT IN NEARBY WACO, CAME TO A
FIERY END AFTER A SHOWDOWN WITH
FEDERAL AGENTS.
IN WEST TONIGHT, 160 PEOPLE ARE
RECOVERING FROM THEIR INJURIES.
THE MAYOR SAYS UP TO 45 PEOPLE
ARE STILL MISSING AS PEOPLE
SEARCH THE RUBBLE FOR SURVIVORS.
LATE TODAY AUTHORITIES RELEASED
THE NAME OF THE FIRST CASUALTY
IN THIS EXPLOSION.
CAPTAIN KENNY HARRIS, WHO
ACTUALLY WORKED FOR THE DALLAS
FIRE DEPARTMENT, BUT LIVED IN
WEST, RESPONDED TO THE CALL.
TONIGHT THEY'RE HAILING HIM AS A
HERO.
DIANE?
>> AGAIN, STEVE, THANK YOU.
AND AS YOU SAID, THEY'VE SAID
IT'S STILL TOO EARLY TO COME UP
WITH ANY CAUSE OR ANY MOTIVE IN
WHAT HAPPENED.
WHAT WE DO KNOW IS THAT THE
LITTLE TEXAS TOWN IS A KIND OF
TEXAS VERSION OF A NORMAN
ROCKWELL PAINTING.
JUST A FEW THOUSAND PEOPLE, AS
YOU HEARD.
AND CECILIA VEGA SPENT THE DAY
WITH PEOPLE WHO TOLD HER EVERY
RESCUER, EVERY PERSON RESCUED,
WAS SOMEONE YOU KNOW.
>> Reporter: SHATTERED AND
BROKEN.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> A WAR ZONE.
EVERY WINDOW IS OUT.
AND THE HOUSE, THE WHOLE
CEILING, IT LOOKS LIKE IT COME
OFF THE FOUNDATION AND SET BACK
DOWN.
THE BRICKS ARE ALL OFF THE
HOUSES.
>> Reporter: MIKE MALER BARELY
MADE IT OUT ALIVE.
HIS FAMILY'S BRICK HOUSE, IT'S
COMPLETELY GONE.
JUST LIKE SO MANY OF HIS
NEIGHBORS.
>> I HAVE RELATIVES JUST DOWN
THE ROAD AND YOU CAN'T GET IN
TOUCH WITH THEM.
IF YOU DO, THE CELLPHONE IS OUT.
AND I WANT TO GET IN TOUCH WITH
THEM, SO THAT'S WHY I'M HERE.
JUST TO SEE IF THEY'RE EVEN
ALIVE.
>> Reporter: IN A PLACE WHERE
EVERYONE KNOWS EVERYONE ELSE,
THE INJURED AND MISSING ARE ALL
SOMEONE'S FAMILY, SOMEONE'S
FRIEND, A FAMILIAR FACE.
WEST, TEXAS, IS THE HEARTLAND OF
AMERICA, HOME TO JUST 2,800
PEOPLE -- AND THE ANNUAL
BARBECUE COOK-OFF BY VOLUNTEER
FIREFIGHTERS.
MANY OF THOSE SAME FIREFIGHTERS
RUNNING INTO YESTERDAY'S BLAZE,
AS OTHERS RAN OUT.
SO MANY STILL UNACCOUNTED FOR.
THEIR STATION FLAGS TODAY --
AT HALF STAFF.
>> HOW MANY PEOPLE DO YOU THINK
YOU KNOW WHO WERE HURT IN THAT?
>> I PROBABLY KNOW ALL OF THEM.
>> Reporter: TODAY THE STREETS
OF WEST, TEXAS, ARE BATTERED AND
BRUISED.
SO ARE ITS RESIDENTS.
>> THIS IS FROM THE BLAST?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: THE BLAST SO
STRONG, IT KNOCKED DOWN ELDIN
PAVELKA RIGHT OUT OF HIS CHAIR
-- HIS WINDOWS BLOWN OUT.
HIS METAL GARAGE DOOR, TWISTED.
BUT HE CALLS HIMSELF ONE OF THE
LUCKY ONES.
>> WHAT E YOU FEELING TOY?ANKF
STILL HERE.E LRE
>> Reporter: MR. PAVELKA LIVES
RIGHT UP THE ROAD, NOT TOO FAR .
BUT THIS IS THE SCENE IN MUCH OF
WEST, TEXAS, BUILDINGS, HOMES,
THAT ARE BOARDED UP, HOMES WITH
MAJOR DAMAGE LIKE THIS ONE.
SOME OF THEM DEMOLISHED.
THE BLAST SITE, HALF A MILE AWAY
FROM HERE.
JUST SHOWS YOU HOW STRONG THAT
BLAST WAS.
>> IT WAS THAT POWERFUL AND A
WHOLE NATION IS STANDING WITH
EVERYONE THERE TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, CECILIA.
>>> AND A NOTE ABOUT THE WILD
WEATHER PUMMELLING THE NATION'S
MID SECTION TODAY.
LOOK AT THE MAP.
A MAD MIX OF SNOW, TORNADOES,
AND FLOODS.
IN CHICAGO, A STORM DUMPING FIVE
INCHES OF RAIN ON THE CITY IN 12
HOURS.
THAT AND A WATER MAIN BREAK ON
THE CITY'S SOUTHEAST SIDE
CAUSING A HUGE SINK HOLE TO OPEN
UP.
ONE MAN HOSPITALIZED AFTER
TRYING TO DRIVE AROUND THE HOLE
THAT QUICKLY GREW TO 40 FEET.
THAT DRIVER SAID TO BE IN GOOD
CONDITION TONIGHT.
>>> AND STILL AHEAD ON "WORLD
NEWS," THE ELVIS IMPERSONATOR.
♪
>> NOW THE SUSPECT IN THE POISON
RICIN SCARE.
SUSPECTED OF MAILING POISON TO
THE PRESIDENT.
WHO IS THIS MAN?
THAT'S NEXT.
MOST PEOPLE THINK
THAT AFTER AN ACCIDENT,
YOU'LL HAVE TO PAY FIVE HUNDRED
BUCKS FOR YOUR DEDUCTIBLE.
THE TRUTH?
AT Allstate, YOU COULD PAY ZERO.
Allstate GIVES YOU
A HUNDRED DOLLARS
OFF YOUR DEDUCTIBLE
THE DAY YOU SIGN UP.
THEN ANOTHER HUNDRED OFF EVERY
YEAR YOU DON'T HAVE AN ACCIDENT.
LET THE GOOD HANDSUCTIBLE
THE DAY YOU SIGN UP.
REWARD YOUR SAFE DRIVING
WITH A DEDUCTIBLE
THAT GOES AWAY.
♪
DUCTIBLE REW
ONE MORE WAY YOU'RE IN
GOOD HANDS WITH Allstate.
♪
CAN YOU START THE DAY
THE WAY YOU WANT?
CAN ORENCIA (ABATACEPT) HELP?
[ Woman ] I WANTED TO GET UP
WHEN I WAS READY,
NOT MY JOINTS.
[ Female Announcer ] COULD YOUR
"I WANT" BECOME "I CAN"?
TALK TO YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST.
ORENCIA REDUCES
MANY RA SYMPTOMS
LIKE PAIN, MORNING STIFFNESS
AND THE PROGRESSION
OF JOINT DAMAGE.
IT'S HELPED NEW RA PATIENTS
AND THOSE NOT HELPED ENOUGH
BY OTHER TREATMENTS.
DO NOT TAKE ORENCIA
WITH ANOTHER BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
FOR RA
DUE TO AN INCREASED RISK
OF SERIOUS INFECTION.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS CAN OCCUR
INCLUDING FATAL INFECTIONS.
CASES OF LYMPHOMA AND
LUNG CANCER HAVE BEEN REPORTED.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU ARE
PRONE TO OR HAVE ANY INFECTION
LIKE AN OPEN SORE OR THE FLU
OR A HISTORY OF COPD,
A CHRONIC LUNG DISEASE.
ORENCIA MAY WORSEN YOUR COPD.
[ Woman ] HERE'S INFORMATION
YOU NEED TO KNOW.
ORENCIA IS AVAILABLE
IN TWO FORMS,
INFUSION AND ALSO
SELF-INJECTION.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR TO SEE
IF ENCIA IS RHT FOR YOU.
AND SEE IF Y CAN CHANGE
"I WANT"
TO "OH, YES I CAN!"
AND HIS NEW BOSS TOLD HIM
TWO THINGS --
COOK WHAT YOU LOVE,
AND SAVE YOUR MONEY.
JOE DOESN'T KNOW IT YET,
BUT HE'LL WORK HIS WAY UP
FROM BUSSER TO WAITER TO CHEF
BENG A RESTAURANT
SPECIALIZING IN FISH AND GAME
FROM THE GREAT NORTHWEST.
HE'LL START INVESTING EARLY,
HE'LL FIND SOME GOOD PEOPLE
TO HELP GUIDE HIM,
AND HE'LL SET MONEY ASIDE
FROM HIS FIRST DAY OF WORK
TO HIS LAST,
WHICH ISN'T ROCKET SCIENCE.
IT'S JUST COMMON SENSE.
FROM TD AMERITRADE.
>>> AND IN THE NEWS TODAY AS
WELL, THE MAN ACCUSED OF SENDING
THOSE LETTERS LACED WITH POISON
TO THE PRESIDENT AND A SENATOR,
WAS IN COURT TODAY.
AND TONIGHT, STRANGE NEW DETAILS
EMERGING.
HE'S SAID TO BE AN ELVIS
IMPERSONATOR, OBSESSED WITH
CONSPIRACY THEORIES AND WITH A
PERSONAL LINK TO ONE OF HIS
TARGETS.
ABC'S MATT GUTMAN HAS THE
PORTRAIT OF THIS MAN COMING INTO
FOCUS TONIGHT.
♪
>> Reporter: THIS IS PAUL KEVIN
CURTIS, THE MAN IN CUSTODY FOR
ALLEGEDLY TERRORIZING THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT FOR TWO DAYS.
♪
A FLAMBOYANT CELEBRITY
IMPERSONATOR WITH HIS OWN
YOUTUBE CHANNEL AND AN UNUSUAL
RING LETTERS
TO THE GOVERNMENT FROM THIS
SLEEPY MISSISSIPPI TOWN.
AND ACCORDG  INVESTIGATORS,
ON APRIL 8th, THREE OF HIS
LETTERS WERE LACED WITH THE
TOXIC CHEMICAL RICIN.
"THERE ARE STILL MISSING PIECES.
MAYBE I HAVE YOUR ATTENTION NOW,
EVEN IF THAT MEANS SOMEONE HAS
TO DIE."
THE FORM LETTERS WERE SENT TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA, SENATOR
ROGER WICKER OF MISSISSIPPI, AND
MISSISSIPPI JUDGE SADIE HOLLAND,
WHO OPENED HERS.
>> A WHITE KIND OF LIKE
GRAINY-TYPE SUBSTANCE LOOSE IN
THE ENVELOPE.
>> Reporter: PROSECUTORS SAY THE
MISSING PIECES IN THE LETTERS
COULD REFER TO CURTIS' OBSESSION
WITH THE SALE OF BLACK MARKET
BODY PARTS.
HE'S EVEN WRITTEN A BOOK AND
TWEETED ABOUT IT.
>> Reporter: IN A STATEMENT, HIS
BROTHER SAID, "WE HAVE NO REASON
TO BELIEVE KEVIN WOULD BE
INVOLVED.
WE LOVE HIM, AND LOOK FORWARD TO
GETTING ANSWERS TO MAKE SENSE OF
ALL THIS."
WE MET HIS NEIGHBOR LACEY ROSS
TODAY.
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THE FACT
THAT HE MIGHT HAVE BEEN COOKING
UP RICIN RIGHT NEXT DOOR?
>> TERRIFYING.
REALLY SCARY.
I HAVE TWO DAUGHTERS.
JUST KNOWING IT COULD BE THAT
CLOSE TO MY CHILDREN.
>> Reporter: JUST MOMENTS AGO,
MEMBERS OF THE HAZMAT TEAM
ARRIVED.
A BREACHED THE DOOR.
TOOK DOWN THE SECURITY CAMERA.
A LOT OF MEN ARE HEAVILY ARMED,
STARTING TO GATHER EVIDENCE.
THE BIG QUESTION, WHAT ARE THEY
GOING TO FIND INSIDE?
>> ON THE SCENE, THANK YOU, MATT
GUTMAN.
>>> AND COMING UP NEXT
HERE -- ♪
>> DO YOU KNOW HOW OLD SUPERMAN
IS AND HOW HE LOOKED WHEN IT ALL
BEGAN?
THAT'S NEXT.
[ all ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA, IN 1999.
S OFTEN HANDED DOWN FROM
GENERATION TO GENERATION
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY.
GET AN AUTO-INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA.
T IT MEANS TO SERVE.
TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS
TO MAKE THE CALL.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE,
MY DOCTOR AND I
WENT WITH AXIRON,
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
E FECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT THE
ONLY UNDERARM LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
BUT WITH ADVAIR,
I'M BREATHING BETTER.
SO NOW I CAN HELP MAKE THIS
A GREAT BLOCK PARTY.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
ADVAIR IS CLINICALLY PROVEN
TO HELP SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE
LUNG FUNCTION.
UNLIKE MOST COPD MEDICATIONS,
ADVAIR CONTAINS
BOTH AN ANTI-INFLAMMATORY
AND A LONG-ACTING
BRONCHODILATOR
WORKING TOGETHER
TO HELP IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION ALL DAY.
ADVAIR WON'T REPLACE
FAST-ACTING INHALERS
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS
AND SHOULD NOT BE USED
MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
PLPEOE WITH COPD TAKING ADVAIR
MAY HAVE
A HIGHER CHANCE OF PNEUMONIA.
ADVAIR MAY INCREASE
YOUR RISK OF OSTEOPOROSIS
AND SOME EYE PROBLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HEART CONDITION
OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING ADVAIR.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
IF INCLUDING ADVAIR COULD HELP
IMPROVE YOUR LUNG FUNCTION.
[ Male Announcer ]
ADVAIR DISKUS
FLUTICASONE PROPIONATE AND
SALMETEROL INHALATION POWDER.
GET YOUR FIRST PRESCRIPTION
FREE
AND SAVE ON REFILLS
AT ADVAIRCOPD.COM.
>>> AND WE BEGIN OUR INSTANT
INDEX TONIGHT WITH A BIRTHDAY
FOR SUPERMAN, WHO IS 75 YEARS
OLD TODAY.
HERE IS THE FIRST TEN-CENT
COMIC BOOK COVER AND THAT WAS
75 YEARS AGO.
IT'S NOW WORTH MORE THAN
$2 MILLION.
OVER THE DECADES, OF COURSE,
WE'VE WATCHED HIM MUSCLE UP AND
GO TO TV WITH GEORGE REEVES.
AND THEN ON TO MOVIES WITH CHRIS
REEVE.
THE KRYPTONITE OF TIME HAS NOT
SLOWED HIM DOWN.
A NEW SUPERMAN MOVIE IS DUE OUT
IN JUNE.
>>> AND SOME OTHER TRUE-LIFE
SUPERMEN, EVEN OLDER.
RETIRED LIEUTENANT COLONEL,
RICHARD COLE IS 97 AND STILL HE
LANDED A B-52 BOMBER THIS WEEK.
IT WAS THE REUNION OF WORLD WAR
II VETERANS IN FLORIDA.
THERE ARE ONLY FOUR LEFT WHO HAD
THE SHEER NERVE TO FLY THAT
APRIL 18th RAID ON JAPAN I
1942, AFTEOR
IT WAS THE RAID MADE FAMOUS IN
THE MOVIE "30 SECONDS OVER
TOKYO."
THEY SAY IT WILL BE THEIR LAST
REUNION, AND THEY'RE OPENING A
BOTTLE OF COGNIAC FROM 1896.
THE YEAR COMMANDER DOO LITTLE
WAS RN
W, LIEUTENANT COLONEL
COLE, I REALIZE I JUST SAID
"B-52," I KNOW YOU WERE FLYING A
B-25.
AND A TOAST TO ALL OF YOU FROM
ALL OF US HERE TONIGHT.
>> AND IF YOU SEE SOMETHING OUT
THERE CRACKLING FOR OUR INSTANT
INDEX, TWEET IT TO ME @DIANE
SAWYER.
>>> IT BRINGS US TO A QUESTION.
ARE THE BRAVEST AMONG US THE
TRUE HEROES, BORN OR MADE?
WE HAVE AN ANSWER IN A MOMENT.
WER IN A MOMENT.
[ Male Announcer ]
WHEN YOU'RE GOING THE DISTANCE,
IT'S NICE TO HAVE
THE EXPERIENCE AND COMMITMENT
TO GO ALONG WITH YOU.
AARP Medicare Supplement
Insurance Plans,
INSURED BY UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
KEEP DREAMING. KEEP DOING.
GO LONG.
INSURED BY UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
AND YOU WOULDN'T HAVE
IT ANY OTHER WAY.E.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
YOU KNOW, THAT COULD BE A
QUESTION OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL
FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY
ANYTIME THE MOMENT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS
THE ONLY DAILY ED TABLET
APPROVED TO TREAT ED
AND SYMPTOMS OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUIS HEANOH
YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
ANFOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU TAKE
NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY
ALLERGIC REACTIONS
SUCH AS RASH, HIVES,
SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS
FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
ARE PROVEN TO BE
EFFECTIVE PAIN RELIEVERS.
Tylenol WORKS BY BLOCKING
PAIN SIGNALS TO YOUR BRAIN.
Bayer Advanced Aspirin
BLOCKS PAIN AT THE SITE.
TRY THE POWER
OF Bayer
Advanced Aspirin.
>>> AND FINALLY FROM US TONIGHT,
SOMEONE SAID THAT COURAGE IS
JUST FEAR THAT HAS SAID ITS
PRAYERS.
BUT WE WONDERED IF COURAGE IS
ALSO A PLACE IN THE MIND, OR IN
THE HEART.
SO ABC'S DAN HARRIS WENT LOOKING
FOR THE ANSWERS, ALL AROUND US
THIS WEEK IN TEXAS AND BOSTON,
AS THE NATION WAS SHAKEN AND
RE-INSPIRED.
>> Reporter: IN BOSTON THIS
WEEK, AMERICA BORE WITNESS TO A
COLLEGE STUDENT WHO, AFTER
RUNNING 26 MILES, GAVE THE SHIRT
OFF HIS BACK TO TREAT A VICTIM'S
WOUND.
THE GRIEVING FATHER WHO'D COME
TO HAND OUT FLAGS IN HONOR OF
HIS DEAD SONS WHO LEAPT INTO THE
FRAY.
AND THE OFF-DUTY FIREFIGHTER WHO
GAVE AID TO A BADLY-INJURED BOY.
WHY DID YOU DO IT?
>> YOU JUST DO IT.
YOU'RE REALLY GLAD THAT YOU'RE
THERE AND YOU CAN DO YOUR PART
TO MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
>> Reporter: IN WEST, TEXAS,
OVERNIGHT, SIMILAR TALES OF
HEROISM.
WILLIAM BIRCH PULLED THE INJURED
OUT OF A DEMOLISHED NURSING
HOME.
>> YOU HAVE TO REACH OUT AND
HELP THOSE WHO CAN'T HELP
THEMSELVES.
>> Reporter: WHAT CAUSES SOMEO
TO RUN TOWARD DANGER WHEN OTHERS
ARE RUNNING AWAY?
SCIENTISTS SAY HAVING A  TCTIM,E
THE BOYFRIENDS WHO SHIELDED
THEIR GIRLFRIENDS IN THE AURORA
MOVIE THEATER MASSACRE, OR TO A
PLACE, AS IN BOSTON AND IN
TEXAS, CAN MAKE DIFFERENCE.
BUT ULTIMATELY, SAID THERE
HARVARD OFESSOR, IT'S A RARE
QUALITY THAT IS NEARLY
IMPOSSIBLE TO PREDICT.
>> NONE OF US KNOW WHETHER HE
HAVE A HERO INSIDE?
>> UNTIL WE'RE FACED WITH A
CRISIS SITUATION THAT PUTS
EXTRAORDINARY DEMAND ON ORDINARY
PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: TRADITIONALLY
MANKIND HAS BEEN VIEWED AS
ESSENTIALLY SELFISH, SURVIVAL OF
THE FITTEST AND ALL THAT, BUT
THE WILLINGNESS TO RISK OUR OWN
LIVES TO HELP STRANGERS MAY BE
WHAT HAS ALLOWED US TO SURVIVE
AS A SPECIES AND CERTAINLY TO
ENDURE DISASTERS LIKE WE'VE SEEN
THIS WEEK.
DAN HARRIS, ABC NEWS, BOSTON.
>> AND WE HOPE YOU WILL TUNE IN
TONIGHT FOR "NIGHTLINE."
I'LL SEE YOU RIGHT BACK HERE
AGAIN TOMORROW.
GOODNIGHT.
>>> FROM TEXAS TONIGHT SCENES
OF UTTER DEVASTATION.
YOU'RE GOING TO HEAR FROM A
BAY AREA EXPERT WHO TELLS ABC
7 NEWS INDUSTRY VALUES PROFITS
OVER SAFETY.
>> ABC 7 NEWS CAPTURES A
RETURN TO GROUND ZERO.
YOU'LL SEE THE VIDEO THAT HAS
THE FBI FOCUSED ON FINDING TWO
MEN.
>> A SUSPECT IN THE MURDER OF
AN OFF DUTY PARAMEDIC, TAKE A
LOOKING INTO THE SURVEILLANCE
VIDEO THAT PUT POLICE ON HIS
TRAIL.
>> AND FROM THE PENINSULA,
NASA SHOWS OFF TECHNOLOGY THAT
WILL PAY BIG DIVIDENDS OVER
THE SUMMER FIRE SEASON.
>> THESE TWO MEN ARE NOW THE
FOCUS OF A NATIONWIDE MANHUNT.
>> AND THIS IS WHAT IS LEFT OF
THE FERTILIZER PLANT THAT BLEW
UP IN TEXAS LAST NIGHT AND
TOOK HALF A TOWN WITH IT.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE, I'M
CAROLYN JOHNSON.
>> WE HAVE MAJOR VEMMENTS ON
BOTH STORIES TONIGHT BUT WE'RE
GOING TO BEGIN IN TEXAS WHERE
THE DEATH TOLL IS RISING.
NOW, IT COULD BE AS HIGH AS 40
PEOPLEMENT TODAY WE BEGAN
GETTING PICTURES LIKE THESE,
HOMES IN RUNZ FOR BLOCKS
AROUND THE PLANT THAT BLEW UP
LAST NIGHT, DESTROYED BY
AT -- BY THE FORCE OF THE
BLAST.
WE SENT LAURA ANTHONY TO THE
SCENE IN THE TOWN OF WEST
ABOUT AN HOUR AND A HALF FROM
DALLAS.
AND LAURA IS THERE TONIGHT
WITH THIS REPORT.>> I GUESS AMMT
CATCHINGIR
I HEARD GO NOW, YOU'RE ABOUT
TO DIE.
>> RYAN AND HIS YOUNG FAMILY
LIVED INE PARMD BILLINGS
BLOWN TO BY WEDNESDAY
NIGHT'S EXPLOSION.
HE KNEW WHEN THE PLANT WAS
JUST ON FIRE WAITS TIME TO
TAKE HIS YOUNG SON AND WIFE
OUT OF THE HOUSE.
>> 20 SECONDS WE GOT IN THE
CAR AND STARTED TO LEAVE.
AND THEN, I TURNED TO THE
RIGHT AND ABOUT 10 SECONDS
LATER THAT THING EXPLODED.
IT PUSHED THE CAR DOWN.
THE CAR WENT UP ON THE SIDE ON
TWO WHEELS.
>> JUST A BIG CRACK OF
THUNDER.
>> BUT THIS FRIEND WAS STILL
HOME WHEN THE