>> ALL OF US HERE, WE APPRECIATE
YOUR TIME.
WE'LL SEE YOU BEGIN AT 6:00.
>> BYE-BYE.
>>> TONIGHT, THE WORLD WATCHING
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THE PRESIDENT DECLARES SYRIA HAS
CROSSED MORE THAN A RED LINE,
THAT ASSAD HAS CROSSED SEVERAL
LINES.
ON THE WORLD STAGE, THE
PRESIDENT SAYS HIS POSITION ON
ASSAD, ON SYRIA, HAS CHANGED
AFTER SEEING THE IMAGES OF THE
FAMILIES, THE CHILDREN, THE
VICTIMS OF THE CHEMICAL ATTACK.
WILL THE U.S. TAKE ACTION?
MARTHA RADDATZ STANDING BY.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, THE SHAKEUP.
THE PRESIDENT'S TOP STRATEGIST
STEVE BANNON REMOVED FROM HIS
POST ON PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
NATIONAL SECURITY COUNCIL.
>>> AT THIS HOUR, WE'RE ALSO
WATCHING THE SEVERE STORMS, THE
TORNADO WATCHES AND WARNINGS
ACROSS SEVERAL STATES.
60 MILLION AMERICANS IN THE
PATH.
THE FLOOD WATCHES RIGHT INTO THE
NORTHEAST.
>>> THE F-16 CRASH.
HOW THE PILOT BARELY AVOIDED A
SUBURBAN AMERICAN NEIGHBORHOOD.
>>> AND TONIGHT, FOUR DOZEN
ADVERTISERS HAVE NOW PULLED
THEIR ADS FROM "THE O'REILLY
FACTOR."
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP DEFENDS THE
FOX HOST BILL O'REILLY.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
IT'S GREAT TO HAVE YOU WITH US
ON A WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP IN FRONT OF THE WORLD ON
SYRIA, ON BASHAR AL ASSAD, ON
THE APPARENT CHEMICAL ATTACK
THAT KILLED SO MANY FAMILIES AND
CHILDREN.
THE PRESIDENT CONDEMNING THE
ATTACK, CALLING IT QUOTE, AN
AFFRONT TO HUMANITY.
SAYING HIS ATTITUDE TOWARD SYRIA
HAS CHANGED VERY MUCH.
THE GRAPHIC IMAGES SEEN AROUND
THE WORLD.
MORE THAN 80 MEN, WOMEN AND
CHILDREN DYING.
THOSE WHO DID SURVIVE GASPING
FOR AIR.
WHAT THE WORLD WAS WAITING FOR
NEXT, WAS WORD FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
HOW HE'LL HANDLE THIS, WILL THE
U.S. ACT?
TONIGHT, YOU'LL HEAR WHAT HE
SAID.
ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: WELCOMING THE KING
OF JORDAN TO THE WHITE HOUSE,
THE PRESIDENT FIRMLY CONDEMNED
THE CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK IN
SYRIA, PLACING THE BLAMING
-- BLAME SQUARELY ON THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT.
>> IT IS A TERRIBLE AFFRONT TO
HUMANITY, I CAN TELL YOU.
TERRIBLE.
>> Reporter: AND LATER AT A
JOINT PRESS CONFERENCE IN THE
ROSE GARDEN, HE SUGGESTED THERE
SHOULD BE RETALIATION.
>> THESE HEINOUS ACTIONS BY THE
ASSAD REGIME CANNOT BE
TOLERATED.
>> Reporter: IN THE PAST, AGAIN
AND AGAIN, DONALD TRUMP SAID THE
U.S. SHOULD NOT GET INVOLVED.
TWEETING "SYRIA IS NOT OUR
PROBLEM" WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA
PROPOSED PROTECTING CIVILIANS.
AND AFTER ASSAD'S MASSIVE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK IN 2013,
HE TWEETED "DO NOT ATTACK SYRIA,
FIX U.S.A."
ADDING, "IF YOU DO MANY BAD
THINGS WILL HAPPEN & FROM THAT
FIGHT THE U.S. GETS NOTHING!"
BUT NOW, THE PRESIDENT SAYS
THESE HORRIFIC IMAGES HAVE
CHANGED HIS VIEWS ON THE ASSAD
REGIME.
INNOCENT CIVILIANS SUFFERING
FROM THIS WEEK'S ATTACK, MORE
THAN 80 DEAD.
HERE A FATHER CLUTCHES HIS TWIN
9-MONTH-OLD BABIES, BOTH OF THEM
KILLED.
TODAY AT THE WHITE HOUSE, TALK
OF A CHANGED SYRIAN POLICY.
>> I DO CHANGE.
AND I AM FLEXIBLE.
AND I'M PROUD OF THAT
FLEXIBILITY.
AND I WILL TELL YOU, THAT ATTACK
ON CHILDREN YESTERDAY, HAD A BIG
IMPACT ON ME.
BIG IMPACT.
AND IT'S VERY, VERY POSSIBLE,
AND I WILL TELL YOU, IT'S
ALREADY HAPPENED, THAT MY
ATTITUDE TOWARD SYRIA AND ASSAD
HAS CHANGED VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: TRUMP BLAMES
PRESIDENT OBAMA FOR THE
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS BUT
ACKNOWLEDGES IT'S NOW HIS
CHALLENGE TO SOLVE.
>> I NOW HAVE RESPONSIBILITY AND
I WILL HAVE THAT RESPONSIBILITY
AND CARRY IT VERY PROUDLY, I
WILL TELL YOU THAT.
IT IS NOW MY RESPONSIBILITY.
>> IF I COULD JUST QUICKLY ASK
YOU IF THE CHEMICAL ATTACKS
CROSSES A RED LINE FOR YOU?
>> IT CROSSED A LOT OF LINES FOR
ME.
WHEN YOU KILL INNOCENT CHILDREN,
INNOCENT BABIES -- BABIES,
LITTLE BABIES -- WITH A CHEMICAL
GAS THAT IS SO LETHAL.
PEOPLE WERE SHOCKED TO HEAR WHAT
GAS IT WAS, THAT CROSSES MANY,
MANY LINES, BEYOND A RED LINE.
MANY, MANY LINES.
>> Reporter: BUT HE GAVE NO
INDICATION OF WHAT HE MAY DO.
>> WELL, ONE OF THE THINGS I
THINK YOU'VE NOTICED ABOUT ME IS
MILITARILY, I DON'T LIKE TO SAY
WHERE I'M GOING AND WHAT I'M
DOING.
I'M NOT SAYING I'M DOING
ANYTHING ONE WAY OR THE OTHER.
BUT I'M CERTAINLY NOT GOING TO
BE TELLING YOU.
>> Reporter: TODAY, KING
ABDULLAH MADE IT CLEAR, THE
WORLD IS LOOKING TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
>> I BELIEVE UNDER YOUR
LEADERSHIP WE WILL BE ABLE TO
UNRAVEL THIS VERY COMPLICATED
SITUATION.
>> Reporter: AND THE PRESIDENT,
WHILE AGAIN BLAMING HIS
PREDECESSOR, IS PROMISING TO
TAKE ACTION.
>> THE WORLD IS A MESS.
I INHERITED A MESS.
WE'RE GOING TO FIX IT.
>>> AND JON KARL WITH US TONIGHT
LIVE AT THE WHITE HOUSE.
THE PRESIDENT MADE IT CLEAR HE
WON'T SAY WHAT HE'S GOING TO DO.
BUT DO WE HAVE ANY KIND OF TIME
LINE FOR POSSIBLE ACTION HERE?
>> WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS SAY
THIS IS VERY HIGH ON THE AGENDA.
IN FACT, THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF
CHAIRED A MEETING OF HIS
NATIONAL SECURITY COUNCIL TODAY
HERE AT THE WHITE HOUSE ON THE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK.
BUT, DAVID, NO TIME LINE YET FOR
A RESPONSE.
>> ALL RIGHT, JON KARL LEADING
US OFF.
JON, THANK YOU.
>>> WE JUST HEARD PRESIDENT
TRUMP SAYING THAT SYRIA CROSSED
NOT ONLY A RED LINE, BUT SEVERAL
LINES.
WE ALSO SAW U.N. AMBASSADOR
NIKKI HALEY HOLDING UP PICTURES
TODAY SAYING, IF THE U.N.
DOESN'T ACT THE U.S. MAY HAVE
TO.
>> HOW MANY MORE CHILDREN HAVE
TO DIE BEFORE RUSSIA CARES?
THE UNITED STATES SEES
YESTERDAY'S ATTACK AS A DISGRACE
AT THE HIGHEST LEVEL.
AN ASSURANCE THAT HUMANITY MEANS
NOTHING TO THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT.
WHEN THE UNITED NATIONS
CONSISTENTLY FAILS IN ITS DUTY
TO ACT COLLECTIVELY, THERE ARE
TIMES WHERE WE ARE COMPELLED TO
TAKE OUR OWN ACTION.
>>> I WANT TO BRING IN MARTHA
RADDATZ, WITH US TONIGHT.
YOU HEARD THE PRESIDENT THERE
SAYING HIS ATTITUDE TOWARD SYRIA
HAS CHANGED.
WE JUST HEARD AMBASSADOR HALEY
SAY, AT TIMES WE'RE QUOTE,
COMPELLED TO TAKE OUR OWN
ACTION.
FOR AMERICANS AT HOME TONIGHT
WONDERING WHAT'S GOING HAPPEN,
WHAT'S NEXT?
>> WHAT'S THE GOAL HERE?
DO THEY WANT TO PREVENT FURTHER
ATTACKS?
DO THEY JUST WANT TO PUNISH OR
DO THEY WANT TO GET RID OF
BASHAR AL ASSAD?
WE DON'T KNOW.
IN 2013, THERE WERE ARRAY OF AIR
STRIKES WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA
SAID THEY CROSSED THE RED LINE.
THEY DIDN'T USE THEM.
THEY STILL HAD THAT
INTELLIGENCE.
BUT MOST OF THOSE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS, THE STOCKPILES, ARE
GONE SO THE CHEMICAL WEAPONS
USED HERE WERE HIDDEN.
THIS IS MUCH MORE DIFFICULT.
>> AND AS WE HEARD, THEY MET
WITH THE NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM
TODAY.
MARTHA, THANK YOU.
>>> ALL OF THIS PLAYING OUT AMID
A SHAKEUP ON THE PRESIDENT'S
NATIONAL SECURITY COUNCIL.
THE PRESIDENT'S CHIEF POLITICAL
STRATEGIST
STEVE BANNON HAS NOW BEEN
REMOVED FROM THE NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNCIL.
WHAT'S BEHIND THE MOVE?
HERE'S ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA.
>> Reporter: AT THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY, A STAFF SHAKEUP.
PRESIDENT TRUMP, REVERSING HIS
CONTROVERSIAL DECISION TO PUT
HIS CHIEF STRATEGIST, STEVE
BANNON, ON THE NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL.
BANNON'S PRESENCE ON THE COUNCIL
DREW HARSH CRITICISM, A
LIGHTNING ROD, HIS RIGHT-WING
VIEWS ON NATIONALISM AND ISLAM
NO SECRET.
>> IT'S PRETTY DARK HERE IN
EUROPE RIGHT NOW, BUT THERE'S
SOMETHING ACTUALLY MUCH DARKER
AND THAT IS ISLAM.
>> Reporter: WHEN PRESIDENT
ADDED BANNON TO THE COMMITTEE,
HE ALSO EXCLUDED KEY MILITARY
AND INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS AND
WAS ACCUSED OF FAVORING POLITICS
OVER NATIONAL SECURITY
EXPERIENCE.
TODAY'S RESTRUCTURING LARGELY
DUE TO THE GROWING INFLUENCE OF
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER,
GENERAL H.R. McMASTER, WHO TOOK
ON THE JOB AFTER MICHAEL FLYNN
WAS FIRED AFTER JUST 24 DAYS.
THE MILITARY AND INTELLIGENCE
LEADERS INITIALLY EXCLUDED, NOW
RESTORED TO THEIR PERMANENT
SEATS ON THE COUNCIL.
VICE PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE SAYING
TODAY, "THIS IS JUST A NATURAL
EVOLUTION TO ENSURE THE NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNCIL IS ORGANIZED IN
A WAY THAT BEST SERVES THE
PRESIDENT IN RESOLVING AND
MAKING THOSE DIFFICULT
DECISIONS."
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS SAY
McMASTER AND BANNON, SHARE THE
SAME PHILOSOPHY AND VISION AND
THERE WAS NO LONGER A NEED FOR
BANNON ON THE COUNCIL.
THEY SAY BANNON HAS NOT BEEN
DEMOTED.
AS THIS NEWS WAS BREAKING, THE
PRESIDENT IN THE OVAL OFFICE
WITH "THE NEW YORK TIMES,"
TALKING ABOUT WHAT HE CALLED
"ONE OF THE BIG STORIES OF OUR
TIME."
IT INVOLVES PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER SUSAN
RICE AND HER ACKNOWLEDGEMENT
THAT SHE ASKED TO KNOW THE
IDENTITIES OF AMERICANS PICKED
UP BY SURVEILLANCE, A PROCESS
KNOWN AS UNMASKING.
SOURCES TELLING ABC NEWS THAT IN
SOME CASES THEY WERE THE NAMES
OF TRUMP CAMPAIGN AND TRANSITION
OFFICIALS, CAUGHT UP IN
SURVEILLANCE AS THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY INVESTIGATED RUSSIA'S
ELECTION MEDDLING.
RICE DENIED LEAKING ANY NAMES.
>> I LEAKED NOTHING TO NOBODY
AND NEVER HAVE AND NEVER WOULD.
>> Reporter: AND RICE SAYS SHE
SIMPLY NEEDED TO KNOW THOSE
NAMES IN ORDER TO UNDERSTAND THE
SIGNIFICANCE OF THE INTELLIGENCE
REPORTS SHE WAS READING.
>> WE CAN'T BE PASSIVE CONSUMERS
OF THIS INFORMATION AND NOT --
AND DO OUR JOBS EFFECTIVELY TO
PROTECT THE AMERICAN PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: BUT TODAY ASKED BY
"THE NEW YORK TIMES" IF RICE
COMMITTED A CRIME, PRESIDENT
TRUMP SAID, "DO I THINK?
YES, I THINK."
>> CECILIA, PRESIDENT TRUMP OF
COURSE HAS ACCUSED PRESIDENT
OBAMA OF WIRETAPPING HIM.
AS YOU JUST REPORTED THERE, HE
NOW JUST SAID THAT SUSAN RICE
MAY HAVE COMMITTED A CRIME.
WHAT IS SHE SAYING TONIGHT?
>> A SPOKESPERSON FOR RICE SAID,
I'M NOT GOING TO DIGNIFY THE
PRESIDENT'S COMMENT WITH A
RESPONSE.
THEY HAVE QUESTIONS FOR RICE AND
THEY'D LIKE HER TO TESTIFY
BEFORE THEIR PANELS.
DAVID.
>> CECILIA VEGA WITH US AGAIN
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, CECILIA.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO ANOTHER
FIRESTORM, THIS ONE INVOLVING
FOX NEWS HOST BILL O'REILLY.
TONIGHT, PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
DEFENDING HIM.
HERE'S ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS.
>> CAUTION, YOU'RE ABOUT TO
ENTER THE NO-SPIN ZONE.
>> Reporter: AS THE EMBATTLED
STAR OF FOX NEWS FACES A
FIRESTORM OVER ALLEGED SEXUAL
HARASSMENT, THE PRESIDENT IS
COMING TO HIS DEFENSE.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH THE "THE
NEW YORK TIMES" PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAID -- I THINK HE'S A GOOD
PERSON.
FOX NEWS IS FACING GROWING CALLS
TO FIRE O'REILLY.
AND NEARLY 50 COMPANIES HAVE
PULLED THEIR ADS FROM THE SHOW.
O'REILLY PAID FIVE WOMEN ALMOST
$13 MILLION IN SETTLEMENTS OVER
CLAIMS OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT.
THE PRESIDENT NOW SAYS
"PERSO.
"PERSONALLY I THINK HE SHOULDN'T
HAVE SETTLED.
BECAUSE YOU SHOULD HAVE TAKEN IT
ALL THE WAY.
I DON'T THINK BILL DID ANYTHING
WRONG."
IT'S NOT THE FIRST TIME HE'S
DEFENDED A FOX TITAN.
LAST SUMMER, WHEN FORMER CEO
ROGER AILES FACED MULTIPLE
ALLEGATIONS OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT, CANDIDATE TRUMP
DEFENDED HIS FRIEND.
>> THEY'RE SAYING THESE HORRIBLE
THINGS ABOUT HIM.
IT'S VERY SAD.
BECAUSE HE'S A VERY GOOD PERSON.
>> Reporter: BUT JUST A MONTH
BEFORE THE ELECTION IT WAS TRUMP
UNDER FIRE FOR THAT INFAMOUS
"ACCESS HOLLYWOOD" TAPE WHERE HE
TALKED ABOUT GROPING WOMEN.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO PLAY TOO
MUCH OF IT BECAUSE IT IS CRUDE
GUY TALK.
>> Reporter: CANDIDATE TRUMP
THEN GAVE O'REILLY THE FIRST
TV INTERVIEW IN THE WAKE OF THAT
EXPLOSIVE TAPE.
>> WELL, FIRST OF ALL, LOCKER
ROOM TALK, AND MOST PEOPLE HAVE
HEARD IT BEFORE.
>> Reporter: HE APOLOGIZED FOR
THE REMARKS.
MORE THAN A DOZEN WOMEN CAME
GUARD ACCUSING HIM OF
INAPPROPRIATE SEXUAL ADVANCES
AND GROPING.
ALLEGATIONS HE DENIES.
IN A STATEMENT OVER THE WEEKEND,
HE SAID HIS FAME MAKES HIM A
TARGET.
HE HAS TO PUT TO REST ANY
CONTROVERSIES TO SPARE HIS
CHILDREN.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S DEFENSE OF
O'REILLY COMES JUST DAYS AFTER
THE PRESIDENT ACKNOWLEDGED APRIL
AS SEXUAL ASSAULT AND AWARENESS
MONTH.
>>> NEXT, THE NEW TORNADO
THREATS.
60 MILLION AMERICANS
BRACING FOR POSSIBLE TWISTERS
AND LARGE HAIL AND FLOOD WATCHES
RIGHT UP INTO THE NORTHEAST.
A CONFIRMED EF-2 TORNADO
TEARING ACROSS GOODMAN,
MISSOURI, ON THE GROUND FOR
ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
THIS ENTIRE SYSTEM PUSHING ITS
WAY EAST.
ABC'S STEVE OSUNSAMI IS IN
ATLANTA, WHERE THEY ARE BRACING
FOR DANGEROUS WEATHER TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: FAMILIES IN THE
DEEP SOUTH TONIGHT ARE FACING AN
EMERGENCY, FROM SWIFT-WATER
RESCUES AT FLOODED STREETS IN
ATLANTA, TO THIS TORNADO IN
WESTON, GEORGIA.
FARMS WERE TORN APART, MOBILE
HOMES DESTROYED.
>> THE TOP OF THE HOUSE STARTED
PEELING OFF, SO WE KNEW IT WAS A
VERY SERIOUS STORM.
>> Reporter: AT THE MASTERS GOLF
TOURNAMENT IN AUGUSTA, IT WASN'T
SAFE TO STAY OUT ON THE GREENS.
>> WE ARE ASKING YOU TO EVACUATE
THE GROUNDS.
>> Reporter: IN NEIGHBORHOODS
ACROSS THE REGION, TORNADO
SIRENS ARE BLARING, THE FLASH
FLOODS ARE RISING.
IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG NIGHT
FOR NEARLY 60 MILLION AMERICANS.
>> YOU NEED TO BE CAREFUL.
THIS IS A VERY DANGEROUS
SITUATION YOU'RE COMING INTO.
>> Reporter: NORTH OF ATLANTA,
LIGHTNING STRUCK SEVERAL HOMES
AND SET THEM ON FIRE.
>> THE HOMEOWNER TOLD ME IT
SOUNDED LIKE A STICK OF DYNAMITE
GOING OFF.
>> Reporter: THIS FAMILY WON'T
BE ABLE STAY HERE TONIGHT.
>> I'VE SEEN A LOT OF LIGHTNING
STRIKES BUT I'VE NEVER SEEN THEM
HIT THIS CLOSE.
>> Reporter: THIS SAME STORM
HURLED AN EF-2 TORNADO AT THE
KIND PEOPLE OF GOODMAN,
MISSOURI.
WINDS AS HIGH AS 120 MILES AND
HOUR HIT A FIRE STATION AND TORE
APART THE ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
LUCKILY, NO ONE WAS SERIOUSLY
HURT.
>> STUNNING IMAGES OF THAT
SCHOOL.
STEVE WITH US LIVE FROM ATLANTA.
THIS ISN'T OVER YET.
A BRAND-NEW TORNADO WATCH JUST
ISSUED FOR THE METRO AREA THERE.
>> Reporter: YES, DAVID.
IT JUST CAME IN, A BRAND-NEW
TORNADO WATCH FOR THE ENTIRE
ATLANTA METRO AREA UNTIL 9:00
P.M. TONIGHT.
AND TALK ABOUT A STORY HITTING
CLOSE TO HOME, THIS IS MY
NEIGHBORHOOD.
THE STREET IS BLOCKED.
POWER CREWS ARE OUT HERE, TRYING
TO CLEAR THE ROAD THAT LEADS TO
MY HOUSE AND RESTORE POWER TO
THIS ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOOD.
DAVID.
>> WE'RE CERTAINLY YOU'RE OKAY.
WE'RE THINKING OF YOUR
AND EVERYONE ACROSS THE SOUTH.
>>> ROB WITH US TRACKING THIS
NOW.
IT'S NOT JUST THE SOUTH, THIS IS
MOVING EASTWARD AS WE SPEAK.
>> SUCH A LARGE, SUCH A DYNAMIC
SYSTEM, A HUGE AREA UNDER THE
GUN.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO IT.
ALABAMA, GEORGIA, CAROLINAS,
PARTICULARLY DANGEROUS SITUATION
IN THAT SPOT THERE.
THAT'S A RARE ISSUANCE.
AND THE RADAR LIT UP.
MORE STORMS FIRING.
IT GOES INTO KENTUCKY, OHIO AND
INDIANA.
IT PUSHES OFF TOMORROW INTO THE
EAST AND MID-ATLANTIC WHERE THE
STORMS WILL BE.
SNOW ON THE BACKSIDE OF THIS.
BIG-TIME RAIN ACROSS THE
NORTHEAST WHERE FLOOD WATCHES
ARE POSTED.
A BIG MESS THROUGH TOMORROW AS
WELL.
>> TRACKING IT THROUGH TOMORROW
FOR US, ROB.
THANK YOU.
>>> THERE'S STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT" --
THE F-16 CRASH.
HOW THE PILOT BARELY MISSED A
SUBURBAN AMERICAN NEIGHBORHOOD.
HE DID SURVIVE.
>>> THE MANHUNT UNDER WAY, TWO
INMATES AUTHORITIES CALL
DANGEROUS.
HOW THEY THINK THE PAIR MAY HAVE
ESCAPED AND WHERE THEY'RE
LOOKING.
>>> AND OF COURSE THE AD
OUTRAGE, TONIGHT, THE NEW
DEVELOPMENT COMING IN HERE, WHY
PEPSI IS NOW PULLING THE
CONTROVERSIAL AD AND IS NOW
APOLOGIZING.
BACK IN A MOMENT.
Needles.
Essential for him,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate did not
work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections,
lymphoma and other cancers have
happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR if you
have an infection.
Tears in the stomach or
intestines,
low blood cell counts and higher
liver tests and
cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ
XR, and monitor
certain liver tests. Tell your
doctor if you were
in a region where fungal
infections are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
Fine for some.
But for you, one pill a day may
provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor about XELJANZ
XR. An "Unjection™".
Well, What are you doing o take
care otomorrow -10AM? but...
Staff meeting.
3:45?
Tai Chi.
6:30?
Sam's Baseball Practice.
You are busy.
Wouldn't it be great if you
had investments
that worked as hard as you do?
Yeah.
Introducing Essential Portfolios
The automated
investing solution.
your date with
destiny has arrived.
Let's do this!
New Cinnamon Frosted
Flakes are finally here.
Sweet cinnamon and the
frosted crunch you love.
Well?
Tastes like victory T.
Tastes like victory.
They're great!
(Roosevelt)smoking just messed
thaup your lungs.
I never thought
that at only 45
it would give me a heart attack.
My tip is;
do your heart a favor,
and quit now.
(Announcer) You can quit.
For free help,
call 1-800-QUIT-NOW.
Bounty is more absorbent,Mom"
per roll
so the roll can last 50% longer
than the leading ordinary brand.
So you get more "Life" per roll.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker Upper
>>> NEXT TONIGHT, THE AD TRYING
TO SELL SODA USING THEMES OF
POLICING AND RACE.
TONIGHT, THAT AD HAS NOW BEEN
PULLED AFTER UNLEASHING OUTRAGE
ACROSS THIS COUNTRY, INCLUDING
MARTIN LUTHER KING JR.'S OWN
DAUGHTER.
ABC'S DAVID WRIGHT ON THE
APOLOGY NOW.
>> Reporter: PEPSI'S EDGY NEW
WEB AD FEATURES REALITY STAR
KENDALL JENNER DISARMING RACIAL
TENSIONS WITH A SUGARY BEVERAGE.
THE SIMILARITY WITH THIS IMAGE
TRIVIALIZING BLACK LIVES MATTER.
ACCORDING TO SOME ACTIVISTS.
THE DAUGHTER OF MARTIN LUTHER
KING JR. TWEETED, "IF ONLY DADDY
WOULD HAVE KNOWN ABOUT THE POWER
OF PEPSI."
THIS AFTERNOON, PEPSI PULLED THE
AD AND APOLOGIZED TO BERNICE
KING.
BUT PEPSI HAS STRUGGLED BEFORE.
>> COME ON.
WHICH ONE IS HE?
>> Reporter: PEPSI ULTIMATELY
PULLED THIS MOUNTAIN DEW AD
FEATURING A GOAT IN A POLICE
LINEUP WITH BLACK MEN.
TODAY, PAPARAZZI CAUGHT UP WITH
KENDALL JENNER IN PARIS.
>> DO YOU HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY
ABOUT THE PEPSI VIDEO?
DO YOU HAVE ANY REGRETS?
>> Reporter: PEPSI DOES HAVE
REGRETS.
SAYING, IT WAS TRYING TO PROJECT
A GLOBAL MESSAGE OF UNITY, PEACE
AND UNDERSTANDING.
ADDING, CLEARLY WE MISSED THE
MARK.
DAVID WRIGHT, ABC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>> DAVID, THANK YOU.
>>> TONIGHT, THE JAILBREAK THE
MANHUNT.
TWO DANGEROUS INMATES ON THE
RUN.
NOW THE MANHUNT.
>>> ALSO THE F-16 CRASH.
BARELY MISSING A SUBURBAN
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>>> THE SPECIAL DELIVERY, THE
WHOLE WORLD WAITING ON ONE
GIRAFFE IN AMERICA.
BUT THE OTHER GIRAFFE THAT BEAT
US TO THE PUNCH.
And markets continue to
rise and fall...
Predictable is one thing you
need in retirement
to help protect what you've
earned and ensure it lasts.
Introducing
Brighthouse Financial.
A new company established
by MetLife
to specialize in annuities
& life insurance.
Talk to your advisor about a
brighter financial future.
Don't let dust and allergens
and life's beautiful moments.
Flonase Allergy Relief
delivers more complete relief.
Flonase helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause all your symptoms,
including nasal congestion
and itchy, watery eyes.
Flonase is an
allergy nasal spray
that works even
beyond the nose.
So you can enjoy every
beautiful moment to the fullest.
Flonase.
6>1 Changes everything.
(de♪p breath)
(phone ringing)
They'll call back.
No one knows your Ford better
than Ford and Ford Service.
Right now, during
The Big Tire Event,
get a $140 rebate by mail,
on four select tires.
♪
>>> TO THE INDEX OF OTHER NEWS
TONIGHT.
THE FIERY CRASH OF AN AMERICAN
FIGHTER JET IN CLINTON,
MARYLAND.
THE F-16 WITH LIVE AMMUNITION ON
BOARD GOING DOWN IN SMOKE AND
FLAMES DURING A TRAINING FLIGHT.
THE AIR NATIONAL GUARD PILOT
ABLE TO STEER THE JET AWAY FROM
HOMES IN THE AREA.
BEFORE EJECTS OVER THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
HE SAFELY PARACHUTED TO THE
GROUND.
THE PLANE SUFFERED MECHANICAL
FAILURE SHORTLY AFTER TAKEOFF
FROM JOINT BASE ANDREWS.
>>> A MANHUNT IS UNDER WAY
TONIGHT FOR A PAIR OF WASHINGTON
STATE INMATES.
AUTHORITIES ARE CALLING THE
INMATES DANGEROUS, THE PAIR
ESCAPING FROM THE JAIL IN YAKIMA
COUNTY.
ONE OF THE INMATES WAS BEING
HELD FOR AN ALLEGED SHOOTING.
AUTHORITIES ARE WARNING
NEIGHBORS TO BE VIGILANT.
>>> WHILE THE WORLD WAITS FOR A
BABY GIRAFFE HERE IN THE U.S.,
SO MANY OF THEM WATCHING ONLINE.
IT TURNS OUT ANOTHER WAS BORN AT
THE CHESTER ZOO IN THE UK AFTER
A FOUR-HOUR LABOR.
THE SPECIAL DELIVERY COMES AS
MANY STILL WATCH APRIL THE
GIRAFFE IN NEW YORK.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK -- ONE
HONOR STUDENT'S INCREDIBLE GIFT.
THREE STRANGERS AND WHAT WE
WITNESSED.
YOU HAVE TO SEE THIS.
Allergy symptoms
distracting you?
[ sneezes ]
Doctors recommend taking
non-drowsy Claritin
every day of your allergy
season for continuous relief.
With Claritin, you get
powerful, non-drowsy relief,
24-hours a day.
Day after day.
Wow!
And with fewer
symptoms to distract you,
you can focus on
the extraordinary things
you do every single day.
[ cheering ]
Live Claritin Clear. Every day.
For one week only, save up
to $32 on Claritin products.
Check this Sunday's newspaper.
Hi, I'm Mindy Kearns. It's great
Nice to meet you too.
Your parents have been
talking about you for years.
Sorry about that.
They're all about me
saving for a house,
or starting a
college fund for my son.
Actually, I want to
know what you're thinking.
Have a seat.
Knowing that the most
important goals are yours.
Multiplied by 14,000 financial
advisors, it's a big deal.
And it's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
I'm 51 years old.m.
When I was diagnosed with
pneumococcal pneumonia,
it was huge for everybody.
She just started to
decline rapidly.
I was rushed to the hospital...
My symptoms were devastating.
The doctor said, "Pam!
If you'd have waited
two more days,
you would've died."
If I'd have known that a vaccine
could have helped prevent this,
I would have asked my doctor
or pharmacist about it.
At Planters, we put fresh
roawhich has its drawbacks.an,
Guys, know anything about
this missing inventory?
Wasn't me!
The cheeks don't lie, Chet...
Irresistibly Planters.
My belly pain
I could build a small city
with all the over-the-counter
products I've used.
Enough!
I've tried enough laxatives
to cover
the Eastern Seaboard.
I've climbed a Mount Everest
of fiber.
Probiotics?
Enough!
(AVO)
If you've had enough,
tell your doctor
what you've tried
and how long you've been at it.
LINZESS works differently
from laxatives.
LINZESS treats adults
with IBS with Constipation
or Chronic Constipation.
It can help
relieve your belly pain,
and lets you have more frequent
and complete bowel movements
that are easier to pass.
Do not give LINZESS
to children under six,
and it should not be given
to children
six to less than eighteen.
It may harm them.
Don't take LINZESS if you have
a bowel blockage.
Get immediate help
if you develop unusual
or severe stomach pain,
especially with bloody
or black stools.
The most common side effect
is diarrhea, sometimes severe.
If it's severe
stop taking LINZESS
and call your doctor right away.
Other side effects include gas,
stomach-area pain
and swelling.
Talk to your doctor about
managing your symptoms
proactively with LINZESS.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
AMERICA STRONG.
THE STORY OF A STAR ATHLETE AND
HONOR STUDENT AND HIS GIFT.
FOR THREE PEOPLE HE NEVER MET.
>> Reporter: A MOTHER'S
LAUGHTER.
HER SMILE.
KNOWING THE GIFT HER SON HAS NOW
GIVEN.
IN FT. WORTH, TEXAS, TODAY, SO
MANY STUDENTS WEARING AARON
SINGLETON'S NUMBER 33.
IT WAS A PROFOUND LESSON IN
GIVING.
AARON GREW UP LOVING SPORTS.
UP AT BAT, PLAYING FOR THE
JOSHUA ALL-STARS.
AND LATER, BASEBALL AND FOOTBALL
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
TOO MANY MEDALS, TOO MANY AWARDS
TO COUNT.
>> TRACK, BASEBALL --
>> Reporter: IT WAS LAST
NOVEMBER, AARON SUFFERED A
SERIOUS HEAD INJURY DURING A
GAME.
HE DID NOT SURVIVE.
HIS TEAM, HIS COMMUNITY,
HEARTBROKEN.
>> I WISH MORE THAN ANYTHING FOR
HIM TO BE HERE WITH US PLAYING
BY OUR SIDE.
>> Reporter: BUT TONIGHT, IN
THAT COMMUNITY, A LESSON ABOUT
LIFE AND THE GIFTS FROM NUMBER
33.
HIS MOTHER MADE THE DIFFICULT TO
CHOICE TO DONATE HIS ORGANS.
AND YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE THE
MOMENT AARON'S MOTHER MEETS THE
THREE PEOPLE WHO ARE ALIVE TODAY
BECAUSE OF HER SON.
32-YEAR-OLD DUSTIN EARLY
RECEIVING A KIDNEY.
>> I CAN DO JUST ABOUT ANYTHING
I WANT TO NOW.
I'M GRATEFUL FOR THAT.
>> Reporter: A MOTHER, BRENDA
FLOREZ, RECEIVING A KIDNEY AND
LIVER.
>> HI, I'M SO GLAD TO MEET YOU.
I'M SO GRATEFUL.
>> ME, TOO.
>> Reporter: TWO MOTHERS BROUGHT
TOGETHER.
AND MIKE NORTON FROM HOUSTON,
RECEIVING AARON'S HEART.
>> I'M SO SORRY FOR YOUR LOSS.
BUT I'M VERY APPRECIATIVE OF
YOUR GIFT.
>> YOU'RE WELCOME.
>> THANK YOU.
EVERYTHING I DO FOR THE REST OF
MY LIFE, AARON IS TAKING ME
THERE.
>> Reporter: AND ALONG WITH THAT
HUG, SHE THEN HEARS HER SON'S
HEART.
A MOTHER'S STRENGTH.
A SON'S GIFT.
AND THREE STRANGERS GRATEFUL.
A BRAVE MOTHER AND HER SON'S
GIFT.
>>> WE THANK WFAA AND WE THANK
YOU FOR WATCHING.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NEXT AT 6:00, A 4-MONTH-OLD
IS BACK IN HER MOTHER'S ARMS,
ENDING AN 18-HOUR ODYSSEY, BUT
THIS CASE IS NOT CLOSED.
>>> ANTI-TRUMP ACTIVISTS FINALLY
GO TO COURT.
>>> PLUS --
>> BAY AREA TEENAGERS GET A
CRASH COURSE ABOUT THE DANGERS
OF DISTRACTED DRIVING.
ABC7 "NEWS AT 6:00" STARTS NOW.
>>> WE'RE JUST RELIEVED THAT HE
IS IN CUSTODY AND NO LONGER ABLE
TO HURT ANYBODY ELSE.
>> POLICE TRACK DOWN AND CAPTURE
THE SUSPECT IN YESTERDAY'S
DEADLY SHOOTING OF A RICHMOND
WOMAN GUNNED DOWN RIGHT IN FRONT
OF HER YOUNG CHILDREN.
GOOD EVENING.
>>> IT TOOK AUTHORITIES A LITTLE
MORE THAN 24 HOURS TO TRACK DOWN
AND ARREST THE 43-YEAR-OLD
SUSPECT HIS NAME IS LAWYER
DESHAWN McBRIDE.
WITNESSES SAY McBRIDE CUT OFF
HIS EX-GIRLFRIEND LA SHONDA
FRANKLIN AS SHE DROVE HER
CHILDREN TO SCHOOL YESTERDAY
MORNING.
>> SURVEILLANCE VIDEO SHOWS
McBRIDE LEAVING THE SCENE OFF
SHE WAS SHOT.
>> HE WAS TRACKED TO A FAST FOOD
RESTAURANT IN THE CITY OF
SACRAMENTO.
AND OUR DETECTIVES IN THE
MARSHALL SERVICES OFFICERS WENT
IN AND APPREHENDED HIM WITHOUT
ANY FIGHT.
>> BOTH OF FRANKLIN'S CHILDREN
WITNESSED HER BEING KILLED,
THEY'RE BOTH UNDER THE AGE OF
10.
McBRIDE AND FRANKLIN HAD A
HISTORY OF DOMESTIC VIOLENCE.
>>> JUST MINUTES AGO SKY 7 WAS
OVER MARKET AND 33rd STREET.
POLICE CONFIRM TO ABC7 NEWS THEY
WERE LOOKING FOR A SUSPECT IN
CONNECTION WITH