SMOKE, AND I RAN FAST AS I
COULD.
>> Reporter: CAMERAS WERE
ROLLING FROM MANY ANGLES AS THE
FORCE OF THE BLAST ACTUALLY
KNOCKS OVER AT LEAST ONE OF THE
MARATHONERS.
LOOK AGAIN.
MOST OF THE INJURIES, THOUGH,
SUFFERED BY SPECTATORS WHO CAME
TO CELEBRATE THE FINISH.
>> A BOMB WENT OFF AND IT
KNOCKED ME TO THE GROUND.
AND THEN, YOU KNOW, EVERYBODY
STARTED RUNNING.
PANICKING, AND ANOTHER BOMB WENT
OFF.
AND THEN I FELT THE GROUND
AGAIN, PEOPLE RUNNING, YOU WERE
GETTING TRAMPLED.
>> IT WAS VERY LOUD.
THE GROUND SHOOK, YOU COULD JUST
FEEL IT GOING DOWN THROUGH YOU.
JUST A SCARY SCENE.
>> Reporter: RIGHT NEXT TO THE
FINISH LINE, BLEACHERS FILLED
WITH SPECTATORS, STUNNED AND
CONFUSED BY THE FIRST BLAST,
THEN WATCH IN HORROR AS 50 TO A
HUNDRED YARDS AWAY, A SECOND
EXPLOSION.
EYEWITNESSES SAY THE INJURED
WERE PILED ON THE SIDEWALK,
SEVERED LIMBS LITTERING THE
STREET, ONLOOKERS COMFORTING
EACH OTHER AS THE VIOLENCE AND
CHAOS ENGULFED THEM.
>> I SAW QUITE A FEW CASUALTIES,
ONE GUY WITH HIS LEGS GONE AT
THE KNEES.
ANKLES AND FEET MISSING,
SHRAPNEL WOUNDS ON THE SIDE OF
THE HEAD.
>> Reporter: THE TWO BOMBS
DESCRIBED BY AUTHORITIES AS
SMALL EXPLOSIVE DEVICES, THERE
WAS NO WARNING, NO ADVANCE
THREAT, BUT PARAMEDICS, NATIONAL
GUARD AND POLICE WERE ALREADY ON
THE SCENE FOR THE MARATHON'S
SECURITY AND MEDICAL NEEDS.
THEY SPED INTO ACTION,
PRONOUNCING TWO DEAD ALMOST
IMMEDIATELY, TRAGICALLY, ONE OF
THEM AN 8-YEAR-OLD CHILD.
THEN CARRYING AT LEAST 99
INJURED INTO THE RACE MEDICAL
TENTS BEFORE THE HOSPITAL.
POLICE AT THE INITIAL PRESS
CONFERENCE WARNING DOWNTOWN
BOSTON TO STAY CALM, BUT THE
-- ADMITTING THE STREETS WERE
NOT SAFE.
>> WE'RE RECOMMENDING TO PEOPLE
THAT THEY STAY HOME, THAT IF
THEY'RE IN MOTELS IN THE AREA,
THAT THEY RETURN TO THEIR ROOMS,
AND THAT THEY DON'T GO ANY PLACE
AND CONGREGATE IN LARGE CROWDS.
WE WANT TO STABILIZE THE
SITUATION.
>> INITIAL REPORTS OF OTHER
BOMBS IN THE AREA, NOW
DISCOUNTED BY POLICE.
AN INCIDENT AT THE LIBRARY NOW
APPEARS TO BE UNRELATED, A
MECHANICAL FIRE.
>> THANKS SO MUCH.
THINKING ABOUT LAW ENFORCEMENT,
KEEP REMEMBER HEARING HOW THEY
RAN STRAIGHT INTO THE DANGER,
NOT THINKING.
IN SECONDS THEY WERE THERE.
WE WANT TO GO TO OUR COLLEAGUE
SHAWN KELLEY WHO IS A REPORTER
AT OUR GREAT BOSTON AFFILIATE.
WE HEARD THAT HOSPITAL OFFICIALS
SAID IT WAS LIKE A WAR ZONE.
WHAT'S THE LATEST YOU'RE HEARING
ON THE VICTIMS?
>> THE LATEST NUMBER WE'RE
GETTING FROM EMERGENCY ROOMS IS
80 PEOPLE TAKEN TO AREA
HOSPITALS.
IT WAS A TRIAGE CENTER AT THE
LOCATION OF THE MARATHON SITE
THAT WAS SET UP QUICKLY, SO THEY
WERE ABLE TO TEND TO THESE
VICTIMS.
WE SAW PEOPLE BEING WHEELED OUT
ON WHEEL CHAIRS AND STRETCHERS
WHO HAD LOST THEIR LIMBS.
FROM WHAT WE'RE HEARING FROM
DOCTORS, THE MAJORITY OF
INJURIES ARE TO PEOPLE'S LOWER
BODIES.
>> BUT THERE ARE INJURIES OF
MANY DIFFERENT KINDS, BURNS AS
WELL.
SHRAPNEL, ALL KINDS OF WOUNDS?
>> Reporter: RIGHT.
THE INJURIES WE WERE SEEING WAS
MOSTLY TO PEOPLE'S LEGS.
I SAW A WOMAN WHO APPEARED TO
HAVE LOST A GOOD PORTION OF HER
JAW.
LOTS OF LACERATIONS.
THE SCENE COMING OUT OF IT WAS
NOT HYSTERICAL.
KEEP IN MIND, THIS WAS AT THE
END OF THE MARATHON.
SO THE RUNNERS THAT WERE INJURED
WERE EXHAUSTED FROM THE RUN AND
THE SPECTATORS WHO WERE INJURED
WERE SIMPLY IN TOTAL SHOCK.
>> ALL RIGHT, THANK YOU.
WE'LL CHECK IN WITH YOU AGAIN
THROUGHOUT THE EVENING AND AGAIN
OUR THANKS TO WCVB IN BOSTON.
>>> AND AS YOU PROBABLY KNOW,
THE BOMB WENT OFF, THE FIRST
ONE, ABOUT 2:50 P.M. ON BOYLSTON
STREET IN BOSTON, AND THAT WAS
JUST FEET FROM THE FINISH LINE.
RIGHT NOW WE WANT TO TAKE YOU TO
THE STREETS OF BOSTON AND SHOW
YOU THE CHAOS, THE CONFUSION,
LET YOU HEAR FROM PEOPLE WHO
WERE THERE.
>> IT SOUNDED JUST LIKE A
BOMB -- WHAT I THOUGHT I BOMB
WOULD SOUND LIKE.
ABSOLUTELY HORRIFIED.
>> IT WAS VERY LOUD.
THE GROUND SHOOK, YOU COULD JUST
FEEL IT GOING DOWN THROUGH YOU.
>> THE EXPLOSION WENT OFF RIGHT
BY THE FINISH LINE.
BOOM, YOU FELT IT, IT HURT YOUR
EARS.
>> SOMETHING JUST BLEW UP.
>> RUN!
>> I SAW A TRASH CAN EXPLODE AND
PEOPLE STARTED THROWING DOWN THE
BARRICADE AND RUNNING OVER EACH
OTHER.
I RAN IN THE OTHER DIRECTION
FAST AS I COULD.
>> I WAS IN THE CITY.
THIS IS LIKE THE SCARIEST THING
I'VE EVER EXPERIENCED.
PEOPLE WORK IN THE RESTAURANTS
TELLING US TO GET AWAY FROM THE
SCENE, GET FAR AWAY.
PEOPLE WERE WALKING OUT LIKE IT
WAS AN EXODUS AT CAMBRIDGE.
>> I SAW RUNNERS IN FRONT OF ME
FALL, SOME WITH INJURIES, AND
THEN I LOOKED OVER AND SAW JUST
A PILE OF BODIES, THE WORST
THING I THINK I'VE EVER SEEN IN
MY LIFE.
MANGLED LIMBS, PEOPLE NOT
BREATHING.
I JUST INTERVIEWED A NURSE HERE
ON THE SCENE WHO SAID SHE
TREATED DOZENS OF PEOPLE,
INCLUDING CHILDREN, MANY PEOPLE
WITH SEVERE TRAUMA, PULMONARY
DISTRESS, YOU NAME IT.
>> THEY RESPONDED WITHIN 15
SECONDS.
YOU SAW EVERYBODY COMING DOWN
HERE.
THE MEDICAL TEAM HERE RESPONDED
INSTANTLY.
>> I'M A COLLEGE STUDENT IN
BOSTON.
YOU THINK PATRIOTS' DAY MARATHON
MONDAY AND YOU DON'T THINK
ANYTHING LIKE THIS IS EVER GOING
TO HAPPEN ON A DAY LIKE THIS IN
BOSTON.
>> AND WHEN THOSE BOMBS WENT
OFF, THERE WAS ONE PERSON
STANDING THERE, AN EMERGENCY
ROOM DOCTOR, WHO WAS JUST 20
FEET AWAY FROM ONE OF THE
EXPLOSIONS.
THIS DOCTOR SPRANG INTO ACTION
TO HELP THE VICTIMS.
DR. ALAN PAINTER JOINS US RIGHT
NOW ON THE PHONE FROM BOSTON.
DR. PAINTER, TELL US ABOUT THE
SCENE AND AS A MEDICAL
PROFESSIONAL, WHAT DID YOU SEE?
WHAT DID YOU DO?
>> BASICALLY THE EXPLOSION
OCCURRED TO MY LEFT.
I REALIZED IT WAS AN EXPLOSION,
TURNED TO MY RIGHT TO LEAVE THE
AREA.
ANOTHER EXPLOSION WENT OFF
APPARENTLY DOWN THE BLOCK.
TURNED ME BACK AROUND FACING THE
BUILDINGS.
THEN I REALIZED THERE WERE
PEOPLE BLEEDING BEHIND ME.
THEN I LOOKED TO MY LEFT WHERE I
HAD BEEN AND THERE WERE AT LEAST
SIX BODIES DOWN THERE.
APPARENTLY THEY HAD TAKEN ALL
THE BLAST AND I WAS UNSCATHED.
>> AND WERE YOU ABLE TO HELP
PEOPLE?
DID YOU GATHER PEOPLE IN YOUR
ARMS?
>> WELL, WHAT HAPPENED WAS, WE
PUT TOURNIQUETS ON PEOPLE QUICK
AS WE CAN.
BECAUSE MOST OF THE INJURIES
WERE TO THE LOWER EXTREMITIES.
WE ATTEMPTED RESUSCITATION OF A
YOUNG LADY, GOT HER BACK TO THE
MEDICAL TENT, BUT SHE DID NOT
MAKE IT.
I WANT TO COMMEND BOSTON POLICE
AND THE MEDICS THERE, THEY WERE
FRANTICALLY GETTING THINGS THAT
EVERYBODY NEEDED TO THE AREA.
AND THE BOSTON ATHLETIC
ASSOCIATION HAD SO MANY PEOPLE
THERE TO HELP, IT WAS FANTASTIC.
>> WELL, AGAIN, DR. PAINTER, A
HARROWING, HARROWING DAY.
AND WE THANK YOU FOR CHECKING IN
WITH US AS WELL.
>> AND OF COURSE AROUND THIS
COUNTRY AND THE WORLD, MAJOR
CITIES ARE RAMPING UP SECURITY
IN RESPONSE TO THE BOMBING AT
THE BOSTON MARATHON.
HERE IN NEW YORK, CRITICAL
RESPONSE TEAMS WERE DEPLOYED
AROUND THE CITY, AT HOTELS AND
LANDMARKS.
IN L.A., THEY'RE DISPATCHING
BOMB SQUADS AND BOMB SNIFFING
DOGS.
AT AIRPORTS AND TONIGHT'S L.A.
DODGERS GAME, AND ALSO IN
LONDON.
POLICE ARE REVIEWING SECURITY
PLANS FOR THE LONDON MARATHON ON
SUNDAY.
SO WHAT HAVE WE LEARNED ABOUT
THE INVESTIGATION?
THE LATEST ON WHO IS BEHIND
THIS, AND THE NATURE OF THESE
BOMBS, LET'S GO TO ABC'S SENIOR
JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT WHO HAS
BEEN WORKING THIS STORY ALL DAY,
PIERRE THOMAS.
>> WHAT WE'RE BEING TOLD BY
SOURCES IS, THEY BELIEVE THAT
TWO PORTABLE DEVICES WERE LEFT
AND PLACED AT THE SCENE AND THEN
DETONATED.
LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS RIGHT
NOW ARE AT THE SCENE, THEY'RE
LOOKING FOR PIECES OF THE DEVICE
IN ORDER TO BEGIN TO PUT THEM
BACK TOGETHER TO GET A SENSE OF
WHO MIGHT BE INVOLVED.
THEY'RE ALSO LOOKING FOR
SURVEILLANCE TAPE.
ANY SURVEILLANCE TAPE THAT WOULD
GIVE THEM AN IDEA WHO MIGHT HAVE
DONE THIS.
ALSO WE'RE TOLD IN ADDITION TO
LOOKING AT POTENTIAL DOMESTIC
SUSPECTS, THEY'RE LOOKING AT
PEOPLE TRYING TO LEAVE THE
BOSTON AREA AIRPORT.
EVERYTHING IS BEING LOOKED AT.
THIS IS THE HIGHEST PRIORITY OF
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT RIGHT
NOW.
>> PIERRE, I WANT TO GO TO THE
VIDEO OF THE EXPLOSION.
WE'RE GOING TO SLOW IT DOWN.
LOOK AGAIN AT THIS VIDEO.
TELL ME, FORENSICALLY, WHAT
INVESTIGATORS THINK THEY CAN
DETERMINE FROM WHAT WE'RE
SEEING.
>> I SPOKE WITH SOURCES WHO WERE
WATCHING AND WITNESSES THAT
PARTICULAR VIDEOTAPE.
THEY SAY IT CONFIRMS WHAT THEY
THINK.
IF YOU LOOK CLOSELY, IT SEEMS TO
COME FROM A FAIRLY CONFINED
SMALL AREA.
AGAIN, THAT WAS ONE OF THE
REASONS WHY THEY THOUGHT THIS
WAS SOME SORT OF PACKAGE LEFT
BEHIND IN THE MIDST OF THAT
CROWD TO HARM EVERYONE IN THE
IMMEDIATE PROXIMITY.
>> AND AGAIN, PERSONS OF
INTEREST TONIGHT, ANY LEADS AT
ALL?
>> AGAIN, ALL OF THE ABOVE, AS
ONE SOURCE TOLD ME, THEY WILL
LOOK AT DOMESTIC GROUPS,
INTERNATIONAL GROUPS UNTIL THEY
GET A SHRED OF EVIDENCE THAT
POINTS THEM IN ONE DIRECTION,
EVERYTHING IS ON THE TABLE.
>> AGAIN, SO MUCH THAT THEY ARE
ASKING THAT EVERYONE WHO HAD ANY
VIDEO AT ALL, SEND IT TO THEM
AND SEND THEM ANY LEADS.
PIERRE THOMAS WILL KEEP WORKING
THROUGHOUT THE NIGHT, I KNOW.
AND RIGHT AFTER THE EXPLOSION,
PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE IN FRONT OF
THE WHITE HOUSE WAS SHUT DOWN.
SHORTLY BEFORE WE CAME ON THE
AIR, THE PRESIDENT ADDRESSED THE
NATION.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL.
>> THE PRESIDENT REFERRED TO THE
BOMBING AS THE EVENT IN BOSTON,
BUT MAKE NO MISTAKE, THE WHITE
HOUSE IS TREATING THIS AS A
TERRORIST ATTACK.
WHEN THE PRESIDENT CAME INTO THE
BRIEFING ROOM A SHORT WHILE AGO,
HE VOWED TO FIND OUT WHO WAS
RESPONSIBLE AND HOLD THEM
RESPONSIBLE.
>> WE STILL DO NOT KNOW WHO DID
THIS OR WHY.
AND PEOPLE SHOULDN'T JUMP TO
CONCLUSIONS BEFORE WE HAVE ALL
THE FACTS.
BUT MAKE NO MISTAKE, WE WILL GET
TO THE BOTTOM OF THIS, AND WE
WILL FIND OUT WHO DID THIS,
WE'LL FIND OUT WHY THEY DID
THIS.
ANY RESPONSIBLE INDIVIDUALS, ANY
RESPONSIBLE GROUPS WILL FEEL THE
FULL WEIGHT OF JUSTICE.
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID HE'S
DIRECTED THE FULL RESOURCES OF
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT TO HELP
NOT ONLY WITH THE INVESTIGATION
IN BOSTON AND THE RECOVERY IN
BOSTON, BUT ALSO TO SECURE OTHER
PARTS OF THE UNITED STATES AS
NECESSARY.
THE PRESIDENT WAS INFORMED OF
THIS JUST MINUTES AFTER IT
HAPPENED AND IMMEDIATELY BEGAN
TO RECEIVE BRIEFINGS FROM HIS
NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM.
WE HAVE A PHOTO OF THE CALL HE
HAD WITH FBI DIRECTOR MULLER IN
THE OVAL OFFICE.
HE WAS BRIEFED BY ALSO HIS
HOMELAND SECURITY SECRETARY
JANET NAPOLITANO.
HERE AT THE WHITE HOUSE THE
SECURITY PERIMETER WAS PUSHED
OUT.
THE PUBLIC MOVED ACROSS THE
STREET TO PENNSYLVANIA AVENUE.
POLICE TAPE PUT ON THE SCENE AS
A PRECAUTION.
BUT THIS OBVIOUSLY BEING TREATED
AS A TERRORIST ATTACK, ALTHOUGH
THE PRESIDENT DID NOT USE THAT
WORD.
WHEN I ASKED ABOUT THAT, A
SENIOR OFFICIAL TOLD ME, ANY
EVENT WITH MULTIPLE EXPLOSIVE
DEVICES, AS THIS APPEARS TO BE,
IS CLEARLY AN ACT OF TERROR AND
WILL BE APPROACHED AS AN ACT OF
TERROR, BUT WENT ON TO SAY, WE
DON'T KNOW WHO WAS RESPONSIBLE,
IF IT WAS DOMESTIC OR FOREIGN.
>> THANKS SO MUCH, JON KARL, AND
WE'LL HAVE MUCH MORE ON THE
SPECIAL EDITION OF "WORLD NEWS"
COMING UP.
TERROR AT THE BOSTON MARATHON.
WHEN WE COME BACK, A RUNNER WHO
WAS CROSSING THE FINISH LINE
WHEN THOSE BOMBS WENT OFF.
WHAT SHE SAW, WHAT SHE HEARD.
See life in the best light.
Outdoors, or in.
automatically filter
amount of light.
the way it's meant to be seen.
Maybe even a little better.
Experience life well lit,
adaptive lenses.
Optical today
Transitions XTRActive Lenses
enhance your vision.
Sam's Club.
Savings Made Simple
[ Male Announcer ]
HOW DO YOU MEASURE HAPPINESS?
BY THE ARMFUL?
BY THE BARRELFUL?
THE CARFUL?
HOW ABOUT...BY THE BOWLFUL?
CAMPBELL'S SOUPS
GIVE YOU NUTRITION, ENERGY,
AND CAN HELP YOU KEEP
A HEALTHY WEIGHT.
CAMPBELL'S.
IT'S AMAZING WHAT SOUP CAN DO.
THE BATTLE OF BATAAN,
1942.
[ all ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA, IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]
USAA AUTO INSURANCE
IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN FROM
GENERATION TO GENERATION
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE THE MILITARY,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
.
USAA.
WE KNOW WHAT IT MEANS TO SERVE.
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
>>> AND NOW WE WANT TO BRING YOU
MORE ON THAT MOMENT WHEN THOSE
BOMBS WENT OFF AT THE BOSTON
MARATHON, AS RUNNERS WERE
CROSSING THE FINISH LINE.
AND ONE OF THEM, ONE OF THOSE
RUNNERS WAS A WOMAN NAMED ALISON
WHO JOINS US ON THE TELEPHONE.
TELL ME EXACTLY WHERE YOU WERE,
WHAT YOU SAW, WHAT YOU HEARD.
>> HI, DIANE.
I HAD JUST CROSSED OVER THE
FINISH LINE AND WAS GETTING MY
WATER AND MY MEDAL AND ALL OF
THAT.
AND I HEARD THIS BIG EXPLOSION.
AND WE ALL KIND OF PAUSED AND
THE EARTH SHOOK.
I'M FROM LOS ANGELES, SO IT FELT
LIKE OF LIKE AN EARTHQUAKE.
THEN I SMELLED A LOT OF SMOKE.
PEOPLE STARTED TO SAY, MAYBE A
TRANSFORMER BLEW.
BUT THEN IMMEDIATELY WE HEARD
ANOTHER ONE.
I TURNED AROUND AND SAW ALL THE
SMOKE.
IT WAS LOTS OF THAT DARK SMOKE
THAT GOES ALONG WITH A FIRE.
IT SMELLED LIKE FIRE.
SO WE ALL STARTED SHUFFLING THE
BEST WE COULD AFTER RUNNING TO
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
>> SO YOU COULD ACTUALLY FEEL
THE GROUND SHAKING?
>> YES, DEFINITELY FELT
EVERYTHING AROUND ME SHAKE AND
MOVE.
>> WHAT DO YOU KNOW ABOUT YOUR
FELLOW RUNNERS?
DO YOU KNOW ANY OF THEM WHO WERE
INJURED?
>> I DO NOT HAVE ANY FRIENDS WHO
WERE INJURED, THANKFULLY.
MY FRIENDS FINISHED AFTER ME, SO
THE EXPLOSION HAPPENED RIGHT
BEFORE THEY FINISHED.
SO I FINISHED FIRST.
THEY'RE ALL SAFE, I LEARNED FROM
FACEBOOK.
THE POWER OF SOCIAL MEDIA.
>> THAT IS WONDERFUL NEWS FOR
YOU, AND I'M SO GLAD TO HEAR IT.
HOW HARD WAS IT TO MAKE YOUR WAY
OUT OF THE SCENE?
AND WAS THERE CHAOS, WAS THERE
PANIC?
>> YOU KNOW, THERE WAS NOT A LOT
OF CHAOS.
I HAVE TO COMMEND REALLY THE AA
FOR DOING AN AMAZING JOB GETTING
EVERYBODY OUT OF THE WAY AND
ORDERLY.
IMMEDIATELY AMBULANCES STARTED
PILING THROUGH.
WE ALL JUST MOVED OUT OF THE WAY
FOR THEM.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS GOING
ON, DIDN'T KNOW HOW MANY PEOPLE
WERE INJURED.
I HAVE SINCE HEARD THE REPORTS,
SO I KNOW HOW DEVASTATING THIS
WAS.
BUT AT THAT POINT WE DIDN'T KNOW
ANYTHING.
BUT PEOPLE JUST WERE VERY CALM.
I HAVE TO SAY THAT, EVERYONE WAS
VERY CALM AND WE JUST MOVED OUT
OF THE WAY AND LET THE
PROFESSIONALS WORK.
>> HOW QUICKLY DID YOU GRASP
WHAT HAD HAPPENED, THAT IT WAS A
BOMB?
>> PRETTY QUICKLY.
RUMORS STARTED -- WE STARTED
HEARING PEOPLE TALK THAT THERE
WAS A BOMB AND ANOTHER BOMB.
THE AMOUNT OF FATALITIES WAS
EXAGGERATED.
I HAD HEARD 26.
I HAVE SINCE LEARNED THAT'S NOT
THE CASE RIGHT NOW.
>> I KNOW IT WAS YOUR FIRST
MARATHON RUNNING IN BOSTON AND I
JUST WANT TO SAY AGAIN, THAT IT
WAS A HARROWING DAY FOR YOU AND
SO MANY MORE PEOPLE.
WE THANK YOU FOR PHONING IN TO
US TONIGHT, THANK YOU.
>>> COMING UP NEXT HERE ON
"WORLD NEWS," WE'LL HAVE MORE ON
THE TERROR AT THE BOSTON
MARATHONS AND SOME OF THE OTHER
HEADLINES FROM THIS DAY.
CLUSTERS OF
PUSTULES, PIMPLES.
I HAD THIS SHINGLE RASH
RIGHT NEXT TO MY SPINE.
THE SORENESS
WAS EXCRUCIATING.
IT WAS IMPOSSIBLE TO
EVEN THINK ABOUT DANCING.
WHEN YOU'RE DANCING,
YOUR PARTNER IS HOLDING YOU.
SO, HIS HAND WOULD HAVE
BEEN RIGHT IN THE SPOT
THAT I HAD THE SHINGLES.
NO TANGO. NO RHUMBA.
YOU CAN'T BE TOUCHED.
FOR MORE OF THE INSIDE STORY,
VISIT SHINGLESINFO.COM
YOU'LL HAVE TO PAY FIVE HUNDRED
BUCKS FOR YOUR DEDUCTIBLE.
THE TRUTH?
AT Allstate, YOU COULD PAY ZERO.
Allstate GIVES YOU
A HUNDRED DOLLARS
OFF YOUR DEDUCTIBLE
THE DAY YOU SIGN UP.
THEN ANOTHER HUNDRED OFF EVERY
YEAR YOU DON'T HAVE AN ACCIDENT.
LET THE GOOD HANDS
REWARD YOUR SAFE DRIVING
WITH A DEDUCTIBLE
THAT GOES AWAY.
♪
DEDUCTIBLE REWARDS.
ONE MORE WAY YOU'RE IN
GOOD HANDS WITH Allstate.
♪
IF YOU HAVE HIGH CHOLESTEROL,
HERE'S SOME INFORMATION
THAT MAY BE WORTH LOOKING INTO.
IN A CLINICAL TRIAL
VERSUS LIPITOR,
CRESTOR GOT MORE HIGH-RISK
PATIENTS' BAD CHOLESTEROL
TO A GOAL OF UNDER 100.
GETTING TO GOAL IS IMPORTANT,
ESPECIALLY IF YOU HAVE
HIGH CHOLESTEROL
PLUS ANY OF THESE RISK FACTORS
BECAUSE YOU COULD BE
AT INCREASED RISK
FOR PLAQUE BUILDUP
IN YOUR ARTERIES OVER TIME.
AND THAT'S WHY WHEN DIET
AND EXERCISE ALONE
AREN'T ENOUGH
TO LOWER CHOLESTEROL
I PRESCRIBE CRESTOR.
[ Female Announcer ] CRESTOR
IS NOT RIGHT FOR EVERYONE.
LIKE PEOPLE
WITH LIVER DISEASE
OR WOMEN WHO ARE NURSING,
PREGNANT
OR MAY BECOME PREGNANT.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT OTHER
MEDICINES YOU'RE TAKING.
CALL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE MUSCLE PAIN
OR WEAKNESS,
FEEL UNUSUALLY TIRED,
HAVE LOSS OF APPETITE,
UPPER BELLY PAIN, DARK URINE
OR YELLOWING OF SKIN OR EYES.
THESE COULD BE SIGNS OF RARE
BUT SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS.
IS YOUR CHOLESTEROL AT GOAL?
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CRESTOR.
[ Female Announcer ] IF YOU
CAN'T AFFORD YOUR MEDICATION,
ASTRAZENECA
MAY BE ABLE TO HELP.
DO YOU REALLY THINK BRUSHING
IS ENOUGH TO KEEP IT CLEAN?
WHILE BRUSHING MISSES GERMS
IN 75% OF YOUR MOUTH,
LISTERINE® CLEANS
VIRTUALLY YOUR ENTIRE MOUTH.
SO TAKE YOUR ORAL HEALTH
TO A WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
LISTERINE®...
POWER TO YOUR MOUTH™.
[ slap! ]
[ slap! slap! slap! slap! ]
OW! OW!
[ Male Announcer ] YOUR
FAVORITE FOODS FIGHTING YOU?
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
CALCIUM-RICH TUMS
STARTS WORKING SO FAST
YOU'LL FORGET
YOU HAD HEARTBURN.
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUM TUMS
>>> AND YOU KNOW IT IS SO
DIFFICULT FOR LAW ENFORCEMENT TO
PROTECT AGAINST THESE EVENTS,
WHAT ARE CALLED SOFT TARGETS AND
ABC'S DAVID KERLEY TELLS US
MORE.
>> Reporter: THE BLOODY BOSTON
EXPLOSION SHATTERED THE MARATHON
AND REOPENED WOUNDS IN THIS
COUNTRY.
THIS ATTACK, FAR FROM THE FIRST,
TARGETING INNOCENT CIVILIANS.
INTERNATIONAL TERRORISTS TRIED
TO BREAK DOWN THE WORLD TRADE
CENTER IN '93.
THE BUILDING WITHSTOOD THE
BLOOFT.
SIX WERE KILLED.
AND DOMESTIC FRUSTRATES PROVED
DEADLY AS WELL.
THE OKLAHOMA CITY BOMBING
KILLING 168.
SIMILAR TO TODAY'S BOSTON BLAST,
THE ATLANTA OLYMPICS BLAST IN
1996.
IT'S THE SOFT TARGET TERRORISTS
ARE LOOKING FOR.
>> UNFORTUNATELY THESE KINDS OF
SETTINGS, MARATHON, FOOTBALL,
BASEBALL, SOCIAL EVENT, CONCERT.
>> TOM RIDGE WAS OUR COUNTRY'S
FIRST SECRETARY OF HOMELAND
SECURITY.
>> YOU HAVE TO MANAGE THE RISKS
UNLESS YOU HAVE SPECIFIC
INFORMATION ABOUT A PARTICULAR
ACTOR, YOU CAN'T GUARANTEE
SAFETY ANYWHERE.
>> Reporter: SO EVEN THOUGH
POLICE WERE ON DUTY WITH PLENTY
OF NATIONAL GUARD SOLDIERS,
SOMEONE WAS ABLE TO PLACE TWO
BOMBS, GIVING SO MANY SECOND
THOUGHTS ABOUT BEING AROUND
LARGE CROWDS.
>> WHAT CAN WE DO AT A LARGE
CROWD EVENT?
WHAT CAN I DO TO KEEP MYSELF
SAFE?
>> IF YOU SEE SOMETHING, SAY
SOMETHING.
BE AWARE OF YOUR ENVIRONMENT.
>> SOUNDS LIKE THE BEST ADVICE
IS DON'T LET THEM AFFECT YOUR
LIFE, LIVE YOUR LIFE?
>> LIVE YOUR LIFE.
WHEN YOU COMPROMISE HOW YOU
LIVE, THAT GIVES THEM A VICTORY.
AS PAINFUL AS IT IS TODAY, YOU
CAN'T LET THEM SUCCEED, BUT US
CHANGING THE NORM, CHANGING HOW
WE LIVE.
>> DAVID KERLEY, ABC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>> AND A RIVETING PICTURE FROM
THIS DAY WHEN WE COME BACK.
I'M ON EXPERT ON SOFTBALL.
AND TEA PARTIES.
I'LL HAVE
MORE AWKWARD CONVERSATIONS
THAN I'M EQUIPPED FOR,
BECAUSE I'M RAISING TWO GIRLS
ON MY OWN.
I'LL WORRY ABOUT THE ECONOMY
MORE THAN A FEW TIMES
BEFORE THEY'RE GROWN.
BUT IT'S FOR THEM,
SO I'VE FOUND A WAY.
WHO MATTERS MOST TO YOU
SAYS THE MOST ABOUT YOU.
AT MassMutual WE'RE OWNED
BY OUR POLICYOWNERS,
AND THEY MATTER MOST TO US.
READY TO PLAN FOR YOUR FUTURE?
WE'LL HELP YOU GET THERE.
OF MILD TO MODERATE
ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE
IS EXELON PATCH.
NOW WITH
MORE TREATMENT OPTIONS,
EXELON PATCH MAY IMPROVE
OVERALL FUNCTION AND COGNITION.
YOUR LOVED ONE CAN GET
A FREE 30-DAY TRIAL.
AND YOU CAN HAVE
ACCESS TO NURSES.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE
HOW THE DISEASE PROGRESSES.
HOSPITALIZATION,
AND RARELY DEATH,
HAVE BEEN REPORTED FROM WEARING
MORE THAN ONE PATCH AT A TIME.
THE MOST COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
ARE NAUSEA, VOMITING, DIARRHEA,
FALL, LOSS OF APPETITE
OR WEIGHT,
APPLICATION SITE REDNESS,
AND URINARY TRACT INFECTION.
THE LIKELIHOOD AND SEVERITY
OF THESE SIDE EFFECTS
MAY INCREASE
AS THE DOSE INCREASES
OR IF PATIENTS
WEIGH LESS THAN 110 POUNDS.
PEOPLE AT RISK
FOR STOMACH ULCERS
WHO TAKE
CERTAIN OTHER MEDICINES
SHOULD TALK TO THEIR DOCTOR
AS SERIOUS STOMACH PROBLEMS
SUCH AS BLEEDING MAY WORSEN.
PATIENTS MAY EXPERIENCE
SLOW HEART RATE.
FREE TRIAL OFFER FOR THEM.
NURSES TO TALK TO FOR YOU.
VISIT EXELONPATCHOFFER.COM.
♪
AND "MULTIPLE CHOICE,"
COME TO WALGREENS
FOR HELP FINDING THE ONE
THAT'S RIGHT FOR YOU...
LIKE CENTRUM.
NOW, GET FOUR DOLLARS OFF
SELECT CENTRUM PRODUCTS
WITH BALANCE REWARDS CARD.
AT THE CORNER
OF HAPPY AND HEALTHY.
FOR OVER 30 YEARS.
AND IT'S NOW
THE MOST DOCTOR RECOMMENDED,
THE MOST PREFERRED
AND THE MOST STUDIED.
SO WHEN IT COMES TO GETTING THE
MOST OUT OF YOUR MULTIVITAMIN,
THE CHOICE IS CLEAR.
CENTRUM.
To swe're bringing their son
cahome from collegellenges,
Along with a few friends...
JIMBO AND CAROL
Whether it's the new Kenmore
Elite Refrigerator...
Or the new Kenmore Elite Front
load washer and dryer...
no one gives you
more capacity...
So you'll be prepared for
any challenge
Bye guys!
Kenmore. Tested for Living.
Found at Sears.
If you're suffering from
constipation,
Miralax or Metamucil may take
days to work.
For faster relief, try Dulcolax
laxative tablets.
Dulcolax provides gentle relief
overnight unlike Miralax
and Metamucil that can take up
to 3 days.
For predictable relief try
Dulcolax.
24/7.
AND A SPECIAL "GOOD MORNING
AMERICA" TOMORROW ON ABC.
>>> POLICE IN ACTION, STANDING
OVER A FALLEN MARATHON RUNNER.
AND WE THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
SOME OF YOU WILL BE LEAVING US,
BUT WE HOPE THE OTHERS WILL STAY
WITH US FOR THE SECOND HALF HOUR
OF THE SPECIAL EDITION OF "WORLD
NEWS."
WE'LL TAKE A SHORT BREAK AND SEE
YOU IN JUST A FEW MINUTES.
YS OFG
TO GIVE A BREAST CANCER SURVIVOR
A LIFETIME--
THAT'S DEFINITELY A FAIR TRADE.
WHOO!
YOU WALK WITH FRIENDS,
YOU MEET NEW FRIENDS,
AND YOU KEEP THOSE FRIENDSHIPS.
IT WAS SUCH
A BEAUTIFUL EXPERIENCE.
(woman) ♪ AND IT'S BEAUTIFUL
♪ UNDENIABLE
(woman) WHY WALK 60 MILES
IN THE BOLDEST BREAST CANCER
EVENT IN HISTORY?
BECAUSE EVERYONE DESERVES
A LIFETIME.
VISIT The3Day.org TO REGISTER
OR TO REQUEST MORE INFORMATION
TODAY.
♪ BURNING LIKE A FIRE
♪ BUILDING UP FROM DEEP INSIDE
IT WAS 3 DAYS OF PURE JOY.
SUSAN G. KOMEN'S INVESTMENTS IN
EARLY DETECTION AND TREATMENT
HAVE HELPED REDUCE
BREAST CANCER MORTALITY
IN THE U.S. BY 33% SINCE 1990.
HELP US CONTINUE SERVING
THE MILLIONS OF WOMEN AND MEN
WITH BREAST CANCER
WHO STILL NEED US EVERY DAY.
REGISTER FOR THE 3-DAY NOW.
(woman) IT'S JUST BEEN
AN AMAZING, AMAZING JOURNEY.
I LOVE THESE PEOPLE.
♪ AND IT'S BEAUTIFUL
>> FROM ABC NEWS, THIS IS IS A
SPECIAL EDITION OF "WORLD NEWS"
WITH DIANE SAWYER.
TERROR AT THE BOSTON MARATHON.
>> GOOD EVENING, THE DETAILS OUT
OF BOSTON ARE STILL POURING IN
AT THIS HOUSE.
PROUD DAY FOR THIS CITY
SHATTERED BY VIOLENCE.
FIRST ONE BOMB AND THEN ANOTHER.
LET'S JUST WATCH AND LISTEN.
>> PEOPLE AROUND THE COUNTRY,
STILL TRYING TO GRASP WHAT
HAPPENED TODAY IN BOSTON.
AND OUR OWN ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS
IS ON THE GROUND THERE WITH THE
LATEST.
>> GOOD EVENING.
WE ARE JUST A FEW SHORT BLOCKS
AWAY FROM THE FINISH LINE.
THIS HAS BECOME A STAGING AREA
FOR AMBULANCES.
YOU CAN SEE DOZENS OF AMBULANCES
LINED UP AND DOWN THIS ROAD,
READY TO BE CALLED IN TO ASSIST
WITH ANY ADDITIONAL INJURIES.
WE'RE HEARING THAT NUMBER RIGHT
NOW, AT LEAST 99 PEOPLE INJURED,
TWO PEOPLE DIED AT THE SCENE.
MULTIPLE AMPUTATIONS.
THERE'S JUST BEEN A MASSIVE
RESPONSE HERE TODAY WITH THE
POLICE AND EMS, AS THEY RUSHED
IN TO HELP BOTH RUNNERS AND
SPECTATORS AMONG THE INJURED.
THE TENTS ORIGINALLY SET UP TO
HELP WITH THE MARATHONERS AS
THEY RAN THE 26.2 MILES TODAY,
THAT INSTANTLY BECAME A TENT
THAT HELPED WITH PEOPLE WHO WERE
CASUALTIES.
THE PLACE THAT THEY WERE ABLE TO
HELP THOSE PEOPLE.
>> ARE YOU THERE?
>> I'M NOT SURE IF YOU'RE STILL
WITH ME.
YES, I AM STILL HERE.
AS YOU CAN SEE, EVEN HOURS
LATER, AMBULANCES REMAIN HERE
STANDING AT THE READY.
>> ALL RIGHT, I KNOW WE'RE
HAVING A LITTLE TECHNICAL
TROUBLE AND IT'S VERY NOISY
THERE.
IN THE AFTERMATH OF THIS, OF
COURSE, AROUND THE COUNTRY,
AMERICAN CITIES WERE PUT ON A
KIND OF ALERT.
LET'S GO TO ABC'S ALEX PEREZ IN
CHICAGO.
ALEX?
>> I CAN TELL YOU WE HAVE SEEN A
STEPPED UP POLICE