>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, UNDER WATER.
THE BRIDGE THAT SUDDENLY
COLLAPSED.
THE DRIVERS PLUNGING INTO THE
RIVER WITH IT.
>> WE HAVE VEHICLES IN THE
WATER.
>> TONIGHT, HEAR FROM ONE OF
THOSE DRIVERS LAUNCHED INTO
MIDAIR.
AND THIS EVENING, THE LIST HERE.
THE MOST WORRISOME BRIDGES IN
AMERICA.
ARE YOU DRIVING OVER ONE?
>>> EMERGENCY LANDING.
THE JET FORCED TO TURN AROUND IN
MIDAIR, THE FIRE, THE SMOKE
SHOOTING FROM THE ENGINE.
NEW PICTURES COMING IN TONIGHT.
HEAR FROM PASSENGERS WHO WATCHED
IT ALL THROUGH THEIR WINDOWS.
>>> WASHOUT.
THE EXTREME WEATHER ON THE WAY
THIS MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND.
THE MASSIVE FLOODS TONIGHT.
AND WHERE THE BLINDING RAIN IS
HEADED NEXT.
AND SNOW IN SOME SPOTS?
GINGER IS RIGHT HERE TONIGHT.
>>> AND THE BRAVERY IN OKLAHOMA
THIS WEEK.
WE HEARD THAT TEACHER TRYING TO
CALM HER STUDENTS THE MOMENT
THAT TORNADO HIT.
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER!
IT'S ALMOST OVER!
>> I HATE THIS!
>> TONIGHT, WHAT WE DIDN'T KNOW.
OUR TRIP THROUGH THE SCHOOLS.
WHAT WE DISCOVERED LEFT
UNTOUCHED ON THIS DESK.
IT GAVE US CHILLS.
OUR "PERSONS OF THE WEEK."
>>> GOOD EVENING ON THIS FRIDAY
NIGHT.
DIANE HAS THE EVENING OFF.
AND WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH THAT
TERRIFYING BRIDGE COLLAPSE, JUST
AS MILLIONS OF FAMILIES TRAVEL
AMERICA'S BRIDGES THIS HOLIDAY
WEEKEND.
TONIGHT, THE IMAGES OF CHAOS IN
THE MOMENTS AFTER THAT BRIDGE
CRUMBLED.
TWISTED STEEL, CARS TURNING INTO
LIFE RAFTS.
A HUMAN CHAIN BACK TO DRY
GROUND.
FAMILIES TRAVELING FOR THE
WEEKEND SUDDENLY PLUNGING INTO
THE WATER BELOW.
TONIGHT, AUTHORITIES BELIEVE
THEY KNOW THE CAUSE, AMID NEW
QUESTIONS ABOUT HOW THIS COULD
HAPPEN.
THAT BRIDGE, INSPECTED TWICE
LAST YEAR, MOST RECENTLY JUST A
FEW MONTHS AGO.
AND LOOK AT THIS TONIGHT.
1 OUT OF EVERY 9 BRIDGES IN THIS
COUNTRY, STRUCTURALLY DEFICIENT.
AND 200 MILLION AMERICANS
DRIVING ACROSS THOSE BRIDGES
EVERY DAY.
TONIGHT, A LIST OF THE MOST
TROUBLING BRIDGES IN THIS
COUNTRY.
BUT FIRST, THE PICTURES AND THE
INVESTIGATION, AND HERE TONIGHT,
ABC'S NEAL KARLINSKY IN MT.
VERNON, WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE FIRST
VIDEO OF THE BRIDGE COLLAPSE AS
IT HAPPENED.
LOOK CLOSELY IN THIS
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO FROM A NEARBY
BUSINESS.
THE MOMENT TWO CARS WERE SENT
PLUMMETING INTO THE ICY WATERS
OF WASHINGTON'S SKAGIT RIVER.
>> I JUST WATCHED THIS EXPLOSION
IN FRONT OF MY EYES AND ALL OF A
SUDDEN, THERE'S NO ROAD TO DRIVE
ON ANYMORE.
>> Reporter: 20-YEAR-OLD BRYCE
KENNING, SEEN HERE SITTING ON
TOP OF HIS SINKING CAR LAST
NIGHT, SPENT TODAY DRYING OUT
HIS WET CLOTHES AFTER WALKING
AWAY FROM WHAT SEEMED CERTAIN
DEATH.
HE WAS HEADED NORTHBOUND GOING
60 MILES PER HOUR WHEN HE SAYS
THE BRIDGE VANISHED IN A PLUME
OF DUST.
>> I LAUNCHED OFF THAT THING.
>> Reporter: YOU LAUNCHED?
>> OH YEAH.
YEAH.
AND STRAIGHT NOSEDIVE INTO THE
WATER.
>> Reporter: AFTER SURVIVING THE
IMPACT, HE WAS AFRAID HE WOULD
DROWN.
>> CAR IMMEDIATELY STARTS
FILLING WITH WATER, AND THAT WAS
THE POINT WHERE, YOU KNOW, I
KIND OF THOUGHT I MIGHT BE A
GONER, YOU KNOW, THAT MIGHT BE
IT FOR ME.
>> Reporter: DAN SLIGH AND HIS
WIFE HAD BEEN HEADED SOUTHBOUND
AT THE SAME TIME.
HE DISLOCATED HIS SHOULDER ON
IMPACT.
>> I COULDN'T SEAT MY WIFE IN
THE PASSENGER SEAT.
I ASKED HER IF SHE WAS OKAY.
SHE WASN'T RESPONDING.
POPPED MY SHOULDER BACK IN SO I
COULD UNBUCKLE EVERYTHING AND
GET OVER TO HER.
>> Reporter: THIS ISN'T THE
FIRST BRIDGE TO FAIL WITH
TERRIFYING RESULTS.
THE 2007 COLLAPSE OF THE
MINNEAPOLIS I-35 BRIDGE KILLED
13 PEOPLE.
AND IN 2009, CRACKS AND
CORROSION ON A BOSTON BRIDGE
SENT ROCKS RAINING DOWN ON A
WOMAN'S WINDSHIELD.
INVESTIGATORS HERE SAY A
SEMI-TRUCK CARRYING AN OVERSIZED
LOAD GASHED THROUGH A STEEL BEAM
AND LIKELY TRIGGERED THIS
COLLAPSE.
BUT THE BRIDGE IS OLD, TOO,
BUILT IN 1955 WITH A PILE OF
MEDIOCRE INFRASTRUCTURE RANKINGS
AND RECENT REPAIRS.
ONE THING INVESTIGATORS BEEN
LOOKING AT ALL DAY IS THAT CLEAN
BREAK OVER THERE.
IT'S ALMOST AS IF THAT CHUNK OF
BRIDGE JUST SNAPPED RIGHT OFF.
THE INVESTIGATION, THOUGH, WILL
TAKE MONTHS TO COMPETE AND IN
THE MEANTIME, GOING INTO THIS
HOLIDAY WEEKEND, TRAFFIC IS
ALREADY BEGINNING TO BACK UP.
DAVID?
>> NEAL KARLINSKY ON THIS STORY
SINCE "GOOD MORNING AMERICA."
NEAL, THANK YOU.
AND THAT BRIDGE, NORTH OF
SEATTLE, HAD SO MANY WONDERING
ABOUT THE BRIDGES IN THEIR OWN
HOMETOWNS.
AND HERE ARE FOUR ICONIC
AMERICAN BRIDGES DEEMED
STRUCTURALLY DEFICIENT BY TOP
ENGINEERS.
CHICAGO'S NORTH LaSALLE STREET
BRIDGE.
PORTLAND, OREGON'S, STEEL
ALSO TONIGHT, BOSTON'S
LONGFELLOW BRIDGE AND THE
BROOKLYN BRIDGE, RIGHT HERE IN
NEW YORK CITY.
AND TONIGHT, FOR THE FULL LIST
OF BRIDGES ENGINEERS ARE MOST
CONCERNED ABOUT, YOU CAN GO TO
ABCNEWS.COM AND CLICK ON "WORLD
NEWS."
>>> BUT WE DO MOVE ON TONIGHT,
FROM THAT SCARE FOR DRIVERS TO A
SCARE IN THE AIR.
THIS IS WHAT PASSENGERS ON BOARD
A BRITISH AIRWAYS FLIGHT SAW OUT
THEIR WINDOW.
SHORTLY AFTER TAKEOFF.
SMOKE POURING FROM THE ENGINE.
THEIR QUICK-THINKING PILOTS
FORCED TO MAKE AN EMERGENCY
LANDING.
TONIGHT, ABC'S NICK SCHIFRIN,
WITH THE PASSENGERS WHO
WITNESSED IT ALL RIGHT THROUGH
THEIR WINDOWS.
>> Reporter: RIGHT AFTER
TAKEOFF, A HARROWING SIGHT.
FLIGHT 762'S ENGINE WAS ON FIRE.
IT HAD SUFFERED A MAJOR
TECHNICAL FAULT OR WAS STRUCK BY
BIRDS.
INSIDE THE CABIN, JON CHAPLIN
LOOKED OUT HIS WINDOW.
THE LEFT ENGINE FLAP HAD BLOWN
OFF.
>> LOUD BOOM AND THEN THERE WAS
ORANGE COLORS FILLING THE CABIN.
SO THAT WAS QUITE SCARY.
>> Reporter: THE RIGHT ENGINE,
CONSUMED BY FLAME, NOW USELESS.
DID YOUR HEART SKIP A FEW BEATS?
>> YEAH.
IT'S -- IT'S -- YOU GET A BIT
PHILOSOPHICAL ABOUT IT AND
WONDER IF THIS IS YOUR MOMENT.
>> Reporter: THE PILOT FLEW LOW,
BACK TOWARD THE AIRPORT.
WHEN HE LANDED SAFELY --
[ APPLAUSE ]
BUT THEN JON HAD TO EVACUATE.
HE SLID OUT AN EMERGENCY EXIT,
HIS HANDS TREMBLING SO MUCH, HE
COULD BARELY HOLD HIS CAMERA
STEADY.
>> THERE WERE PEOPLE THROWING UP
AS WE GOT OFF THE PLANE, ON THE
GRASS AND THEY WERE CRYING AND
HYSTERICS.
>> Reporter: HE CAN'T FORGET THE
MOMENT WHEN HE TRIED TO CALL HIS
WIFE.
>> I WAS THINKING BACK TO THE
PHONE CALLS FROM 9/11, ACTUALLY,
AND HOW MOVING SOME OF THOSE
MESSAGES WERE.
AND I WONDERED IF I WOULD BE THE
ONE LEAVING A MESSAGE.
>> Reporter: JON TOLD ME HE'LL
TOAST THE PILOT, BECAUSE IT
COULD HAVE BEEN SO MUCH WORSE.
NICK SCHIFRIN, ABC NEWS, AT
HEATHROW AIRPORT.
>> NICK, THANK YOU.
AND THAT WASN'T THE ONLY WHITE
KNUCKLE MOMENT IN THE AIR TO
REPORT TONIGHT.
FIGHTER JETS SCRAMBLED, SENT TO
INTERCEPT A PASSENGER JET WITH
MORE THAN 300 PEOPLE ON BOARD EN
ROUTE FROM PAKISTAN TO LONDON,
AFTER REPORTS THAT TWO MEN ON
BOARD THREATENED TO DESTROY THE
PLANE.
THE JET WAS DIVERTED.
THOSE TWO MEN, UNDER ARREST
TONIGHT.
>>> AND FROM LONDON THIS
EVENING, WE ARE GETTING NEW
CLUES AND NEW IMAGES AFTER THAT
ATTACK, THE YOUNG VETERAN AND
FATHER KILLED IN BROAD DAYLIGHT.
TONIGHT, NEW VIDEO SHOWS THE
FINAL MOMENTS AND WE'VE BEEN
CAREFUL WITH WHAT WE'RE GOING TO
SHOW HERE.
ABC'S LAMA HASAN FROM LONDON
AGAIN THIS EVENING.
>> Reporter: IN NEW VIDEO OF THE
ATTACK, FILMED BY AN EYEWITNESS,
WE SEE THE DRAMATIC FINAL
MOMENTS OF THE SHOOTOUT.
AS THE ATTACKERS, CHARGING THE
POLICE OFFICERS, COMING WITHIN
JUST TWO FEET OF THEM.
POLICE ENDING THE TERRIFYING
ATTACK IN JUST 13 SECONDS.
AFTER THE TWO KILLERS BRUTALLY
MURDERED BRITISH SOLDIER LEE
RIGBY, HIS BODY LYING IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE STREET, TOO
GRUESOME TO SHOW.
TODAY, HIS FAMILY PAID A PAINFUL
FAREWELL TO THE MAN THEY
DESCRIBE AS THEIR LOVING SON,
FATHER AND HUSBAND.
READING OUT HIS LAST TEXT
MESSAGE TO HIS MOTHER.
>> BECAUSE YOU ARE THE MOST
FANTASTIC, ONE IN A MILLION MOM
THAT ANYONE COULD EVER WISH FOR.
THANK YOU FOR SUPPORTING ME ALL
THESE YEARS.
YOU ARE NOT JUST MY MOM, YOU ARE
MY BEST FRIEND.
>> Reporter: AS FOR THE
INVESTIGATION, POLICE SEARCHED
AT LEAST FOUR HOMES IN LONDON
TODAY, BUT SECURITY SERVICES
HERE ARE COMING UNDER FIRE, FOR
LETTING THE TWO ATTACKERS WHO
WERE KNOWN TO THEM TO DROP OFF
THE RADAR.
DAVID?
>> WHAT A HORRIFIC SCENE.
LAMA HASAN, THANK YOU.
>>> BACK IN THIS COUNTRY
TONIGHT, AND SOME FORCEFUL WORDS
FROM PRESIDENT OBAMA, DELIVERED
AS PART OF A COMMENCEMENT
ADDRESS TODAY.
THE PRESIDENT, AT AN ICONIC
AMERICAN INSTITUTION, THE NAVAL
ACADEMY, OFFERING AN INSPIRING
MESSAGE FOR THE GRADUATES, ALONG
WITH A CALL TO ACTION TO THE
AMERICAN ARMED FORCES IN THE
WAKE OF A STRING OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT ALLEGATIONS.
SO TONIGHT, I WANT TO BRING IN
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT JONATHAN KARL.
JON, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
WELL, THE PRESIDENT HAS TAKEN AN
INTENSE, PERSONAL INTEREST IN
THIS ISSUE, CALLING IT SHAMEFUL
AND DISGRACEFUL, EVEN A THREAT
TO NATIONAL SECURITY.
AND THAT WAS THE MESSAGE HE TOOK
TODAY, DIRECTLY TO THOSE
GRADUATES OF THE NAVAL ACADEMY.
>> THOSE WHO COMMIT SEXUAL
ASSAULT ARE NOT ONLY COMMITTING
A CRIME, THEY THREATEN THE TRUST
AND DISCIPLINE THAT MAKES OUR
MILITARY STRONG.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO BE
DETERMINED TO STOP THESE CRIMES.
>> JON, WHAT IS HE TRYING TO
ACCOMPLISH HERE BY INSERTING
THAT INTO THE ADDRESS HE GAVE
TODAY?
>> Reporter: WELL, WHAT HE'S
TRYING TO ACCOMPLISH HERE IS TO
SAY, THIS IS A TOP PRIORITY TO
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
AS HE SAID LAST WEEK, WHEN HE
HAD THE MILITARY LEADERS HERE TO
THE WHITE HOUSE TO TALK ABOUT
IT, TO THE VICTIMS OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT IN THE MILITARY, THE
COMMANDER IN CHIEF HAS YOUR
BACK.
>> JON KARL AT HIS POST AT THE
WHITE HOUSE.
JON, OUR THANKS TO YOU AGAIN, AS
ALWAYS.
>>> RIGHT NOW, WITH MEMORIAL DAY
UPON US, MILLIONS OF FAMILIES
TRAVELING, BUT IN SOME PARTS, IT
IS GOING TO BE TOUGH GOING THIS
WEEKEND.
LOOK AT THIS TONIGHT.
FLOODING ACROSS THE NORTHEAST.
NEIGHBORS ACTUALLY KAYAKING DOWN
THE STREET, ALONG WITH THOSE
CARS.
THAT IS UNREAL.
ABC METEOROLOGIST GINGER ZEE IS
HERE TO TELL US WHAT WE'RE IN
FOR.
EVERYTHING FROM RAIN TO POSSIBLE
SNOW, YOU TOLD ME, JUST MOMENTS
AGO.
>> Reporter: NO.
IS IT MEMORIAL DAY?
I MEAN, LET'S JUST CHECK IN ON
THAT.
A FEW FLURRIES, YES, IN UPSTATE
NEW YORK AND PARTS OF NEW
ENGLAND.
BUT REALLY, THE RAIN IS THE
DANGEROUS PART.
THAT'S WHY I WANT TO GET TO HOW
MUCH RAIN IS STILL GOING TO
FALL.
PARTS OF VERMONT HAVE SEEN A
MONTH'S WORTH IN JUST A WEEK.
RECORD RAIN YESTERDAY, AND
THEY HAVE ANOTHER TWO INCHES
POSSIBLE THROUGH SUNDAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, GINGER ZEE WITH
US.
AND ANOTHER WARNING SPOT TO
WATCH?
>> RIGHT, FLASH FLOOD WARNINGS
ALL DAY HERE, AUSTIN, YOU CAN
SEE PICTURES HERE, FROM AUSTIN,
BIG THUNDERSTORMS COMING DOWN.
DOWN TO SAN ANTONIO, CLOSING
NUMEROUS ROADS IN BOTH THOSE BIG
STILLS AS SO MANY FOLKS GET ON
CITIES AS SO MANY FOLKS GET ON
THE ROADS.
THAT'S GOING TO BE A BIG MESS.
BUT I'VE GOT GREAT NEWS FOR THE
MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND, ON THE DAY
ITSELF, ON MONDAY, LOOKING MUCH
DRYER AS THE STORMS MOVE OUT OF
THE NORTHEAST.
YOU CAN SEE IT THERE.
IF YOU WANT WARMTH, GO TO THE
SOUTHEAST OF THE SOUTHWEST,
BECAUSE THE CENTER OF THE
NATION, GOING TO STAY STORMY.
>> THE CENTER ONCE AGAIN.
GINGER ZEE WITH THE ENTIRE
WEATHER PICTURE.
GINGER, THANK YOU.
>>> AND WE MOVE ON TONIGHT TO A
CONSUMER ALERT EFFECTING MANY
THIS HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
FOR ANY FAMILY HEADED OUT TO AN
AMUSEMENT PARK, A NEW REPORT
OUT, STUDYING INJURIES IN THE
PAST TWO DECADES AND LOOK AT
THIS NUMBER.
MORE THAN 90,000 CHILDREN
INJURED ON AMUSEMENT PARK
RIDES, ENDING UP IN THE E.R.
BUT THE MOST DANGEROUS RIDES
AREN'T THE TWISTY, GRAVITY
DEFYING ROLLER COASTERS.
IN FACT, TONIGHT, ABC'S AMY
ROBACH ON THE REAL DANGER.
>> Reporter: FROM FRIGHTENING
NEWS REPORTS --
>> SHE'S THROWN SIX TO EIGHT
FEET.
>> THE TRAIN DERAILED, AND
THERE'S LITTLE BOYS AND LITTLE
GIRLS AND THEY NEED HELP NOW!
>> Reporter: TO PERSONAL YOUTUBE
VIDEOS.
>> THE BOAT BEHIND US IS FALLING
OFF.
>> Reporter: THERE IS NO
SHORTAGE OF AMUSEMENT RIDE
SCARES.
BUT A NEW STUDY HAS FOUND THAT
IT'S NOT ALWAYS THE BIGGEST AND
FASTEST RIDES WE SHOULD FEAR.
IT THE SMALLER ONES, THAT
PARENTS MIGHT NOT CONSIDER
DANGEROUS.
THAT CONTRIBUTE TO INJURIES OF
MORE THAN 4,000 U.S. CHILDREN
EACH YEAR.
DESTINY MALONE WAS JUST 8 WHEN
SHE BROKE HER ARM BY REACHING
OUT ON A RIDE LIKE THIS
SEEMINGLY INNOCUOUS KIDDIE
ROLLER COASTER.
>> I WAS JUST TORN TO PIECES.
>> Reporter: THE NEW STUDY HAS
TRACKED INJURIES ON ALL KINDS OF
RIDES.
4,400 A YEAR.
UP TO 20 A DAY.
BUT WHAT'S SURPRISING IS WHEN
RESEARCHERS LOOKED AT EMERGENCY
RECORDS FOR THE TYPE OF RIDE WAS
RECORDED.
ROLLER COASTERS ACCOUNTED FOR
10%.
BUMPER CARS, 4%.
BUT CAROUSELS?
21%, WHICH MIGHT EXPLAIN WHY A
THIRD OF KIDS INJURED WERE 5 OR
YOUNGER.
THE MOST COMMON ACCIDENT?
FALLING.
>> PARENTS CAN CERTAINLY ENJOY A
BEAUTIFUL RIDE LIKE THIS, BUT
ENJOY THE RESTRAINT, PUT THAT ON
FIRST, NEVER WALK AWAY FROM A
YOUNG CHILD AND ACTUALLY HELP
THEM GO ON AND GO OFF THE RIDE.
>> Reporter: INDUSTRY ADVOCATES
TELL ABC NEWS THAT SAFETY IS
THEIR TOP PRIORITY, AND POINT
OUT THAT INJURIES AMONG THE
NEARLY 300 MILLION RIDERS ARE
RARE, AND LESS THAN 2% OF THE
INJURIES REQUIRED A TRIP TO THE
HOSPITAL.
THE BEST ADVICE?
HEED THE WARNINGS AND
INSTRUCTIONS ON THE RIDES, AND
IF YOUR CHILD CAN'T FOLLOW THE
RULES, GET ICE CREAM INSTEAD.
AMY ROBACH, ABC NEWS, NEW YORK.
>> AMY ROBACH, OUR THANKS TO YOU
THIS MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND.
>>> AND STILL AHEAD ON "WORLD
NEWS" THIS FRIDAY NIGHT, COME
FLY WITH ME, AS THE SONG GOES.
AND HE MEANS IT TONIGHT.
THE DARING FLIGHT LEO DiCAPRIO
IS ABOUT TO TAKE, AND HE WANTS
YOU AS HIS SEAT MATE.
HOW TO JOIN HIM, AND WHERE IS HE
GOING?
>>> AND LATER TONIGHT, YOU
REMEMBER THIS THIS WEEK.
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER!
IT'S ALMOST OVER!
>> THE TEACHER AND THE BRAVERY.
TONIGHT, WHAT WE DIDN'T SHOW
YOU.
WHAT WE FOUND STILL SITTING ON A
DESK IN A CLASSROOM.
IT GAVE US CHILLS.
A HEARTWARMING ENDING TO A VERY
DIFFICULT WEEK.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS IS KEVIN.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT Aleve
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HIM,
HE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HIM ALL DAY
AS HE GOES BACK
TO TAKING TYLENOL.
THAT WAS OKAY, BUT AFTER LUNCH
MY KNEE STARTED TO HURT AGAIN,
AND NOW I GOTTA TAKE MORE PILLS.
♪
YUP ANOTHER PILL STOP.
CAN I GET MY Aleve BACK YET?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY Aleve.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS MAY, BUY Aleve
AND HELP THOSE IN NEED.
AND THOSE PEOPLE ARE WHAT I LIKE
TO CALL...WRONG.
METAMUCIL HAS PSYLLIUM,
WHICH HELPS LOWER CHOLESTEROL,
PROMOTES DIGESTIVE HEALTH,
AND HELPS MAINTAIN
HEALTHY BLOOD SUGAR LEVELS.
METAMUCIL. 3 AMAZING BENEFITS,
1 SUPER FIBER.
I ON MY FEET AND EXACTLY, AND
ITWHERE I NEEDED MORE SUPPORT.TS
THEN, I GOT MY NUMBER.
MY TIRED, ACHY FEET
AFFECTED MY WHOLE LIFE.
UNTIL I FOUND MY NUMBER.
I TRIED THE FREE DR. SCHOLL'S
FOOT MAPPING CENTER.
IN TWO MINUTES, I GOT MY
FOOT MAP AND CUSTOM NUMBER.
I'M A 440.
THAT MATCHED UP TO THE
DR. SCHOLL'S CUSTOM FIT
ORTHOTIC INSERTS WITH THE RIGHT
SUPPORT AND CUSHIONING I NEED.
I AM A BELIEVER.
I'M A BELIEVER!
I'M A BELIEVER.
GO TO DRSCHOLLS.COM
FOR LOCATIONS
AND LEARN HOW TO SAVE $10.
SHE'S ALWAYS BEEN ABLE
IT'S JUST HER WAY.DAY.
BUT YOUR ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION -
THAT COULD BE A QUESTION
OF BLOOD FLOW.
CIALIS TADALAFIL
FOR DAILY USE
HELPS YOU BE READY
ANYTIME THE
MOMENT'S RIGHT.
YOU CAN BE
MORE CONFIDENT
IN YOUR ABILITY
TO BE READY.
AND THE SAME CIALIS IS THE
ONLY DAILY ED TABLET APPROVED
TO TREAT ED AND
SYMPTOMS OF BPH,
LIKE NEEDING TO GO
FREQUENTLY OR URGENTLY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS HEALTHY
ENOUGH FOR SEXUAL ACTIVITY.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU TAKE
NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL
IN EXCESS WITH CIALIS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, UPSET STOMACH,
DELAYED BACKACHE OR MUSCLE ACHE.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE ANY SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS IN HEARING OR VISION,
OR IF YOU HAVE ANY ALLERGIC
REACTIONS SUCH AS RASH,
HIVES, SWELLING OF THE LIPS,
TONGUE OR THROAT,
OR DIFFICULTY BREATHING
OR SWALLOWING,
STOP TAKING CIALIS AND GET
MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE
AND A 30-TABLET FREE TRIAL.
[ Female Announcer ]
STRESS SWEAT IS DIFFERENT
THAN ORDINARY SWEAT.
IT SMELLS WORSE.
GET 4X THE PROTECTION
AGAINST STRESS SWEAT.
INTRODUCING NEW SECRET CLINICAL
STRENGTH STRESS RESPONSE SCENT.
>>> NOW TO THAT HEADLINE.
LEO DiCAPRIO AND THAT FAMOUS
COME FLY WITH ME IN "CATCH ME IF
YOU CAN."
TONIGHT, HE IS SERIOUS.
HE WANTS YOU ON THAT FLIGHT, AND
IT'S A DARING ONE.
HERE'S ABC'S DAVID WRIGHT.
>> Reporter: AT A CANNES FILM
FESTIVAL FUND-RAISER, EVERY BIT
AS FABULOUS AS ONE OF THE GREAT
GATSBY'S PARTIES --
>> YOU WERE THERE ALL ALONG.
>> Reporter: A PITCH THAT
SOUNDED A BIT LIKE A SCI-FI
SEQUEL TO "CATCH ME IF YOU CAN."
♪ LET'S FLY
♪ LET'S FLY AWAY
>> WELL, HOW WOULD YOU LIKE TO
GO TO SPACE WITH LEONARDO
DiCAPRIO?
>> Reporter: A TICKET FOR THE
MAIDEN VOYAGE OF VIRGIN
GALACTIC, SITTING RIGHT NEXT TO
LEONARDO DiCAPRIO.
HIS FIRST ROLE IN A SPACE SUIT.
NOT AS AN ACTOR, BUT A
PASSENGER.
>> TO GO WITH LEONARDO DiCAPRIO
FOR THREE DAYS TRAINING AND INTO
OUTER SPACE.
>> Reporter: THE FLIGHT SET TO
TAKE OFF FROM THE NEW MEXICO
DESERT THIS FALL, DETACH FROM
THE MOTHER SHIP AND LAUNCH ALL
THE WAY INTO SUB-ORBITAL SPACE.
A COMMERCIAL SUCCESSOR TO THE
SPACE SHUTTLE.
>> AND LIFTOFF.
>> Reporter: NASA USED TO SAY
THAT THE SPACE SHUTTLE
ASTRONAUTS HAD A 1 IN 100 CHANCE
OF DYING.
1 IN 100.
THE QUESTION IS, HOW DOES THIS
NEW VESSEL FOR SPACE TOURISTS
COMPARE?
>> A MILLION TWO GOING TWICE --
WE'RE SELLING.
>> Reporter: $1.5 MILLION.
THE LUCKY WINNER, A RUSSIAN
BILLIONAIRE WHO WILL SOON BE
GETTING A CLOSE-UP LOOK AT THE
STARS, IN MORE WAYS THAN ONE.
DAVID WRIGHT, ABC NEWS, LOS
ANGELES.
>>> AND WHEN WE COME BACK ON THE
BROADCAST TONIGHT, THE LITTLE
GIRL TAKING ON A GIANT --
McDONALD'S.
IN A MOMENT HERE, YOU'LL HEAR
HER CHALLENGING THE CEO, RIGHT
TO HIS FACE.
AND SHE'S MAD ABOUT MORE THAN
JUST THE BIG MAC.
YOU'VE GOT TO HEAR THIS, AFTER
THE BREAK.
of store management started as
ere over seve percent
hourly associates. There's
opportunity here. I can use
Walmart's education benefits to
get a degree, Maybe work in IT,
Or be an engineer, helping
Walmart conserve energy. Even
today, when our store does well,
I earn quarterly bonuses. When
people look at me, I hope they
see someone working their way
up. VO: Opportunity, that's the
real Walmart.
ACCOMPLISHING EVEN LITTLE THINGS
CAN BECOME MAJOR VICTORIES.
I'M PHIL MICKELSON, PRO GOLFER.
WHEN I WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH PSORIATIC ARTHRITIS,
MY RHEUMATOLOGIST
PRESCRIBED ENBREL
FOR MY PAIN AND STIFFNESS,
AND TO HELP STOP JOINT DAMAGE.
[ Male Announcer ]
ENBREL MAY LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL EVENTS
INCLUDING INFECTIONS,
TUBERCULOSIS,
LYMPHOMA, OTHER CANCERS,
NERVOUS SYSTEM
AND BLOOD DISORDERS,
AND ALLERGIC REACTIONS
HAVE OCCURRED.
BEFORE STARTING ENBREL,
YOUR DOCTOR SHOULD TEST YOU
FOR TUBERCULOSIS
AND DISCUSS WHETHER
YOU'VE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL INFECTIONS
ARE COMMON.
YOU SHOULD NOT START ENBREL
IF YOU HAVE AN INFECTION
LIKE THE FLU.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU'RE PRONE TO INFECTIONS,
HAVE CUTS OR SORES,
HAVE HAD HEPATITIS B,
HAVE BEEN TREATED
FOR HEART FAILURE,
OR IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS PERSISTENT FEVER,
BRUISING, BLEEDING,
OR PALENESS.
SINCE ENBREL HELPED RELIEVE
MY JOINT PAIN,
IT'S THE LITTLE THINGS
THAT MEAN THE MOST.
ASK YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST
IF ENBREL IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
[ Doctor ] ENBREL,
THE NUMBER ONE BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
PRESCRIBED BY RHEUMATOLOGISTS.
[ Doctor ] ENBREL,
THE NUMBER ONE BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
AS SOON AS YOU FEEL IT,
WEIGH YOU DOWN?
TRY MIRALAX.
IT WORKS
DIFFERENTLY
THAN OTHER
LAXATIVES.
IT DRAWS WATER INTO YOUR COLON
TO UNBLOCK YOUR
SYSTEM NATURALLY.
DON'T WAIT TO FEEL GREAT.
MIRALAX.
TAKE THE MIRALAX PLEDGE
TO FEEL BETTER SOONER.
GET A REWARD
LIKE A BEAUTY TREATMENT,
A DANCE CLASS
OR A $5 GIFT CARD
WITH PURCHASE OF
A SPECIALLY MARKED PACK.
GO TO MIRALAX.COM FOR DETAILS.
>>> NOW TO OUR "INSTANT INDEX"
HERE ON A FRIDAY NIGHT AND IT
STARTS WITH A DAVID AND GOLIATH
BATTLE OVER THE FAST FOOD SO
MANY LOVE.
MEET HANNAH ROBERTSON, 9 YEARS
OLD, IN THE FOURTH GRADE AND
APPARENTLY FULL OF MOXY.
SHE TOOK ON McDONALD'S.
SHE AND HER MOM FLEW IN FOR
THE ANNUAL SHAREHOLDER MEETING.
SHE CALLED THE CHEESEBURGERS
AND FRIES JUNK FOOD.
AND THAT'S NOT ALL SHE SAID.
>> SOMETHING THAT I DON'T THINK
IS FAIR IS WHEN BIG COMPANIES
TRY TO TRICK KIDS INTO EATING
FOOD THAT ISN'T GOOD FOR THEM BY
USING TOYS AND CARTOON
CHARACT
CHARACTERS.
IT WOULD BE NICE IF
YOU STOPPED TRYING TO TRICK KIDS
INTO WANTING TO EAT YOUR FOOD
ALL THE TIME.
>> HANNAH'S MOM, BY THE WAY, A
NUTRITION BLOGGER.
THE CEO FIRING BACK, TELLING
HANNA, THEY DON'T SELL JUNK
FOOD, THEY ALSO SELL SALADS.
>>> WE KNOW HIM HERE IN NEW YORK
CITY AS SPIDER-MAN, AND A
SURPRISE APPEARANCE BY THE
SPIDEY, HERE IN NEW YORK,
WALKING RIGHT INTO THEIR
BASKETBALL GAME.
WATCH THIS.
THE MASKED MAN REBOUNDING,
DRIBBLING, DRIVES TO THE BASKET,
LAYS IT UP RIGHT THERE.
AND THAT, BY THE WAY, IS ANDREW
GARFIELD, THE ACTOR, WHO STARS
AS SPIDER-MAN.
HE APPARENTLY WALKED OFF THE SET
NEARBY TO GET INTO THE GAME.
NEVER BREAKING CHARACTER.
AND NEVER TOOK HIS MASK OFF.
>>> AND WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT, WE ARE
JUST BACK FROM OKLAHOMA TONIGHT,
FROM COVERING THAT TORNADO.
AND WHAT I FOUND WRITTEN ON A
PIECE OF PAPER RIGHT THERE IN
THAT CLASSROOM.
IT MADE US SMILE, AND WE NEEDED
TO, AFTER THIS WEEK.
WHILE A BODY IN MOTION
TENDS TO STAY IN MOTION.
STAYING ACTIVE CAN ACTUALLY
EASE ARTHRITIS SYMPTOMS.
BUT IF YOU HAVE ARTHRITIS,
STAYING ACTIVE
CAN BE DIFFICULT.
PRESCRIPTION CELEBREX
CAN HELP RELIEVE ARTHRITIS PAIN
SO YOUR BODY
CAN STAY IN MOTION.
BECAUSE JUST ONE
200MG CELEBREX A DAY
CAN PROVIDE 24 HOUR RELIEF
FOR MANY WITH ARTHRITIS PAIN
AND INFLAMMATION.
PLUS, IN CLINICAL STUDIES,
CELEBREX IS PROVEN TO IMPROVE
DAILY PHYSICAL FUNCTION
SO MOVING IS EASIER.
CELEBREX CAN BE TAKEN
WITH OR WITHOUT FOOD.
AND IT'S NOT A NARCOTIC.
YOU AND YOUR DOCTOR
SHOULD BALANCE THE BENEFITS
WITH THE RISKS.
ALL PRESCRIPTION NSAIDS,
LIKE CELEBREX, IBUPROFEN,
NAPROXEN AND MELOXICAM
HAVE THE SAME
CARDIOVASCULAR WARNING.
THEY ALL MAY INCREASE
THE CHANCE
OF HEART ATTACK OR STROKE,
WHICH CAN LEAD TO DEATH.
THIS CHANCE INCREASES
IF YOU HAVE HEART DISEASE
OR RISK FACTORS
SUCH AS HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
OR WHEN NSAIDS ARE TAKEN
FOR LONG PERIODS.
NSAIDS, LIKE CELEBREX,
INCREASE THE CHANCE OF SERIOUS
SKIN OR ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR STOMACH AND INTESTINE
PROBLEMS,
SUCH AS BLEEDING AND ULCERS,
WHICH CAN OCCUR WITHOUT WARNING
AND MAY CAUSE DEATH.
PATIENTS ALSO TAKING ASPIRIN
AND THE ELDERLY
ARE AT INCREASED RISK FOR
STOMACH BLEEDING AND ULCERS.
DON'T TAKE CELEBREX
IF YOU HAVE BLEEDING
IN THE STOMACH OR INTESTINE,
OR HAD AN ASTHMA ATTACK, HIVES,
OTHER ALLERGIES TO ASPIRIN,
NSAIDS OR SULFONAMIDES.
GET HELP RIGHT AWAY IF YOU HAVE
SWELLING OF THE FACE OR THROAT,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
YOUR MEDICAL HISTORY.
AND FIND AN ARTHRITIS TREATMENT
FOR YOU.
VISIT CELEBREX.COM AND ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CELEBREX.
FOR A BODY IN MOTION.
[ Female Announcer ]
FOR EVERYTHING YOUR FACE
HAS TO FACE.
FACE IT
WITH PUFFS ULTRA SOFT & STRONG.
PUFFS HAS SOFT,
AIR-FLUFFED PILLOWS
THAT ARE DERMATOLOGIST TESTED
TO BE GENTLE ON YOUR SKIN.
FACE EVERY DAY
WITH PUFFS SOFTNESS.
SO YOU CAN CAPTURE
YOUR RECEIPTS, INK FOR
ALL BUSINESS PURCHASES.
AND MANAGE THEM
ONLINE WITH JOT,
THE LATEST APP FROM INK.
SO YOU CAN SPEND LESS
TIME DOING PAPERWORK.
AND MORE TIME DOING PAPERWORK.
INK FROM CHASE.
SO YOU CAN.
If you think a prune is a prune,
you havThe AMAZING Prune.t,
Enjoy Plum Amazins,
Diced Prunes.
I'd put these on a salad.
These would be perfect
for cookies.
Delicious AND Nutritious.
Sunsweet, The Amazing Prune.
WITH THERMACARE HEATWRAPS.
THE ONLY WRAP WITH PATENTED
HEAT CELLS THAT PENETRATE DEEP
AND NOW, INTRODUCING
REUSABLE THERMACARE COLD WRAPS.
PAIN RELIEF
WITHOUT THE SHOCK OF ICE.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT HERE, WE ARE
JUST BACK FROM OKLAHOMA, AND IT
WASN'T DIFFICULT CHOOSING OUR
"PERSONS OF THE WEEK."
THE TEACHERS PROTECTING THEIR
STUDENTS, EVEN THOUGH SO MANY OF
THEM ARE PARENTS, TOO, WITH
THEIR OWN CHILDREN IN THOSE TWO
SCHOOLS.
THEIR SCREAMS WE WILL NEVER
FORGET.
THE CHILDREN BURYING THEIR HEADS
AT BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY, TRAPPED
UNDER THAT TORNADO HOVERING
OVERHEAD.
WE WILL ALSO NEVER FORGET THE
CALM INSTINCTS OF THEIR TEACHER.
SO MANY TEACHERS.
MRS. DIEDZIK, WHO TOLD THEM
THIS --
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER!
IT'S ALMOST OVER!
>> Reporter: BUT THERE WAS
SOMETHING ELSE ABOUT THESE BRAVE
TEACHERS.
SO MANY OF THEM ARE ALSO
PARENTS.
AND SO MANY OF THEM HAD CHILDREN
SOMEPLACE ELSE IN THOSE SCHOOLS.
MRS. DIEDZIK, WHO WAS HELPING
HER OWN STUDENTS --
>> YOU ARE SAFE AND YOU ARE
FINE.
>> Reporter: SHE DIDN'T KNOW
ABOUT HER OWN DAUGHTER IN THE
FOURTH GRADE OR HER SON IN THE
FIRST GRADE.
BOTH SURVIVED.
AND WE SAW THE
MOMENT LITTLE SAM FOUND HIS
MOTHER, LOOKING UP AT HER,
CONCRETE GRIT IN HIS HAIR.
WHEN SHE TOOK US BACK THIS WEEK,
SHE SHOWED US WHERE HE WAS, IN
THE BACK CORNER OF THAT ROOM.
AND LYING ON TOP OF HIM AND THE
OTHER CHILDREN, HIS TEACHER,
MRS. BITTLE.
>> MY SON AND ALL OF THE KIDS
HUDDLED DOWN WITH THEIR HANDS
CLASPED BEHIND THEIR HEADS.
SHERI IS A FRIEND AND A
COWORKER.
AND I KNOW THAT MY SON AND
DAUGHTER WERE BOTH IN THE HANDS
OF PEOPLE WHO LOVED THEM.
>> Reporter: AND THIS IS
MRS. BITTLE.
>> MY ENTIRE CLASS WAS SAFE AND
WELL.
AND GOT DELIVERED TO THEIR
PARENTS, AND -- THE TEACHERS AT
PLAZA TOWERS DIDN'T HAVE THAT
BLESSING.
AND -- AND I CAN'T EVEN IMAGINE.
>> Reporter: WE WERE GIVEN A
TOUR OF THAT OTHER SCHOOL, TOO,
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY, WHERE
THEY LOST SEVEN LITTLE FACES IN
ONE HALLWAY.
WHAT'S STILL A MYSTERY, A
MIRACLE, IS HOW SO MANY OTHERS
GOT OUT.
MOST EVERYTHING THERE IS GONE.
BUT WE NOTICED
MRS. MARINELLI'S FIRST GRADE
CLASSROOM IN TACT.
THE SCHOOLWORK RIGHT THERE ON
THE DESK WHERE IT WAS LEFT.
AND JUST BEFORE THAT TORNADO
HIT, THEY WERE WRITING WHAT THEY
LIKED MOST ABOUT THEIR TEACHER.
I WILL REMEMBER SHE GAVE ME
CUPCAKES.
THEY WERE REMEMBERING, BECAUSE
THIS WAS JUST A COUPLE OF DAYS
LEFT OF SCHOOL FOR THE YEAR.
WE ALSO LEARNED THAT WHEN THE
TORNADO HIT, SHE HAD HER
CHILDREN SINGING IN THE HALLWAY,
TRYING TO DISTRACT THEM.
AND IN THE CLASSROOM NEXT DOOR,
WE WERE SURPRISED TO MEET MISS
DOMINICK, ALREADY BACK PICKING
UP THE PIECES.
SHE TAUGHT THE AUTISTIC
CHILDREN.
SHE SAID MANY DIDN'T UNDERSTAND
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
BUT SHE HAD THE PRESENCE OF
MIND TO PULL OUT HER iPAD TO
HAVE THEM TEXT MESSAGE THEIR
PARENTS.
EVEN THOUGH SHE KNEW IT WOULDN'T
GO THROUGH.
BUT SHE KNEW IT WOULD CALM THEM.
WHAT DID THEY WANT TO SAY?
>> THEY JUST WANTED TO SAY MOM,
COME GET ME, OR, YOU KNOW, I
WANT TO GO HOME.
>> Reporter: AND FROM
MRS. BITTLE, WHAT GOT HER
THROUGH.
I CAN'T HELP BUT NOTICE YOUR
NECKLACE.
PRAY BIG.
>> YES.
YES.
>> Reporter: AND YOU DID, YOU
SAID.
>> I DID.
>> Reporter: I KNOW A LOT OF
THOSE PARENTS ARE GRATEFUL TO
YOU.
AND TO THEM YOU WOULD SAY?
>> YOUR CHILD IS MY CHILD.
ALL DAY LONG AND ALL YEAR LONG.
>> Reporter: AND SO WE CHOOSE
THE OKLAHOMA TEACHERS
AND EVERY TEACHER IN THIS
COUNTRY WHO JUMPS IN WHEN OUR
CHILDREN NEED THEM.
OUR CHILD IS MY CHILD, SHE SAID.
THAT IS "WORLD NEWS" FOR THIS
FRIDAY.
FOR DIANE AND ALL OF US, HAVE A
HAPPY HOLIDAY.
HAVE A GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NEW AT 6:00 LIMOUSINE
SAFETY F YOU WELL KAUL FROM
ONE OF THE AIRPORTS AT THE BAY
AREA CHANCES ARE THE LIMO IS
OPERATING ILLEGALLY.
>> A CRACK DOWN ON STREET
CRIME IN UPTOWN OAKLAND.
WHAT HAPPENED TO ONE MAN AFTER
CELEBRATING HIS BIRTHDAY.
>> TEAM COVERAGE ON THE BRIDGE
COLLAPSE IN WASHINGTON STATE.
FIND OUT ABOUT BAY AREA
BRIDGES NOW CONSIDERED
OBSOLETE.
>> TEAM NEW ZEALAND
HYDROFOILING ON THE BAY.
HOW THE BOAT HANDLES ON THE
FOIL COMING UP.
IS.
>>> GOOD EVENING, YOUR SAFETY
COULD BE IN JEOPARDY IF YOU
RELY ON CAR SERVICES.
>> ABC 7 NEWS LEARNED
LIMOUSINES WITHOUT PERMITS ARE
LISTED ON THE WEB SITE.
ABC 7 NEWS IS IN THE NEWSROOM
WITH THE STORY ONLY ON ABC 7
NEWS TONIGHT.
>> ON OAKLAND AIRPORT'S WEB
SITE, YOUL SEE A LINK TO
TAXIES, SHUTTLES AND LIMOS AND
PHONE NUMBERS SO YOU CAN BOOK
A RIDE TO AND FROM THE
AIRPORT.
AND THAT IS WHERE THESE LIMOS
ARE LISTED.
TRANSPORTATION REVIEWS.COM
ALERTED TO US THIS PROBLEM.
AND WE CONTACTED THE STATE
PUBLIC UTILITIES COMMISSION,
VERIFIED NUMBER, AND NAMES OF
THE COMPANY AUTOS WHAT IF I
WERE TO TELL YOU THAT 13% OF L
LIMOS HERE HAVE NO PERMITS?
>> MY GOODNESS.
THAT IS NOT RIGHT.
>> ROSE IS CORRECT.
IT'S NOT RIGHT WHAT. WE TOLD
HER IS TRUE.
13% OF THE SERVICES LISTED ON
THE OAKLAND AIRPORT WEB SITE
HAVE NO VALID PERMITS.
10 OF THE 80 COMPANIES HAVE
HAD PERMITS REVOKED OR DENIED
BY THE STATE PUBLIC UTILITIES
COMMISSION.
THE AGENCY THAT REGULATES
LIMOUSINES.
JUST YESTERDAY, A MULTI AGENCY
STRIKE FORCE LED BY THE CHP
LAUNCHED A SURPRISE STING HERE,
TARGETING