>>> THIS IS WORLD NEWS TONIGHT,
AMERICA WARSHIPS AT THE READY.
WILL THERE BE ACTION AT THE NEW
TROUBLING IMAGES FROM SYRIA
TONIGHT.
THE PRESIDENT HUDDLING WITH
NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM, DOCTORS
ON THE GROUND TREATING THOUSANDS
OF PATIENTS, REVEALING THE
SYMPTOMS  TONIGHT.
ABC'S MARTHA RADDATZ STANDING BY
IN THE REGION.
YOSEMITE ON FIRE.
OUR TEAM INSIDE THE PARK
TONIGHT.
HOW CLOSE ARE THE FLAMES TO
SITES.
A MAJOR CITY, THAT FIRE
THREATENING POWER AND WATER.
REMEMBER THE DREAM.
TONIGHT THE MARCH TO WASHINGTON
50 YEARS AFTER THE REVEREND
MARTIN LUTHER KING MADE THAT
DREAM FIRST.
HOW HIS "I HAVE A DREAM" SPEECH
IS BEING KEPT ALIVE.
AND AN AMERICAN VOICE SILENCED.
♪ YOU'RE NO GOOD, BABY YOU'RE NO
GOOD ♪
>> SINGER LINDA ROSTADT
REVEALED, THE CONDITION THAT HAS
STOLEN HER VOICE.
>>> GOOD EVENING, GREAT TO HAVE
YOU WITH US ON A SATURDAY NIGHT.
WE BEGIN WITH THAT GROWING
URGENCY OVER SYRIA.
AMERICAN WARSHIPS BEING
REPOSITIONED, WHAT IS COMING
NEXT?
PRESIDENT OBAMA IN A RARE WHITE
HOUSE MEETING WITH HIS NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISORS TODAY.
THIS PROMPTED THE MEETING.
GROWING PROOF THAT CHEMICAL
WEAPONS MIGHT HAVE BEEN USED TO
KILL MORE THAN 1,000 IN SYRIA,
AMONG THEM SO MANY CHILDREN.
TONIGHT VOLUNTEERS, DOCTORS
WITHOUT BORDERS, INSIDE SYRIA,
TREATING PATIENTS.
NOW REVEALING THE SYMPTOMS THEY
ARE TREATING.
SAYING MORE THAN 3,000 PATIENTS
WERE RUSHED IN WITH WHAT THEY
CALL NEUROTOXIN SYMPTOMS,
SIMILAR TO WHAT YOU'D SEE IN A
CHEMICAL ATTACK.
MORE THAN 300 PEOPLE THEY SAY
DIED.
>>> TONIGHT HERE THREE URGENT
QUESTIONS, IS AMERICA ABOUT TO
GET INVOLVED?
WHAT ARE THE OPTIONS?
AND IF SO, HOW SOON?
ABC'S CLEAVE GLOBAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT MARTHA RADDATZ
REPORTS FROM THE REGION ON THE
CRIS THIS SYRIA.
MARTH RA.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
DAVID.
AS WE STAND HERE TONIGHT, U.S.
WARSHIPS ARE BEING REPOSITIONED
VERY NEARBY IN CASE OF A
MILITARY AIR STRIKE ON SYRIA.
TONIGHT, EVIDENCE OF A CHEMICAL
ATTACK IN SYRIA IS MOUNTING.
NEW IMAGES SHOWING THE HORROR.
THE PRESIDENT SPENT THE DAY
HUDDLED BEHIND CLOSED DOORS WITH
HIS NATIONAL SECURITY TEAM,
WEIGHING THE EVIDENCE AND HIS
MILITARY OPTIONS.
>> WE'RE GATHERING INFORMATION
ABOUT THIS EVENT.
BUT IT'S VERY TROUBLESOME.
>> Reporter: AMONG THE OPTIONS
ON THE TABLE, TARGETING SYRIAN
MILITARY OR GOVERNMENT BUILDINGS
WITH MISSILES, FOUR NAVY
WARSHIPS ARE ALREADY IN THE
MEDITERRANEAN LOADED WITH
TOMAHAWK MISSILES.
U.S. FIGHTER JETS COULD ALSO
ATTACK FIRING FROM OUTSIDE
SYRIAN AIR SPACE, SOAPY LOTS
WOULD BE OUT OF HARM'S WAY.
>> THE ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN
FORTHCOMING IN SAYING THAT RISK
MUST BE LOW.
WE CANNOT RISK GETTING
SERVICEMEN AND WOMEN HURT.
AND WE DON'T WANT TO GET PULLED
INTO ANOTHER QUAGMIRE IN THE
MIDDLE EAST.
>> Reporter: NOTHING WILL HAPPEN
UNTIL THE U.S. CONFIRMS THE
CHEMICAL ATTACK.
TODAY SYRIAN STATE TV CLAIMS THE
REBELS WERE BEHIND THE ATTACK.
ABANDONING THE POSITION THAT NO
CHEMICAL ATTACK OCCURRED.
UN OFFICIALS IN SYRIA ARE
PUSHING FOR ACCESS TO THE SITE
FOR INSPECTION.
THE GROUP DOCTORS WITHOUT
BORDERS SAID TODAY, THAT 3600
PATIENTS WITH NEUROTOXIC
SYMPTOMS WERE TREATED THE DAY OF
THE SUSPECTED ATTACK.
THEY SAY 355 OF THOSE PATIENTS
DIED.
DAVID, THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN
VERY RELUCTANT TO INTERVENE IN
SYRIA.
BUT WITH THESE URGENT MEETINGS,
AND HIS STRONG LANGUAGE, IT
SUGGESTS HE MAY BE CHANGING HIS
MIND.
DAVID.
>> MARTHA RADDATZ LEADING OFF.
THANK YOU.
ONE MORE NOTE ON THIS TONIGHT.
THE WHITE HOUSE REVEALING THE
PRESIDENT DID SPEAK WITH BRITISH
PRIME MINISTER DAVID CAMERON
TODAY.
THE SUBJECT WAS SYRIA AND
POSSIBLE RESPONSES BY THE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY TO THE
USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
AND WE SHOULD POINT OUT TONIGHT
MARTHA WILL ANCHOR AB'S CHRIS
WEEK FROM THE REGION FIRST THING
TOMORROW MORNING.
WE MOVE ON TONIGHT TO THE OTHER
URGENT HEADLINE HERE, THE WILD
FIRE NOW SPREADING IN YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK.
A STATE OF EMERGENCY NOW FOR SAN
FRANCISCO, THEIR WATER COMES
FROM YOSEMITE.
TONIGHT OUR TEAM INSIDE THE
PARK, THE FIRE ALMOST COMPLETELY
OUT OF CONTROL.
THOUSANDS OF FAMILIES ALERT,
THEIR HOMES THREATENED, STUNNED
BY THE SPEED OF THE FIRE.
AND LOOK AT THIS TONIGHT.
THE VIEW FROM SPACE.
THE WILD FIRES SO BIG, THE SMOKE
CLEARLY VISIBLE THERE.
TONIGHT WE ASK ABC'S NEIL
KARLINSKY HOW CLOSE THE FIRE IS
TO SOME OF THE MOST FAMOUS SITES
INSIDE YOSEMITE.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
FROM THE EDGE OF THIS ANGRY
FIRE, HERE'S A FLARE UP FROM THE
LAST TEN MINUTES OR SO.
WE'RE JUST BACK FROM DOWN THE
ROAD HERE INSIDE YOSEMITE, WHERE
WE GOT AN UP CLOSE LOOK AT
EFFORTS TO PROTECT THE PARK.
YOSEMITE IS BURNING, THESE ARE
THE FIRST PICTURES INSIDE THE
PARK OF FIREFIGHTERS MASSING TO
KEEP THE DAMAGE TO A MINIMUM AT
ONE OF AMERICA'S MOST PRISTINE
TREASURES.
WE'RE IN YOSEMITE.
THIS IS EVERYONE'S WORST FEARS.
A FIRE IN YOSEMITE.
>> I'VE BEEN HERE FOUR DAYS,
IT'S JUST BEEN GOING AND GOING
AND GOING.
IT'S JUST NONSTOP.
>> Reporter: YOSEMITE WITH ITS
WATERFALLS AND PEEKS IS STILL
OPEN.
AND THE CONCERN IS REAL.
>> WE ARE HERE TO STOP THE FIRE
FROM GETTING WORSE THAN IT IS
RIGHT NOW.
IF IT PICKS UP INTENSITY, WE'LL
KNOCK IT DOWN TO KEEP IT FROM
MOVING.
>> Reporter: CALIFORNIA'S
GOVERNOR DECLARED A STATE OF
EMERGENCY FOR THE CITY OF SAN
FRAN, 150 MILES AWAY, BECAUSE
THE POWER LINES THAT FEED THE
CITY COULD BE CUT OFF BY THE
FIRE.
WATER IS AN ISSUE AS WELL.
WE TRAVELED TO THE MASSIVE
RESERVOIR INSIDE YOSEMITE, WHICH
PROVIDES 85% OF SAN FRANCISCO'S
WATER.
THE CONCERN EVIDENCE IN THESE
PICTURES, THAT ASH AND DEBRIS
WILL POLEUTE THE WATER.
OFFICIALS SAY THE SIZE OF THE
FIRE HASN'T ACTUALLY CHANGED
THAT MUCH.
IT'S THE INTENSITY.
STILL THERE ARE EVACUATIONS
UNDERWAY AND ONE SMALL PIECE OF
GOOD NEWS.
THE FIRE IS NOW ABOUT 5%
CONTAINED.
THAT'S NOT MUCH.
BUT IT'S A LOT MORE THAN THE 1%
THEY HAD JUST A DAY AGO.
DAVID.
>> 5%, NEIL, A LONG WAY TO GO.
GINGER ZEE IS WITH US HERE AT
THE DESK.
YOU'VE BEEN FOLLOWING THIS AS
WELL.
THE FIRE FORECAST TONIGHT.
>> THE HUMIDITY IS LOW IN THESE
PLACES, THEY ARE NOT GOING TO
GET A LOT OF HELP, ESPECIALLY BY
THE COLD FRONT THAT IS FLIPPING
DOWN FROM THE NORTHWEST.
DAVID, YOU SEE HOW IT COMES IN.
THE LIGHTNING COMES WITH IT.
YOU GET THUNDERSTORMS.
THE WINDS HIT THE GROUND.
THEY GUST AND MAKE THE FIRES
EVEN MORE ERRATIC THAN THEY
ALREADY ARE.
>> WHAT ABOUT THE MOISTURE TO
THE SOUTH OF THERE, THERE WAS
SOME THOUGHT MAYBE IT WOULD
HELP.
>> YEAH.
IT'S NOT GOING TO.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE NOW.
EVO NO THREAT TO LAND AND
WEAKENING.
THIS IS THE PATH.
STAYS OFFSHORE.
WE'RE STILL GOING TO SEE PIECES
OF MOISTURE, THAT TROPICAL AIR
REALLY RISING INTO A SATURATED
SOUTHWEST.
AND WHAT HAPPENS AFTER THAT, YOU
GET ISOLATED THUNDERSTORMS, THAT
COULD DROP REALLY HEAVY RAINS.
WE'RE TALKING ONE TO TWO INCHES
PER HOUR.
AND IN PLACES LIKE THIS, THEY DO
NOT DO WELL.
FROM LAS VEGAS, SAN DIEGO,
PHOENIX, NOT AS WELL AT ALL WITH
THAT TYPE OF HEAVY RAIN.
YOU SEE WHERE YOSEMITE'S FIRE
IS, NOT IN THE RAIN ZONE.
>> ALL THE WAY AROUND IT.
BUT NOT WHERE IT'S NEEDED.
THANK YOU.
>>> TO WASHINGTON TONIGHT, TENS
OF THOUSANDS OF AMERICANS
MARCHED ON THE NATIONAL MALL TO
THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL TO REMEMBER
A DREAM.
IT WAS INSPIRED BY THIS HISTORIC
MARCH BACK IN 1963.
THAT LANDMARK EVENT IN THE CIVIL
RIGHTS MOVEMENT, SOME 50 YEARS
AGO.
THAT LED TO SO MANY CHANGES.
AND TODAY, ALL OF THESE YEARS
LATER, SO MANY STILL DETERMINED
TO FINISH THAT WORK.
TODAY THEY MARCHED AGAIN STILL
INSPIRED BY THOSE STIRRING WORDS
FROM DR. MARTIN LUTHER KING.
>> I HAVE A DREAM.
MY FOUR LITTLE CHILDREN, ONE DAY
LIVE IN A NATION, WHERE THEY
WILL NOT BE JUDGED BY THE COLOR
OF THEIR SKIN BUT BY THE CONTENT
OF THEIR CHARACTER.
I HAVE A DREAM.
>> THE I HAVE A DREAM SPEECH.
50 YEARS AGO THIS WEEK.
TONIGHT HERE ABC HAS SOME OF THE
SAME FACE WHO IS HAVE RETURNED
TO THE NATION'S CAPITOL.
>> Reporter: 50 YEARS AFTER THE
MARCH, THEY CAME TO RETRACE
THEIR STEPS THAT CHANGED A
COUNTRY.
THE MOVEMENT WAS BORNE OUT OF
THE BLACK CHURCHES WITH A
MESSAGE HERALDED BY A MINISTER.
>> I HAVE A DREAM.
>> Reporter: TODAY THAT DREAM
CARRIED ON BY HIS SON.
>> I KNOW DADDY IS SMILING UP
ABOVE.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN 200,000
PEOPLE GATHERED ON THAT AUGUST
DAY.
KATHLEEN JOHNSON WAS ONE OF
THEM.
THIS PHOTO CAPTURING THE MOMENT
AFTER SHE TUMBLED INTO THE
REFLECTING POOL, TRYING TO SNAP
A PICTURE.
>> I JUST WANTED TO GET HELP TO
GET OUT.
>> Reporter: THE CAMERA LOST,
BUT THIS IMAGE WINDING UP ON
NEWSPAPERS THE NEXT MORNING.
EDITH LEE PAYNE TURNED 12 ON
THAT DAY.
ONLY FIVE YEARS AGO HER COUSIN
DISCOVERING THIS PHOTO OF HER IN
THE BACK OF A CALENDAR.
>> I WAS IN DISBELIEF, THAT MY
PICTURE WOULD BE ON A COMED WITH
MARTIN LUTHER KING.
>> Reporter: 50 YEARS LATARY
COMPANY NEED BY HER
GRANDCHILDREN CARRYING THE SAME
BANNER, AND HER MEMORIES.
THAT LITTLE GIRL'S FACE NOW
RECREATED ON THE WALL AT BEN'S
CHILI BOWL RESTAURANT IN
WASHINGTON D.C.
THE WORDS ON THE SIGNS ARE
DIFFERENT TODAY.
BUT THE DREAM LIVES ON.
PRESIDENT OBAMA SAID HE'S A
TESTAMENT TO THE ENORMOUS
STRIDES MADE SINCE THE 1963
MARCH.
HE WOULD DELIVER A SPEECH RIGHT
HERE AT THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL ON
WEDNESDAY.
DAVID.
>> GREAT TO SEE KATHLEEN AND
EDITH AND SO MANY RETURNING.
THANK YOU.
>>> FROM SOUTH AFRICA, NEW WORD
ON ANOTHER HUMAN RIGHTS
CHAMPION, NELSON MANDELA, THE
GOVERNMENT SAYING THE FORMER
PRESIDENT REMAINING IN CRITICAL
BUT STABLE CONDITION IN THE
HOSPITAL, THOUGH QUOTE, MEDICAL
INTERVENTIONS ARE REQUIRED FROM
TIME TO TIME, THEY SAY.
ADDING THAT DOCTORS ARE STILL
WORKING HARD FOR A TURN AROUND.
THE 95-YEAR-OLD MANDELA HAS BEEN
HOSPITALIZED SINCE EARLY JUNE.
>>> BACK HERE AT HOME TONIGHT
FROM CALIFORNIA NOW, A FUNERAL
FOR THE MOTHER AND BROTHER OF
HANNAH ANDERSON, THE 16-YEAR-OLD
GIRL ABDUCTED AND THEN RESCUED
FROM THE WOODS.
HANNAH WAS AMONG THE MOURNERS
TODAY, THREE WEEKS AGO TODAY IN
FACT THAT CHRISTINA AND ETHAN
ANDERSON DIED.
ALLEGEDLY KILLED BY JAMES
DiMAGGIO WHO ABDUCTED HANNAH.
HE WAS KILLED AS HE EXCHANGED
GUN FIRE WITH RESCUERS.
>>> TO A DEEPENING MYSTERY IN
THE SOUTHWEST OF OREGON.
A MISSING COLLEGE STUDENT THERE,
18-YEAR-OLD JONATHAN KROOM
VISITING A FRIEND IN SEATTLE WAS
EXPECTED HOME IN SEATTLE LAST
WEEKEND.
POLICE FOUND HIS SUV ABANDONED
IN THE SMALL TOWN IN OREGON.
UNLOCKED.
GAS IN THE TANK.
MONEY INSIDE.
POLICE TONIGHT STILL SEARCHING
>>> NEWS ABOUT A BELOVED
AMERICAN SINGER AND HER HEALTH.
LINDA ROSTADT SAYING SHE HAS
PARKINS
PARKINSON'S AND CAN NO LONGER
SING.
SINGER LINDA ROSTADT AND
DESPERADO KNOWN FOR THAT VOICE,
HER EXTRAORDINARY RANGE.
NOW SAYING SHE WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH PARKINSON'S DISEASE, A
NEUROLOGICAL DISORDER EIGHT
MONTHS AGO, REVEALING HER
ABILITY TO SING HAS BEEN STOLEN.
AT 67 YEARS OLD, SAYING I CAN'T
SING A NOTE, TELLING AARP
MAGAZINE, NOBODY CAN SING WITH
PARKINSON'S DISEASE, NO MATTER
HOW HARD YOU TRY.
I COULDN'T SING.
I COULDN'T FIGURE OUT WHY SHE
TOLD THE MAGAZINE.
I KNEW IT WAS MECHANICAL.
I KNEW IT HAD TO DO WITH THE
MULC.
PARKINSON'S AFFECTS THE NERVOUS
SYSTEM.
THOUSANDS GO UNDETECTD EVERY
YEAR.
THERE ARE TREATMENTS BUT NONE
REVERSE THE EFFECTS.
AMONG S
AMONG THE SYMPTOMS ARE TREMORS.
SHE USES POLES TO WALK SOMETIMES
RELYING ON A WHEELCHAIR.
SHE WON 11 GRAMMYS OVER THE
YEARS, FAMOUS FOR SO MANY SONGS.
NUMBER ONE HIT EARLY ON, HURT SO
BAD.
SO MANY MORE SONGS SKYROCKETING
ON THE BILLBOARD CHARTS IN THE
YEARS THAT FOLLOWED.
YOU'RE NO GOOD.
♪ YOU'RE NO GOOD
>> SHE STARTED PERFORM AGG AT
14.
LATER IN HER CAREER WINNING A
GRAMMY FOR THAT DUO WITH AARON
NEVILLE, DON'T KNOW MUCH
♪ DON'T KNOW MUCH, BUT I KNOW I
LOVE YOU ♪
>> WHAT A GORGEOUS VOICE,
ROSTADT HAS A MEMOIR COMING OUT
NEXT MONTH CALLED SIMPLE DREAMS.
SO MANY PEOPLE PUMPING FOR LINDA
ROSTADT TONIGHT.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON WORLD NEWS THIS
SATURDAY EVENING.
A MAJOR DEVELOPMENT IN THE PAULA
DEEN CASE, A SETTLEMENT, AND
WHAT THE ACCUSER IS SAYING NOW
ABOUT DEEN, IS THIS THE START OF
A COMEBACK?
AND WHO WANTS TO BE A
MILLIONAIRE TONIGHT, THE
UNCLAIMED WINNING TICKET WORTH
$1 MILLION.
BUT YOU ONLY HAVE UNTIL MIDNIGHT
TO CLAIM IT.
EARS...
IT'S BEEN A HAPPY UNION.
HE DOES LAUNDRY,
AND I DO THE CLEANING.
THERE'S ONLY TWO OF US...
HOW MUCH DIRT
CAN WE MANUFACTURE?
MORE THAN YOU THINK.
VERY LITTLE.
[ DOORBELL RINGS ]
[ Lee ]
LET'S HAVE A LOOK, MORTY.
IT'S A SWEEPER.
WHAT'S THIS?
WHAT'S THAT?
WELL WE'LL FIND OUT.
WE'LL FIND OUT.
[ Lee ] IT GOES UNDER
ALL THE WAY TO THE BACK WALL.
I CAME IN UNDER THE ASSUMPTION
THAT IT WAS CLEAN.
I'VE BEEN LIVING
IN A FOOL'S PARADISE!
OH BOY...
THERE YOU GO...
MORTY JUST SUMMED IT UP.
THE NEXT 44 YEARS
WE'LL BE FINE.
WHEN I FIRST FELT
THE DIABETIC NERVE PAIN,
OF COURSE
I HAD NO IDEA WHAT IT WAS.
I FELT LIKE
MY FEET WERE GOING TO SLEEP.
IT PROGRESSED FROM THERE
TO BURNING
LIKE I WAS WALKING
ON HOT COALS...
TO LIKE 1,000 BEES
THAT WERE JUST STINGING MY FEET.
I HAVE A GREAT RELATIONSHIP
WITH MY DOCTOR...
HE FOUND LYRICA FOR ME.
[ Female Announcer ] IT'S KNOWN
THAT DIABETES DAMAGES NERVES.
LYRICA IS FDA APPROVED
TO TREAT DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
LYRICA IS NOT FOR EVERYONE.
IT MAY CAUSE
SERIOUS ALLERGIC REACTIONS
OR SUICIDAL THOUGHTS
OR ACTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE THESE,
NEW OR WORSENING DEPRESSION,
OR UNUSUAL CHANGES
IN MOOD OR BEHAVIOR.
OR SWELLING, TROUBLE BREATHING,
RASH, HIVES, BLISTERS,
CHANGES IN EYESIGHT
INCLUDING BLURRY VISION,
MUSCLE PAIN WITH FEVER,
TIRED FEELING,
OR SKIN SORES FROM DIABETES.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS ARE
DIZZINESS, SLEEPINESS,
WEIGHT GAIN AND SWELLING
OF HANDS, LEGS AND FEET.
DON'T DRINK ALCOHOL
WHILE TAKING LYRICA.
DON'T DRIVE OR USE MACHINERY
UNTIL YOU KNOW
HOW LYRICA AFFECTS YOU.
THOSE WHO HAVE HAD A DRUG
OR ALCOHOL PROBLEM
MAY BE MORE LIKELY
TO MISUSE LYRICA.
HAVING LESS PAIN --
IT'S A WONDERFUL FEELING.
[ Female Announcer ] ASK
YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT LYRICA TODAY.
IT'S SPECIFIC TREATMENT
FOR DIABETIC NERVE PAIN.
TO HEAR MORE OF PHYLLIS'S
STORY, VISIT LYRICA.COM.
[ CRASHING ]
[ Male Announcer ] WHEN YOUR
FAVORITE FOOD STARTS A FIGHT,
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
HEARTBURN RELIEF THAT
NEUTRALIZES ACID ON CONTACT
AND GOES TO WORK IN SECONDS.
♪ TUM, TUM TUM TUM TUMS!
>>> A NEW CHAPTER TONIGHT.
PERHAPS THE FINAL ONE IN THE
PAULA DEEN DISCRIMINATION CASE.
WORD OF A SETTLEMENT, NO MONEY
CHANGING HANDS.
AND IT'S WHAT THE ACCUSER IS NOW
SAYING ABOUT THE CELEBRITY CHEF
THAT HAS SOME PEOPLE PUZZLED.
IS THIS THE BEGINNING OF A
COMEBACK?
HERE'S ABC'S LINZIE JANIS.
>> Reporter: SHE'S TAKEN THE
HEAT AND TONIGHT PAULA DEEN IS
READY TO GET BACK IN THE
KITCHEN, AFTER THE HARDEST FEW
MONTHS OF HER CAREER.
>> ONE TABLESPOON OF BUTTER.
>> Reporter: FRESH DETAILS ARE
EMERGING ABOUT THE SETTLEMENT
BETWEEN DEEN AND FORMER EMPLOYEE
LISA JACKSON, WHO CLAIMS SHE
SUFFERED FROM RACIAL
DISCRIMINATION AND SEXUAL
HARASSMENT.
THE TWO SIDES SETTLING IN COURT,
WITH NO MONEY CHANGING HANDS.
AND THEN A BIZARRE ABOUT FACE,
JACKSON EVEN STATES HER
ADMIRATION, SAYING QUOTE, THE
PAULA DEEN I HAVE KNOWN FOR MORE
THAN EIGHT YEARS IS A WOMAN OF
COMPASSION AND KINDNESS.
AND WILL NEVER TOLERATE
DISCRIMINATION OR RACISM OF ANY
KIND TOWARD ANYONE.
THE QUESTION NOW, WILL IT BE
ENOUGH TO REPAIR HER DAMAGED
MULTIMILLION DOLLAR REPUTATION?
>> YOU HAVE TO LIVE IN THE COURT
OF LAW.
YOU HAVE TO LIVE IN THE COURT OF
PUBLIC OPINION.
SHE'S CLEARLY WINNING IN THE
COURT OF LAW.
BUT SHE'S ALREADY LOST IN THE
COURT OF PUBLIC OPINION.
AND THAT'S THE REALITY SHE HAS
TO LIVE WITH.
>> Reporter: IN MAY, DEEN SWORE
UNDER OATH, SHE ONCE USED THE N
WORD.
>> PLEASE FORGIVE ME.
>> Reporter: DESPITE MULTIPLE
APOLOGIES, THE FOOD NETWORK,
QVC, SEARS AND MANY OTHERS HAVE
DISTANCED THEMSELVES FROM THE
CHEF, COSTING HER AT LEAST $12.5
MILLION IN ENDORSEMENT DEALS.
DEALS SHE MAY STRUGGLE TO WIN
BACK.
DEEN'S ACCUSER ALSO SAYS SHE
DISCOVERED THE COMPLAINTS SHE
HAD BEEN MAKING ABOUT HER WORK
PLACE ENVIRONMENT WERE NOT
GETTING TO PAULA DEEN.
TONIGHT DAVID DEEN IS THANKING
THOSE WHO STUCK BY HER SAYING
GOD BLESS Y'ALL, AND THANK YOU
FOR YOUR SUPPORT.
>> WHAT A TURN.
ALL RIGHT.
LINDSAY, THANK YOU.
WHEN WE COME BACK, THERE IS A
MILLION DOLLARS WAITING TO BE
CLAIMED, THAT'S RIGHT, A WINNING
TICKET, NOT PICKED UP.
HERE'S THE CATCH.
YOU HAVE UNTIL MIDNIGHT TO CLAIM
IT.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHERE AND WHICH
STORE, COMING UP TONIGHT.
Discover the new way to help
keep teeth clean
and breath fresh.
New Beneful Healthy Smile Food
and Snacks.
He'll love the crunch of the
Healthy Smile kibbles.
You'll love how they help clean.
With soft, meaty centers,
and teeth cleaning texture
Healthy Smile Snacks help keep a
shine on his smile.
It's dental that tastes so good.
New Beneful Healthy Smile Food
and Snacks.
APPLY COLD THERAPY
IN THE FIRST 24 HOURS.
BUT NOT JUST ANY COLD.
I ONLY USE
NEW THERMACARE® COLD WRAPS.
TARGETTEMP TECHNOLOGY DELIVERS
A CONSISTENT, THERAPEUTIC COLD
TO STOP PAIN AND START HEALING.
NEW THERMACARE® COLD WRAPS.
A BETTER WAY TO TREAT PAIN.
TO STOP PAIN AND START HEALING.
We provide the exact
individualization that
your body needs.
This Labor Day, don't
invest in a mattress until
you visit a Sleep Number
store.
Once you experience it,
there's no going back.
Oh, yeah!
At our Biggest Sale of the
Year,
every bed is on sale.
Queen mattresses now start
at just $599.
And save an incredible 40%
on our Limited Edition
Memory Foam mattress sets.
Only at a Sleep Number
store.
Sleep Number.
Comfort individualized.
is sweatier and messier
than my family on the field.
So like the NFL I use Tide...
...because I'm the equipment
manager in this house.
That's my Tide.
What's yours?
>>> INSTANT INDEX ON SATURDAY
NIGHT INTO WHAT BROUGHT A
VIRGINIA WOMAN TO TEARS ON HER
WEDDING DAY.
NOT JUST THE WEDDING ITSELF SHE
WAS ABOUT TO WALK DOWN THE AISLE
AND GOT THE SURPRISE OF HER
LIFE, HER BROTHER A SOLDIER IN
THE ARMY WHO SHE HADN'T SEEN IN
YEARS STEPPING IN TO SUPPORT HER
AT THE LAST MOMENT.
THE PHOTOGRAPHER CATCHING THE
TEARFUL REUNION ON CAMERA AND
THEN THE TEARS OF THE WEDDING
CAME NEXT.
>>> A STORY OF LOVE GONE WRONG.
A CHICAGO WOMAN RACKING UP THE
BIGGEST PARKING FINE IN HISTORY.
JENNIFER FITZGERALD OWING
$105,000 FOR A CAR REGISTERED IN
HER NAME PARKED AT O'HARE
AIRPORT FOR THREE YEARS.
HER EX-BOYFRIEND LEFT IT THERE
ON PURPOSE.
THE CITY HAS DECIDED THAT
EX-BOYFRIEND SHOULD HAVE TO PAY
A HUGE PORTION OF THOSE FINES.
>>> TO A BIGGER NUMBER TONIGHT,
WHO WANTS TO BE A MILLIONAIRE I
ASKED A MOMENT AGO.
$1 MILLION UP FOR GRABS IN
UNCLAIMED POWERBALL TICKET.
SOLD EXACTLY ONE YEAR AGO
TONIGHT AT THE PLAY LANDMARK ET
IN RYE, NEW YORK.
I CAN'T TALK, I'M TRYING TO
THINK IF I'VE BEEN THERE.
NOBODY CAME FORWARD.
THE OWNER PUTTING UP SIGNS IN
THE WINDOW TO JOG SOMEONE'S
MEMORY.
THE WINNER HAS UNTIL MIDNIGHT TO
CLAIM THE PRIZE.
IF YOU SEE SOMETHING THAT
CATCHES YOUR EYE TWEET ME ON
TWITTER OR SEND ME A MESSAGE ON
FACEBOOK.
WHEN WE COME BACK ON WORLD NEWS
THIS EVENING, OUR CAMERAS
ALLOWED INSIDE THE PANDA
NURSERY, THE VERY DELICATE
MISSION UNDERWAY TO KEEP BABY
TWIN PANDAS ALIVE AND WELL.
WHAT OUR CORRESPONDENT HAD TO DO
BEFORE THEY EVEN LET THEM IN.
THAT MR. CLEAN REALIZED CH
THE WAY TO HANDLE BIGGER,
TOUGHER MESSES
WAS BETTER LEVERAGE.
THAT'S WHY HE CREATED HIS NEW
MAGIC ERASER HANDY GRIP.
IT HAS A HANDLE THAT FIRMLY
ATTACHES TO THE ERASER
SO YOU GET BETTER LEVERAGE
AND MORE OOMPH
WITH LESS EFFORT.
IT'S THE PERFECT MAGIC ERASER
FOR MAKING STUFF
THAT'S BIG AND TOUGH
NOT SO TOUGH, AFTER ALL.
MR. CLEAN'S HANDY GRIP --
THE NEWEST MEMBER
OF THE MAGIC ERASER FAMILY.
IN ALL PURPOSE AND BATH.
[ engine revs ]
>>> AND FINALLY TONIGHT HERE
THAT NEW BABY PANDA IN
WASHINGTON, THOSE TWIN PANDAS
BORN IN ATLANTA, IT'S A BABY
BOOM FOR AMERICAN ZOOS.
MATT GUTTMAN WITH AN EXCLUSIVE
LOOK INSIDE THE ATLANTA NURSERY
WHERE THEY ARE KEEPING WATCH AND
EVEN MATT HIMSELF FORCED TO BE
EXTRA CAREFUL AROUND THOSE
PRECIOUS TWINS.
>> Reporter: COULD IT POSSIBLY
BE?
PANDA BABY BOOM.
WATCH AS PANDA GIVES BIRTH TO A
TINY CUB ABOUT THE SIZE OF A
STICK OF BUTTER FRIDAY AT THE
SMITHSONIAN NATIONAL ZOO IN
WASHINGTON D.C.
IN SIX WEEKS OR SO, THAT CUB
WILL BE SQUIRMING AND SQUAWKING,
LIKE THESE TWIN FUZZ BALLS.
PANDA CUBS ARE IMPOSSIBLY CUTE.
>> BROTHERLY LOVE.
LOOK AT THAT.
>> Reporter: ALSO DANGEROUSLY
FRAGILE.
>> THESE ARE THE ONLY PANDA
TWINS TO EVER SURVIVE IN THE
UNITED STATES.
>> EVER.
>> Reporter: FOR THE VETS HERE
AT ZOO ATLANTA, KEEPING THEM
ALIVE IS A FULL TIME MISSION.
>> THEY GAINED 36.5 GRAMS.
ABOUT AN OUNCE.
>> Reporter: REQUIRING STAFF IN
A BIO SECURED ENVIRONMENT.
WHICH REQUIRES LOTS OF WASHING.
>> WE'LL HAVE YOU WEAR SCRUBS,
SHOWER IN TO WASH OFF GERMS.
>> Reporter: I DID AS I WAS
TOLD.
SCRUBS AND HAND SANITIZER ARE
MUST.
WHOO!
IN THE WILD, PANDA TWINS RARELY
SURVIVE PAST INFANCY.
SO THE VETS HERE CAREFULLY
CHOREOGRAPH CUB SWAPS, SO EACH
ONE GETS TO FEED WITH MOTHER.
>> WE ARE VERY CAUTIOUS.
WE STILL WORRY A LOT.
>> Reporter: EVERY DAY, THERE'S
A LITTLE MORE HOPE AND A LOT
MORE CUTENESS.
MATT GUTTMAN, ABC NEWS, ATLANTA.
>> THAT'S THE CLEANEST WE'VE
SEEN MATT.
GOOD MORNING AMERICA COMING YOUR
WAY IN THE MORNING.
GREAT TO SEE THE PANDAS.
A REMINDER, SPECIAL EDITION OF
ABC'S THIS WEEK, MARTHA RADDATZ
ON THE CRISIS IN SYRIA.
I HOPE TO SEE YOU BACK HERE
TOMORROW NIGHT.
FROM ALL OF US, GOOD NIGHT.
>>> SIMPLY PUT, WHEN THEY BUILT
BRISTOL THEY BROKE THE MOLD.
WELCOME TO BRISTOL MOTOR
SPEEDWAY.
THIS PLACE LIVES UP TO THE HYPE
AND EVERY BIT OF IT.
IT IS A SATURDAY NIGHT, EASTERN
TENNESSEE.
THIS IS NASCAR'S SPRINT CUP
SERIES COUNTDOWN.
NORMAL DAY, BRISTOL ONLY BOASTS
A POPULATION OF 230,000.
THIS TONIGHT, THOUGH, IS THE
THIRD MOST POPULATED CITY IN THE
STATE.
NORMALLY THIS IS WHERE WE
WELCOME YOU TO THE