>> WE APPRECIATE YOUR
>>> TONIGHT, WE ARE ON THE
SCENE, THE MASSACRE HERE IN LAS
VEGAS.
THE DEADLIEST MASS SHOOTING IN
MODERN AMERICAN HISTORY.
THE GUNMAN FIRING DOWN AT
THOUSANDS WHO WERE GATHERED AT
AN OUTDOOR CONCERT, FROM HIS
HOTEL ROOM ON THE 32nd FLOOR.
THE CROWD ERUPTING INTO MASS
PANIC.
SOME DIVING FOR COVER.
OTHERS RUNNING FOR THEIR LIVES.
AND TONIGHT, THE STAGGERING NEW
TOLL.
AT LEAST 59 KILLED, MORE THAN
500 WOUNDED.
AND TONIGHT, RIGHT HERE, THE
AUDIO, AS S.W.A.T. TEAMS MOVE
IN, SURROUNDING THE SUSPECT'S
HOTEL DOOR.
>> BREACH, BREACH, BREACH.
>> POLICE DISCOVERING AN ARSENAL
OF WEAPONS.
THE SHOOTER TAKING HIS OWN LIFE.
A 64-YEAR-OLD LIVING IN A
RETIREMENT COMMUNITY OUTSIDE LAS
VEGAS.
YOU WILL HEAR FROM HIS FAMILY,
RIGHT HERE THIS EVENING.
A BROTHER IN DISBELIEF.
ALSO TONIGHT, HOSPITALS
OVERWHELMED WITH THE INJURED.
HUNDREDS OF THEM.
AT ONE HOSPITAL, MORE THAN A
DOZEN DYING AFTER ARRIVING IN
THE E.R.
OTHERS IN CRITICAL CONDITION.
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE LINING UP FOR
BLOCKS TO DONATE BLOOD TONIGHT.
AND THE FACES OF THE VICTIMS
BEGINNING TO EMERGE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND THE FIRST
LADY WITH A MOMENT OF SILENCE
OUTSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE.
AFTER CALLING IT AN ACT OF EVIL.
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT" BEGINS NOW.
>>> AND GOOD EVENING FROM LAS
VEGAS.
AND WE ARE HERE AT THE SCENE OF
THE WORST MASS SHOOTING IN
AMERICAN HISTORY.
A LONE GUNMAN FROM A 32nd FLOOR
HOTEL WINDOW SHOOTING AT
THOUSANDS OF HELPLESS
CONCERT-GOERS BELOW.
ON STAGE, COUNTRY MUSIC STAR
JASON ALDEAN.
THE MUSIC SUDDENLY MIXING WITH
THE SOUND OF BULLETS.
TERRIFIED PEOPLE ON THE GROUND,
DURING THE ROUNDS OF RELENTLESS
GUNFIRE, THEY WERE HUDDLING.
AND THEN, THE PAUSE.
THEY WOULD RUN FOR THEIR LIVES
BEFORE WITNESSES SAY THE GUNFIRE
WOULD THEN BEGIN AGAIN.
POLICE AND FIRST RESPONDERS
RUSHING IN.
IN MINUTES, S.W.A.T. TEAMS
REACHING THAT HOTEL ROOM IN THAT
BUILDING RIGHT HERE BEHIND ME.
AND TONIGHT, THE HORRIFIC TOLL
NOW EMERGING.
JUST A SHORT TIME AGO, THEY
REVEALED AT LEAST 59 NOW KILLED.
MORE THAN 500 INJURED.
WHAT THEY'VE NOW DISCOVERED IN
THE SUSPECT'S HOME.
HIS FAMILY, YOU'LL HEAR FROM
THEM TONIGHT.
AND THE FACES OF THE VICTIMS.
BUT FIRST, WHAT BEGAN TO PLAY
OUT SHORTLY AFTER 10:00 P.M.
LOCAL TIME, RIGHT HERE IN LAS
VEGAS.
ABC SENIOR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MATT GUTMAN
LEADING US OFF.
>> Reporter: THE CHAOS UNFOLDING
IN THE HEART OF THE LAS VEGAS
STRIP.
10:08 P.M., 22,000 COUNTRY MUSIC
FANS PACKED IN, ENJOYING THE
ROUTE 91 HARVEST FESTIVAL.
BUT HIGH ABOVE THEM, ON THE 32nd
FLOOR OF THE GLITTERING MANDALAY
BAY RESORT, POLICE SAY
64-YEAR-OLD STEPHEN PADDOCK WAS
WATCHING.
THEY SAY HE HAMMERED THROUGH THE
HOTEL'S THICK WINDOWS AND
STARTED FIRING ON THE CROWD
BELOW.
COUNTRY STAR JASON ALDEAN WAS ON
STAGE, BUT AUTOMATIC GUNFIRE
QUICKLY DROWNING OUT HIS VOICE.
♪
THE MUSIC STOPS, AND HE RUNS
OFFSTAGE.
THE AUDIENCE, HUDDLING ON THE
GROUND, THE MANDALAY LOOMING
OVER THEM.
FOR SO MANY, CONFUSION.
WAS THIS PART OF THE SHOW?
>> THAT'S JUST A FIRECRACKER.
>> I KNOW, BUT WHY WOULD YOU DO
THAT?
>> Reporter: SECONDS LATER, THE
RAPID FIRE SHOOTING STARTS
AGAIN.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Reporter: TERRIFIED PEOPLE
PILE ON TOP OF EACH OTHER,
SHELTERING BEHIND ANYTHING THEY
COULD.
BUT THEY WERE IN AN OPEN FIELD,
EASY TARGETS FOR THE GUNMAN IN
THE TOWER.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHERE TO GO!
OH MY GOD!
>> Reporter: THOUSANDS LOOKING
FOR SAFETY, ANYWHERE, EVEN A
STRANGER'S CAR.
>> TURN AROUND.
>> CAN WE GET IN?
CAN WE GET IN?
>> YEAH, GET IN.
>> TURN AROUND.
>> THERE'S A MASS SHOOTING!
THERE'S A MASS SHOOTING!
>> RELAX, RELAX.
>> MY HUSBAND AND I RAN OUT
TOWARD OUR CAR, AND THERE WERE
PEOPLE HIDING UNDERNEATH MY CAR
FOR COVER.
>> Reporter: IT WAS EARLY THIS
MORNING, WE FOUND MIKE CRONK,
HEAD IN HIS HANDS, STILL STAINED
WITH HIS FRIEND'S BLOOD.
>> GOT HIT THREE TIMES.
>> Reporter: MIKE USED HIS SHIRT
TO KEEP HIS FRIEND FROM BLEEDING
OUT.
YOU GUYS WERE TRYING TO DO
TRIAGE WHILE THE SHOOTING IS
STILL GOING ON?
>> YEAH, EVERYBODY WAS JUMPING
OVER THE FENCES AND STUFF, BUT
THERE'S NO WAY I'M GOING TO
LEAVE MY BUDDY.
WE HAD TO KEEP COMPRESSION ON
IT, SO -- ONCE WE -- WE WEREN'T
EVEN SURE IF THE SHOOTING WAS
STOPPED.
WE GOT HIM OVER THE FENCE, AND
UNDER THE STAGE SO AT LEAST WE
KNEW WE WERE SAFE.
>> Reporter: AS AN ARMY OF
POLICE DESCENDED HIGH ABOVE THE
PANICKED CROWDS, S.W.A.T. TEAMS
ARE CLOSING IN ON THE SHOOTER.
THEY APPROACH HIS HOTEL DOOR
ARMED WITH AN EXPLOSIVE.
>> EVERYONE IN THE HALLWAY NEEDS
TO MOVE BACK.
ALL UNITS, MOVE BACK.
>> BREACH, BREACH, BREACH.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY THEY
FOUND PADDOCK DEAD INSIDE.
HE HAD KILLED HIMSELF.
>> RIGHT NOW, WE NEED YOUR
TRUCK.
WE JUST NEED TO GET PEOPLE OVER
TO THE HOSPITAL, OKAY?
>> OKAY.
>> Reporter: DOWN ON THE GROUND,
THE SIDEWALK NOW A TRIAGE
CENTER.
THE WOUNDED CARRIED ON
BARRICADES, TURNED INTO
STRETCHERS, EVEN IN
WHEELBARROWS.
>> WE JUST SAW A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
THAT NEEDED HELP, SO, WE JUST
STARTED PILING THEM UP IN THE
TRUCK.
>> Reporter: THE ENTIRE VEGAS
STRIP, FROZEN, TOTAL LOCKDOWN.
THIS AMERICAN PLAYGROUND, NOW A
KILLING FIELD.
>> AND MATT GUTMAN JOINING US
TONIGHT RIGHT HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
AND POLICE STILL POURING OVER
THIS CRIME SCENE.
AND THEY TOLD YOU, THIS IS GOING
TO BE A COMPLEX INVESTIGATION AT
EACH OF THESE SCENES.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
BECAUSE THERE ARE MULTIPLE
SCENES COVERING SEVERAL CITY
BLOCKS, AND, OF COURSE, THERE
ARE THOSE HUNDREDS OF VICTIMS.
BUT PERHAPS, WHAT'S MOST
STRIKING ABOUT THIS SHOOTING IS
THE DISTANCE BETWEEN WHERE THAT
SNIPER WAS PERCHED ON THE 32nd
STORY OF THE MANDALAY, AND THAT
CONCERT BELOW, YOU CAN SEE,
ABOUT 40 YARDS AWAY FROM WHERE
I'M STANDING.
THOSE BULLETS HAD TO TRAVEL WELL
OVER 300 YARDS TO HIT THEIR
VICTIMS AT THE CONCERT.
DAVID?
>> ALL RIGHT, MATT GUTMAN
LEADING US OFF TONIGHT.
MATT, WHO HAS BEEN HERE SINCE
THE EARLY MORNING HOURS, THANK
YOU.
>>> AND NEXT HERE TONIGHT, A
CHILLING LOOK INSIDE THE ATTACK.
FROM THE FIRST RESPONDERS AND
POLICE ON THE SCENE, TONIGHT, WE
ARE NOW HEARING THE RADIO CALLS
THAT THEY MADE FOR HELP.
AND THEIR TENSE CONVERSATIONS
WHEN THEY WENT TO TAKE THE
GUNMAN DOWN IN THAT HOTEL
HALLWAY, AND THEY APPROACHED
THAT DOOR.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT TOM LLAMAS, ALSO
HERE IN NEVADA TONIGHT.
>> SHOTS FIRED FROM
MANDALAY BAY, THERE'S MANY
PEOPLE DOWN.
>> Reporter: AS BULLETS RAINED
DOWN ON CONCERT-GOERS LIKE HELL
FIRE, LAS VEGAS S.W.A.T. TEAMS
JUMPED INTO ACTION TO TAKE DOWN
THE SHOOTER.
>> 790-RI, I'M GOING TO FORM A
STRIKE TEAM.
MANDALAY BAY AND THE BOULEVARD.
I NEED FIVE OFFICERS ON ME.
>> Reporter: HEAVILY ARMED
OFFICERS MOVING UP THE MASSIVE
GLASS TOWER.
>> CONTROL ZEBRA-20.
WE ARE AT THE END OF THE HALL.
WE ARE GOING TO BE PEEKING OUT
INTO THE HALLWAY.
THOSE OFFICERS THAT ARE DOWN THE
HALL NEED TO ACKNOWLEDGE SO WE
DON'T HAVE A CROSSFIRE.
>> Reporter: CAREFUL OF FRIENDLY
FIRE, S.W.A.T. MEMBERS ADVANCE.
>> I HAVE THE HALLWAY OF THE
SUSPECT'S ROOM ON THE 32nd
FLOOR.
>> Reporter: AND RIGHT BEFORE
THEY STORM PADDOCK'S ROOM, THIS
WARNING, JUST IN CASE THEY'RE
WALKING INTO AN AMBUSH.
>> I'M AT THE SUSPECT'S DOOR.
I NEED EVERYBODY IN THAT HALLWAY
TO BE AWARE OF IT AND GET BACK.
WE NEED TO POP THIS AND SEE IF
WE GET ANY TYPE OF RESPONSE FROM
THIS GUY, TO SEE IF HE'S IN HERE
OR IF HE'S ACTUALLY MOVED OUT
SOMEWHERE ELSE.
>> BREACH, BREACH, BREACH.
>> Reporter: AFTER THAT
EXPLOSION, OFFICERS MOVE IN.
>> WE ARE CLEARING THIS ROOM.
WE HAVE ONE SUSPECT DOWN.
>> IS THAT ROOM 135?
>> THAT'S AFFIRMATIVE.
ONE SUSPECT DOWN IN 135, I HAVE
THE FLOOR.
>> Reporter: AND AS THEY
DISCOVER PADDOCK'S BODY, THEY
ALSO FIND HIS ARSENAL.
>> WE HAVE THE EAST ROOM SECURE.
WE'VE GOT ONE SUSPECT DOWN.
MULTIPLE FIREARMS.
THIS IS DEFINITELY THE PLACE
WHERE THEY WERE FIRING INTO THE
CROWD.
>> Reporter: DAVID, AS YOU KNOW,
THIS MAYHEM TOOK PLACE OVER A
COUPLE OF HOURS.
AS THIS WAS HAPPENING, THE LAS
VEGAS S.W.A.T. TEAM WAS PUTTING
TOGETHER THEIR PLAN.
THAT'S WHEN THEY FINALLY ENTERED
THE MANDALAY BAY RESORT ON THE
29th FLOOR.
THEY MADE IT TO THE 32nd FLOOR.
HOW DID THEY DO THIS?
THE SHERIFF OF THE LAS VEGAS
POLICE DEPARTMENT TELLS US
PEOPLE, HOTEL GUESTS LET THEM
KNOW EXACTLY WHERE THIS WAS
HAPPENING AND THEY WERE ABLE TO
PINPOINT THE SUITE WHERE THE
SHOOTER WAS STAYING.
ONCE THEY BLEW UP THAT DOOR,
THEY SAW THE SHOOTER HAD KILLED
HIMSELF, BUT THEY SAW HIS
ARSENAL, SO THEY KNEW THEY HAD
THEIR MAN.
DAVID?
>> TOM LLAMAS WITH US TONIGHT.
TOM, THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> WHAT WOULD DRIVE SOMEONE TO
TAKE SO MANY INNOCENT LIVES?
THAT'S THE QUESTION WE ASK AFTER
SO MANY OF THESE MASS SHOOTINGS.
TONIGHT, A PORTRAIT OF THE
GUNMAN, NOW COMING INTO FOCUS.
HIS GAMBLING HABIT, HIS FAMILY
HISTORY, AND THIS QUESTION --
DID HE HAVE ANY TIES TO FOREIGN
GROUPS?
REMARKABLY TODAY, HIS FAMILY
SAID THERE WERE NO SIGNS THAT
ANY OF THIS WAS COMING.
HERE'S OUR CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: AS INVESTIGATORS
TONIGHT SEARCH FOR CLUES AT HIS
HOME IN A RETIREMENT COMMUNITY
IN MESQUITE, NEVADA, THE MOTIVE
OF 64-YEAR-OLD STEPHEN PADDOCK,
SEEN IN THIS PHOTO POSTED ON
FACEBOOK BY HIS GIRLFRIEND,
REMAINS A MYSTERY.
>> WE'VE CHECKED ALL THE FEDERAL
DATABASES AND LOCAL DATABASES
AND STATE DATABASES.
AND WE HAD NO KNOWLEDGE OF THIS
INDIVIDUAL.
>> Reporter: HIS FAMILY
REMEMBERS PADDOCK AS A MAN WHO
GREW UP WITHOUT CONVICTION.
>> STEVE HAD NOTHING TO DO WITH
ANY POLITICAL ORGANIZATION,
RELIGIOUS ORGANIZATION, NO WHITE
SUPREMACIST, NOTHING.
>> Reporter: THE FBI SAYS NO
CONNECTION, EITHER, TO ANY
OVERSEAS TERROR GROUP, DESPITE A
CLAIM TODAY BY ISIS.
>> WE HAVE DETERMINED TO THIS
POINT NO CONNECTION WITH THE
INTERNATIONAL TERRORIST GROUP.
>> reporter: YET, FOR SOME
REASON, THIS OTHERWISE
UNREMARKABLE MAN CHECKED INTO
HIS 32nd FLOOR LAS VEGAS HOTEL
ROOM LAST THURSDAY ON A
WELL-PLANNED MISSION TO KILL.
ASSEMBLING A REMARKABLE ARSENAL.
AUTHORITIES HOPE HIS GIRLFRIEND,
MARILOU DANLEY, WHO ONCE WORKED
AS A CASINO HOSTESS FOR HIGH-END
PLAYERS, CAN PROVIDE SOME
INSIGHT.
SHE IS OF FILIPINO DECENT AND
AUTHORITIES SAY SHE IS OVERSEAS
TONIGHT.
ADDING TO THE MYSTERY, FEDERAL
OFFICIALS TELL ABC NEWS PADDOCK
SENT TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
DOLLARS TO SOMEONE IN THE
PHILIPPINES IN THE LAST FEW
WEEKS.
PADDOCK'S ONLY REAL PASSION
APPEARS TO HAVE BEEN GAMBLING.
HIS BROTHER, ERIC, SAYS PADDOCK
RECENTLY WON A $40,000 JACKPOT,
AND WAS A MULTIMILLIONAIRE.
>> HE WAS A WEALTHY GUY AND HE
LIKED TO PLAY VIDEO POKER.
HE PLAYED MULTI-HUNDRED DOLLAR A
HAND VIDEO POKER.
>> Reporter: SIX YEARS AGO,
PADDOCK SUED A LAS VEGAS CASINO.
WHEN HE SLIPPED AND FELL ON A
CASINO FLOOR.
VIDEO SHOWS HIM LATER RUBBING
HIS LEG IN PAIN.
AN ARBITRATOR FOUND IN FAVOR OF
THE CASINO.
UNTIL TODAY, THE ONLY KNOWN
CONNECTION TO CRIME WAS
PADDOCK'S LATE FATHER, A VIOLENT
BANK ROBBER WHO SPENT SEVEN
YEARS IN THE 1960s AS AN FBI
FUGITIVE, DESCRIBED AS
PSYCHOPATHIC, SUICIDAL, ARMED
AND DANGEROUS.
>> AND BRIAN ROSS WITH US FROM
NEW YORK TONIGHT.
AND BRIAN, WE HEARD THERE, IN
YOUR REPORTING, THE SHOOTER'S
BROTHER SAY THAT HE HAD NO
POLITICAL TIES, RELIGIOUS TIES,
NO CRIMINAL HISTORY.
EVEN SAYING TODAY, NO PARKING
TICKETS.
BUT HE DID DESCRIBE HIS BROTHER
AS A MULTIMILLIONAIRE, WHO
PLAYED HIGH STAKES POKER, BUT
EVEN THERE, NO SIGNS YET TONIGHT
OF ANY FINANCIAL PROBLEMS?
>> Reporter: YES, DAVID.
NOT ONLY DID HE HAVE REAL ESTATE
HOLDINGS, BUT HE'S A PRIVATE
PILOT WHO OWNED HIS OWN PLANE.
HIS BROTHER SAID THAT HE MADE
HIS FORTUNE IN REAL ESTATE AND
BY GAMBLING AND THE STOCK
MARKET.
HE'S THE KIND OF HIGH ROLLER THE
CASINOS WELCOME OFTEN WITH OPEN
ARMS, DAVID.
>> ALL RIGHT, BRIAN ROSS AND
YOUR TEAM, OUR THANKS TO YOU, AS
WELL.
>>> AND NEXT HERE TONIGHT, TO
THE VICTIMS OF THIS AWFUL
ATTACK.
OFFICIALS HERE SAY THEY ARE
STILL IDENTIFYING THE DEAD, AND
NOTIFYING NEXT OF KIN.
IT WILL TAKE SOME TIME, BUT WE
ARE BEGINNING TO SEE MANY OF THE
FACES HERE THIS EVENING, THE
LOVED ONES LOST.
TONIGHT, WE ARE LEARNING THE
NAMES OF THOSE WHO LOST THEIR
LIVES AT THE CONCERT HERE
OVERNIGHT.
THERE WAS DANA GARDNER.
FORMER HIGH SCHOOL CHEERLEADER
ANGIE GOMEZ.
28-YEAR-OLD AFGHANISTAN NAVY VET
CHRIS ROYBAL, FROM SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA.
HANNAH AHLERS, A 35-YEAR-OLD
MOTHER OF THREE FROM
MURRIETA, CALIFORNIA.
JORDAN McILDOON FROM CANADA.
HE WOULD HAVE TURNED 24 THIS
WEEK.
SONNY MELTON, A TENNESSEE
HUSBAND AND NURSE.
ON THE RIGHT.
HE DIED WHILE PROTECTING HIS
WIFE, HEATHER, AS BULLETS RAINED
DOWN ON THEM.
"I FELT HIM GET SHOT IN THE
BACK," SHE TOLD REPORTERS.
AMONG THE VICTIMS, TEACHERS,
EDUCATION PROFESSIONALS.
LISA ROMERO, A SECRETARY AT
MIYAMURA HIGH SCHOOL IN
GALLUP, NEW MEXICO.
SUSAN SMITH, AN OFFICE MANAGER
AT VISTA ELEMENTARY IN
SIMI VALLEY, CALIFORNIA.
MANHATTAN BEACH SPECIAL
EDUCATION TEACHER SANDY CASEY,
HER STUDENTS IN MOURNING TODAY.
>> IT WAS PAINFUL.
THERE WAS A LOT OF PAIN ON THE
CAMPUS TODAY.
IT'S A VERY DIFFICULT DAY IN OUR
DISTRICT.
>> Reporter: RACHAEL PARKER, A
MANHATTAN BEACH POLICE RECORDS
TECHNICIAN, LOST HER LIFE.
TWO LAS VEGAS METROPOLITAN
POLICE OFFICERS WERE ALSO HIT,
THE SHERIFF, EMOTIONAL.
>> ONE WAS CRITICAL, BUT HE IS
STABLE, AND ONE OF MY OFFICERS
WAS OFF-DUTY, ATTENDING THE
CONCERT AND LOST HIS LIFE.
>> Reporter: AND AMIDST THE
HORROR, TONIGHT WE ARE ALSO
LEARNING OF ASTONISHING ACTS OF
HEROIC BRAVERY, HUDDLING
TOGETHER, CARRYING THE INJURED
THROUGH THE CHAOS AND TO SAFETY,
USING THEIR OWN BODIES AS
PROTECTION.
>> THERE WERE MEN GOING OVER
THEIR WIVES, THEIR GIRLFRIENDS
TO BLOCK THEM.
THERE WERE LIVES SAVED.
>> Reporter: MICHELLE SCHMIDT
PACKING HER CAR WITH STRANGERS
BEFORE GETTING OUT AND CALLING
HER OWN FAMILY.
>> I CALLED MY HUSBAND AND I
TOLD HIM THAT I LOVED HIM AND MY
LITTLE GIRL, IN CASE I DIDN'T
MAKE IT.
>> Reporter: BRIAN CLAYPOOL
TRAPPED IN A ROOM WITH OTHERS
NEAR THE STAGE.
>> POLICE OFFICERS SCREAMED GO,
GO, AND I RALLIED EVERYBODY OUT
OF THAT ROOM.
I WAS DETERMINED.
I SAID TO MYSELF, THESE GIRLS
AREN'T GOING TO DIE.
I'M NOT GOING TO DIE.
I NEED TO GET HOME TO SEE MY
DAUGHTER.
THIS IS NOT HAPPENING.
NOT HAPPENING.
>> INCREDIBLE BRAVERY, EVEN IN
THE FACE OF THAT GUNFIRE THAT
SIMPLY WOULD NOT LET UP
OVERNIGHT.
>>> THE HOSPITALS AND MEDICAL
TEAMS IN THIS CITY ARE STRETCHED
TO THE LIMITS TONIGHT.
THE MGM RESORTS, OWNER OF THE
MANDALAY AND OTHER HOTELS,
OFFERING HELP TO GUESTS AND
EMPLOYEES.
BUT THEY ALSO TWEETED THIS
TODAY, SAYING WE ARE IN NEED OF
CERTIFIED TRAUMA COUNSELORS.
IF YOU CAN VOLUNTEER YOUR TIME,
PLEASE GO TO CIRCUS CIRCUS.
AND AFTER AN URGENT CALL FOR
BLOOD DONORS, HUNDREDS SHOWING
UP TO HELP.
BUT EVEN AT ONE HOSPITAL HERE IN
LAS VEGAS TONIGHT, THEY REPORTED
THAT AT LEAST 14 OF THE VICTIMS
WERE BROUGHT THERE FOR HELP,
DIED AFTER ARRIVING AT THE E.R.
IT IS AN INCREDIBLE SCENE
UNFOLDING HERE TONIGHT, AND
ABC'S LINSEY DAVIS IS OUTSIDE
UNIVERSITY MEDICAL CENTER IN LAS
VEGAS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE RACE
TO TREAT THE INJURED.
>> SHOTS FIRED FROM MANDALAY
BAY, THERE'S MANY PEOPLE DOWN.
>> Reporter: CONCERT-GOERS
BECAME FIRST RESPONDERS
OVERNIGHT, PUSHING THE WOUNDED
ANY WAY THEY COULD TO GET THEM
HELP.
SO MANY RUSHED TO AREA
HOSPITALS.
>> IT WAS NON-STOP SURGERY AFTER
SURGERY UNTIL ABOUT 4:30, 5:00
THIS MORNING.
>> Reporter: HOSPITALS AND
DOCTORS OVERWHELMED WITH
HUNDREDS OF PATIENTS.
>> WE BROUGHT IN EXTRA TRAUMA
SURGEONS, EXTRA CRITICAL CARE
NURSES, EXTRA, EVEN, YOU KNOW,
EVS FOLKS TO MAKE SURE WE WERE
KEEPING OUR TRAUMA CENTER CLEAN
TO BE ABLE TO MOVE OUR PATIENTS
THROUGH QUICKLY.
>> Reporter: NEVADA'S GOVERNOR
TODAY MADE AN URGENT PLEA.
>> WE NEED BLOOD, SO, IF ANYBODY
CAN CONTRIBUTE BLOOD.
>> Reporter: AND NOW, SO MANY
ARE RESPONDING TO HIS CALL.
>> I HEARD THIS HAPPENED, THE
LEAST I COULD DO, GIVE ME BLOOD
AND I'M O-NEGATIVE, SO, MY BLOOD
IS ACTUALLY THE UNIVERSAL GIVER.
>> Reporter: SOME REPORTEDLY
WAITING UP TO FIVE HOURS TO
DONATE.
>> YOU CAN SEE -- I DON'T EVEN
KNOW IF YOU CAN SEE HOW FAR THIS
LINE GOES.
IT IS INCREDIBLE.
>> LINSEY DAVIS JOINS US
TONIGHT OUTSIDE UNIVERSITY
MEDICAL CENTER.
AND SOME OF THE DOCTORS WE
LEARNED HAD JUST RECEIVED SOME
TRAINING THAT PROVED CRITICAL IN
THEIR RESPONSE HERE?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT,
DAVID.
MANY OF THOSE DOCTORS RECENTLY
HAD JUST UNDERGONE TRAINING WITH
A PHYSICIAN WHO WAS ON-CALL IN
ORLANDO THE NIGHT OF THE PULSE
NIGHTCLUB SHOOTING AND HE WAS
ABLE TO SHARE WITH THEM WHAT
WORKED AND WHAT THEY COULD HAVE
DONE BETTER.
DAVID?
>> LINSEY DAVIS LIVE HERE IN LAS
VEGAS TONIGHT.
ON THE INCREDIBLE WORK DOCTORS
AND NURSES ARE DOING IN THIS
CITY.
>>> THERE IS STILL MUCH MORE
AHEAD ON THIS SPECIAL EDITION OF
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT" THIS
MONDAY.
THE KILLER'S ARSENAL.
WHAT WE HAVE JUST LEARNED
TONIGHT ABOUT THE HEAVY
ARTILLERY DISCOVERED IN THAT
HOTEL ROOM, ON THE 32nd FLOOR.
SOURCES NOW REVEALING THE
ASSORTMENT OF HIGH POWERED
WEAPONS, CAPABLE OF SLICING
THROUGH BODY ARMOR WORN BY
POLICE.
WHAT ELSE POLICE REPORTEDLY
FOUND ONCE THEY WERE INSIDE.
AND ALSO, THE DISCOVERY AT HIS
HOME HERE IN NEVADA.
LEARNING ABOUT THAT LATE TODAY.
>>> AND PRESIDENT TRUMP AND THE
FIRST LADY WITH A MOMENT OF
SILENCE OUTSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE.
AFTER THE PRESIDENT CALLED THIS
AN ACT OF PURE EVIL.
OUR TEAM COVERAGE CONTINUES HERE
IN JUST A MOMENT.
When you have a cold...
stuff happens.
Shut down cold symptoms fast
with Maximum
Strength Alka Seltzer
Plus Liquid Gels.
Only have a sore throat?
Get long-lasting
relief for up to 6 hours
with New Alka Seltzer
Plus Sore Throat Relief.
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
Essential for vinyl,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and further
joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma
and other cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Tears in the stomach
or intestines,
low blood cell counts
and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels
have happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you start
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you
were in a region
where fungal infections
are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
A must for vinyl.
But for you,
one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
>>> WE'RE GOING TO TURN NEXT
TONIGHT TO THAT DISCOVERY ON THE
32nd FLOOR OF MANDALAY BAY.
THE HOTEL ROOM FILLED WITH
WEAPONS AND WHAT WE'VE JUST
LEARNED ABOUT THAT HEAVY
ARTILLERY.
HERE'S ABC'S SENIOR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PIERRE THOMAS
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
INVESTIGATORS FOCUSING ON THE
KILLER'S ARSENAL.
THE SHOOTING FROM THE 32nd FLOOR
COMING FROM AT LEAST ONE RIFLE
FUNCTIONING LIKE AN AUTOMATIC
MACHINE GUN.
THE GUNMAN FIRING BULLETS
CONTINUOUSLY.
LISTEN.
THE UNMISTAKABLE SOUND DIFFERENT
FROM ANYTHING WE'VE HEARD FROM
ALL OTHER RECENT MASS SHOOTINGS.
NONE OF THEM INVOLVING FULLY
AUTOMATIC GUNS.
>> WE ARE STILL GOING THROUGH
THE SEARCH WARRANT ACTIVELY AT
THIS TIME, BUT IT'S IN ACCESS OF
TEN RIFLES.
>> Reporter: SOURCES TELLING ABC
NEWS PADDOCK HAD AT LEAST 16
RIFLES AND HANDGUNS.
ONE OF THEM AN ASSAULT RIFLE,
MODIFIED TO FIRE LIKE A MACHINE
GUN.
SOURCES SAY SOME OF THE RIFLES
WERE HIGH POWERED, CAPABLE OF
SLICING THROUGH POLICE BODY
ARMOR.
>> THIS IS A CLASSIC WMD, THIS
IS A WEAPON AND A MAN OF MASS
DESTRUCTION.
>> Reporter: WE EXAMINED THE
FIRST 90 SECONDS OF THE
MASSACRE, HEARING NEARLY 200
ROUNDS FIRED.
HUNDREDS MORE WITHIN THE
FOLLOWING MINUTES.
PADDOCK TOOK BRIEF PAUSES,
LIKELY TO SWITCH WEAPONS OR
RELOAD.
THE KILLER PERCHED MORE THAN 300
FEET ABOVE.
THE PACKED CROWD, 1,100 FEET
AWAY, PROVIDING A SHOOTING
GALLERY FOR THE KILLER, WITH A
CROWD OF EASY TARGETS REQUIRING
LITTLE SKILL.
DISTURBINGLY, A LAW ENFORCEMENT
SOURCE TELLS ABC NEWS, A CAMERA
WAS DISCOVERED IN THE ROOM,
SUGGESTING THE GUNMAN MAY HAVE
RECORDED HIMSELF.
LATE TODAY, THIS GUN STORE IN
MESQUITE, NEVADA, CONFIRMING
THAT PADDOCK PURCHASED GUNS
HERE.
THE STORE SAYING HE PASSED ALL
NECESSARY BACKGROUND CHECKS.
IT'S UNKNOWN IF THESE WERE THE
GUNS USED IN THE RAMMAGE.
DAVID, AS THE SEARCH CONTINUES,
AUTHORITIES FOUND AN ADDITIONAL
18 WEAPONS AND AN EXPLOSIVE AT
THE SUSPECT'S HOME.
DAVID?
>> PIERRE THOMAS IN WASHINGTON.
>>> AND WHEN WE COME BACK
TONIGHT, WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAID TO THE NATION TODAY ABOUT
WHAT WE WITNESSED HERE IN LAS
VEGAS.
58,007 ste
That's the height of
Mount Everest.
Because each day she
chooses to take the stairs.
At work, at home...
even on the escalator.
That can be hard on
her lower body,
so now she does it
with Dr. Scholl's orthotics.
Clinically proven to
relieve and prevent
foot, knee or
lower back pain,
by reducing
the shock and stress
that travel up her body
with every step she takes.
So keep on climbing, Sarah.
You're killing it.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
Do I use ...one that'sthat
wgood for my teeth? ..
Now I don't have to choose!
From Crest 3D White comes new
Whitening Therapy.
It's our best whitening
technology.
Plus, it has a fortifying
formula to protect your enamel.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
now's the time to get your ducks
in a row.ng 65...
[Quack!]
Medicare only covers about 80%
of your Part B medical expenses.
The rest is up to you.
So think about an AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like any standardized Medicare
Supplement insurance plans,
they help cover some of what
Medicare doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide and learn more.
>>> NEXT TONIGHT HERE, A SOMBER
PRESIDENT TRUMP ADDRESSING THE
NATION TODAY, CALLING THE
MASSACRE HERE IN LAS VEGAS AN
ACT OF PURE EVIL.
HERE'S ABC'S SENIOR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT CECILIA VEGA.
>> Reporter: IN HIS ADDRESS TO
THE NATION TODAY, PRESIDENT
TRUMP STRIKING A SOMBER TONE.
>> IT WAS AN ACT OF PURE EVIL.
>> Reporter: HE NEVER SAID THE
GUNMAN'S NAME, INSTEAD FOCUSING
ON THE VICTIMS AND SURVIVORS.
>> WE ARE PRAYING FOR YOU, AND
WE ARE HERE FOR YOU, AND WE ASK
GOD TO HELP SEE YOU THROUGH THIS
VERY DARK PERIOD.
>> Reporter: AND HE CALLED FOR
UNITY.
>> IT IS OUR LOVE THAT DEFINES
US TODAY, AND ALWAYS WILL,
FOREVER.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT
LEADING A MOMENT OF SILENCE,
ORDERING FLAGS FLOWN AT HALF
STAFF AND PERSONALLY CALLING THE
LAS VEGAS SHERIFF.
>> THE FAST RESPONSE THAT YOU
GAVE SAVED HUNDREDS OF
ADDITIONAL PEOPLE FROM BEING
KILLED.
>> Reporter: BUT WAS THIS
TERRORISM?
THE WHITE HOUSE WON'T SAY.
DOES THE PRESIDENT BELIEVE THAT
WHAT HAPPENED AMOUNTS TO AN ACT
OF DOMESTIC TERRORISM?
>> WE ARE STILL IN A
FACT-FINDING MISSION.
IT WOULD BE PREMATURE TO WEIGH
IN ON SOMETHING LIKE THAT BEFORE
WE HAVE ANY MORE FACTS.
>> AND THE PRESIDENT HEADS TO
LAS VEGAS ON WEDNESDAY, WHERE HE
WILL THANK FIRST RESPONDERS.
HE WILL MEET WITH VICTIM'S
FAMILY MEMBERS, BUT FIRST, THAT
TRIP TO PUERTO RICO TO SURVEY
THE DAMAGE THERE, DAVID.
THAT HAPPENS TOMORROW.
>> CECILIA, THANK YOU.
>>> AND WHAT THE SHERIFF HERE
REVEALED JUST A SHORT TIME AGO,
IN A MOMENT.
ot
from our eyes every day.
I should know.
I have Chronic Dry Eye
caused by reduced
tear production
due to inflammation.
So I use RESTASIS MultiDose®.
It helps me make more
of my own tears,
with continued use,
twice a day, every day.
It's also what I prescribe
to my patients
who have this condition.
RESTASIS MultiDose®
helps increase your
eyes' natural ability
to produce tears,
which may be reduced
by inflammation
due to Chronic Dry Eye.
RESTASIS MultiDose® did
not increase tear production
in patients using
anti-inflammatory eye drops
or tear duct plugs.
To help avoid eye injury
and contamination,
do not touch the bottle tip
to your eye or other surfaces.
Wait 15 minutes after use
before inserting
contact lenses.
The most common side effect
is a temporary
burning sensation.
Ask your eye doctor about
RESTASIS MultiDose®.
Savings Card
holders pay as
little as $0
for three bottles.
Start saving today
at restasis.com.
♪
♪You are loved
DEPEND REAL FIT BRIEFS
FEATURE BREATHABLE,
COTTON-LIKE FABRIC.
IN SITUATIONS LIKE THIS,
THERE'S NO TIME
FOR DISTRACTIONS.
IT'S NOT ENOUGH
TO THINK I'M READY.
I NEED TO KNOW I'M READY.
NO MATTER WHAT LIES AHEAD.
GET A FREE SAMPLE
AT DEPEND.COM.
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night,
so he got home safe.
Yeah, my dad says our
insurance doesn't have that.
What?!
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
My shoulders carry
Some I deserve
Others I don't
But in the end
Only one name really matters
Because shoulders were made for
greatness, not dandruff
This
This is my body of proof.
Proof of less joint pain
and clearer skin.
This is my body of proof that I
can take on psoriatic
arthritis with HUMIRA.
HUMIRA works by targeting and
helping to block a specific
source of inflammation that
contributes to both joint and
skin symptoms.
It's proven to help relieve
pain, stop further joint damage,
and clear skin in many adults.
HUMIRA is the #1
prescribed biologic
for psoriatic arthritis.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested for
TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas where certain
fungal infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
Want more proof? Ask your
rheumatologist about HUMIRA.
What's your body of proof?
>>> THE SHERIFF HERE, JOSEPH
LOMBARDO, REVEALING A SHORT TIME
AGO THE DEATH TOLL IS NOW UP TO
59.
HUNDREDS IN
The energy conscious
Whopeople among usle?
Say small actions can add up
to something... humongous.
A little thing here.
A little thing there.
Starts to feel like a badge
maybe millions can wear.
Who are all these caretakers,
advocates too?
Turns out, it's Californians
It's me and it's you.
Don't stop now,
It's easy to add to the routine.
Join Energy Upgrade California
And do your thing.
[male narrator]
Visit USO dot org slash force
to learn how you can be the
force behind the forces.
>>> TONIGHT, OUR SPECIAL EDITION
OF "WORLD NEWS TONIGHT,"
MASSACRE IN LAS VEGAS.
INSIDE THE ATTACK.
GUNFIRE AND PANIC AT AN OUTDOOR
MUSIC FESTIVAL.
THIS EVENING, INVESTIGATORS ON
THE SCENE OF THE GUNMAN'S HOME.
SENDING A ROBOT TO THE DOOR.
YOU WILL HEAR FROM THE GUNMAN'S
FAMILY, STUNNED.
WHAT THEY REVEAL, SAYING HE HAD
NO CRIMINAL PAST.
>>> GOOD EVENING AGAIN FROM LAS
VEGAS, AND WE WELCOME YOU BACK
TO THIS SPECIAL EDITION OF
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT."
AND WE BEGIN THIS EXTENDED
PROGRAM WITH NEW DETAILS, NEW
REPORTING LATE THIS AFTERNOON,
ABOUT THE LIFE OF STEPHEN
PADDOCK.
HE'S THE SUSPECT, THE MAN WHO
ASSEMBLED A MASSIVE ARSENAL,
POLICE SAY IN A HOTEL ROOM ON
THE 32nd FLOOR OF THE BUILDING
RIGHT BEHIND ME, PERPETRATING
THE WORST MASS SHOOTING IN THE
UNITED STATES IN MODERN TIMES.