HAPPY FATHER'S DAY EVERYBODY.
>> FROM ALL OF US HERE, THANKS
FOR WATCHING.
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS."
TONIGHT, STRANDED.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF FAMILIES
WONDER, WILL THEY HAVE HOMES TO
RETURN TO?
WE'RE ON THE FRONT LINES OF
THESE HISTORIC FIRES, THE JETS
RACING ACROSS THE SKY, TRYING TO
GET AHEAD.
PLUS, THE NEW SEVERE WEATHER
THREAT AS WE HEAD INTO THE
WEEKEND.
>>> THE DRAMATIC DECK COLLAPSE.
THE INJURIES, THE CLOSE CALLS
TONIGHT.
>> THERE'S A LEAST A HUNDRED
PEOPLE IN THE WATER.
>>> WE'VE SEEN IT BEFORE.
THE FLOOR BENEATH, SUDDENLY
GONE.
TONIGHT, THE HIDDEN WARNING
SIGNS, THE SIGNALS YOUR DECK
COULD BE NEXT.
>>> AND "MADE IN AMERICA."
THE SMALL-TOWN INVENTOR.
THE FATHER AND HIS GENIUS TOOL.
WAS HIS IDEA STOLEN?
TONIGHT "WORLD NEWS" VIEWERS AND
THE VICTORY JUST IN TIME FOR
FATHER'S DAY.
>> MADE IN AMERICA!
>> GOOD EVENING, AND THANKS FOR
BEING HERE.
DIANE HAS THE EVENING OFF.
WE BEGIN IN THE WEST TONIGHT IN
COLORADO, WHERE, FOR TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF FAMILIES, THERE IS
AN UNKNOWN HEADING INTO THIS
HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
WILL THEY HAVE A HOME TO RETURN
TO?
THIS IS FAST-MOVING.
THIS EVENING, TAKE A LOOK.
A NORMAN ROCKWELL NEIGHBORHOOD,
JUST ONE HOME SPARED THERE.
TREES COVERED IN ASH.
JUST THE SKELETON OF A HOME
THERE.
THEN THIS, TWO PEOPLE HUGGING,
ONLY THE FIREPLACE STILL
STANDING TONIGHT.
AND ONE MORE SIGN OF THE INTENSE
HEAT OF THESE FIRES, THESE
MAILBOXES, MELTED IN AN INSTANT.
TONIGHT OUR TEAM IS ON THE FRONT
LINES.
ABC'S CLAYTON SANDELL LEADS US
OFF NEAR COLORADO SPRINGS.
>> Reporter: FOR FIREFIGHTERS
LOCKED IN AN EPIC BATTLE, TODAY
A GIFT FROM THE SKY.
THE WEATHER, HELPING QUENCH THIS
MONSTROUS FIRE THAT'S KILLED TWO
PEOPLE, DESTROYED ALMOST 400
HOMES AND TURNED ENTIRE
NEIGHBORHOODS INTO CHARRED
WASTELANDS.
>> WE GOT OUR TAILS KICKED FOR A
COUPLE DAYS.
AND I THINK TODAY WE DELIVERED
SOME BLOWS AND WE'VE GOT SOME
GOOD NEWS TO GIVE OUT.
>> Reporter: THE SHERIFF
BELIEVES SOMEONE STARTED THIS
FIRE, BUT DOESN'T KNOW IF BY
ACCIDENT OR ON PURPOSE.
AND FOR NOW, THE FIRE ZONE IS
STILL TOO DANGEROUS TO LET
PEOPLE GO HOME.
>> YOU DON'T KNOW IF WE'RE GOING
TO EVEN HAVE A HOME.
>> Reporter: LIKE 40,000 OTHER
FIRE REFUGEES, CINDY AND HER
FAMILY NEED A PLACE TO SAY, BUT
THERE'S NO ROOM AT THE INN.
ANY INN.
>> BACK ON THE ROAD AGAIN.
>> Reporter: TODAY THEY PACKED
UP AGAIN, FORCED TO DRIVE TO THE
ONLY HOTEL THEY COULD FIND, TWO
HOURS AWAY.
>> WE HAVE OUR FAMILY, AND THAT
IS -- IF ANYTHING, WE HAVE EACH
OTHER AND WE'VE ALWAYS BEEN ABLE
TO RELY ON EACH OTHER.
>> Reporter: EXACTLY ONE YEAR
AGO, THE MASSIVE WALDO CANYON
FIRE JUST A FEW MILES AWAY
TURNED SHAWNA'S HOUSE INTO
ASHES.
>> THIS IS MY HOUSE.
>> SO THIS IS THE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: TODAY SHE'S
REBUILDING, OFFERING HOPE TO ALL
THOSE FAMILIES SUFFERING
TONIGHT.
>> THERE'S JUST SO MUCH LOSS,
AND THAT IT DOES GET BETTER.
IT'S A JOURNEY OF HEALING.
IT TAKES TIME.
>> Reporter: FOR THOMAS, SOME OF
THAT HEALING BEGAN WHEN HE WAS
REUNITED WITH THE HORSE HE HAD
TO LEAVE BEHIND.
>> I'M REAL EXCITED TO SEE HIM.
I THOUGHT I LOST HIM.
>> Reporter: THIS ROADBLOCK HAS
BEEN UP ALL DAY.
BUT NOW THAT THE WEATHER IS
STARTING TO COOPERATE, THEY'RE
TAKING IT DOWN AND SOME PEOPLE
WILL BE ALLOWED TO GO HOME.
>> CLAYTON SANDELL, THANK YOU.
>>> FROM THE FIRES IN THE WEST,
TO THE EAST, TO THE STORMFRONT
THAT LEFT A TRAIL OF
DESTRUCTION.
SEVERAL DEATHS ARE BEING BLAMED
ON FALLING TREES.
ABC'S GINGER ZEE ON THE REAL
DANGER AND THE NEW SEVERE
WEATHER THREAT AS WE HEAD INTO
THE WEEKEND.
>> Reporter: THE RAIN FELL IN
SHEETS.
IN WEST VIRGINIA, FLASH
FLOODING.
A RESCUER, HERE TRYING TO GET A
CHILD TO SAFETY.
DOWNED TREES KILLING AT LEAST
THREE PEOPLE.
MUCH OF THE TREE DAMAGE BEING
BLAMED IN PART ON ALREADY
SATURATED SOIL.
YOUR TYPICAL SUBURBAN 85-FOOT
TREE HAS ROOTS THAT EXTEND THREE
TO FOUR FEET INTO THE GROUND.
THREE TO FOUR INCHES OF RAIN CAN
SOFTEN THE SOIL ENOUGH THAT
WINDS CAN EASILY KNOCK IT DOWN.
WATCH IT IN REAL TIME.
WHEN A STORM HITS, HAVE SHELTER
THAT YOU KNOW IS SAFE, EVEN IF
TREES FALL INTO YOUR HOME.
MORE DAMAGING WINDS ROLLING
THROUGH PARTS OF THE PLAINS
TONIGHT.
HERE'S WHO NEEDS TO BE ON ALERT.
EASTERN NEBRASKA, PARTS OF
WESTERN IOWA, AND THAT AREA YOU
SEE SHADED THERE, THEN MOVE TO
THE EAST AS WE GO INTO SATURDAY.
KANSAS CITY TO CHICAGO AND
NORTHEAST COLORADO FOR ISOLATED
TORNADOES, DAMAGING WINDS AND
HAIL.
>> AND WE KNOW YOU'LL BE ON THE
WATCH THROUGH "GMA" IN THE
MORNING.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE'LL MOVE ON TO THE MAJOR
HEADLINE INVOLVING SYRIA AND
WORD THAT THE U.S. IS NOW READY
TO ARM THE REBELS.
CONVINCED THAT PRESIDENT ASSAD
USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS AGAINST
HIS OWN PEOPLE.
TONIGHT OUR TEAM TACKLING THE
BIG QUESTIONS.
JUST WHAT KIND OF WEAPONS ARE WE
GIVING?
WHO ARE WE GIVING THEM TO?
AND WHAT DOES THIS MEAN FOR
AMERICA AFTER THE WARS IN IRAQ
AND AFGHANISTAN?
IS SYRIA NOW NEXT?
WE HAVE TEAM COVERAGE BEGINNING
WITH ALEX MARQUARDT, ON THE
SYRIAN BORDER.
HE LEADS US OFF.
>> Reporter: IT HAS NOT BEEN AN
EVEN FIGHT.
FOR MORE THAN TWO YEARS,
PRESIDENT ASSAD'S ARMY
INFLICTING UNTOLD DEATH AND
DESTRUCTION, POUNDING AWAY WITH
TANKS AND HEAVY ARTILLERY.
WHILE THE REBELS RESPOND WITH
MORTARS AND ROCKET-PROPELLED
GRENADES.
THE REGIME'S JETS STREAK ACROSS
THE SKY.
AS THE REBELS TRY TO TAKE THEM
DOWN WITH WEAPONS THEY'VE
STOLEN.
SOME REBEL GROUPS ARE WELL
EQUIPPED, WHILE MANY ARE
DESPERATE FOR AMMUNITION AND
RESORT TO HOME-MADE WEAPONS LIKE
THIS GIANT SLINGSHOT.
WE'VE SEEN THE SPARSE REBEL
ARSENAL FIRST HAND.
THE REGIME HAS TANKS, PLANES,
HELICOPTERS AND YOU JUST HAVE
AK-47s AND RPGs.
HOW CAN YOU DEFEAT THEM IN
ALEPPO?
"WE HAVE GOD ALMIGHTY," HE SAID,
"WHO IS FIGHTING WITH US."
AMERICA NOW SAYS IT WILL SEND
WEAPONS TO THE REBELS, SMALL
ARMS, NOT THE ROCKETS NEEDED TO
TAKE OUT TANKS OR PLANES.
TONIGHT, WE MET A REBEL LEADER
WHO SAYS, THAT'S NOT ENOUGH.
THE WEAPONS WON'T BE GOOD ENOUGH
FOR US TO WIN, HE SAID.
I'M AFRAID THEY'LL JUST MAKE THE
WAR GO ON LONGER.
>> Reporter: THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION HAS BEEN HESITANT
TO OFFER BIGGER WEAPONS, KNOWING
HOW DISORGANIZED THE REBEL
FORCES ARE AND RECOGNIZING THAT
SOME OF THE STRONGEST AMONG
THEM HAVE SWORN ALLEGIANCE TO
AL QAEDA.
THE FEAR BEING SOME OF THESE
AMERICAN WEAPONS COULD EASILY
FALL INTO THE WRONG HANDS.
DAVID?
>> ONE OF THE MAJOR CONCERNS.
I WANT TO BRING IN ABC'S MARTHA
RADDATZ.
WE WERE ALL TALKING EARLIER
ABOUT FEARS ACROSS THIS COUNTRY
THAT THIS COULD BE A SLIPPERY
SLOPE, THAT THIS COULD BE
ANOTHER WAR WE'RE HEADED INTO.
>> WELL, THE WHITE HOUSE HAS
SAID EMPHATICALLY, NO BOOTS ON
THE GROUND IN SYRIA.
BUT I DO THINK MANY AMERICANS
WORRY ABOUT THAT SLIPPERY SLOPE.
WE WERE AT WAR IN IRAQ FOR
NEARLY TEN YEARS, ALTHOUGH WE
WERE TOLD IT WOULD BE OVER IN NO
TIME.
AND WE ARE STILL IN AFGHANISTAN
AFTER NEARLY 12 YEARS.
WE HAVE LEARNED LESSONS FROM
THOSE CONFLICTS AND NO ONE LIKES
TO SEE SUCH HORRIBLE, HORRIBLE
SLAUGHTER IN SYRIA, BUT THERE
ARE MANY MILITARY OFFICERS I'VE
SPOKEN TO WHO ARE CONCERNED
ABOUT THE GOAL IN SYRIA, WITH
THE SMALL ARMS, AND EVEN MORE
CONCERNED, DAVID, ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENS NEXT IF THEY DON'T DO
ANY GOOD.
>> ALL RIGHT, MARTHA, THANK YOU.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO MOVE ON NOW
TO THE HEADLINE FROM THE
HEARTLAND THIS EVENING, WHAT'S
BEING CALLED THE NAZI NEXT DOOR.
A TOP COMMANDER IN THE SS DURING
WORLD WAR II, LIVING IN PLAIN
SIGHT.
HERE'S ABC'S DAN HARRIS.
>> GET OFF THE PROPERTY NOW!
>> Reporter: THIS WAS THE
REACTION THE ASSOCIATED PRESS
GOT AT THIS MODEST HOUSE IN
MINNEAPOLIS, HOME TO AN ALLEGED
NAZI WAR CRIMINAL.
NEWS THAT STUNNED NEIGHBORS.
>> WOW, WHAT A BACKGROUND.
IT'S A SHOCKER.
>> Reporter: HE IS MICHAEL
KARKOC, 94.
AN ASSOCIATED PRESS
INVESTIGATION SHOWS THAT KARKOC
WAS A TOP COMMANDER IN A UNIT
LED BY THE NAZI SS, ACCUSED OF
BURNING VILLAGES IN THE UKRAINE
AND KILLING DOZENS OF WOMEN AND
CHILDREN.
KARKOC CAME TO AMERICA IN 1949,
LYING TO OFFICIALS ON THIS
QUESTIONNAIRE, TELLING THEM HE
NEVER SERVED IN THE MILITARY.
SINCE THEN, HE'S LIVED OPENLY IN
MINNEAPOLIS, RAISING A FAMILY,
AND SERVING AS A LEADER IN THE
LOCAL UKRAINIAN COMMUNITY.
REPORTS OF HIS DARK PAST ONLY
CAME TO LIGHT BECAUSE OF AN
AMATEUR NAZI HUNTER OVER IN
ENGLAND WHO STUMBLED ACROSS THE
INFORMATION AND TIPPED OFF THE
A.P.
WHEN CONFRONTED BY THE A.P., ALL
KARKOC WOULD SAY WAS, QUOTE, I
DON'T THINK I CAN EXPLAIN.
HE MAY HAVE TO.
EXPERTS SAY HE COULD BE DEPORTED
TO FACE TRIAL FOR WAR CRIMES.
DAN HARRIS, ABC NEWS, NEW YORK.
>> OUR THANKS TO DAN HARRIS
TONIGHT.
>>> NOW TO THE FRIGHTENING SCENE
IN MIAMI.
NEW HERE THIS EVENING, THE 911
CALLS AFTER THE DECK AT A
POPULAR SPORTS BAR, PACKED WITH
FANS, CHEERING ON THE MIAMI
HEAT, SUDDENLY COLLAPSED.
TONIGHT ABC'S MATT GUTMAN ON THE
HIDDEN SIGNALS YOUR OWN DECK
COULD BE NEXT.
>> Reporter: CHEERS MUTATING
INTO SCREAMS.
ARE YOU OKAY?
>> Reporter: HEARD TONIGHT ON
THESE 911 CALLS.
>> THE DOCK FELL IN THE WATER.
>> THE WHOLE DECK AND THE WHOLE
BAR FELL AND EVERYONE'S IN THE
WATER AND I DON'T KNOW IF
THEY'RE OKAY.
>> Reporter: THE DECK CRASHING
INTO THE BAY --
>> IS EVERYBODY OUT?
>> Reporter: -- DUMPING 100
PATRONS PACKED IN TO WATCH THE
NBA FINALS.
WE TOOK A BOAT TO SURVEY THE
DAMAGE MORE CLOSELY.
YOU CAN SEE THE FORCE OF THE
COLLAPSE FOLDED THE CONCRETE
PILINGS LIKE A BOOK, SMASHING
EVERYBODY INSIDE.
NO FATALITIES, BUT 24 PEOPLE
RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THIS HAPPENS
MORE THAN YOU THINK.
POSING FOR THE PROM.
LAST MONTH, THIS WEDDING PARTY
TUMBLING INTO A LAKE.
HOW TO SPOT THE WARNING SIGNS ON
YOUR OWN DECK.
LOOK FOR CRACKED AND ROTTED
WOODS.
DECKS POORLY BOLTED TO THE
BUILDING.
CORROSION.
AND LISTEN FOR CREAKING.
SOMETHING WITNESSES IN MIAMI
TOLD US THEY HEARD.
>> IT STARTED CREAKING AND IT
COLLAPSED.
>> Reporter: MATT GUTMAN, ABC
NEWS, MIAMI.
>> GREAT TIPS FROM MATT TONIGHT.
THANKS.
>>> NOW TO "MADE IN AMERICA"
THIS EVENING AND A VICTORY JUST
IN TIME FOR FATHER'S DAY.
IT'S A DAVID-AND-GOLIATH STORY
WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING FOR MONTHS.
THAT AMERICAN INVENTOR.
TONIGHT THE "MADE IN AMERICA"
TEAM GETTING ACTION WITH HELP
FROM SO MANY OF YOU.
IT WAS LAST YEAR WE TOOK YOU TO
CABOT, PENNSYLVANIA, PROUDLY
FLYING THEIR AMERICAN FLAGS AND
MAKING THEIR AMERICAN INVENTION.
>> YOU WERE DETERMINED TO MAKE
IT IN AMERICA?
>> YES, THAT WAS MY GOAL FROM
DAY ONE.
>> Reporter: DAN BROWN INVENTED
THE BIONIC WRENCH.
SEARS WAS HIS BIGGEST SELLER.
>> FOR ONLY $19.99 AT SEARS.
THEN SUDDENLY HE SAID THE DEAL
ENDED.
>> DID YOU WONDER WHAT WAS GOING
ON?
>> OF COURSE, WE DID.
>> BUT THEN HE SAYS THERE WAS
SOMETHING FISHY.
HE DISCOVERED THERE WAS A
ANOTHER WRENCH ON THAT SHELF
INSTEAD, ONE MADE IN CHINA AND
SOLD UNDER THE SEARS BRAND
CRAFTSMAN.
SIDE BY SIDE, LISTEN TO THE OLD
AD FOR DAN'S WRENCH.
>> BECAUSE IT GRIPS ON ALL SIX
SIDES.
>> THE NEW ONE.
>> THE SIX LOCKING JAWS.
>> OR THIS PART OF THE PITCH.
>> IT'S 14 WRENCHES IN ONE.
>> AND THEN THE NEW WRENCH.
>> REPLACES 14 WRENCHES WITH A
SINGLE TOOL.
>> WHAT DID YOU THINK WHEN YOU
SAW IT?
>> IT'S A KNOCK-OFF.
NO QUESTION.
>> DAN SUED SEARS.
THE CASE IS STILL ONGOING.
SEARS IN A STATEMENT TO US,
SAYING THEY DIDN'T STEAL
ANYTHING.
"THE ALLEGATIONS MADE BY MR.
BROWN SIMPLY ARE UNTRUE."
BUT WITH SALES SLOWING AND THE
COST OF THE LAWSUIT, HE HAD IT
LAY-OFF 30 WORKERS.
>> TEARS ME APART.
WHAT MORE CAN WE DO?
WE DON'T WANT TO STOP.
WE'LL HAVE NO JOBS.
>> WE HAVEN'T FORGOTTEN DAN OR
HIS WRENCH.
SEVEN MONTHS LATER WE MET HIM IN
PARK AVENUE IN NEW YORK CITY.
GREAT TO SEE YOU.
AND WHERE DID WE MEET HIM?
WALGREEN'S.
YOU FOUND WHERE IT IS?
>> IT'S BACK HERE.
HEADED STRAIGHT TO AISLE TEN.
>> WE MADE PARK AVENUE.
>> AND THERE WAS HIS DISPLAY.
HALFWAY SOLD OUT ALREADY.
IN FACT, HE'S IN 4,600
WALGREEN'S STORES ALL OVER
AMERICA TONIGHT, JUST IN TIME
FOR FATHER'S DAY.
>> AS YOU CONTINUE TO FIGHT WITH
ANOTHER GIANT RETAILER --
>> YES.
>> -- YOU FOUND A NEW ONE?
>> RIGHT.
>> AND WHO HELPED SEAL THE DEAL?
SO MANY OF YOU.
>> I SAW YOUR STORY ON "WORLD
NEWS" LAST NIGHT.
>> I SAW YOUR BIONIC WRENCH ON
"WORLD NEWS" MADE IN AMERICA.
>> PART OF HIS PITCH, IT WAS NOT
ONLY THE QUALITY OF THE WRENCH,
BUT HE TOLD US, HE'S GOT
THOUSANDS WHO WANT THE WRENCH
ALREADY.
LIKE RUTH WHO ASKED WHAT MANY
ARE ASKING FROM THEIR HOMETOWN.
>> IS YOUR WRENCH CARRIED IN ANY
STORES IN SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA?
>> ARE YOU IN A WALGREEN'S IN
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA?
>> YEAH, WE'RE IN CALIFORNIA.
WE HOPE RUTH IS WATCHING
TONIGHT.
>> MADE IN AMERICA!
>> HOPE RUTH IS WATCHING.
AND DAD IF YOU'RE WATCHING,
GUESS WHAT I BOUGHT YOU FOR
FATHER'S DAY.
>>> STILL MUCH MORE AHEAD ON
"WORLD NEWS" THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
THE RED HOT DEBATE, WE WANT TO
KNOW WHAT YOU THINK THIS EVENING
ABOUT THE MOTHERS WHO CHOOSE TO
MOVE OUT AND LEAVE THEIR
CHILDREN BEHIND.
THE ASTONISHING NUMBERS AND
ABC'S ELIZABETH VARGAS WITH THE
TOUGH QUESTIONS.
>> DO YOU LOVE YOUR CHILDREN?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
>> MORE THAN YOURSELF?
>> HOW SHE ANSWERS THAT QUESTION
RIGHT AFTER THE BREAK.
>>> AND THEN LATER TONIGHT, TAKE
A CLOSE LOOK AT THIS IMAGE.
TRAVELING AT LIGHTNING SPEED
ACROSS FACEBOOK AND BEYOND, A
COUPLE ABOUT TO BECOME HUSBAND
AND WIFE, HIS LAST WISH BEFORE
WALKING DOWN THAT AISLE.
THE WHEAT IN EVERY Mini-Wheat
HAS GOTTA BE JUST RIGHT.
PERFECT GOLDEN COLOR.
RICH IN FIBER.
MY DAD TAUGHT ME,
AND I TAUGHT MY SON OUT THERE.
MORNING, PA.
WAIT...
WHO'S DRIVING THE...?
♪ 99 BUSHELS OF WHEAT ON
THE FARM, 99 BUSHELS OF WHEAT ♪
[ Male Announcer ]
YEP, THERE'S 8 LAYERS
OF WHOLE GRAIN FIBER IN
THOSE Mini-Wheats® BISCUITS...
TO HELP KEEP YOU FULL...
♪ 45 BUSHELS OF WHEAT
...ALL MORNING LONG.
THERE'S A BIG BREAKFAST...
[ Mini ] YEE HAW!
...IN THOSE FUN
LITTLE BISCUITS.
YEAH...
TRY NEW Alka Seltzer
Fruit Chews.
THEY WORK FAST ON HEARTBURN
AND TASTE AWESOME.
THESE ARE GOOD.
TOLD YA!
I'M FEELING BETTER ALREADY.
[ Male Announcer ]
NEW Alka Seltzer Fruits Chews.
ENJOY THE RELIEF!
♪
HANDS, FOR HOLDING.
FEET, KICKING.
BETTER THINGS THAN
THE JOINT PAIN AND SWELLING
OF MODERATE TO SEVERE
RHEUMATOID ARTHRITIS.
IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO MANAGE YOUR RA,
NOW MAY BE THE TIME
TO ASK ABOUT XELJANZ.
XELJANZ (TOFACITINIB)
IS A SMALL PILL
FOR ADULTS
WITH MODERATE TO SEVERE RA
FOR WHOM METHOTREXATE
DID NOT WORK WELL.
XELJANZ IS AN RA MEDICINE
THAT CAN ENTER CELLS
AND DISRUPT JAK PATHWAYS,
THOUGHT TO PLAY A ROLE
IN THE INFLAMMATION
THAT COMES WITH RA.
XELJANZ CAN LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS,
INCLUDING TUBERCULOSIS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL
INFECTIONS AND CANCERS
HAVE HAPPENED
IN PATIENTS TAKING XELJANZ.
DON'T START TAKING XELJANZ
IF YOU HAVE
ANY KIND OF INFECTION,
UNLESS OK WITH YOUR DOCTOR.
TEARS IN THE STOMACH
OR INTESTINES,
LOW BLOOD CELL COUNTS
AND HIGHER LIVER TESTS
AND CHOLESTEROL LEVELS
HAVE HAPPENED.
YOUR DOCTOR
SHOULD PERFORM BLOOD TESTS,
INCLUDING CERTAIN LIVER TESTS
BEFORE YOU START,
AND WHILE
YOU ARE TAKING XELJANZ.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL INFECTIONS
ARE COMMON,
AND IF YOU HAVE HAD TB,
HEPATITIS B OR C,
OR ARE PRONE TO INFECTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL THE MEDICINES YOU TAKE,
AND IF YOU ARE PREGNANT,
OR PLAN TO BE.
TAKEN TWICE DAILY,
XELJANZ CAN REDUCE
THE JOINT PAIN AND SWELLING
OF MODERATE TO SEVERE RA,
EVEN WITHOUT METHOTREXATE.
ASK IF XELJANZ
IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
THEY'RE ABOUT 10 TIMES SOFTER
AND MAY HAVE SURFACE PORES
WHERE BACTERIA CAN MULTIPLY.
POLIDENT KILLS 99.99%
OF ODOR CAUSING BACTERIA
AND HELPS DISSOLVE STAINS
SO DENTURES ARE CLEANER,
FRESHER, AND BRIGHTER.
[ Male Announcer ] POLIDENT.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO TURN NOW TO
THE DEBATE OVER MOMS WHO CHOOSE
TO LEAVE THEIR CHILDREN BEHIND,
MANY OF THEM ARGUING IT MAKES
THEM A BETTER MOM.
HERE'S MY "20/20" ANCHOR,
ELIZABETH VARGAS.
>> Reporter: IN 2008,
TALYAA LIERA MOVED TO SEATTLE
AFTER A DIVORCE, LEAVING HER
THREE CHILDREN TO LIVE WITH
THEIR DAD 2,800 MILES AWAY IN
PENNSYLVANIA.
TALYAA SPENDS HER DAYS PAINTING,
WRITING, MAKING MUSIC, AND
PRACTICING MARTIAL ARTS.
"MOTHERING," WELL, THAT'S DONE
FROM AFAR.
>> I'LL WALK YOU THROUGH THE
STEPS OF SCRAMBLED EGGS.
>> Reporter: OH SURE, SHE EMAILS
RECIPES FOR THEM TO COOK
THEMSELVES AND SHE STAYS IN
TOUCH ON THE PHONE AND VIA
SKYPE.
>> YOU SOUND A LITTLE LIKE YOU
HAVE A COLD.
>> YEAH, I HAVE A COLD.
>> Reporter: BUT THEY ONLY SEE
EACH OTHER IN PERSON AROUND ONCE
A YEAR.
>> OKAY, WELL, MISS SWEET CAKE.
>> Reporter: I KNOW A LOT OF
PEOPLE LISTENING TO THIS WILL
WANT TO KNOW, DO YOU LOVE YOUR
CHILDREN?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
MORE THAN ANYTHING.
>> MORE THAN YOURSELF?
>> SHOULD A MOTHER LOVE HER
CHILDREN MORE THAN HERSELF?
>> Reporter: TAYLAA SAYS,
CONFLICT BETWEEN HER AND HER
HUSBAND WAS CAUSING ENORMOUS
STRESS FOR HER AND THE KIDS.
AND THAT LEAVING THEM WAS THE
ONLY WAY TO EASE THAT TENSION.
>> WHY SO FAR AWAY?
WHY DID YOU HAVE TO MOVE 3,000
AWAY?
>> WELL, AT THAT POINT, WHETHER
IT WAS TEN MILES OR 3,000 MILES
OR THREE MILLION MILES, IT
REALLY WOULDN'T MAKE ANY
DIFFERENCE.
>> Reporter: WELL, BECAUSE AT
TEN MILES, YOU COULD STILL SEE
THE KIDS AND BE A PRESENCE IN
THEIR LIVES.
>> RIGHT, BUT IN ORDER FOR THE
CONFLICT TO GO AWAY, THERE HAD
TO BE A CERTAIN DISTANCE.
>> Reporter: DAVID SAYS THERE
WAS NO CONFLICT AND HE SAYS
TALYAA'S SUDDEN TRANSFORMATION
FROM STAY-AT-HOME MOM TO WEST
COAST BOHEMIAN WAS ASTONISHING.
AND HIS FRIENDS?
>> THEY WERE SHOCKED.
IT'S LIKE, HOW COULD A MOM LEAVE
HER CHILDREN LIKE THIS?
>> THIS IS SOMETHING MY PARTNER
FROM "20/20," ELIZABETH VARGAS
WITH US HERE NOW.
YOU DIVE INTO THIS TONIGHT.
YOU WERE TELLING ME THAT
DIVORCED DADS WHO DO THIS DON'T
FACE NEARLY THE SAME BACKLASH.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
SHE SAYS THERE'S A DOUBLE
STANDARD THAT EXISTS.
SHE SAID, EVEN THOUGH SHE
DOESN'T FIT THE MOLD OF A
PERFECT MOM, SHE DOES FIT THE
MOLD OF A TERRIFIC DIVORCED DAD.
SO, INTERESTING TO HEAR WHAT
THEY HAVE TO SAY, YOU CAN MAKE
YOUR OWN JUDGEMENT.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE WILL.
WE WANT EVERYONE TO WEIGH IN ON
THIS.
MORE OF HER REPORTING TONIGHT ON
"20/20," WITH PARENTS LIKE
THESE, AT 10:00/9:00 CENTRAL.
ELIZABETH, WE'LL SEE YOU THEN.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, WHY THIS
IMAGE OF MICHAEL FELL PDS ON A
DIVING BOARD HAS SO MANY FOLKS
WONDERING IF HE'S ABOUT TO TAKE
THE PUNGE.
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
PHELPS ON A
DIVING BOARD HAS SO MANY FOLKS
WONDERING IF HE'S ABOUT TO TAKE
THE PUNGE.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
EVERY DAY WE'RE WORKING TO
AND TO KEEP OUR COMMITMENTS.
AND WE'VE MADE A BIG
COMMITMENT TO AMERICA.
BP SUPPORTS NEARLY
250,000 JOBS HERE.
THROUGH ALL OF OUR
ENERGY OPERATIONS,
WE INVEST MORE IN THE U.S. THAN
ANY OTHER PLACE IN THE WORLD.
IN FACT, WE'VE INVESTED
OVER $55 BILLION HERE
IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS -
MAKING BP AMERICA'S
LARGEST ENERGY INVESTOR.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS
NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
BUT WITH ADVAIR,
I'M BREATHING BETTER.
SO NOW I CAN HELP MAKE THIS
A GREAT BLOCK PARTY.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
ADVAIR IS CLINICALLY PROVEN
TO HELP SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE
LUNG FUNCTION.
UNLIKE MOST COPD MEDICATIONS,
ADVAIR CONTAINS
BOTH AN ANTI-INFLAMMATORY
AND A LONG-ACTING
BRONCHODILATOR
WORKING TOGETHER
TO HELP IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION ALL DAY.
ADVAIR WON'T REPLACE
FAST-ACTING INHALERS
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS
AND SHOULD NOT BE USED
MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
PEOPLE WITH COPD TAKING ADVAIR
MAY HAVE
A HIGHER CHANCE OF PNEUMONIA.
ADVAIR MAY INCREASE
YOUR RISK OF OSTEOPOROSIS
AND SOME EYE PROBLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HEART CONDITION
OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING ADVAIR.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
IF INCLUDING ADVAIR COULD HELP
IMPROVE YOUR LUNG FUNCTION.
[ Male Announcer ]
ADVAIR DISKUS
FLUTICASONE PROPIONATE AND
SALMETEROL INHALATION POWDER.
GET YOUR FIRST PRESCRIPTION
FREE
AND SAVE ON REFILLS
AT ADVAIRCOPD.COM.
GET YOUR FIRST PRESCRIPTION
FREE
WE REPLACED PEOPLE
WITH A MACHINE.R,
WHAT?
CUSTOMERS DIDN'T LIKE IT.
SO WHY DO BANKS DO IT?
HELLO?
HELLO?!
IF YOUR BANK DOESN'T LET YOU
TALK TO A REAL PERSON 24/7,
YOU NEED AN ALLY.
HELLO?
ALLY BANK.
YOUR MONEY NEEDS AN ALLY.
>>> OUR "INSTANT INDEX" ON A
FRIDAY NIGHT STARTING WITH THE
SECOND CHANCE FOR 10-YEAR-OLD
SEBASTIAN DE LA CRUZ, THE TARGET
OF MEAN TWEETS ATTACKING HIS
MEXICAN AMERICAN HERITAGE AFTER
SINGING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM AT
THE NBA FINALS.
SO MANY PEOPLE RALLIED AROUND
HIM.
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE BRAVE
>> WELCOME BACK, SEBASTIAN.
NOW TO THE IMAGES TRENDING.
MICHAEL PHELPS ON THE STARTING
BLOCK.
HE SENT THIS OUT AND STIRRED
SPECULATION ABOUT A COMEBACK.
AFTER HE SAID HE WAS DONE FOR
GOOD.
STAY TUNED ON THIS ONE.
>>> AND THIS IMAGE, TWO HANDS
CLASPED, A BRIDE AND GROOM, THE
GROOM ASKING FOR THE PRAYER, AND
PROMISING NOT TO LOOK AT HER
DRESS, TELLING HER, HE SIMPLY
WANTED TO GIVE THANKS.
INCREDIBLY.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, YOU'LL
REMEMBER THIS.
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER.
IT'S ALMOST OVER!
>> THAT BRAVE TEACHER AND THOSE
BRAVE STUDENTS, AND WE'VE JUST
LEARNED WHAT THEY DID BEFORE
THAT TORNADO HIT.
I'm the next American success
story. Working for a company
where over seventy-five percent
of store management started as
hourly associates. There's
opportunity here. I can use
Walmart's education benefits to
get a degree, Maybe work in IT,
Or be an engineer, helping
Walmart conserve energy. Even
today, when our store does well,
I earn quarterly bonuses. When
people look at me, I hope they
see someone working their way
up. VO: Opportunity, that's the
real Walmart.
[ slap! ]
[ Male Announcer ] YOUR
FAVORITE FOODS FIGHTING YOU?
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
CALCIUM-RICH TUMS
STARTS WORKING SO FAST
YOU'LL FORGET
YOU HAD HEARTBURN.
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUM TUMS
YOU'LL FORGET
YOU HAD HEARTBURN.
THE BLISTERS WERE OOZING,
AND PAINFUL TO TOUCH.
I WOKE UP TO A BLISTERING
ON MY SHOULDER.
I SPENT 23 YEARS AS A
DEPUTY UNITED STATES MARSHAL
AND I'VE BEEN PRETTY
WELL BANGED UP
BUT THE WORST PAIN
I'VE EXPERIENCED
WAS WHEN I HAD SHINGLES.
WHEN I WENT TO THE CLINIC,
THE NURSE TOLD ME
THAT IT WAS A RESULT OF
HAVING HAD CHICKENPOX.
I WOULDN'T WISH IT
ON MY WORST ENEMY.
ICAUSED BY ACID REFLUX DISEASE,
RELIEVING HEARTBURN,
RELIEF IS AT HAND.
FOR MANY, NEXIUM PROVIDES
24-HOUR HEARTBURN RELIEF
AND MAY BE
AVAILABLE
FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
THERE IS RISK OF BONE FRACTURE
AND LOW MAGNESIUM LEVELS.
SIDE EFFECTS MAY INCLUDE
HEADACHE, ABDOMINAL
PAIN, AND DIARRHEA.
IF YOU HAVE PERSISTENT DIARRHEA,
CONTACT YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
OTHER SERIOUS STOMACH
CONDITIONS MAY EXIST.
DON'T TAKE NEXIUM IF
YOU TAKE CLOPIDOGREL.
RELIEF IS AT
HAND FOR JUST
$18 A MONTH.
TALK TO
YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT NEXIUM.
>>> AND FINALLY TONIGHT HERE,
OUR PERSONS OF THE WEEK.
IN THIS AGE OF E-MAILS AND
TEXTS, CHILDREN FROM TWO
SEPARATE CLASSROOMS, TWO CITIES,
REMINDING US OF THE POWER OF THE
WRITTEN WORD.
>> WE WILL NEVER FORGET THOSE
SCREAMS.
AS THE TORNADO HOVERED OVER
BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN
OKLAHOMA.
THAT TEACHER, MRS. DIEDZIK
HUDDLED WITH HER STUDENTS IN THE
BATHROOM.
AND HER PROMISE --
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER.
IT'S ALMOST OVER!
>> Reporter: IN THE HOURS
AFTERWARD, SHE TOOK US THROUGH
THAT SCHOOL, THE CLASSROOMS
GONE, THE HALLWAYS CRUMBLED, THE
BATHROOM WHERE HER FIFTH GRADERS
SURVIVED.
>> I WAS RIGHT HERE.
>> Reporter: IN THE WEEKS SINCE,
LITTLE DID WE KNOW WE'D BE
INVITED TO ANOTHER FIFTH GRADE
AT THE MARTIN LUTHER KING
SCHOOL, 1,500 MILES AWAY FROM
OKLAHOMA.
>> WELCOME TO OUR SCHOOL.
>> Reporter: BECAUSE HERE AT
THIS SCHOOL IN NEW JERSEY,
THEY'D WRITTEN TO OTHER SCHOOLS
ALL OVER THE COUNTRY.
AND ONE STUDENT HERE HAD PICKED
BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY IN
OKLAHOMA.
BUT WHAT THEY DIDN'T KNOW WAS
THAT, AS THE TORNADO HIT, THOSE
FRIGHTENED OKLAHOMA STUDENTS HAD
ALREADY WRITTEN BACK.
AND THEIR UNOPENED LETTERS WERE
SITTING IN THAT CLASSROOM IN NEW
JERSEY.
>> SO THERE WAS A PACKAGE OF
LETTERS ON THE DESK OF YOUR
TEACHER, AND YOU HADN'T OPENED
IT YET?
>> HE OPENED THEM.
>> DEAR AKHILASH, HI, I'M
CAMBRY.
I LIVE IN OKLAHOMA CITY,
OKLAHOMA, AND GO TO BRIARWOOD
ELEMENTARY.
>> WE CALL OURSELVES THE
BRIARWOOD BEARS.
MY TEACHER'S NAME IS MRS.
DIEDZIK.
SHE'S SO NICE.
AND SHE HAS TWO WONDERFUL KIDS.
>> Reporter: AT THAT MOMENT,
LIFE WAS NORMAL?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: AND YOU CAN TELL.
SUDDENLY THAT TORNADO, SO MANY
MILES AWAY, LEAVING ITS MARKS
HERE TOO.
THERE WAS SO MUCH JOY IN THOSE
LETTERS.
>> YEAH.
>> AND THEN THE TORNADO HIT.
>> RIGHT.
AND YOU THINK, WHAT CAN WE DO?
>> Reporter: SO THEY STARTED A
DRIVE.
RAISING MONEY.
AND BUYING GIFTS TO REPLACE LOST
BELONGINGS FOR THOSE STUDENTS
WHO WROTE THEM.
>> WHAT'S A LADY BUG SCOOPER?
>> I DON'T KNOW.
I SAW AN ADVERTISEMENT FOR THAT.
>> Reporter: DID YOU EVER THINK
YOU'D BE SHOPPING IN THE FIFTH
GRADE?
>> NOT AT ALL.
>> YEAH, ALL THOSE BOXES.
>> Reporter: AND WE WERE THERE
IN OKLAHOMA AS THE FIRST
SHIPMENT ARRIVED.
>> HEY, ROBIN.
>> HI, DAVID.
>> GREAT TO SEE YOU.
>> GREAT TO SEE YOU AGAIN.
>> Reporter: THAT OKLAHOMA
TEACHER AND THREE OF HER
STUDENTS WHO LOST THEIR HOMES.
OPENING GIFTS FOR THE ENTIRE
CLASS.
HARRY POTTER BOX SET, THEY FOUND
THIS BOOK JUST FOR YOU.
THEY HAD TO SPECIAL ORDER IT.
A PILLOW PET, SOME LIP GLOSS.
WHILE BACK IN NEW JERSEY, ONE
MORE DISCOVERY FOR THE STUDENT
WHO PICKED BRIARWOOD TO BEGIN
WITH -- AKHILASH.
HE NEVER KNEW THE VOICE IN THAT
VIDEO.
>> IT'S ALMOST OVER.
>> Reporter: -- WAS THE TEACHER
FROM THE CLASSROOM HE CHOSE.
>> AND IT WAS MRS. DIEDZIK WHO
TOOK THAT VIDEO?
>> Reporter: SHE WAS THE TEACHER
SAYING "IT'S ALMOST OVER."
WHAT WOULD YOU SAY TO HER NOW?
>> I'D SAY YOU'RE VERY BRAVE,
VERY STRONG.
>> VERY STRONG.
SO WE CHOOSE AKHILASH AND HIS
FIFTH GRADE CLASS IN EDISON, NEW
JERSEY, FOR REACHING OUT TO THAT
FIFTH GRADE IN NEED.
FOR DIANE AND ALL OF US,
GOODNIGHT.
>>> CREWS ARE LEAVING TREES
FOR A VERY UNUSUAL REASON.
WE'LL SHOW YOU WHY IN A LIVE
REPORT.
>> AND BREAKING THEIR SILENCE
FOR THE FIRST TIME SINCE A
DEATH ONLY ABC 7 NEWS TALK WAS
THE ARTEMIS TEAM ABOUT HOW THE
TEAM FEEL NOUZ.
>> AND WHEN THE MILITARY MADE
CUTS, MOMS STEPPED IN.
EFFORTS TO HELP FEED OUR
TROOPS OVERSEAS AFTER TGOVERNMEG
SOME MEALS.
>> PRO TESTORS HOPES COME
CRASHING DOWN.
CREWS IN SAN FRANCISCO BEGIN
TURNING THIS NARM INTO A CONDO
DEVELOPMENT.
GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE I'M
CAROLYN JOHNSON.
>> IT'S HAPPENING NOW ON A
PLOT OF LAND THAT FELL N.HAYS
VALLEY.
VIC LEE IS THERE LIVE TONIGHT
IN THE LATEST IN THIS
DEVELOPING STORY.
>> IT IS DEVELOPING.
IT'S A BIG PROBLEM DEVELOPERS
SAY IS WHAT ABC 7 NEWS
REPORTED LAST NIGHT.
THE DISCOVERY OF BIRD'S NESTS
ON SOME TREES ON THIS
PROPERTY.
NOW, REGARDING RALLY THAT
THEY'RE GOING TO HOLD TONIGHT,
WELL, THEY'RE SUPPOSED TO BE
GATHERING AT THAT URBAN PARK
BEHIND ME.
AT 6:00 TONIGHT TO PLAN
STRATEGIES ON HOW TO RECLAIM
THE PROPERTY.
SO FAR THERE HAS BEEN VERY
LITTLE TURNOUT.
SOME OFFICERS WERE POSITIONED
AT THE GREEN URBAN PARK.
BUT AT 5:00 TONIGHT ONE HOUR
BEFORE THE PLANNED GATHERING
THERE WAS NOTHING UNUSUAL HERE,
ALL ACTIVITY HAPPENED AT THE
NOW-VACANT LOT TODAY.
BIOLOGISTS MONITORING CREWS AS
THEY CLEARED TREES AND DEBRIS
FROM THE PROPERTY.
YESTERDAY, BIRD NESTS HAD BEEN
DISCOVERED IN TREES WHEN
DEVELOPERS INSPECTED THE
SECOND.
THE MAYOR'S OFFICE OF HOUSING.
>> THE SURROUNDING TREES HAVE
BEEN SORT OF IDENTIFIED AND
ARE GOING TO BE SAVED AND
THEY'RE GOING TO WORK THROUGH
A PROCESS BUT TO IDENTIFY
THOUSAND LONG -- HOW LONG
TREES HAVE TO BE UP.