RECOVERED?
THEY SAID YES.
>> WHAT A GREAT DAY.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING
>>> THIS IS "WORLD NEWS,"
TONIGHT DANGER ZONE, MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS FACING A POWER-PACKED
STORM.
TORNADOS ALREADY ON THE GROUND.
A SYSTEM LIKE THE ONE A YEAR AGO
WITH EXPLOSIVE WINDS AND
FLOODING RAIN AND STRETCHING
HUNDREDS OF MILES.
>>> HIGH ANXIETY.
THE DRAMATIC RACE TO SAVE TWO
WINDOW WASHERS AT THE TOP OF A
SKY SCRAPER HAS THE SCAFFOLDING
FOLDS BENEATH THEM.
>>> AIR UNFAIR?
HOW CAN YOUR PLANE TICKET COST
HUNDREDS OF DOLLARS MORE THAN
SOMEONE ELSE IN ANOTHER SEAT ON
THE SAME FLIGHT?
>>> GOOD EVENING.
WE BEGIN WITH THE SEVERE STORM
ROLLING ACROSS THE NATION RIGHT
NOW, WEATHER EXPERTS PUTTING OUT
A KIND OF ALL-POINTS BULLETIN.
ONE IN FIVE AMERICANS IN THE
PATH OF WHAT COULD BECOME A
WEATHER PHENOMENON CALLED A
DERECHO, A 240-MILE STRETCH OF
WICKED WIND.
GINGER ZEE IS STANDING WATCH
WITH THE PEOPLE OF CHICAGO RIGHT
NOW.
GINGER?
>> Reporter: WE'RE JUST HEARING
THE FIRST RUMBLES OF THUNDER AND
SEEING THE LIGHTNING OVER
THE SKYLINE OF CHICAGO.
WE'RE NOT SOMEWHERE RURAL.
TONIGHT MILLIONS IN SOME OF THE
BIGGER CITIES IN THE MIDWEST
INCLUDED IN THIS HIGHEST RISK
ZONE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE
ATMOSPHERE IS FULLY CHARGED.
TORNADOS POPPING UP IN IOWA,
SEVERE STORMS IN ILLINOIS AND WE
ARE RIGHT HERE.
I'M JUST LOOKING UP AT THE
ATMOSPHERE REALLY FIRED UP
ALREADY HERE.
JUST OUTSIDE CHICAGO, THE HIGH
RISK ISSUED FOR CITIES LIKE
DAVENPORT, IOWA, ALL THE WAY TO
FORT WAYNE AND INCLUDING
CHICAGO, ILLINOIS.
>> A HIGH RISK IS JUST OFF THE
CHARTS.
THAT'S WHEN WE'RE REALLY
SOUNDING THE BELL AS LOUDLY AS
WE CAN TO LET FOLKS KNOW THEY
REALLY NEED TO PAY ATTENTION AND
THEY NEED TO TAKE THIS
SERIOUSLY.
>> Reporter: THE NATIONAL
WEATHER SERVICE OUTSIDE CHICAGO
ABUZZ.
>> WE COULD SEE THOSE
THUNDERSTORMS GATHER TOGETHER
AND COALESCE INTO A SERIES OF
LINES AND SEGMENTS THAT WOULD
PRODUCE DAMAGING WIND GUSTS.
>> Reporter: THE CHAOS IN THE
ATMOSPHERE COULD PRODUCE A
DANGEROUS WEATHER PHENOMENON
KNOWN AS A DERECHOES.
ITS CALLING CARD?
OMINOUS SHELF CLOUDS LIKE THESE.
>> Reporter: A DERECHO IS A
POWERFUL LINES OF STORMS.
WINDS BLASTING UP TO 100 MILES
PER HOUR.
IT TAKES ON A BOW SHAPE BECAUSE
AIR RISES IN STORMS, COOLS, THEN
FALLS BEHIND THEM AND THEN
PUSHES THE FRONT OF THE LINE
OUT.
THEY CAN BE DEADLY AND CERTAINLY
AS DAMAGING AS WEAK TORNADOS.
LAST YEAR'S DERECHO TORE THROUGH
12 STATES, WITH IT BLINDING
DOWNPOURS FROM ILLINOIS TO D.C.,
WINDS GUSTING OVER 100 MILES PER
HOUR AND A HUGE PART OF THE
NATION PEPPERED WITH LIGHTNING.
TREES WERE PLUCKED AND CHUCKED
INTO HOMES AND CARS.
THIS STREET IN OHIO BLANKETED IN
POWER LINES.
IT LEFT $1 BILLION IN DAMAGE AND
KILLED 13 PEOPLE.
I NEED TO SHOW YOU THOSE BIG
AREAS THAT ARE ON ALERT TONIGHT.
SO FROM EASTERN IOWA ALL THE WAY
THROUGH CHICAGO, INTO NORTHWEST
INDIANA AND SOUTHWEST MICHIGAN.
THAT'S THE HIGHEST RISK BUT
THERE'S A BIGGER AREA THAT YOU
SEE HIGHLIGHTED THERE.
IT HAS THE POTENTIAL ALL THE WAY
THROUGH PARTS OF OHIO AND
TOMORROW INTO PARTS OF THE EAST
COAST.
>> GINGER, I KNOW YOU SAID
PEOPLE SHOULD STAY INDOORS BUT
WHAT IF YOU ARE CAUGHT OUTSIDE?
>> WE WANT EVERYONE TO BE IN
SHELTER ALWAYS.
IF YOU ARE OUTSIDE, IN YOUR CAR,
YOU WANT TO BE IN YOUR CAR, PUT
YOURSELF THERE AND SEATBELT OF
COURSE, PUT THAT ON, PUT THE
HEAD DOWN, THE FLASHERS ON AND
COVER YOUR HEAD FROM DEBRIS.
IF YOU CAN GET TO SHELTER,
PLEASE DO.
>> EVERYONE IS WARNED TO DO JUST
THAT.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
GINGER ZEE REPORTING AND
STANDING WATCH TONIGHT.
>>> FROM CHICAGO AND THAT STORM
WE HEAD TO COLORADO SPRINGS
WHERE TONIGHT ALL EYES ARE ON
WILDFIRES, HOMES DESTROYED AND
THOUSANDS OF FAMILIES ON THE
MOVE.
ABC'S CLAYTON SANDELL HAS THE
VERY LATEST FROM THERE.
>> Reporter: COLORADO IS
ERUPTING IN FLAMES.
HOT, DRY WINDS ARE FANNING SEVEN
FIRES, THE WORST BLOWING UP AND
FORCING EVACUATIONS OVER 50
SQUARE MILES.
WALLS OF FLAME FROM THE BLACK
FOREST FIRE NEAR COLORADO
SPRINGS ARE TAKING OUT
MILLION-DOLLAR HOMES.
EVERY HOUSE ON THIS STREET GONE.
>> WE HAVE AN ASSESSMENT
COMPLETED ON 4 12 HOMES.
92 ARE TOTAL LOSSES.
>> Reporter: SEVEN THOUSAND
PEOPLE ORDERED TO LEAVE HAD
LITTLE WARNING --
>> I'M JUST COMPLETELY TERRIFIED
AT THIS MOMENT.
>> Reporter: -- STALKED BY GIANT
FLAMES AND OMINOUS SMOKE.
>> ONE OF THE WORST FEARS IS
THAT PEOPLE TOOK THEIR CHANCES
AND IT MAY HAVE COST THEM THEIR
LIFE.
>> Reporter: LYNN BROWN HAD JUST
90 FRANTIC MINUTES TO DECIDE
WHAT SHE COULD TAKE.
>> PEOPLE WERE GRABBING PHOTOS
OFF THE WALL, PHOTO ALBUMS.
WHETHER THE HOUSE IS STILL
STANDING, I DON'T KNOW, EVERYONE
SEEMS TO THINK THAT IT'S GONE.
>> Reporter: LATE TODAY SHE
LEARNED HER FAMILY'S HOME FOR
18 YEARS BURNED TO THE GROUND.
>> THE MINUTE YOU LEAVE YOU
REALIZE THERE'S A LOT THAT YOU
FORGOT.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER BLAZE
THREATENED ROYAL GORGE BRIDGE
AND FORCED STATE PRISON
OFFICIALS TO MOVE 900 INMATES
OUT OF THE FIRE'S PATH.
THESE FIRES ARE AGGRAVATED BY
WINDS AND DROUGHT.
DRY BRUSH LIKE THIS IS TURNED
INTO SUPER FUEL.
THE FIRES ARE BAD FOR PEOPLE BUT
ALSO WILDLIFE.
THIS BABY DEER WAS RESCUED BY A
FIREFIGHTER, ONE SMALL ACT AMID
OVERWHELMING DESTRUCTION.
CLAYTON SANDELL, ABC NEWS,
COLORADO SPRINGS.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> NOW WE TURN TO THAT MANHUNT,
THE 29-YEAR-OLD GIVING CHASE TO
THE U.S. SECURITY ESTABLISHMENT.
EDWARD SNOWDEN WHO MADE ALL
THOSE TOP SECRET DOCUMENTS
PUBLIC EMERGED FOR A SHADOWY
MOMENT BEFORE DISAPPEARING
AGAIN.
HE EVEN HINTED THERE MAY BE MORE
SECRETS TO COME.
HERE'S ABC'S CHIEF INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT, BRIAN ROSS.
>> Reporter: TODAY SNOWDEN MADE
IT CLEAR HE IS STILL IN HONG
KONG TELLING THE SOUTH CHINA
POST IT IS HERE THAT HE WANTS TO
MAKE HIS LAST STAND TO REVEAL
WHAT HE CALLED the CRIMINALITY
of the U.S. GOVERNMENT
SURVEILLANCE PROGRAMS AND
TARGETS WORLDWIDE.
SNOWDEN MAY BE HOLDING A LOT
MORE SECRETS.
HIS LAST POST WAS AT THE NSA,
THE NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY
FACILITY IN HAWAII THAT IS A HUB
FOR AMERICAN SPYING AND COMPUTER
HACKING ON CHINA AND NORTH KOREA
AS WELL AS HONG KONG.
IF HE MAKES PUBLIC THE NAMES OF
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS AND OTHERS
WHO ARE TARGETS IT COULD BE FAR
MORE DEVASTATING THAN WHAT HE
HAS DONE SO FAR.
>> THAT'S THE $64,000 QUESTION
WE DON'T KNOW WHO THE TARGETS
ARE.
IF THAT COMES OUT THEN THERE
WILL BE SERIOUS DAMAGE TO
NATIONAL SECURITY.
>> Reporter: IN CONGRESS TODAY
THE HEAD OF THE NSA, GENERAL
KEITH ALEXANDER, SAID SNOWDEN
ALREADY HURT THE U.S.
>> GREAT HARM HAS ALREADY BEEN
DONE BY OPENING THIS UP.
OUR SECURITY IS JEOPARDIZED.
>> Reporter: ALEXANDER AND
OTHERS SAID THE 29-YEAR-OLD
SNOWDEN HAD BEEN DISHONEST ABOUT
HIS BACKGROUND AND HIS CLAIMS TO
"THE GUARDIAN" NEWSPAPER THAT
U.S. CITIZENS ARE BEING WIRE
TAPPED.
>> I, SITTING AT MY DESK, HAVE
THE AUTHORITY TO WIRE TAP ANYONE
FROM YOU OR YOUR ACCOUNTANT TO A
FEDERAL JUDGE TO EVEN THE
PRESIDENT IF I HAD A PERSONAL
E-MAIL.
>> FALSE.
I KNOW OF NO WAY TO DO THAT.
>> Reporter: EVEN SO THE HEAD OF
THE NSA ACKNOWLEDGED HE WAS
STUNNED THAT A 29-YEAR-OLD
ANALYST WHO DROPPED OUT OF HIGH
SCHOOL IN HIS SOPHOMORE YEAR
COULD HAVE ACCESS TO SO MANY TOP
SECRET DOCUMENTS.
>> I HAVE GREAT CONCERNS OVER
THAT.
THE ACCESS THAT HE HAD, THE
PROCESS THAT WE DID.
>> Reporter: BUT THE GENERAL
STRONGLY DEFENDED THE NSA'S
SECRET PROGRAMS AS LEGAL,
NECESSARY AND RESPONSIBLE HE
SAID, FOR STOPPING DOZENS OF
TERRORIST EVENTS IN THE U.S. AND
ABROAD.
>> BRIAN ROSS REPORTING IN AGAIN
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU, BRIAN.
>>> WE HEAD OVERSEAS TO THE
UNCERTAINTY INSIDE AMERICA'S
VITAL ALLY, TURKEY.
WE SHOWED YOU THE VIOLENT
CLASHES BETWEEN PROTESTORS AND
POLICE YESTERDAY.
TODAY THE SCENE CALMER AS THE
PRIME MINISTER ORDERED THE
PROTEST TO END WITHIN 24 HOURS.
DEMONSTRATORS GATHERED AGAIN BUT
POLICE WERE NEARBY AND THERE WAS
NO WIDESPREAD VIOLENCE.
>>> WORD OUT OF SOUTH AFRICA
94-YEAR-OLD NELSON MANDELA
RESPONDING TO TREATMENT
FOLLOWING WHAT'S BEEN DESCRIBED
AS A DIFFICULT FEW DAYS.
THIS IS HIS FIFTH DAY IN THE
HOSPITAL FOR A LUNG INFECTION.
49 YEARS AGO TODAY BY THE WAY,
MANDELA WAS SENTENCED TO LIFE IN
PRISON FOR BATTLING AGAINST
APARTHEID.
>>> BACK HERE AT HOME A WAKEUP
CALL FROM TRIPLE A.
WE HAVE BEEN WARNED ABOUT
TEXTING WHILE DRIVING.
NOW THERE'S A NEW STUDY ABOUT
HANDS-FREE DEVICES AND SOMETHING
CALLED A KIND OF BLINDNESS
BEHIND THE WHEEL WHICH IS WHERE
WE FIND DAVID KERLEY TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: SO HOW MANY
ELECTRODES ARE YOU PUTTING ON?
I AM GETTING WIRED FOR RESEARCH.
>> I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD AND
STRETCH THIS OVER YOUR HEAD.
>> Reporter: MAYBE NOT A GREAT
LOOK.
>> I'M GOING TO GO AHEAD AND PUT
THE CHIN STRAP ON.
>> Reporter: BUT ALL THESE
CONNECTIONS --
>> GO AHEAD AND SCAN YOUR EYES
TO THE LEFT AND RIGHT AS FAR AS
YOU CAN.
>> Reporter: WILL MEASURE HOW
MUCH MY BRAIN CAN HANDLE BEHIND
THE WHEEL.
REACTION TIME.
WHERE MY EYES LOOK.
9 MILLION CARS TODAY HAVE
SYSTEMS THAT LET YOU TALK TO
YOUR CAR SO YOU CAN KEEP YOUR
HANDS ON THE WHEEL.
62 MILLION WILL HAVE THEM IN
FIVE YEARS.
BUT IS IT SAFER?
WITH A SMALL BUTTON ON MY THUMB,
I CLICK WHEN A GREEN LIGHT
FLASHES, SIMULATING SOMETHING ON
THE ROAD THAT NEEDS MY
ATTENTION.
I DRIVE LISTENING TO THE RADIO.
THEN ANOTHER TRIP, WITH SPEECH
TO TEXT, HEARING AND ANSWERING
EMAIL.
>> HEY, I HAVEN'T HEARD FROM YOU
IN A WHILE.
>> Reporter: REPLY.
>> OKAY, WHAT WOULD YOU LIKE TO
SAY?
>> Reporter: I'LL TALK TO YOU
SOON.
SEND.
I CLICKED THE BUTTON, BUT --
HOW DID I DO, JOEL?
>> YOUR RESPONSE TIMES WERE A
BIT DELAYED WHEN YOU ARE ENGAGED
IN THAT SPEECH TO TEXT TASK.
>> Reporter: HERE'S WHAT
RESEARCHERS FOR AAA FOUND --
THE LEAST AMOUNT OF DISTRACTION
WAS THE RADIO.
GOING UP THE SCALE, TALKING ON A
HANDS-FREE PHONE, TALKING TO A
PASSENGER.
A HANDHELD PHONE WAS NEXT.
BUT IT'S THOSE SPEECH-TO-TEXT
PROGRAMS CAUSING THE MOST
DISTRACTION.
A FRACTION OF A SECOND.
IT CAN BE DANGEROUS.
THEY CALL IT, "INATTENTION
BLINDESS."
>> EVEN IF YOUR HANDS ARE ON THE
WHEEL AND YOUR EYES ARE ON THE
ROAD, YOU MAY NOT BE SAFE.
>> Reporter: AUTOMAKERS SAY THE
STUDY SENDS A MISLEADING
MESSAGE, SUGGESTING HANDS-FREE
AND HANDHELD DEVICES ARE EQUALLY
RISKY.
THE RISK, SAYS AAA, IS THAT
THESE SYSTEMS SOLD AS SAFE MAY
REALLY LEAD US TO DISTRACTION.
>> YOUR NEXT MESSAGE IS LOADING.
>> DAVID KERLEY, MARYLAND.
>>> NEXT A MOMENT OF TERROR 46
STORIES IN THE AIR, TWO WINDOW
WASHERS IN NEW YORK CITY NEAR
THE TOP OF A SKY SCRAPER, THEIR
SCAFFOLDING REFUSED TO FLATTEN
OUT, BUCKLED IN THE MIDDLE FROM
THE GROUND.
YOU CAN SEE HOW HIGH THEY WERE
STRANDED.
THEY WERE EVENTUALLY SAVED BY
RESCUERS WHO REMOVED PART OF A
WINDOW NEXT TO THEM, PULLED THEM
INSIDE THE BUILDING.
THE RESCUERS SAY THE WINDOW
WASHERS WERE NOT PANICKED.
IN FACT, THEY SMILED AND SAID,
"ALL THIS FOR US?"
>>> NOW TO A TRIUMPH FOR AN
AMERICAN FAMILY WHO REFUSED TO
TAKE NO FOR AN ANSWER.
A 10-YEAR-OLD GIRL NAMED SARAH
NEEDED A NEW LIFE SAVING SET OF
LUNGS BUT THE FINE PRINT OF THE
DONOR RULES STOOD IN HER WAY.
AN OUTPOURING OF SUPPORT CHANGED
THE STORY AND DAVID WRIGHT TELLS
US THE LATEST TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: SARAH MURNAGHAN IS
A TEN-YEAR-OLD GIRL WHO CAN
BREATHE A BIT EASIER TONIGHT.
>> RIGHT NOW WE HAVE A CHANCE, A
HOPE.
>> Reporter: SHE WAS DYING OF
CYSTIC FIBROSIS AND NEEDED A NEW
SET OF LUNGS, A RARE COMMODITY
ESPECIALLY FOR KIDS BECAUSE OF
THEIR SIZE.
CHILDREN UNDER 12 HAVE TO WAIT
FOR DONOR LUNGS FROM OTHER KIDS.
ADULT LUNGS HAVE TO BE TRIMMED
DOWN TO FIT THEM.
A RISKY PROPOSITION.
THAT'S WHY THE U.S. REQUIRES ALL
AVAILABLE ADULT LUNGS TO BE
OFFERED TO ADULTS FIRST.
>> MADAM SECRETARY, I WOULD URGE
YOU THIS WEEK TO ALLOW THE LUNG
TRANSPLANT TO MOVE FORWARD.
>> Reporter: THE MURNAGHANS
FOUGHT FOR SARAH ALL THE WAY TO
WASHINGTON.
>> UNFORTUNATELY THERE ARE ABOUT
40 VERY SERIOUSLY ILL
PENNSYLVANIANS OVER THE AGE OF
12 ALSO WAITING FOR A LUNG
TRANSPLANT.
>> Reporter: FINALLY LAST WEEK A
FEDERAL JUDGE ORDERED SHE BE
PLACED ON THE ADULT LIST, A
CONTROVERSIAL DECISION.
>> I DON'T THINK WE WANT JUDGES
MAKING MEDICAL DECISIONS ANYMORE
THAN WE WANT DOCTORS DECIDING
SUPREME COURT CASES.
>> WHOA!
>> Reporter: TODAY SARAH GOT HER
LUNGS.
>> MY HOPE IS SHE ACCOMPLISHES
ALL THOSE LITTLE THINGS THAT TEN
YEAR OLDS SHOULD ACCOMPLISH.
>> Reporter: FOR ONE LITTLE GIRL
A SECOND CHANCE.
DAVID WRIGHT ABC NEWS LOS
ANGELES.
>>> STILL AHEAD HERE ON "WORLD
NEWS."
HOW CAN IT BE, SAME AIRPLANE,
PASSENGERS WITH THE SAME TICKETS
BUT PAYING WILDLY DIFFERENT
FARES.
HOW YOUR FAMILY CAN GET A GOOD
DEAL WITH THE AIRLINES.
>>> COMING UP A REAL LIFE
MERMAID, ONE WOMAN'S JOURNEY TO
SHOW US THE POSSIBILITIES IN OUR
LIVES.
THIS IS GOING TO TAKE YOUR
BREATH AWAY.
WHEN WE MADE OUR COMMITMENT TO
THE GULF, BP HAD TWO BIG GOALS:
HELP THE GULF RECOVER, AND
LEARN FROM WHAT HAPPENED
SO WE COULD BE A BETTER,
SAFER ENERGY COMPANY.
I'VE BEEN WITH BP FOR 24 YEARS.
I WAS PART OF THE TEAM
THAT HELPED DELIVER
ON OUR COMMITMENTS TO THE GULF -
AND I CAN TELL YOU, SAFETY IS AT
THE HEART OF EVERYTHING WE DO.
WE'VE ADDED CUTTING-EDGE SAFETY
EQUIPMENT AND TECHNOLOGY,
LIKE A NEW DEEPWATER WELL CAP
AND A STATE-OF-THE-ART
MONITORING CENTER,
WHERE EXPERTS WATCH OVER
ALL OUR DRILLING ACTIVITY,
TWENTY-FOUR-SEVEN.
AND WE'RE SHARING
WHAT WE'VE LEARNED,
SO WE CAN ALL PRODUCE
ENERGY MORE SAFELY.
SAFETY IS A VITAL PART OF
BP'S COMMITMENT TO AMERICA -
AND TO THE NEARLY 250,000
PEOPLE WHO WORK WITH US HERE.
WE INVEST MORE IN THE U.S. THAN
ANYWHERE ELSE IN THE WORLD.
OVER FIFTY-FIVE BILLION DOLLARS
HERE IN THE LAST FIVE YEARS -
MAKING BP AMERICA'S
LARGEST ENERGY INVESTOR.
OUR COMMITMENT HAS
NEVER BEEN STRONGER.
on my feet and exactly where
I needed more support.
Then, I got my number.
My tired, achy feet affected my
whole life.
Until I found my number.
I tried the free Dr. Scholl's
Foot Mapping Center.
In two minutes, I got my foot
map and custom number.
I'm a 440.
That matched up to the Dr.
Scholl's Custom Fit Orthotic
inserts with the right support
and cushioning I need.
I am a believer.
I'm a believer!
I'm a believer.
Go to DrScholls.com to
find your closest Walmart
with a Foot Mapping Center.
I HAVE A GREAT FIT
WITH MY DENTURES.
I LOVE KIWIS.
I'VE ALWAYS HAD THAT ISSUE
WITH THE SEEDS
GETTING UNDER MY DENTURE.
SUPER POLIGRIP FREE --
IT CREATES A SEAL
OF THE DENTURES IN MY MOUTH.
EVEN WELL-FITTING DENTURES
LET IN FOOD PARTICLES.
SUPER POLIGRIP IS ZINC FREE.
WITH JUST A FEW DABS,
IT'S CLINICALLY PROVEN
TO SEAL OUT MORE FOOD PARTICLES
SO YOU'RE MORE COMFORTABLE
AND CONFIDENT WHILE YOU EAT.
SUPER POLIGRIP FREE
MADE THE KIWI
AN ENJOYABLE EXPERIENCE.
[ Charlie ]
TRY ZINC FREE SUPER POLIGRIP.
>>> NOW A KIND OF TRUTH OR DARE,
2 MILLION AMERICANS A DAY TRAVEL
BY AIRPLANE FOR WORK OR
VACATION.
TRAVELERS DON'T KNOW IF THEY
PAID A LOT MORE FOR THEIR TICKET
THAN SOMEONE SMART SITTING RIGHT
NEXT TO THEM.
LINSEY DAVIS ON THE NEW MAGAZINE
SHOW THE LOOKOUT ASKING ARE YOU
GETTING THE BEST DEAL?
>> Reporter: EVERYONE KNOWS THAT
TICKET PRICES VARY BUT HERE IN
ATLANTA WE WERE SURPRISED TO
FIND A SPREAD OF MORE THAN $600
FOR THE SAME TICKET.
HOW MUCH DID YOU PAY FOR YOUR
TICKET?
>> $320.
>> ROUND TRIP $240.
>> A LITTLE OVER $600.
>> THIS MAN NAMED DAVE GOT US
SCRATCHING OUR HEADS.
>> FATHER WAS $427.91, A GRAND
TOTAL OF $481600.
>> WHEN DID YOU BOOK THAT?
>> ABOUT THREE WEEKS AGO.
>> WOULD YOU BE REALLY
DISAPPOINTED TO KNOW THE LADY
SITTING RIGHT THERE ON THE END
PAID ABOUT $250.
>> I WOULD BE DISAPPOINTED.
>> SHE BOOKED TWO WEEKS AGO ON
EXPEDIA.
>> WOW.
>> DELTA TOLD US FARES ARE
DETERMINED BY MARKET SUPPLY AND
DEMAND AND DUE TO GOVERNMENT
REGULATIONS THEY COULDN'T
DISCUSS IT FURTHER.
>> FINAL CALL FOR ALL
PASSENGERS.
>> I GUESS I BETTER GET ON THIS
FLIGHT NOW.
ONCE WE STARTED ASKING --
>> DO YOU GUYS REMEMBER HOW MUCH
YOU PAID FOR YOUR FLIGHT TICKET?
>> 50,000 POINTS.
>> PEOPLE COULDN'T STOP TALKING
ABOUT IT.
>> HOW MUCH DID YOU PAY FOR YOUR
TICKET?
>> 280 TO 300.
>> 259.
>> PER PERSON?
>> Reporter: WHAT'S THE REASON
FOR ALL THE DIFFERENT PRICES?
FOR ANSWERS WE WENT TO THIS
LITTLE GUY.
DON'T KNOW HIM?
HE'S HIPMUNK, THE FACE OF A
TRAVEL SITE THAT MAKES IT THEIR
BUSINESS TO TRY TO MAKE SENSE OF
ALL THE PRICES.
>> AIRLINES REALIZE THAT PEOPLE
ARE WILLING TO PAY
DIFFERENT AMOUNTS DEPENDING ON
DIFFERENT THINGS.
>> THEY'RE TAKING FULL
ADVANTAGE.
>> Reporter: PRICES FLUCTUATE
ALL DAY LONG.
THERE'S NO GREAT WAY TO GAIN THE
SYSTEM.
>> INCREDIBLE RANGE OF PRICES
YOU SHOWED US THERE SO YOU SAID
THERE ARE A COUPLE OF TIPS THAT
REALLY DO WORK.
>> THE OLD STAND BY OF BUYING
EARLY AT LEAST 21 DAYS IN
ADVANCE AND YOU WANT TO TRY TO
STAY OVER SATURDAY NIGHT IF YOU
CAN.
>> STAY OVER SATURDAY.
>> SHOULD MAKE A DIFFERENCE.
>> EVERYONE, BE SURE TO WATCH
LINSEY TONIGHT FOR MORE OF HER
REPORT ON THE LOOKOUT AT 10:00
P.M. EASTERN.
>>> COMING UP NEXT, FIRST HE
SANG.
♪ OH, SAY CAN YOU SEE.
♪ BY THE DAWN'S EARLY LIGHT.
>> Reporter: AFTER THE APPLAUSE,
AN ANONYMOUS SERIES OF
ATTACKERS.
TONIGHT A LITTLE BOY STANDS UP
FOR WHAT IT TRULY MEANS TO BE
AMERICAN.
NEVER ASK A STRANGER.
[ Lorenzo ] I'M LORENZO.
I WORK FOR 47
DIFFERENT COMPANIES.
WELL, TECHNICALLY
I WORK FOR ONE.
THAT COMPANY, THE UNITED STATES
POSTAL SERVICE®
WORKS FOR THOUSANDS
OF HOME BUSINESSES.
BECAUSE AT USPS.COM®
YOU CAN PAY, PRINT
AND HAVE YOUR PACKAGES PICKED UP
FOR FREE.
I CAN EVEN DROP OFF FREE BOXES.
I WEAR A LOT OF HATS.
WELL, TECHNICALLY I WEAR ONE.
THE U.S. POSTAL SERVICE®,
NO BUSINESS TOO SMALL.
WELL, TECHNICALLY I WEAR ONE.
THE BLISTERS WERE OOZING,
AND PAINFUL TO TOUCH.
I WOKE UP TO A BLISTERING
ON MY SHOULDER.
I SPENT 23 YEARS AS A
DEPUTY UNITED STATES MARSHAL.
WE'D GET UP EARLY AND,
AND STAY UP LATE.
THERE WAS A LOT OF RUNNING,
A LOT OF FIGHTING.
I'VE BEEN PRETTY WELL BANGED UP
BUT THE WORST PAIN
I'VE EXPERIENCED
WAS WHEN I HAD SHINGLES.
I WAS GOING THROUGH SOME
EXTREMELY DIFFICULT TRAINING,
AND I COULDN'T DO IT.
WHEN WE WERE GOING
THROUGH PURSUIT DRIVING,
I COULDN'T PUT A SEAT BELT
ON BECAUSE THE PAIN
THAT WOULD HAVE BEEN
CAUSED BY THE SEAT BELT
RUBBING AGAINST THE SHINGLES
WOULD HAVE BEEN EXCRUCIATING.
WHEN I WENT TO THE CLINIC,
THE NURSE TOLD ME
THAT IT WAS THE RESULT OF
HAVING HAD CHICKENPOX.
I HAD NEVER HEARD OF SHINGLES
PRIOR TO THAT POINT
AND I HAD ALWAYS BEEN
RELATIVELY HEALTHY.
THE RASH, THE ITCHING, THE
BURNING THAT I EXPERIENCED
ON THE SIDE OF MY NECK
AND MY SHOULDER,
I WOULDN'T WISH IT
ON MY WORST ENEMY.
DIARRHEA, GAS, BLOATING?
YES!
ONE Phillips' Colon Health
PROBIOTIC CAP EACH DAY
HELPS DEFEND
AGAINST THESE DIGESTIVE ISSUES
WITH THREE STRAINS
OF GOOD BACTERIA.
LIVE THE REGULAR LIFE.
Phillips'.
>>> OUR "INSTANT INDEX" BEGINS
WITH A KIND OF TINY FREEDOM
FIGHTER, REMINDING US WHAT IT IS
TO BE AMERICAN.
SEBASTIAN DELA CRUZ, A BIG FAN
OF THE SAN ANTONIO SPURS LAST
NIGHT BELTING OUT THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM AT GAME THREE OF THE NBA
FINALS.
JUST LISTEN.
♪
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE BRAVE
>> AFTERWARDS MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
CHEERED HIM, BUT A FEW PEOPLE IN
THE ANONYMOUS VENOM OF THE
INTERNET BEGAN TWEETING ATTACKS
ON HIS HERITAGE.
TODAY HIS POWERFUL ANSWER ON A
LOCAL TV SHOW.
>> THEY DON'T KNOW MY LIFE.
MY FATHER WAS IN THE NAVY FOR A
PRETTY LONG TIME.
PEOPLE DON'T KNOW.
THEY JUST ASSUME THAT I'M JUST
MEXICAN BUT I'M NOT FROM MEXICO.
I'M FROM SAN ANTONIO, BORN AND
RAISED, SPURS FAN.
>> ALL AMERICAN BOY SPEAKING UP
FOR AMERICA AT ITS BEST.
>>> AND HELP CELEBRATE HIS 89th
BIRTHDAY TODAY FORMER PRESIDENT
GEORGE H.W. BUSH, A CERTIFIED
SOCK FANATIC, ASKED EVERYONE TO
TRY OUT THEIR MOST EXUBERANT
SOCKS.
SO MANY ANSWERED THE CALL,
BABIES, DOG, DIGGING INTO THE
SOCK DRAWER THE STAFF AT THE
PRESIDENTIAL LIBRARY AND EVEN A
DEMOCRAT, NANCY PELOSI.
BY THE WAY, THE BIRTHDAY BOY
WORE A PAIR OF SUPERMAN SOCKS.
HAPPY BIRTHDAY.
>>> COMING UP A REAL LIFE
MERMAID READY TO CHANGE YOUR
LIFE.
TRUST YOUR INSTINCTS
TO MAKE THE CALL.
TO TREAT MY LOW TESTOSTERONE,
MY DOCTOR AND I
WENT WITH AXIRON,
THE ONLY UNDERARM
LOW T TREATMENT.
AXIRON CAN RESTORE
T LEVELS TO NORMAL
IN ABOUT 2 WEEKS IN MOST MEN.
AXIRON IS NOT FOR USE IN WOMEN
OR ANYONE YOUNGER THAN 18
OR MEN WITH PROSTATE
OR BREAST CANCER.
WOMEN, ESPECIALLY THOSE WHO
ARE OR WHO MAY BECOME PREGNANT
AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WHERE AXIRON IS APPLIED
AS UNEXPECTED SIGNS OF
PUBERTY IN CHILDREN
OR CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR INCREASED ACNE
IN WOMEN MAY OCCUR.
REPORT THESE SYMPTOMS
TO YOUR DOCTOR.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT ALL
MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS COULD
INCLUDE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER;
WORSENING PROSTATE SYMPTOMS;
DECREASED SPERM COUNT;
ANKLE, FEET OR BODY SWELLING;
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS;
PROBLEMS BREATHING
WHILE SLEEPING;
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
SKIN REDNESS OR
IRRITATION WHERE APPLIED,
INCREASED RED BLOOD CELL COUNT,
HEADACHE, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
AND INCREASE IN PSA.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT THE
ONLY UNDERARM LOW T TREATMENT,
AXIRON.
I am an American
I'm a teacher.
I'm a firefighter.
I'm a carpenter.
I'm an accountant.
A mechanical engineer.
And I shop at Walmart.
Truth is, over sixty
percent of America
shops at Walmart
every month.
I find what I need,
at a great price.
And the money I save goes
to important things.
Braces for my daughter.
A little something for my
son's college fund.
When people look at me,
I hope they see someone
building a better life.
VO: Living better:
that's the real Walmart.
♪
HANDS, FOR HOLDING.
FEET, KICKING.
BETTER THINGS THAN
THE JOINT PAIN AND SWELLING
OF MODERATE TO SEVERE
RHEUMATOID ARTHRITIS.
IF YOU'RE TRYING
TO MANAGE YOUR RA,
NOW MAY BE THE TIME
TO ASK ABOUT XELJANZ.
XELJANZ (TOFACITINIB)
IS A SMALL PILL
FOR ADULTS
WITH MODERATE TO SEVERE RA
FOR WHOM METHOTREXATE
DID NOT WORK WELL.
XELJANZ IS AN RA MEDICINE
THAT CAN ENTER CELLS
AND DISRUPT JAK PATHWAYS,
THOUGHT TO PLAY A ROLE
IN THE INFLAMMATION
THAT COMES WITH RA.
XELJANZ CAN LOWER YOUR ABILITY
TO FIGHT INFECTIONS,
INCLUDING TUBERCULOSIS.
SERIOUS, SOMETIMES FATAL
INFECTIONS AND CANCERS
HAVE HAPPENED
IN PATIENTS TAKING XELJANZ.
DON'T START TAKING XELJANZ
IF YOU HAVE
ANY KIND OF INFECTION,
UNLESS OK WITH YOUR DOCTOR.
TEARS IN THE STOMACH
OR INTESTINES,
LOW BLOOD CELL COUNTS
AND HIGHER LIVER TESTS
AND CHOLESTEROL LEVELS
HAVE HAPPENED.
YOUR DOCTOR
SHOULD PERFORM BLOOD TESTS,
INCLUDING CERTAIN LIVER TESTS
BEFORE YOU START,
AND WHILE
YOU ARE TAKING XELJANZ.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE BEEN TO A REGION
WHERE CERTAIN FUNGAL INFECTIONS
ARE COMMON,
AND IF YOU HAVE HAD TB,
HEPATITIS B OR C,
OR ARE PRONE TO INFECTIONS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ALL THE MEDICINES YOU TAKE,
AND IF YOU ARE PREGNANT,
OR PLAN TO BE.
TAKEN TWICE DAILY,
XELJANZ CAN REDUCE
THE JOINT PAIN AND SWELLING
OF MODERATE TO SEVERE RA,
EVEN WITHOUT METHOTREXATE.
ASK IF XELJANZ
IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
>>> NOW SOMEONE WHO WILL MAKE
YOU THINK ABOUT POSSIBILITY.
ABC'S JOHN DONVAN WITH THE WOMAN
WE WILL NEVER FORGET.
>> Reporter: JUST WATCH FOR A
MOMENT.
IT REALLY IS WHAT IT LOOKS LIKE.
EXCEPT, LOOK CLOSE.
BEHIND THE WHEELS.
A DOUBLE SET OF PROPELLERS.
AND SO SHE GOES.
WEIGHTLESS.
AND EVERY NOW AND THEN COMES UP
FOR AIR.
MEET SUE AUSTIN ON DRY LAND.
GIVING A TALK THAT HAS BEEN
DOWNLOADED BY HALF A MILLION
PEOPLE.
>> IT'S WONDERFUL TO BE HERE TO
TALK ABOUT MY JOURNEY.
>> Reporter: SIXTEEN YEARS AGO,
SHE BEGAN EXPERIENCING RARE
NEUROLOGICAL PROBLEMS AFTER
CONTRACTING CYTOMEGALOVIRUS, AND
EVENTUALLY LOST ALMOST ALL OF
HER MOBILITY.
FOR YEARS IT BOTHERED HER TO BE
PERCEIVED AS LIMITED, CONFINED.
>> IT WAS IF THEY COULDN'T SEE
ME ANYMORE.
AS IF AN INVISIBILITY CLOCK
DESCENDED.
>> Reporter: SO SHE WENT TO THE
SEA SO WE WOULD SEE THE DEVICE
SHE RIDES IN A WHOLE NEW WAY.
>> I LITERALLY HAVE THE FREEDOM
TO MOVE IN 360 DEGREES OF SPACE
IN AN ECSTATIC EXPERIENCE OF JOY
AND FREEDOM.
>> Reporter: THE TECHNOLOGY, IT
TOOK A LITTLE DOING.
>> I STARTED TALKING TO
ENGINEERS.
THEY SAID NO, YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO BE ABLE TO DO IT WHICH IS
PROBABLY THE BEST THING ANYONE
COULD HAVE SAID TO ME.
>> Reporter: WITH THE HELP OF
DRIVERS, SUE INVENTED A WATER
CHAIR WITH CUSTOM FINS AND AN
AIR TANK AND SHE TOOK THE PLUNK
FOR A RIDE THAT NO ONE HAS EVER
TAKEN BEFORE.
>> LITERALLY PUSHED ME THROUGH
INTO A NEW WAY OF BEING, INTO
NEW DIMENSIONS AND A NEW LEVEL
OF CONSCIOUSNESS.
>> JOHN DONVAN ABC NEWS
WASHINGTON.
>> NEXT SHE WANTS TO FLY.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
DON'T FORGET ABCNEWS.COM.
WE'LL SEE YOU AGAIN TOMORROW
NIGHT.
>>> TONIGHT AN END TO RED
LIGHT CAMERAS.
THE BAY AREA CITY PULLING THE
PLUG.
>> A FIELD TRIP MAKING A
DANGEROUS TURN ON A MUNI BUS.
THE PLACE THAT THE KIDS WERE
GOING.
>> AND IN COLORADO HOMES GO UP
IN FLAMES WE'LL HAVE AN UPDATE
ON WILDFIRES BURNING NOW.
>> AND THE FIGHT AGAINST A
HOSPITAL ACCUSED OF DUMPING
PATIENTS IN CALIFORNIA.
THE GROUP IS NOW STEPPING INTO
THE FRAY.
ABC 7 NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>> POLICE TO ENFORCE OUR LAWS.
I DON'T THINK CAMERAS ARE
DOING ANY GOOD, AT ALL.
>> THE CITY OF BELMONT TURNING
OFF RED LIGHT CAMERAS.
MANY CALL THE EXPERIMENT A
FAILURE.
I'M LARRY BEIL.
>> AND I'M CAROLYN JOHNSON
WELL. BEGIN A STORY ONLY ON
ABC 7 NEWS.
VIC?
>> THIS IS THE INTERSECTION
AND OVER THERE YOU CAN SEE ONE
OF THE RED LIGHT CAMERAS.
IN JULY THE CAMERAS MAID FADE
TO BLACK LIKE THEY DID IN
REDWOOD CITY AND BURLINGAME.
RED LIGHT CAMERAS ARE AT TWO
INTERSECTIONS.
IN THE SECOND SET AT RALSTON
AND OLD COUNTY ROAD.
THE COUNCIL MEMBER HAS BEEN A
CRITIC FROM THE START.
>> THAT IS WHAT WE PAY OUR
POLICE TO DO.
TO ENFORCE OUR LAWS.
>> THE CAMERAS MADE BY RED
FLEX TRAFFIC SYSTEMS AVERAGED
ABOUT 170 CITATIONS PER MONTH.
MOSTLY FOR ROLLING STOPS.
POLICE CHIEF BELIEVES THE
CAMERAS WERE ABLE TO
ACCOMPLISH FOR PUBLIC SAFETY
WHAT OFFICERS COULD NOT.
>> IT'S DIFFICULT TO HAVE
OFFICERS THERE WE FELT IT HAD
REACHED OUR GOAL.
>> THERE WERE VERY FEW
STRAIGHT ARM COLLISIONS BEFORE,
OR AFTER CAMERAS WERE
INSTALLED BUT ACCORD TOGETHER