>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT,
THE AIR WAR AGAINST EXPLODING
AND NOW DEADLY WILDFIRE IN
COLORADO.
TONIGHT, NEWS OF PROGRESS IN THE
ASSAULT.
>>> WHAT NOW?
AS THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
PREPARES TO INTERVENE IN SYRIA,
RICHARD ENGEL LOOKS AT THE STATE
OF PLAY.
>>> HILLARY'S RETURN TO THE
NATIONAL STAGE AFTER FOUR YEARS
ABOVE THE FRAY.
THE FORMER SECRETARY OF STATE
RETURNS TO THE POLITICAL ARENA
AND THE POSSIBLE 2016 OPPONENT
IS THERE AS WELL.
>>> AND TO THE RESCUE.
WITH STORM SEASON RAGING, IT'S
THIS ELITE UNIT'S JOB TO SAVE
PEOPLE IN DANGER.
AND TONIGHT, LESTER HOLT FINDS
OUT WHAT IT TAKES.
>>> PLUS, OUR FRIDAY MAKING A
DIFFERENCE REPORT.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>> FROM NBC NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS
IS "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH BRIAN
WILLIAMS.
>>> GOOD EVENING, I'M NATALIE
MORALES IN FOR BRIAN.
HE'LL BE BACK ON MONDAY.
IT HAS BEEN A FIERCE FIREFIGHT
OVER THE LAST FOUR DAYS IN
COLORADO AS A BLACK FOREST FIRE
NEAR COLORADO SPRINGS TURNED
DEADLY, CLAIMING ITS FIRST
VICTIMS.
HUNDREDS OF HOMES DESTROYED AND
NEARLY 40,000 HAD TO FLEE FROM
THE RAGING INFERNO.
AT THIS HOUR, FIREFIGHTERS
CONTINUE TO GO HOUSE TO HOUSE,
SAVING WHAT THEY CAN.
AND FINALLY TODAY, THEIR EFFORTS
TO CONTAIN THE FLAMES ARE PAYING
OFF.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER IS ONCE
AGAIN THERE FOR US TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: AFTER EXPLODING OUT
OF CONTROL THIS WEEK, TODAY
FIREFIGHTERS HELD THEIR GROUND.
THE BURN ZONE, 24 SQUARE MILES.
BUT WHERE THERE IS NO FIRE,
THERE IS PROGRESS.
>> WE MADE TREMENDOUS GROUND,
ESPECIALLY WHEN IT CAME TO THE
STRUCTURE PROTECTION.
I SAW A LOT OF RESOURCES IN
THERE.
I HEARD THEM ON THE RADIO LAST
NIGHT.
THEY WERE REALLY HOPPING.
>> Reporter: THOUSANDS OF HOMES
HAVE BEEN SAVED, BUT WE KNOW TWO
LIVES HAVE BEEN LOST.
AUTHORITIES BELIEVE THE COUPLE
WAS TRYING TO ESCAPE WHEN THEY
WERE OVERCOME BY FLAMES.
>> MY HEART AND I KNOW THE HEART
OF THIS COMMUNITY, GOES OUT TO
THE FAMILY AND FRIENDS THEY
LEAVE BEHIND.
>> Reporter: THE MOST
DESTRUCTIVE FIRE IN STATE
HISTORY HAS DAMAGED OR DESTROYED
AT LEAST 400 HOMES.
>> OH, JESUS.
>> HEATHER AND KATIE DUBOIS TOOK
PICTURE OF THEIR HOUSE BURNING
AS THEY FLED.
>> TAKE IT AS A CHALLENGE AND
MOVE ON.
YOU JUST HAVE TO MOVE ON.
>> Reporter: TODAY, WE FOUND
THEIR BARN STILL STANDING.
>> WE HAD TEN HORSES, SIX DOGS,
THREE CATS, TWO RATS, TWO PIGS,
FOUR BIRDS AND THEY ALL GOT OUT.
>> Reporter: OF THE 38,000
PEOPLE TOLD TO EVACUATE, SOME
REFUSED TO LEAVE.
>> IT WOULD HAVE BURNED TO THE
GROUND.
>> Reporter: DALE MELKE MADE HIS
FLAMINGO, BUT HE STAYED BEHIND,
USING BUCKETS OF RAINWATER TO
SAVE HIS HOME.
>> I BELIEVE GOD PROTECTED ME
AND TOOK CARE OF ME, KEPT ME
SAFE.
>> Reporter: THESE ARE ANXIOUS
TIMES FOR DAN BRENNEN, WHO ISN'T
SURE IF HIS HOUSE ISN'T STILL
STANDING.
>> WELL, YOU'RE A REFUGEE.
HOW DO YOU DESCRIBE A CRISIS YOU
NEVER EXPECTED?
>> Reporter: THE BLACK FOREST
FIRE STILL A THREAT.
TONIGHT STORMS BRING OPTIMISM.
FIREFIGHTERS HOPE THE BRUNT OF
THE DAMAGE IS BEHIND THEM.
THOUGH THE RAIN WAS BRIEF AND
INTERMITTENT TODAY, THE FORECAST
THIS WEEKEND SHOULD BRING
FAVORABLE CONDITIONS FOR
FIREFIGHTERS.
THE CAUSE OF THIS FIRE HAS NOT
BEEN DETERMINED.
A CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION,
THOUGH, IS UNDER WAY.
NATALIE?
>> MIGUEL ALMAGUER IN COLORADO
SPRINGS, THANK YOU, MIGUEL.
>>> THE MASSIVE STORM SYSTEM
THAT SPREAD ACROSS SEVERAL
STATES FROM THE PUBLIC IS BEING
BLAMED FOR FOUR DEATHS,
WIDESPREAD FLOODING AND POWER
OUTAGES.
HUNDREDS OF THOUSANDS LEFT
WITHOUT POWER AFTER HEAVY RAINS
AND STRONG WINDS SLAMMED THE
EAST COAST.
ON THE WEST COAST, A RARE
TORNADO TOUCHED DOWN IN OREGON,
DAMAGING BUILDINGS AND HOMES.
>>> WE TURN TO THE OTHER MAJOR
STORY WE'RE FOLLOWING TONIGHT,
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION'S
DECISION TO SEND ARMS TO THE
REBELS IN SYRIA.
THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT DISMISSED
U.S. CLAIMS THAT IT USED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS AS LIES, AND
ONE OF SYRIA'S KEY MILITARY
ALLIES VOWED TO CONTINUE
SUPPORTING THE REGIME.
WE HAVE MORE TONIGHT FROM NBC'S
CHIEF FOREIGN CORRESPONDENT
RICHARD ENGEL WHO IS IN
NEIGHBORING TURKEY.
>> Reporter: IN ALEPPO, SOME OF
THE HEAVIEST FIGHTING IN WEEKS.
IN A WAR THE U.N. SAID KILLED AT
LEAST 93,000 PEOPLE SO FAR.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT WAS THE
REGIME'S KILLING OF 150 BY
CHEMICAL WEAPONS THAT CROSSED A
RED LINE.
THE U.S. NOW PROMISES THE REBELS
MILITARY SUPPORT, BUT TODAY GAVE
FEW DETAILS.
>> I CAN'T GIVE YOU A SPECIFIC
TIMELINE OR AN ITEMIZED LIST OF
WHAT THAT ASSISTANCE IS AND WHEN
IT WILL GET THERE.
>> Reporter: U.S. MILITARY
SOURCES TELL NBC NEWS THE
ASSISTANCE WILL COME GRADUALLY.
THEY RULE OUT SENDING U.S.
TROOPS AND FOR NOW, IMPOSING A
NO-FLY ZONE AND NO HEAVY WEAPONS
THAT COULD TAKE OUT AIRCRAFT.
BUT THAT'S JUST WHAT REBEL
COMMANDER SAYS THE OPPOSITION
URGENTLY NEEDS.
>> NOBODY TOLD ME WHEN I'M GOING
TO RECEIVE THE FIRST SHIPMENT.
I HOPE TO RECEIVE IT TODAY, NOT
TOMORROW, BECAUSE I NEEDED IT
YESTERDAY.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS SYRIA IS
BEING DESTROYED, A THIRD OF THE
COUNTRY HE CLAIMS IN RUINS.
300,000 IN REGIME JAILS,
MILLIONS DRIVEN FROM THEIR
HOMES, ASSAD HAS BEEN WEAKENED.
THERE ARE FREQUENT MILITARY
DEFECTIONS, WITH SCORES MORE
TODAY, INCLUDING SEVERAL
GENERALS CROSSING INTO TURKEY.
BUT AFTER MONTHS OF GAINS, THE
REBELS ARE NOW LOSING GROUND TO
A SHIITE ALLIANCE OF ASSAD
FORCES, IRAN'S REVOLUTIONARY
GUARDS, IRAQI MILITIAS, AND
CRACK UNITS FROM HEZBOLLAH.
TODAY THEIR LEADER, HASAN
NASRALLAH SAID HEZBOLLAH WOULD
FIGHT WHENEVER AND WHEREVER IT
PLEASED.
JUST LAST MONTH, THEY DEVASTATED
THE TOWN OF QUSAR AND DROVE THE
REBELS OUT.
GENERAL ADRIZ TOLD US
HEZBOLLAH'S NEXT TARGET IS
ALEPPO, A CITY THE SIZE OF
CHICAGO.
CRITICS SAY WASHINGTON IS DOING
TOO LITTLE TOO LATE.
REBELS SAY THERE IS STILL TIME,
BUT NOT MUCH, AND UNLESS
SOMETHING IS DONE SOON, THERE
MIGHT NOT BE ANY REBELS LEFT TO
SUPPORT.
NATALIE?
>> NBC'S RICHARD ENGEL IN
TURKEY, THANK YOU, RICHARD.
>>> INVESTIGATORS ON THE SCENE
AT THE TERRIFYING DECK COLLAPSE
AT A POPULAR SPORTS BAR NEAR
MIAMI.
THEY ARE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT CAUSED THE STRUCTURE TO
GIVE WAY LAST NIGHT.
OFFICIALS SAY ABOUT 100 PEOPLE
WERE ON THE OUTDOOR DECK AT THE
TIME WATCH MIAMI HEAT PLAY THE
SAN ANTONIO SPURS IN GAME FOUR
OF THE NBA FINALS WHEN THE DECK
SUDDENLY COLLAPSED SENDING THEM
INTO THE WATER.
TWO REMAIN IN SERIOUS CONDITION.
>>> A SOMBER SCENE IN NEWTOWN,
CONNECTICUT, TODAY.
THE 26-SECOND MOMENT OF SILENCE
AT A CEREMONY MARKING SIX MONTHS
SINCE THE SHOOTING AT SANDY HOOK
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL THAT CLAIMED
THE LIVES OF 20 CHILDREN AND 6
ADULTS.
THE EVENT WAS ORGANIZED BY THE
GROUP MAYORS AGAINST GUNS, AND
THEY READ THE NAMES OF 6,000
PEOPLE KILLED BY GUN VIOLENCE
SINCE NEWTOWN.
>>> LOTS OF FOLKS WHO COULD
BECOME PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATES
PUT THEMSELVES OUT THERE TODAY
AND YESTERDAY, TESTING THE
WATERS AT TWO BIG CONFERENCES.
AMONG THE MOST PROMINENT WAS
HILLARY CLINTON.
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL HAS BEEN
WATCHING ALL OF THIS AND TRYING
TO READ BETWEEN THE LINES.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN CALL IT A
TRIAL RUN FOR POSSIBLE 2016
CANDIDATES THIS WEEK.
IN CHICAGO, HILLARY CLINTON BACK
ON STAGE IN A ROLL-OUT
CALCULATED TO KEEP HER OPTIONS
OPEN.
>> WHEN WOMEN PARTICIPATE IN
POLITICS, THE EFFECTS RIPPLE OUT
ACROSS SOCIETY.
>> Reporter: PLUS A VIDEO
UNVEILING HER NEW FOCUS, INFANTS
AND PRESCHOOL CHILDREN.
>> TOO SMALL TO FAIL IS ALL
ABOUT GIVING PARENTS, FAMILIES,
BUSINESSES, AND COMMUNITIES THE
TOOLS WE NEED TO HELP ALL OUR
CHILDREN SUCCEED.
SO PLEASE JOIN US FOR THE FUTURE
OF OUR KIDS AND THE FUTURE OF
OUR COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: TAKING SELFIES
TODAY WITH CHELSEA ON TWITTER,
AND THIS TEASE ON THE TWITTER
ACCOUNT, WIFE, MOM, LAWYER,
FLOAT FUSS, SENATOR, SECRETARY
OF STATE, GLASS CEILING CRACKER,
TBD.
IS TBD A HINT ABOUT BECOMING THE
FIRST WOMAN PRESIDENT?
CLINTON'S RECENT POLLS HAVE
SLIPPED AFTER BENGHAZI AND OTHER
STATE DEPARTMENT INVESTIGATIONS.
AND POTENTIAL REPUBLICAN
COMPETITORS WERE ALSO SEEKING
THE SPOTLIGHT TODAY.
IN WASHINGTON, MARCO RUBIO.
>> IF AMERICA IS SO BAD, THEN
WHY ARE PEOPLE ALWAYS TRYING TO
GET IN?
>> Reporter: AND JEB BUSH.
>> YOU'LL BE HAPPY TO KNOW I
WON'T SPEND MUCH TIME REHASHING
THE RESULTS OF LAST NOVEMBER.
>> Reporter: ALREADY HE IS
GETTING CAMPAIGN STYLE ATTENTION
FOR A COMMENT HE MADE TODAY
ABOUT IMMIGRATION.
AND JOINING THEM AT A NONPROFIT
TODAY CHRIS CHRISTIE, WHO COULD
END UP RUNNING AGAINST HILLARY.
OF ALL THE POSSIBLE CANDIDATES,
CHRISTIE HAS BEEN THE BEST AT
FUELING 2016 SPECULATION.
>> YOU THINK I WOULD COME ON
THIS SHOW TO ANNOUNCE A
PRESIDENTIAL RUN?
>> SAY WHAT YOU WANT, BUT WE ALL
KNOW IN 2016 --
♪ BABY YOU WERE BORN TO RUN
>> Reporter: THE QUESTION IS,
HAVE THEY ALREADY STARTED
RUNNING?
ANDREA MITCHELL, NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> AND NOW TO A STORY THAT IS
GETTING ATTENTION AROUND THE
NATION.
FAST FOOD WORKERS GOING ON
STRIKE TO DEMAND BETTER WAGES.
AS THE ECONOMY SLOWLY RECOVERS,
MANY OF THE NEW JOBS ARE
CONCENTRATED IN LOW-WAGE AREAS
LIKE FAST FOOD RESTAURANTS.
NBC NEWS REPORTING ON POVERTY IN
AMERICA, SUPPORTED BY THE FORD
FOUNDATION AND IN TONIGHT'S "IN
PLAIN SIGHT" REPORT, YOU MAY BE
SURPRISED TO LEARN WHO SOME OF
THESE FOLKS ARE AND WHAT IT
TAKES FOR THEM TO FEED THEIR
FAMILIES.
WE GET OUR REPORT FROM NBC'S
KEVIN TIBBLES IN CHICAGO.
♪ WE SERVE IT UP WITH A SMILE
>> Reporter: FOR MANY, THIS IS
THE FACE OF THE FAST FOOD
INDUSTRY, HAPPY YOUNG KIDS
FLIPPING BURGERS AFTER SCHOOL.
BUT THESE DAYS THAT PERSON
TAKING YOUR ORDER FOR MINIMUM
WAGE IS MUCH MORE LIKELY TO BE
OLDER.
>> WE CAN'T AFFORD TO LIVE ON
WHAT WE MAKE.
>> Reporter: PEOPLE LIKE
56-YEAR-OLD INTERIOR DESIGNER
AMY CRAWFORD, WHO NOW WORKS
BEHIND THE COUNTER FOR $8.75 AN
HOUR.
>> I WOULD HAVE DESCRIBED MYSELF
AS VERY COMFORTABLY MIDDLE
CLASS.
>> Reporter: AND NOW?
>> AND NOW I'M GETTING BY.
>> Reporter: CRAWFORD SAYS SHE
HAS BEEN SEEKING A JOB IN HER
FIELD OVER A YEAR, DIPPING INTO
RETIREMENT SAVINGS TO PAY THE
RENT, AND RELYING ON FOOD
STAMPS.
>> THESE FOLKS USE FOOD STAMPS
AT 2 1/2 TIMES THE RATE OF THE
REST OF THE U.S. WORKFORCE.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO THE
CENSUS BUREAU, FAST FOOD WORKERS
MAKE A MEDIAN ANNUAL SALARY OF
ABOUT $18,000 A YEAR.
AND THAT'S IF THEY CAN GET
FULL-TIME HOURS.
>> $8.56.
>> Reporter: THAT'S HOW MUCH
44 TYREE JOHNSON MAKES AN HOUR.
HE SAYS HE IS DOUBLY CONSTRAINED
BECAUSE THE NUMBER OF HOURS HE
IS SCHEDULED TO WORK ARE
LIMITED.
>> I'M PUTTING TOGETHER RESUMES
FOR IMPORTANT JOBS LIKE
COMPUTERS, YOU KNOW,
TELEMARKETING, YOU NAME IT.
>> I AM ENCOURAGING EVERYBODY TO
FIGHT.
>> Reporter: JOHNSON AND
CRAWFORD PART OF A GROWING
NATIONAL MOVEMENT, DEMANDING
BETTER WAGES AND WORKING
CONDITIONS.
SINCE EARLY APRIL, THERE HAVE
BEEN PROTESTS BY FAST FOOD
WORKERS IN SEVEN CITIES.
IN A STATEMENT, THE NATIONAL
RESTAURANT ASSOCIATION SAYS THE
RESTAURANT INDUSTRY PROVIDES 13
MILLION JOBS AND HAS BEEN ONE OF
THE MOST CONSISTENT JOB
PRODUCERS DURING A DIFFICULT AND
SLUGGISH ECONOMY, ADDING THE
INDUSTRY IS ONE OF THE BEST
PATHS TO ACHIEVING THE AMERICAN
DREAM.
AMY CRAWFORD SAYS SHE NEVER
THOUGHT ABOUT THE STRUGGLES FAST
FOOD WORKERS FACE UNTIL SHE
BECAME ONE.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHO THAT PERSON
IS.
BECAUSE MOST OF US LIVE OUR
LIVES UNAWARE THAT WE'RE
UNAWARE.
>> Reporter: UNAWARE THAT WORKER
MAY BE STRUGGLING TO PUT FOOD ON
HIS OR HER OWN TABLE.
KEVIN TIBBLES, NBC, CHICAGO.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT, AS
STORM SEASON RAGES, LESTER HOLT
GOES INSIDE THE ELITE COAST
GUARD TEAM THAT TACKLES SOME OF
THE MOST DANGEROUS RESCUE
MISSIONS ON THE WATER.
>>> AND LATER, HOW AN
EXTRAORDINARY ARMY OF VOLUNTEERS
IS MAKING A DIFFERENCE BY MAKING
SURE A LOT OF KIDS ENJOY THE
PROM THEY THOUGHT THEY WOULD
NEVER HAVE.
>>> WE'RE BACK TONIGHT WITH A
RARE LOOK INSIDE ONE OF THE MOST
ELITE UNITS OF THE U.S.
MILITARY.
THE COAST GUARD SWIMMERS WHO GET
DROPPED INTO TREACHEROUS WATERS
TO SAVE THOSE IN
LIFE-THREATENING SITUATIONS.
AS THEY GET READY FOR ANOTHER
BUSY SEASON, LESTER HOLT SPENT
SOME TIME WITH THEM ON A
TRAINING EMOTION IN NORTH
CAROLINA.
>> EASY BACK.
>> Reporter: IT WAS A DISASTROUS
END TO ATTEMPT TO SAIL AROUND
HURRICANE SANDY.
A FAILED ENGINE AND GENERATOR
LEFT THE "HMS BOUNTY" SINKING
OFF THE NORTH CAROLINA COAST.
BY THE TIME COAST GUARD
HELICOPTERS ARRIVED, THE CREW
HAD ABANDONED SHIP, LOWERED INTO
WAVES UP TO 20 FEET HIGH, COAST
GUARD RESCUE SWIMMERS BATTLED
THEIR WAY TO THE SURVIVORS.
>> SOMETIMES WE GOT HIT BY A
COUPLE BIG WAVES.
ONE TIME WE GOT MASKS KNOCKED
OFF.
>> Reporter: OF THE 16 PEOPLE ON
BOARD, 14 POUND ALIVE.
NOW NEARLY 8 MONTHS LATER, WITH
A NEW STORM SYSTEM UNDER WAY, WE
JOIN RANDY HABBA AND OTHER
VETERANS OF THE "BOUNTY" RESCUE
ON A TRAINING MISSION OUTSIDE
NORTH CAROLINA'S OUTER BANKS.
>> HURRICANE SEASON RIGHT.
WE EXPECT THE TEMPO TO PICK UP.
>> I THINK THE TEMPO WILL PICK
UP JUST BECAUSE IT'S WARM
SEASON, AND ALSO THERE IS MORE
BOATERS OUT THERE, MORE PEOPLE
ON THE WATER.
>> Reporter: OF THE CREW OF
FOUR, ONLY THE RESCUE SWIMMER
GOES INTO THE WATER, LITERALLY
DROPPING INTO THE THICK OF
DANGER.
THEY ARE CONSIDERED THE ELITE OF
THE COAST GUARD.
THEIR SLOGAN?
SO THAT OTHERS MAY LIVE.
>> GET YOUR FEET UP!
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
>> Reporter: BUT, FIRST, THEY
HAVE TO LIVE THROUGH 18 WEEKS OF
SOME OF THE MILITARY'S TOUGHEST
TRAINING.
>> LET'S GO!
>> Reporter: WHERE THE ENEMY IS
THE SEA AND FEAR.
DRILLS PUSH TRAINEES TO THE EDGE
OF MENTAL AND PHYSICAL
EXHAUSTION, BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT
THEY WILL FACE AGAINST AN ANGRY
OCEAN.
>> SOMEBODY WHO IS JUST
PANICKING.
MAYBE THEY CAN SWIM, BUT THEY
DON'T KNOW WHAT TO DO.
>> Reporter: MOST TRAINEES DON'T
MAKE IT THROUGH.
OUT OF A CLASS OF 18, JOSH AND
ADAM ARE THE ONLY ONES LEFT.
>> IT'S LIKE THEY TRY TO GET
INTO YOUR HEAD.
ARE WE GOING DOWN TO A CLASS OF
ONE?
>> MY RESPONSIBILITY IS TO GET
HIM THROUGH HERE, AND HIS
RESPONSIBILITY IS GET ME THROUGH
HERE.
>> Reporter: AT A TRAINING
FACILITY, OPENED JUST BEFORE THE
"BOUNTY" SINKING, DARKNESS,
WAVES, RAIN, EVEN THE ROTOR
BLAST OF A HOVERING HELICOPTER
ARE SIMULATED AS TRAINEES LEARN
TO RESCUE SURVIVORS IN ALL KINDS
OF CONDITIONS.
AS I EXPERIENCED FIRSTHAND, EVEN
A SIMULATED SINKING AT SEA CAN
BE TERRIFYING.
THEIR GRUELING TRAINING ENSURES
THAT WHEN THE TIME COMES FOR
REAL, THESE RESCUERS WILL BE THE
CALM IN THE STORM.
LESTER HOLT, NBC NEWS, ELIZABETH
CITY, NORTH CAROLINA.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
A BIG SENDOFF TO A LONG-TIME
MEMBER OF THE NBC NEWS FAMILY.
WE'LL TAKE A LOOK BACK AT HIS
STORIED CAREER.
>>> WE'RE SAYING SO LONG TO A
BELOVED COLLEAGUE HERE TONIGHT.
ROBERT BAZELL, WHO HAS BEEN THE
CHIEF SCIENCE CORRESPONDENT AT
NBC NEWS FOR ALMOST FOUR
DECADES.
BOB IS LEAVING US TO BEGIN A NEW
CHAPTER IN HIS CAREER.
>> Reporter: IN HIS 38 YEARS
WITH NBC NEWS, ROBERT BAZELL HAS
BEEN ON THE FRONT LINES AND AT
THE FOREFRONT OF SCIENCE AND
HEALTH REPORTING.
>> OTHERS GET AN INFECTION.
>> Reporter: IN THE EARLY 1980s,
HE WAS AMONG THE FIRST
JOURNALIST TO REPORT ON A NEW
ILLNESS, EVEN BEFORE IT WAS
CALLED AIDS.
>> THE SCIENTISTS SAY THIS
PROBABLY MEANS THEY'RE DEALING
WITH SOME NEW DEADLY SEXUALLY
TRANSMITTED DISEASE.
>> Reporter: HE CHRONICLED THE
DEVELOPMENT OF THE SHUTTLE
PROGRAM.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR THOUGHTS ABOUT
THE FUTURE OF NASA NOW?
>> Reporter: AND HELPED GUIDE US
THROUGH THAT TRAGIC DAY WHEN THE
CHALLENGER EXPLODED IN 1986.
HE TRACKED MEDICAL MYSTERY,
INCLUDING FEARS THAT BIRD FLU
MIGHT SPREAD WORLDWIDE.
>> AND IF THAT HAPPENS, IT WILL
BECOME A MAJOR GLOBAL HEALTH
THREAT.
>> Reporter: A SPECIAL INTEREST
GENE RESEARCH ON ILLNESSES FROM
BREAST CANCER TO ALZHEIMER'S.
>> THE RESEARCH ALSO SOLVES A
GREAT MYSTERY IN BIOLOGY.
>> Reporter: IN IRAQ, BOB
BROUGHT HOME THE HEAVY TOLL OF
THE CONFLICT.
>> SOLDIERS AND MARINES ARE
RUSHED IN.
>> Reporter: AND HE DOCUMENTED
THE SUFFERING AFTER THE
EARTHQUAKE IN HAITI.
>> SUPPLIES ARE STARTING TO COME
IN, BUT THERE ARE STILL HUGE
SHORTAGES.
>> Reporter: HELPING US
UNDERSTAND THE WORLD TOOK HIM TO
SOME OF THE MOST FASCINATING
PLACES ON EARTH.
>> THESE STEAM VENTS ARE
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTRY.
OCCUR BECAUSE WATER SEEPS INTO
THE EARTH AND HITS THE MOLTEN
ROCK WHICH IS RIGHT BENEATH THE
SURFACE.
>> Reporter: BOB REPORTED IT ALL
WITH INSIGHT, CREDIBILITY, AND
SKEPTICISM WHEN CALLED FOR.
>> SHOW ME WHY THAT IS THE CASE?
>> Reporter: SETTING THE
STANDARD FOR SCIENCE JOURNALISM.
AND BOB HAS BEEN MUCH MORE THAN
A COLLEAGUE TO MANY OF US HERE
AT NBC NEWS.
HE IS A FRIEND AND HAS NEVER
HESITATED TO LEND A HAND WHEN
HEALTH BECOME PERSONAL.
LATER THIS SUMMER, BOB WILL JOIN
THE FACULTY OF YALE UNIVERSITY,
BECOMING AN ADJUNCT PROFESSOR IN
THE DEPARTMENT OF MOLECULAR,
CELLULAR AND DEVELOPMENTAL
BIOLOGY.
WE THANK HIM, AND WE WISH BOB
AND HIS FAMILY ALL THE BEST.
>>> AND COMING UP NEXT TONIGHT,
MAKING A DIFFERENCE WITH A NIGHT
TO REMEMBER FOR A LOT OF HIGH
SCHOOL SENIORS WHEN PROM JUST
DIDN'T SEEM POSSIBLE.
>>> OUR FINAL STORY TONIGHT
COMES TO US FROM THE ROCKAWAY
SECTION OF QUEENS HERE IN NEW
YORK CITY, HARD HIT AFTER
HURRICANE SANDY, INCLUDING ONE
SCHOOL SO BADLY DAMAGED THAT
IT'S HARDLY BEEN A NORMAL SCHOOL
YEAR FOR THE STUDENTS WHO GO
THERE, AND A CHALLENGING TIME
FOR THE SENIOR CLASS, WHO DIDN'T
THINK PROM WOULD BE POSSIBLE.
THAT WAS UNTIL AN ARMY OF
VOLUNTEERS STEPPED IN TO MAKE A
DIFFERENCE AND GAVE THEM A NIGHT
TO REMEMBER.
WE GET THE STORY TONIGHT FROM
NBC'S KATY TUR.
>> Reporter: ALL DRESSED UP AND
DAPPER.
HE IS FINISHING HIS SENIOR YEAR
OF HIGH SCHOOL EXACTLY THE WAY
HE IS SUPPOSED TO.
>> WHICH HAND DO I PUT IT ON?
>> Reporter: FIGURING OUT HOW TO
PUT A CORSAGE ON HIS PROM DATE.
>> FORGIVE ME.
I'M LEARNING, I'M LEARNING.
>> Reporter: SEVEN MONTHS AGO,
FOLEY AND HIS CLASSMATES
COULDN'T IMAGINE ANYTHING NORMAL
ABOUT THEIR LAST YEAR OF HIGH
SCHOOL.
>> YOU DON'T THIS REALLY KNOW
WHAT YOU HAVE UNTIL YOU LOSE IT.
THE STORM CAME FROM BOTH SIDES
AND THEY MET IN THE MIDDLE.
>> Reporter: A FEW MILES AWAY,
CHRISTY'S HOUSE WAS ALSO BADLY
DAMAGED.
>> WITHIN MINUTES, THE WATER
BURST THROUGH THE DOOR, THE
WINDOWS, EVERYWHERE, AND IT CAME
UP TO RIGHT ABOUT HERE.
>> Reporter: THEIR SCHOOL,
CHANNELVIEW SCHOOL FOR RESEARCH
WAS FLOODED LOST POWER, FORCING
THEM TO RELOCATE FOR MONTHS.
WITH ALL TO FIX, SPENDING MONEY
ON NONESSENTIALS WASN'T
HAPPENING.
PROM SEEMED LIKE A LUXURY.
NOEL KNEW IT WAS A JOB FOR HER
CHARITY, OPERATION PROFIT.
>> YOU WANT TO TAKE ONE MORE IN?
>> WE'RE A PROM ORGANIZATION.
WE CAN'T BUILD HOUSES,
UNFORTUNATELY, BUT WE CAN GIVE A
PROM TO THESE STUDENTS WHO MIGHT
NOT HAVE BEEN ABLE TO AFFORD
GOING.
>> WHAT ABOUT THIS ONE?
>> THIS ONE IS PRETTY.
>> $200 FOR A DRESS, $150 FOR A
TICKET, LIMO PRICES.
THERE IS SO MUCH MONEY INVOLVED.
>> Reporter: THEY RAISED MORE
THAN $11,000, PROVIDING DONATED
DRESSES.
THE TUXES.
>> I'LL GO WITH THE PINK.
>> Reporter: YOU'LL GO WITH THE
PINK PAISLEY?
>> Reporter: AND THE PROM
ITSELF.
OPERATION PROM AND MEN'S
WAREHOUSE PAID FOR EVERYTHING.
>> IT'S JUST THE BEGINNING.
>> Reporter: AND THE START OF A
FUTURE THAT EVEN A HURRICANE
COULDN'T WASH AWAY.
KATY TUR, NBC NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> AND THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR
THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M NATALIE MORALES.
BRIAN WILL BE BACK ON MONDAY.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC NEWS, HAVE
A GREAT WEEKEND AND GOOD NIGHT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US ON THIS
FRIDAY.
I'M RAJ MATHAI.
>> I'M JESSICA AGUIRRE.
SIX MONTHS LATER, THE HEART ACHE
IS EXCRUCIATING ANNAN BEARABLE.
NEWTOWN WENT SILENT TODAY AS THE
20 CHILDREN AND SIX EDUCATORS
MASSACRED IN DECEMBER WERE
REMEMBERED.
AS THE FIGHT OVER GUN CONTROL
RAGES ON IN WASHINGTON, D.C., A
GROUP OF PARENTS IS ASKING BAY
AREA BUSINESS AND TECH LEADERS
TO STEP IN AND OFFER INNOVATIVE
SOLUTIONS TO PREVENT SHOOTINGS.
STEPHANIE TRUONG HAS MORE ON THE
PROGRESS BEING MADE.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
GOOD EVENING, JESSICA.
THOSE PARENTS A PART OF SANDY
HOOK PROMISE, A NON-PROFIT
LAUNCHED BY PEOPLE IN MANY NEW
2001 ENCOURAGING PEOPLE TO COME
UP WITH IDEAS HOW TO IMPROVE
MENTAL HEALTH, SCHOOL SAFETY,
GUN SAFETY.
IT SEEMS IT'S WORKING.
WE SPOKE WITH A MAN WHO SAYS HIS
COMPANY HAS BEEN WORKING ON
SAFETY FOR THE LAST TEN YEARS.
IT'S TILL NOW HE'S SEEING REAL
MOVEMENT.
>> CODED STEEL.
>> A GUN THAT CAN ONLY BE USED
BY ITS OWNER.
IT WAS TECHNOLOGY FEATURED IN
LAST YEAR'S BOND MOVIES "SKY
FALL," A LITTLE BIT OF FRICTION
NOT FAR FROM REALITY.
>> EACH PERSON HAS A UNIQUE
BIOMETRIC SIGNATURE.
>> SAFE GUN TECHNOLOGY INK HAS
THIS IS PROTOTYPE FINGERPRINT
READING DEVICE.
>> CURRENTLY I'M THE ONLY
AUTHORIZED USER OF THE GUN.
>> THIS SHOWS WHAT HAPPENS WHEN
AN UNAUTHORIZED PERSON TRIES TO
SHOOT.
SAFE GUN'S BOARD CHAIRMAN
CHARLIE MILLER SAID H