JOINS US NEXT ON NIGHTLY NEWS".
>> GOOD NIGHT FOLKS, BYE.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT, A MASSIVE
CYBER ATTACK AROUND
THE WORLD HITTING
COMPANIES AND
UNIVERSITIES IN OVER
70 COUNTRIES.
HOSPITALS HELD FOR
RANSOM, EMERGENCY
ROOMS CLOSED.
TONIGHT THE U.S. ON
ALERT.
>>> THREATENING COMEY,
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
HE BETTER HOPE THERE
ARE NO TAPES OF THEIR
CONVERSATIONS.
THE WHITE HOUSE
REFUSING TO DENY THAT
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
SECRET RECORDING
DEVICES.
PLUS, MORE OF THE
TERVIEW THE
PRESIDENT'A REVEALING
COMMENTS ON THE COMEY
CASE.
>>> BANNED ON BOARD,
BRACING FOR AN
EXPANSION OF
ELECTRONICS NOT
ALLOWED ON TRIPS FROM
THE U.S. TO EUROPE.
LAPTOPS AND E-READERS
WOULD NEED TO BE
CHECKED IN FEARS OF
HIDDEN EXPLOSIVES.
>>> AND MAY FLOWERS, A
KALEIDOSCOPE OF
COLORS, AN AMERICAN
CITY'S INCREDIBLE
CELEBRATION OF SPRING.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
NOW.
>> Announcer: FROM NBC
NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW
YORK, THIS IS "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AS WE COME ON THE AIR
IN THE WEST, A MASSIVE
CYBER EXTORTION ATTACK
IS UNDER WAY ACROSS AT
LEAST 70 COUNTRIES
TONIGHT HOLDING
COMPUTER DATA HOSTAGE
FOR RANSOM.
THE DEPARTMENT OF
HOMELAND SECURITY IS
WARNING AMERICAN
COMPANIES TO BE ON
GUARD AS THE ATTACK
SWEEPS ACROSS EUROPE
AND BEYOND, INCLUDING
BRITISH HOSPITALS
WHERE FROZEN COMPUTER
SCREENS FORCED STAFF
TO TURN AWAY SOME
PATIENTS.
WE GET LATE DETAILS
FROM LONDON AND NBC'S
KELLY KOBIA.
>> Reporter: COMPANIES
HELD FOR RANSOM.
A COMPUTER VIRUS
PARALYZING BRITAIN'S
NATIONAL HEALTH
SERVICE.
EMERGENCY ROOMS
CLOSED.
AMBULANCES WERE
DIVERTED.
ROUTINE SURGERIES
CANCELLED.
>> WE TURNED UP FOR
OUR APPOINTMENT TO
HAVE HIS FOOT CHECKED,
AND THEY SAID, I'M
REALLY SORRY, BUT THE
COMPUTER SYSTEM IS
DOWN.
YOU HAVE TO GO AWAY.
>> Reporter: THE VIRUS
LOCKED COMPUTERS.
ON SCREEN A MESSAGE
DEMANDING $300 IN
BITCOIN TO GET ACCESS.
>> THIS WAS NOT
TARGETED AT THE NHS.
IT'S AN INTERNATIONAL
ATTACK.
>> Reporter: THE
ATTACK REPORTEDLY
AFFECTING COMPUTER
NETWORKS IN AT LEAST
70 COUNTRIES.
RUSSIA HIT THE WORST.
EVEN SPREADING THROUGH
THAT COUNTRY'S
INTERIOR MINISTRY.
SECURITY EXPERTS SAY
THE VIRUS EXPLOITS
HOLES IN SOFTWARE
SECURITY FIRST
IDENTIFIED BY THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
AGENCY AND LEAKED BY
HACKERS.
IT'S CALLED WANNA
DECRYPTOR OR WANNA
CRY.
THE GOAL, NOT PATIENT
FILES OR DATA, JUST
MONEY.
LAST YEAR, A HOSPITAL
IN L.A. PAID $17,000
TO UNLOCK THEIR FILES.
IN JANUARY, A HOTEL
IN AUSTRIA WAS HIT.
>> IF YOU KEEP YOUR
SECURITY UP TO DATE,
IF YOU MAKE REGULAR
BACKUPS OF IMPORTANT
DATA, THEN YOU CAN
RECOVER FROM AN
INSTANCE LIKE THIS.
THE PROBLEM IS MANY
ORGANIZATIONS DON'T
DEFEND THEMSELVES IN
ADVANCE.
>> Reporter: THE
MESSAGE TO BRITAIN'S
HOSPITALS, PAY UP BY
MAY 19th OR THEIR DATA
WILL DISAPPEAR.
IT'S NOT YET CLEAR WHO
IS BEHIND THE ATTACK
BUT TONIGHT AS DHS IS
PUTTING OUT THAT ALERT
TO U.S. COMPANIES, A
MICROSOFT SPOKESPERSON
SAID TO GUARD AGAINST
THE VIRUS, SIMPLY MAKE
SURE YOUR COMPUTERS
ARE UPDATED AND
RUNNING THEIR LATEST
SOFTWARE.
LESTER?
>> KELLY COBIELLE,
IN LONDON, THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS NEW
FALLOUT TONIGHT FROM
OUR EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP WHO
UNLEASHED A MORNING
TIRADE ON TWITTER, TO
SOME LOOKED MORE LIKE
A THREAT TO THE FBI
DIRECTOR HE JUST
FIRED, TELLING JAMES
COMEY HE BETTER HOPE
THERE ARE NO TAPES OF
THE CONVERSATIONS AND
THE WHITE HOUSE IS NOT
CONFIRMING OR DENYING
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS
A SECRET RECORDING
SYSTEM.
OUR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT KRISTEN
WELKER HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP ALL SMILES AT
THIS MOTHER'S DAY
CELEBRATION WITH THE
FIRST LADY BUT THIS
MORNING LASHING OUT IN
A TWEET STORM SEEMING
TO UNLEASH A WARNING
TO HIS RECENTLY FIRED
FBI DIRECTOR.
JAMES COMEY BETTER
HOPE THERE ARE NO
TAPES OF OUR
CONVERSATIONS BEFORE
HE STARTS LEAKING TO
THE PRESS.
THOSE STRIKING
COMMENTS COME AFTER
MR. TRUMP DESCRIBED A
JANUARY 27th DINNER
WITH COMEY DURING AN
INTERVIEW WITH LESTER.
>> WE HAD A VERY NICE
DINNER AND AT THAT
TIME HE TOLD ME YOU'RE
NOT UNDER
INVESTIGATION.
>> Reporter: THAT IS
IN DISPUTE AND SO IS
THE PRESIDENT TAPING
DISCUSSIONS?
TODAY MR. TRUMP DIDN'T
DENY IT.
>> I WON'T TALK ABOUT
THAT.
ALL I WANT IS FOR
COMEY TO BE HONEST.
>> Reporter: A SIMILAR
DODGE FROM PRESS
SECRETARY.
>> ARE THERE RECORDING
DEVICES IN THE
RESIDENCE?
>> AS I SAID FOR THE
THIRD TIME, THERE IS
NOTHING FURTHER TO ADD
ON THAT.
>> THERE IS NO EXAMPLE
OF ANY MODERN WHITE
HOUSE RECORDING ANY
CONVERSATIONS THAT
TAKE PLACE INSIDE IT
UNLESS YOU GO BACK TO
THE DARK SINISTER TIME
OF NIXON.
>> Reporter: THE WHITE
HOUSE IS STILL ALSO
TRYING TO EXPLAIN WHAT
LED TO COMEY'S FIRING
AFTER INITIALLY
BLAMING THE CLINTON
INVESTIGATION, THE
PRESIDENT NOW
ADMITTING --
>> I SAID, YOU KNOW,
THIS RUSSIA THING WITH
TRUMP AND RUSSIA IS A
MADE-UP STORY.
IT'S AN EXCUSE FOR THE
DEMOCRATS FOR HAVING
LOST AN ELECTION THEY
SHOULD HAVE WON.
>> Reporter: A VERY
DIFFERENT EXPLANATION
THAN THE ONES GIVEN
INITIALLY.
>> NO ONE FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE.
THAT WAS A D.O.J.
DECISION.
>> BECAUSE OF THE
ACTIONS THE DEPARTMENT
ATTORNEY GENERAL
OUTLINED.
>> Reporter:
INCREASINGLY ON
DEFENSE OVER THE MIXED
MESSAGING, MR. TRUMP
TWEETING TODAY HE'S AN
ACTIVE PRESIDENT.
IT IS NOT POSSIBLE FOR
MY SURROGATES TO STAND
AT PODIUM WITH PERFECT
ACCURACY.
AND TODAY THE
PRESIDENT FURTHER
PUSHED BACK AGAINSTAL
LAGSS OF HIS BUSINESS
TIES WITH RUSSIA
MAKING PUBLIC A LETTER
FROM HIS ATTORNEYS
SENT TO CONGRESS THAT
STATES A REVIEW OF THE
LAST TEN YEARS OF TAX
RETURNS DO NOT REFLECT
ANY INCOME FROM
RUSSIAN SOURCES WITH
SOME EXCEPTIONS,
INCLUDING THE 2013
MISS UNIVERSE PAGEANT
HELD IN MOSCOW.
STILL, FRUSTRATED
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
URGING COMEY TO
TESTIFY.
>> I WOULD LIKE TO
KNOW IF THE PRESIDENT
ORDERED MR. COMEY TO
END THE INVESTIGATION.
>> Reporter: COMEY WAS
INVITED TO TESTIFY
BEFORE THE SENATE
INTELLIGENCE COMMITTEE
ON TUESDAY.
HE'S NOT AVAILABLE
THEN BUT LAWMAKERS ARE
WORKING WITH HIM TO
FIND ANOTHER TIME.
ALSO TONIGHT, THE
PRESIDENT THREATENING
TO CANCEL THE DAILY
PRESS BRIEFINGS, BUT
NO FINAL DECISION YET.
LESTER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
KRISTEN WELKER AT THE
WHITE HOUSE FOR US
TONIGHT.
>>> MEANTIME, FRIENDS
OF JAMES COMEY ARE
PUSHING BACK FROM THE
DINNER THE TWO HAD
FIRST DESCRIBED IN OUR
INTERVIEW BUT STILL NO
COMMENT FROM COMEY
HIMSELF.
OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS HAS THAT END
OF THE STORY.
>> Reporter: ONE WEEK
AFTER HIS
INAUGURATION,
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAD
DINNER AT THE WHITE
HOUSE WITH FBI
DIRECTOR JAMES COMEY.
>> LET'S TALK ABOUT
JAMES COMEY.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT TOLD LESTER
HOLT THE MEETING WAS
COMEY'S IDEA.
>> I HAD A DINNER WITH
HIM.
HE WANTED TO HAVE
DINNER BECAUSE HE
WANTED TO STAY ON.
WE HAD A VERY NICE
DINNER AT THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> HE ASKED FOR THE
DINNER?
>> THE DINNER WAS
ARRANGED.
I THINK HE ASKED FOR
THE DINNER, AND HE
WANTED TO STAY ON AS
THE FBI HEAD, AND I
SAID I'LL CONSIDER.
WE'LL SEE WHAT
HAPPENS.
>> Reporter: BUT TODAY
THE FORMER DIRECTOR OF
NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE
TOLD NBC'S ANDREA
MITCHELL ON THE
MORNING OF THE DINNER,
COMEY SAID IT WASN'T
HIS IDEA.
>> HE MENTIONED THAT
HE HAD BEEN INVITED TO
THE WHITE HOUSE TO
HAVE DINNER WITH THE
PRESIDENT AND HE WAS
UNEASY WITH THAT
BECAUSE OF EVEN
COMPROMISING EVEN THE
OPTICS, THE APPEARANCE
OF INDEPENDENCE, NOT
ONLY OF HIM BUT OF THE
FBI.
>> Reporter: SEVERAL
PEOPLE WHO KNEW COMEY
SAY THEY HEARD FROM
HIM SHORTLY AFTER THE
DINNER AND HE TOLD
THEM BACK THEN DURING
THE DINNER MR. TRUMP
ASKED A COUPLE TIMES
IF HE WOULD BE LOYAL
TO THE PRESIDENT AND
THAT COMEY SAID HE
COULDN'T PROMISE THAT
BUT HE COULD PROMISE
HE WOULD ALWAYS BE
HONEST.
MR. TRUMP TOLD FOX
NEWS TODAY HE NEVER
ASKED ABOUT IT.
>> DID YOU ASK THAT
QUESTION?
>> NO, NO, I DIDN'T
BUT I DON'T THINK IT
WOULD BE A BAD
QUESTION TO ASK.
>> Reporter: AS FOR
THE PRESIDENT'S TWEET
THAT COMEY BETTER HOPE
THERE ARE NO TAPES OF
THE CONVERSATION,
FRIENDS OF COMEY SAY
THEY ARE SURE HE WOULD
BE DELIGHTED IF IT WAS
RECORDED SINCE THE TWO
ACCOUNTS OF WHAT
HAPPENED ARE SO
DIFFERENT.
FRIENDS OF COMEY SAY
THE WHITE HOUSE
INVITATION CAME THE
DAY BEFORE OR THE DAY
OF THE DINNER.
THE SAME TIME AS THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT WAS
WARNING THAT MICHAEL
FLYNN, THEN THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISOR, LIED TO THE
VICE PRESIDENT ABOUT
CONTACT WITH THE
RUSSIAN AMBASSADOR.
LESTER?
>> PETE WILLIAMS IN
WASHINGTON, THANK YOU.
IN FIRING COMEY, THE
PRESIDENT SAID HE
AGREED WITH THE
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
ASSESSMENT THAT
COMEY'S PUBLIC
STATEMENTS ABOUT THE
CLINTON E-MAIL
INVESTIGATION VIOLATED
JUSTICE DEPARTMENT
PRINCIPLES.
AS A CANDIDATE, DONALD
TRUMP SUPPORTED
COMEY'S REOPENING OF
THAT CASE AND IN MY
INTERVIEW WITH THE
PRESIDENT YESTERDAY,
HE APPEARED TO BE MORE
CONCERNED THAT COMEY
DECLINED TO CHARGE
MRS. CLINTON THEN HE
WAS ABOUT ANY BROKEN
RULES.
WOULD YOUR
JUSTIFICATION THAT HE
SHOULDN'T BE DOING
THAT OR YOU DIDN'T
LIKE THE FACT THAT THE
INVESTIGATION DIDN'T
LEAD INTO AN
INDICTMENT?
>> WHEN I WAS A
CANDIDATE, A LOT
DIFFERENT THAN BEING
PRESIDENT BUT WHEN I
WAS A CANDIDATE, WHAT
HE DID, WHAT COMEY DID
HAD GOOD MOMENTS FOR
ME.
AS A CANDIDATE.
I'M ONLY TALKING AS A
CANDIDATE WHERE I WANT
TO DO WHAT IS RIGHT
FOR THE COUNTRY
NECESSARILY.
I'M TALKING PURELY AS
A CANDIDATE.
WHEN HE CAME OUT WITH
THE SCATHING SET OF
CIRCUMSTANCES, THE
SERVER, THE ILLEGAL
SERVER, THE E-MAILS,
33,000 E-MAILS YOU GET
SUBPOENAED AND DON'T
SHOW YOU ERASE THOSE,
DELETE THEM, YOU RID
OF THEM, ACID WASH
THEM, WHEN HE DID ALL
OF THAT STUFF, IT WAS
DISGRACEFUL WHEN HE'S
COVERING EVERYTHING
POINT AFTER POINT.
I WAS WITH LAWYERS
WATCHING THAT.
>> THEY WERE EXTREMELY
CARELESS IN THEIR
HANDLING OF VERY
SENSITIVE HIGHLY
CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION.
>> I HAPPEN TO HAVE
SOME LAWYERS IN THE
ROOM, UNRELATED
LAWYERS AND THEY WERE
SAY, WOW, SHE'S GUILTY
HERE, GUILTY, GUILTY.
THEN HE GETS TO THE
END AND HE SAYS SHE'S
FREE AS A BIRD.
>> ALTHOUGH THE
DEPARTMENT OF JUSTICE
MAKES FINAL DECISIONS
ON MATTERS LIKE THIS,
WE ARE EXPRESSING TO
JUSTICE OUR VIEW THAT
NO CHARGES ARE
APPROPRIATE IN THIS
CASE.
>> SO YOU DIDN'T LIKE
THE OUTCOME?
>> NO, WHAT HAPPENED,
HE HAD A LOT OF
PRESSURE PUT ON AND HE
EXONERATED HER.
HE SHOULD HAVE NEVER
>> THE PRESIDENT
CALLED COMEY'S RECENT
EXPLANATION OF THE
DECISIONS IN THE
CLINTON CASE HORRIBLE.
>>> WE'LL TURN NOW TO
OHIO WHERE A GUNMAN
TODAY OPENED FIRE AT A
NURSING HOME OUTSIDE
COLUMBUS KILLING A
POLICE CHIEF AND TWO
EMPLOYEES.
CHIEF STEVEN ERIC
DISARIO HAD A BABY AND
ONLY BEEN AT THE JOB
ABOUT THREE WEEKS.
THE SUSPECTED GUNMAN
WAS FOUND DEAD AT THE
SCENE.
POLICE HAVE NOT
IDENTIFIED HIM OR
REVEALED THE MOTIVE.
>>> ANOTHER STORY OUT
OF OHIO, A
HEARTBREAKING ONE
CONCERNING AN
8-YEAR-OLD BOY WHO
TOOK HIS OWN LIFE DAYS
AFTER AN ALLEGED
BULLYING INCIDENT AT
SCHOOL.
TODAY SCHOOL OFFICIALS
RELEASED THE VIDEO OF
THAT INCIDENT AFTER
THE BOY'S MOTHER
CLAIMED THE SCHOOL
WASN'T BEING STRAIGHT
WITH HER ABOUT WHAT
HAPPENED.
NBC'S BLAKE McCOY HAS
MORE.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN
NEARLY FOUR MONTHS
SINCE CORNELIA
REYNOLDS DISCOVERED
THE UNTHINKABLE, HER
8-YEAR-OLD SON DEAD IN
HIS BEDROOM.
GABRIEL HAD HANGED
HIMSELF FROM HIS BUNK
BED.
>> HE PROBABLY DIDN'T
WANT TO SAY, MOM,
SOMEBODY BULLYING OR
PICKING ON ME, YOU
KNOW.
HE JUST DIDN'T KNOW
HOW TO TELL ME.
>> Reporter: REYNOLDS
SPOKE WITH OUR
CINCINNATI AFFILIATE
WLWT DAYS AFTER
GABRIEL'S DEATH AND
SAYS SHE WAS NEVER
TOLD HER THIRD GRADER
WAS BEING BULLIED BUT
TONIGHT THIS VIDEO
HAS BEEN RELEASED
SHOWING AN ALLEGED
ASSAULT IN A SCHOOL
BATHROOM WHERE
GABRIEL IS KNOCKED
UNCONSCIOUS TWO DAYS
BEFORE HE ENDED HIS
LIFE.
>> THE SCHOOL DISTRICT
NEVER TOLD MOM THAT
THERE WAS A VIDEO.
THEY NEVER TOLD MOM HE
HAD BEEN ASSAULTED.
>> Reporter: FAMILY
ATTORNEYS WERE GIVEN
THE VIDEO AFTER THEY
BEGAN ASKING
QUESTIONS.
THE SCHOOL DISTRICT
DENIES ANY WRONGDOING
SAYING, IN PART, THROW
THE CONNECTION BETWEEN
THIS INCIDENT AT
SCHOOL AND GABRIEL'S
SUICIDE ARE NOT CLEAR,
THE DISTRICT SHARED
THIS VIDEO WITH POLICE
INVESTIGATORS AT THE
TIME OF THE INCIDENT.
THEIR INVESTIGATION
HAS CONCLUDED AND NO
CHARGES WERE FILED.
THEY SAY A SCHOOL
NURSE CHECKED
GABRIEL'S VITALS AT
THE TIME, WHICH WERE
NORMAL AND CALLED HIS
MOM.
SHE SAYS SHE WAS ONLY
TOLD HER SON HAD
FAINTED.
>> THEY BUSTED MY
BABY'S LIP.
THEY BUSTED HIS NOSE,
AND -- I'M SORRY.
>> Reporter: THIS NEW
VIDEO IS PROMPTING THE
CORONER TO REOPEN THE
DEATH INVESTIGATION AS
GABRIEL'S MOTHER
WONDERS WHAT COULD
HAVE BEEN DONE IF SHE
HAD ONLY KNOWN.
BLAKE McCOY, NBC NEWS.
>>> SWEEPING CHANGES
ARE COMING TO THE DRUG
POLICY IN THIS COUNTRY
AFTER THE ATTORNEY
GENERAL ANNOUNCED A
TOUGH CRACKDOWN.
JEFF SESSIONS ORDERING
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS TO
CHARGE DRUG OFFENDERS
WITH THE MOST SERIOUS
CRIMES THEY CAN
CARRYING THE MAXIMUM
PUNISHMENTS, REVERSING
AN OBAMA ERA PUSH FOR
MORE LENIENCY FOR
NON-VIOLENT OFFENDERS.
NBC'S HALLIE JACKSON
HAS DETAILS FOR US.
>> Reporter: WHEN
NORMAN BROWN WAS 22 HE
RECEIVED A MANDATORY
LIFE SENTENCE FOR
DISTRIBUTING CRACK
COCAINE.
>> I DO DESERVE TO
HAVE SERVED SOME TIME.
BUT THAT MUCH?
I THINK THAT WAS
OVERKILL.
>> Reporter: AFTER 24
YEARS, HIS SENTENCE
WAS COMMUTED BY THEN
PRESIDENT OBAMA IN
2015 AS PART OF HIS
PUSH TO ROLLBACK WHAT
HE DESCRIBED AS
EXCESSIVE PENALTIES
FOR NON-VIOLENT, LOWER
LEVEL OFFENDERS.
>> THEIR PUNISHMENTS
DIDN'T FIT THE CRIME.
>> Reporter: TODAY, A
SIGNIFICANT SHIFT BACK
TO STRICTER
GUIDELINES.
>> THIS IS A KEY PART
OF PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
PROMISE TO KEEP
AMERICA SAFE.
IF YOU ARE A DRUG
TRAFFICKER, WE WILL
NOT LOOK THE OTHER
WAY.
>> Reporter: ATTORNEY
GENERAL JEFF SESSIONS
IS ORDERING
PROSECUTORS TO GO
AFTER THE TOUGHEST
POSSIBLE SENTENCES,
INCLUDING THOSE WITH
MANDATORY MINIMUMS
ALLOWING FOR CERTAIN
EXCEPTIONS IF APPROVED
BY A U.S. ATTORNEY OR
ASSISTANT ATTORNEY
GENERAL.
IT REVERSES OBAMA ERA
POLICIES THAT GAVE
MORE LEEWAY TO
PROSECUTORS.
>> WHAT WE'LL PROBABLY
BE SEEING IS
INCREASING PRISON
POPULATIONS IN A
FEDERAL SYSTEM.
>> Reporter: CIVIL
LIBERTIES ADVOCATES
ARGUE THE DECISION
WILL REPEAT A FAILED
EXPERIMENT WITH FORMER
A.G. ERIC HOLDER WHO
IMPLEMENTED THE POLICY
CALLING THE NEW ONE
NOT TOUGH ON CRIME BUT
DUMB ON CRIME, QUOTE
AN IDEOLOGICALLY
MOTIVATED COOKIE
CUTTER APPROACH.
AS FOR NORMAN BROWN,
HE HOPES THE NEW
ATTORNEY GENERAL WILL
CHANGE HIS MIND.
>> THERE ARE MORE
PEOPLE LIKE ME DYING
IN PRISON THAT NEED TO
GET OUT AND GIVE BACK.
>> Reporter: HALLIE
JACKSON, NBC NEWS, THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>>> STILL AHEAD HERE
TONIGHT, NO LAPTOPS
ALLOWED.
HOMELAND SECURITY
CONSIDERING A MASSIVE
EXPANSION OF ITS BAN
ON ELECTRONIC DEVICES
LARGER THAN A CELL
PHONE TO HUNDREDS MORE
FLIGHTS.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHEN IT
COULD GO INTO EFFECT.
>>> ALSO, A MAJOR
SCANDAL FOR ONE OF THE
NATION'S LARGEST
BANKS, MAYBE BIGGER
THAN PREVIOUSLY
THOUGHT.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH POTENTIALLY BIG
NEWS IN THE AIR.
U.S. HOMELAND SECURITY
IS CONSIDERING A NEW
BAN ON ELECTRONICS ON
PASSENGER AIRCRAFT
TRAVELING
TRANSATLANTIC ENTERING
THE U.S. FROM EUROPE.
NOTHING BIGGER THAN A
CELLPHONE WOULD BE
ALLOWED ON BOARD.
IT WOULD BE A
EXPANSION INVOLVING
FLIGHTS FROM THE
MIDDLE EAST AMID FEARS
OF CONCEALED
EXPLOSIVES.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO HAS
DETAILS.
>> Reporter: THE ORDER
WOULD PROHIBIT
PASSENGERS FROM
BRINGING ANY
ELECTRONIC DEVICE
LARGER THAN A
CELLPHONE LEAVING
EUROPE TO THE U.S.
LAPTOPS, GAMING
DEVICES, DVD PLAYERS.
AS INTELLIGENCE
REPORTS SUGGEST,
TERRORISTS HAVE FOUND
A WAY TO CONCEAL
EXPLOSIVES IN PERSONAL
ELECTRONICS.
>> WHAT WE MIGHT SEE
IS THIS BAN GO FOR
QUITE A WHILE UNTIL
EITHER THE THREAT GOES
AWAY, WHICH I DON'T
SEE THAT HAPPENING ANY
TIME SOON, OR ALL
THESE COUNTRIES START
UPGRADING THE
SCREENING TECHNOLOGY.
>> Reporter: AND
CHECKED LUGGAGE GOES
THROUGH MORE THOROUGH
EXPLOSIVE SCREENING
THAN CARRY-ON BAGS.
ALREADY U.S. AIRLINES
HAVE BEEN TOLD TO
PREPARE.
TODAY DELTA
PREMATURELY POSTED A
NOTICE IN CINCINNATI.
A SIMILAR ELECTRONICS
BAN HAS BEEN IN PLACE
SINCE LATE MARCH
AFFECTING FLIGHTS FROM
TEN AIRPORTS IN THE
MIDDLE EAST AND NORTH
AFRICA.
ROUGHLY 50 FLIGHTS A
DAY BUT EXPANDING THE
BAN TO FLIGHTS FROM
EUROPE WOULD AFFECT
MANY MORE FLIGHTS.
142,000 PASSENGERS
EACH DAY ARRIVE FROM
THE EIGHT BUSIEST
EUROPEAN COUNTRIES.
A MAJOR DISRUPTION FOR
BUSINESS TRAVELERS.
>> NOTHING, I WOULD
SAY MY LAPTOP WOULD
AFFECT ME BECAUSE I
LIKE TO DO MY WORK ON
LONG-HAUL FLIGHTS.
>> YOU NEED
ENTERTAINMENT,
YOU NEED SOMETHING TO
KEEP YOU BUSY.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER
SERIOUS CONCERN, THE
FIRE RISK FROM LOADING
SO MANY ELECTRONIC
DEVICES WITH LITHIUM
ION BATTERIES INTO THE
BOTTOM.
PLANE'S LUGGAGE HOLDS.
TONIGHT, HOMELAND
SECURITY SAYS THE NEW
ELECTRONICS BAN COULD
BE ANNOUNCED IN TWO
WEEKS.
WHILE SOME TRAVELERS
MAY BE UPSET, SECURITY
SOURCES SAY THE PRIME
OBJECTIVE IS THE
SAFETY OF THE
AIRCRAFT.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC
NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A
MOMENT WITH FORMER
FIRST LADY MICHELLE
OBAMA FIGHTING BACK
AFTER THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION
TARGETED A PIECE OF
HER LEGACY.
>>> A SCANDAL OF THE
NATION'S SECOND
LARGEST BANK MAY BE
FAR LARGER THAN FIRST
THOUGHT.
ATTORNEYS IN THE
CLASS-ACTION LAWSUIT
AGAINST WELLS FARGO
NOW ESTIMATE 3.5
MILLION FAKE ACCOUNTS
WERE OPENED IN
CUSTOMER'S NAMES IN
ORDER TO MEET SALES
GOALS.
PREVIOUSLY, REGULATORS
ONLY DISCLOSED ABOUT 2
MILLION.
WELLS FARGO DISPUTES
THE NEW NUMBERS SAYING
IT HAS NOT BEEN
VERIFIED.
>>> AS WE HEAD INTO
THE WEEKEND, EXTREME
WEATHER IS IN THE
FORECAST.
A NOR'EASTER WILL
AFFECT OVER 50 MILLION
PEOPLE IN THE
NORTHEAST WITH HEAVY
RAIN AND HIGH WINDS.
THE SYSTEM WILL IMPACT
D.C. AND NEW YORK CITY
ON SATURDAY.
THEN BOSTON ON SUNDAY.
THERE IS THE POTENTIAL
FOR FLOODING, WIND
GUSTS UP TO 40 MILES
AN HOUR ALONG THE
COAST THAT COULD DELAY
TRAVEL IN THE AIR AND
ON THE ROAD FOR
MOTHER'S DAY.
>>> BACK IN THE
SPOTLIGHT TODAY,
FORMER FIRST LADY
MICHELLE OBAMA
SPEAKING OUT AGAINST
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION'S
DECISION TO ROLLBACK
HEALTHIER SCHOOL LUNCH
STANDARDS THAT SHE
CHAMPIONED.
MRS. OBAMA SAYS IT'S
MORE ABOUT MORE THAN
HER LEGACY.
>> WHY DON'T YOU WANT
OUR KIDS TO HAVE GOOD
FOOD AT SCHOOL?
WHAT IS WRONG WITH
YOU?
AND WHY IS THAT A
PARTISAN ISSUE?
WHY WOULD THAT BE
POLITICAL?
WHAT IS GOING ON?
>> THE RULES
MRS. OBAMA PROMOTED
REQUIRED MORE FRUITS,
VEGETABLES AND WHOLE
GRAINS, BUT THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION SITED
CLAIMS STUDENTS THROW
AWAY MANY OF THOSE
HEALTHIER OPTIONS.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
NOW THAT SPRING IS IN
FULL BLOOM, WE'LL STOP
AND SMELL THE FLOWERS
AT ONE OF AMERICA'S
MOST BREATHTAKING
CELEBRATIONS OF THE
SEASON.
===TAKE VO===
HOW LAWYERS FOR SIERRA LAMAR )S
CONVICTED KILLER -- HOPE TO SWAY
THE JURY.
===JESS/TAKE VO===
PLUS:
THIS VIRAL PHOTO IS PUTTING A
LOCAL SHERIFF )S OFFICE ON THE
DEFENSE.
===NEXT CLOSE===
THE NEWS IS NEXT.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
AN AMAZING SPRINGTIME
SITE.
A SMALL TOWN WITH A
BIG CELEBRATION
INVITING VISITORS TO
TIPTOE THROUGH THE
TULIPS, NEARLY 5
MILLION OF THEM IN ALL
THE COLORS OF THE
RAINBOW.
KEVIN TIBBLES TAKE US
TO HOLLAND, HOLLAND,
MICHIGAN, THAT IS, FOR
THE STORY.
>> Reporter: LIKE A
BREATH OF FRESH AIR
FOR THE SENSES, THE
COLORS HAVE RETURNED
TO HOLLAND, MICHIGAN.
>> SPRING HAS SPRUNG!
>> Reporter: AND JUST
LIKE EVERY YEAR FOR
THE LAST 37, JAN
KARSTIN WANTS EVERYONE
TO KNOW.
WHAT ATTRIBUTES DO YOU
NEED TO BE THE TOWN
CRIER?
>> THE FIRST ONE,
OBVIOUSLY, YOU GOT TO
HAVE A BIG MOUTH.
>> Reporter: FOR 88
YEARS THEY HAVE
PLANTED THE BULBS AND
WAITED PATIENTLY TO
CELEBRATE THEIR DUTCH
HERITAGE DURING TULIP
TIME.
MORE THAN 4.5 MILLION
TULIPS AND 100
DIFFERENT VARIETIES
OFFERED UP TO THOSE
WHO MIGRATE HERE EVERY
MAY.
>> CITY ITSELF HAS A
POPULATION OF 33,000.
SO ADDING 500,000 OF
YOUR CLOSEST FRIENDS
AND FAMILY TO THE
COMMUNITY MAKES IT A
LITTLE BUSY.
>> Reporter: AND
HOLLANDERS LIKE
FESTIVAL DIRECTOR GWEN
SPEND MONTHS PREPARING
THEIR AWE THEY WANTIC
KO
COSTUMES.
MY FEET ARE KILLING
ME.
>> BECAUSE YOU DON'T
HAVE EIGHT PAIRS OF
SOCKS ON LIKE I DID.
>> Reporter: YOU WOULD
NEVER GUESS WE'RE
HERE SMACK DAB IN THE
MIDDLE OF MICHIGAN BUT
THIS IS THE ONLY
WORKING DUTCH WIND
MILL IN THE UNITED
STATES OF AMERICA.
AND IN THIS NATION OF
OURS WITH US RICH
ASSORTMENT OF
CULTURES, PASSING THE
TRADITION TO THE NEXT
GENERATION IS KEY.
KIDS FROM THE LOCAL
HIGH SCHOOL
DEMONSTRATE THE
APTLY NAMED CLOPING
DANCE CELEBRATING THE
ROOTS THAT GREW
AMERICA BY CELEBRATING
THE ARRIVAL OF SPRING.
KEVIN TIBBLES, NBC
NEWS, HOLLAND,
MICHIGAN.
>>> THAT'S GOING TO DO
IT FOR US ON A FRIDAY
NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
==RAJ/TAKE VO==
RIGHT NOW AT 6: WILL HE BE
FORCED OUT?
>>> THE SITUATION IS NOT
ACCEPTABLE.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00.
WILL HE BE FORCED OUT IN NEW
CALLS FOR A BAY AREA DROESHT TO
STEP DOWN AFTER MISUSING
CAMPAIGN FUNDS.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW GOOD EVENING THANKS
FOR BEING WITH US.
>>> THE TOP COP IN CONTRA COSTA
COUNTY FACE AGO FIRESTORM
TONIGHT.
THOSE CALLS FOR HIM TO GO COME
AFTER HE ADMITTED TO PETITION
SPENDING THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS IN
CAMPAIGN FUNDS ON HIMSELF.
TODAY FELLOW PROSECUTORS
AUTHORIZED A ANY CONFIDENCE
VOTE.
NBC BAY AREA JOINS US FROM
MARTINEZ AND THERE IS A JOINING
CHORE US OF VOICES CALLING FOR
HIM TO WALK AWAY.
>> Reporter: HE IS JESSICA THIS
APPEARS TO BE SNOWBALLING.
THE D. A.'S CRITICS ARE LINING
UP.
I'LL TELL YOU THEY ARE NOT
HOLDING BACK.
MEANWHILE, THE DISTRICT ATTORNEY
HERE IS KEEPING QUIET.
>> Reporter: MR. PETERSON.
>> CONTRA COSTA DISTRICT
ATTORNEY MARK PETERSON AVOIDED
OUR CAMERAS TODAY.
AND AMID CALLS FOR THE TOP COP'S
FIRING.
>> THE GRAND JURY INVESTIGATED
CERTAIN ACTIONS OF MR. PETERSON
AND CONCLUDED THAT THERE IS
ENOUGH EVIDENCE THAT IT SHOULD
BE BROUGHT TO TRIAL.
>> THE FOREMAN OF THE CIVIL
GRAND JURY SAYS A LOT OF WORK
WENT IN THE ACCUSATION FILED
WITH THE COURT THIS WEEK CALLING
FOR PETERSON'S REMOVAL FROM
OFFICE.
PETERSON ADMITTED TO THE FAIR
POLITICAL PRACTICE COMMISSION
LAST YEAR HE USED MORE THAN
$66,000 IN CAMPAIGN FUNDS FROM
2011 THROUGH 2015 FOR PERSONAL
ITEMS SUCH AS MEALS, CLOTHING
AND MOVIE