THE DIVISION TITLE WE ARE
ROUTING FOR THEM TONIGHT IN A
BIG WAY.
THAT'S GOING TO DO IT FOR US.
>> WE'RE GOING TO BE BACK AT
6:00.
SEE YOU THEN.
>>> TONIGHT, McCAIN'S
BOMBSHELL.
THE SENATOR DEALS
ANOTHER MAJOR BLOW TO
HIS OWN PARTY'S
EFFORTS TO REPEAL
OBAMACARE.
IS THIS NEWEST GOP
PLAN DOOMED?
>>> BREAKING POINT.
HEART-POUNDING RESCUES
AND NEW EVACUATIONS AS
FLOODWATERS RISE IN
PUERTO RICO.
THE ENTIRE ISLAND
STILL WITHOUT POWER.
TONIGHT THE URGENT
RELIEF MISSION UNDER
WAY.
>>> RACE AGAINST TIME.
SURVIVORS PULLED FROM
THE RUBBLE THREE DAYS
AFTER MEXICO'S
EARTHQUAKE.
BUT THE CLOCK IS
TICKING TO SAVE OTHERS
STILL TRAPPED.
>>> WAR OF WORDS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP CALLS
KIM JONG-UN A MADMAN
AFTER KIM LABELED HIM
MENTALLY DERANGED,
WHILE NORTH KOREA
THREATENS TO DETONATE
ANOTHER H-BOMB.
>>> 911 EMERGENCY.
WHEN NO ONE ANSWERS
YOUR CALL FOR HELP.
THE LIFE-THREATENING
PROBLEM PLAGUING
COMMUNITIES.
>>> AND TOP COPS.
THE WOMEN TAKING
COMMAND IN ONE MAJOR
AMERICAN CITY.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>> Announcer: FROM NBC
NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW
YORK, THIS IS NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>>> GOOD EVENING TO
OUR VIEWERS IN THE
WEST.
THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE TONIGHT.
SENATE REPUBLICANS MAY
FEEL LIKE THEY'VE SEEN
THIS MOVIE BEFORE, THE
ONE ABOUT A LAST-DITCH
EFFORT TO REPEAL AND
REPLACE OBAMACARE
DOOMED BY A KEY
DEFECTION IN THEIR OWN
PARTY.
ONCE AGAIN ITS STAR
SENATOR JOHN McCAIN
WHO ANNOUNCED TODAY HE
WILL NOT SUPPORT THE
LATEST REPEAL AND
REPLACE PLAN.
IT WAS McCAIN WHO
DOOMED THE PREVIOUS
GOP HEALTHCARE BILL.
AND NOW HISTORY MAY BE
REPEATING ITSELF.
NBC NEWS CAPITOL HILL
CORRESPONDENT KASIE
HUNT STARTS US OFF
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: MAVERICK
SENATOR JOHN McCAIN
ALL BUT SINKING THE
REPUBLICAN PLAN TO
REPEAL AND REPLACE
OBAMACARE AGAIN.
IN JULY HE CAST THE
DECIDING VOTE AGAINST
REPEAL.
AND TODAY HE SAID
HE'LL VOTE NO ON THE
NEW VERSION OF THE
PLAN BACKED BY
SENATORS BILL CASSIDY
AND LINDSEY GRAHAM,
WHO IS ONE OF McCAIN'S
BEST FRIENDS IN THE
SENATE.
"I CANNOT IN GOOD
CONSCIENCE VOTE FOR
THE GRAHAM-CASSIDY
PROPOSAL," McCAIN
WROTE IN A LENGTHY
STATEMENT.
"WE SHOULD NOT BE
CONTENT TO PASS
HEALTHCARE LEGISLATION
ON A PARTY-LINE
BASIS."
COMEDIAN JIMMY KIMMEL,
WHO JUMPED INTO THE
DEBATE AFTER HIS SON
WAS BORN WITH A
PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION, THIS WEEK
TARGETING SENATOR
CASSIDY.
>> BILL CASSIDY JUST
LIED RIGHT TO MY FACE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
CHEERING McCAIN.
"THANK YOU, SENATOR
JOHN McCAIN, FOR BEING
A HERO AGAIN AND AGAIN
AND NOW AGAIN," HE
TWEETED.
REPUBLICANS ARE
RUSHING TO PASS A
REPEAL BILL BEFORE
SEPTEMBER 30th SO
THEY'LL ONLY NEED 50
VOTES TO GET IT DONE.
WITH 52 REPUBLICANS IN
THE SENATE AND McCAIN
AND RAND PAUL NOW IN
THE NO COLUMN,
REPUBLICANS CAN'T LOSE
ANOTHER VOTE.
IN THE SPOTLIGHT,
UNDECIDED SENATOR LISA
MURKOWSKI.
VICE PRESIDENT MIKE
PENCE GOING ON ALASKA
RADIO TO KEEP UP THE
PRESSURE.
>> I PROBABLY DON'T
NEED TO TELL THE
PEOPLE OF ALASKA ABOUT
THE FAILINGS OF
NATIONAL SOCIALIZED
HEALTHCARE.
>> Reporter: AND
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS
OF MAINE WHO TOLD
REPORTERS TODAY --
>> I OBVIOUSLY HAVE
VERY SERIOUS
RESERVATIONS ABOUT THE
BILL.
>> Reporter: PENCE
PRESSING HARD FOR A
VOTE NEXT WEEK.
>> A VOTE AGAINST
GRAHAM-CASSIDY IS A
VOTE TO SAVE
OBAMACARE.
>> Reporter: THE
CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
OFFICE, WHICH IS
NONPARTISAN, STILL
HASN'T GIVEN A SCORE
FOR THIS BILL THAT
WOULD GIVE SENATORS
SOME IDEA OF HOW MANY
PEOPLE MIGHT LOSE
THEIR COVERAGE, AND
TONIGHT THE QUESTION
WHETHER REPUBLICAN
LEADERS WILL EVEN PUT
IT ON THE FLOOR FOR A
VOTE.
LESTER?
>> KASIE HUNT AT THE
CAPITOL TONIGHT.
THANKS.
>>> NOW TO PUERTO RICO
WHERE A FAILING DAM
PUSHED PAST THE LIMIT
BY HURRICANE MARIA IS
TRIGGERING NEW FLASH
FLOODS AND EVACUATIONS
TONIGHT.
WHILE POWER OUTAGES
HAVE CRIPPLED
COMMUNICATIONS,
HAMPERING SEARCH AND
RESCUE EFFORTS ACROSS
THE BATTERED AMERICAN
TERRITORY.
OUR GABE GUTIERREZ IS
THERE.
GABE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER,
IN MANY PLACES THE
FLOODWATERS ARE
RECEDING, BUT MANY
COMMUNITIES ARE STILL
INUNDATED.
THROUGHOUT PUERTO RICO
THERE IS NO POWER, NO
COMMUNICATION AND NO
IDEA HOW LONG IT WILL
TAKE TO RECOVER.
TONIGHT, PUERTO RICO
IS EXHAUSTED.
TOWN AFTER TOWN UNDER
WATER AND UNDER
PRESSURE.
MARIA MAY HAVE PASSED
BUT THE STORM'S
AFTERMATH IS
OVERWHELMING.
IN THE NORTHWEST PART
OF THE ISLAND AN
EXTREMELY DANGEROUS
DAM FAILURE IS FORCING
MORE FRANTIC
EVACUATIONS.
>> IT'S DEVASTATING
BECAUSE YOU LOSE
EVERYTHING.
YOU LOSE EVERYTHING.
YOU HAVE TO START FROM
ZERO.
>> Reporter: IN
TOA BAJA, 30 MILES
WEST OF SAN JUAN,
CHRISTOPH ANADOR IS
DESPERATE.
THE WATER FLOODED HER
ENTIRE FIRST FLOOR AND
SHE SAYS THE LOCAL
SHELTER HAS RUN OUT OF
FOOD.
>> WE NEED GAS, FOOD.
I DON'T KNOW.
SOMEONE TO HELP US.
>> Reporter: THE
TOWN'S MAYOR TELLS US
AT LEAST EIGHT PEOPLE
DROWNED HERE AND
AUTHORITIES HAVE
RESCUED 4,000 TO 5,000
TRAPPED BY
FLOODWATERS.
WITHOUT WORKING CELL
PHONES HE'S
COORDINATING WITH
RESCUE CREWS FROM
FLORIDA AND VIRGINIA
BY WORD OF MOUTH.
IT'S CHAOS.
>> IT'S CHAOS.
>> Reporter: NEW VIDEO
RELEASED BY THE U.S.
COAST GUARD SHOWS A
WOMAN AND TWO CHILDREN
BEING HOISTED TO
SAFETY AFTER THEY WERE
STRANDED ON A CAPSIZED
BOAT OFF THE COAST.
POWER IS OUT TO THE
ENTIRE ISLAND AND 95%
OF CELL SERVICE IS
DOWN.
THE GOVERNMENT HAS NOW
HIRED MORE THAN 50
SMALL CONTRACTORS TO
HELP GET THINGS UP AND
RUNNING.
ELECTRICAL CREWS
CLEARING DEBRIS BUT
NOT FIXING LINES YET
BECAUSE THEY SAY THEY
CAN'T EVEN COMMUNICATE
WITH HEADQUARTERS.
>> IT'S A NEW
EXPERIENCE FOR US.
I'M WORKING IN GEORGE
AND I'M WORKING IN
HUGO AND I NEVER SEE
SOMETHING LIKE THIS.
>> Reporter: YOU
WORKED MANY HURRICANES
BEFORE BUT YOU'VE
NEVER SEEN SOMETHING
LIKE THIS.
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN IT.
>> Reporter: ROSA
AVILAS RODE OUT THE
STORM IN OLD SAN JUAN
WHILE A BUILDING IN
THIS HISTORIC
NEIGHBORHOOD CRUMBLED
NEXT TO HER.
>> I SAID TO MYSELF
AND TO MY SON, WE HAVE
TO LEAVE THE HOUSE.
THIS IS GOING TO
COLLAPSE.
>> Reporter: FOR MANY
IN PUERTO RICO MORE
HELP CAN'T COME SOON
ENOUGH.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, TOA BAJA, PUERTO
RICO.
>>> I'M GADI SCHWARTZ
IN PUERTO RICO, WHERE
THIS HOTEL LOBBY IS
MISSION CONTROL FOR
HUNDREDS OF RESCUERS.
>> SO THIS AREA IS
STILL SOMEWHAT DARK?
>> CORRECT.
YEAH.
>> Reporter: FOR MANY
OF THEM, LIKE THIS
CREW FROM VIRGINIA,
HURRICANE MARIA IS YET
ANOTHER DISASTER IN
WHAT SEEMS LIKE AN
UNRELENTING SEASON OF
CATASTROPHE.
>> FOLKS HERE HAVE
TAKEN A PRETTY BIG HIT
WITH THESE STORMS.
WE'RE GOING TO DO
WHATEVER WE CAN TO
HELP THEM.
>> Reporter: SO MANY
ORGANIZATIONS HAVE
BEEN STRETCHED THIN.
FEMA SUPPORTING MORE
THAN 30,000 PEOPLE IN
DISASTER ZONES.
THE RED CROSS
DEPLOYING MORE THAN
5,000 WORKERS AND
NEARLY ITS ENTIRE
VEHICLE FLEET.
SAMARITAN'S PURSE, A
NORTH CAROLINA
NONPROFIT, RESPONDING
TO THEIR THIRD
HURRICANE IN THE LAST
FEW WEEKS WITH 50,000
POUNDS OF EMERGENCY
SUPPLIES TO PUERTO
RICO.
THE SCENES OF
DEVASTATION AND
SUFFERING STIR AN
OVERWHELMING NEED TO
HELP.
THIS CREW IN SAN JUAN
ARE HEADED TO CHECK ON
A FAMILY WHO HASN'T
BEEN HEARD FROM SINCE
THE STORM.
BUT THEN CONTACT.
AND A SATELLITE PHONE
CALL BACK HOME.
>> LISA?
I'M OKAY.
>> Reporter: THROUGH
THE STRAIN OF
BACK-TO-BACK
CALAMITIES --
>> THEY CAME, ALL
RIGHT?
>> Reporter: IT'S
THESE MOMENTS OF
HUMANITY --
>> OKAY, I LOVE YOU.
>> Reporter: -- THAT
HELP THEM PERSEVERE.
>> I'M GLAD WE'RE
ALIVE.
>> Reporter: GADI
SCHWARTZ, NBC NEWS,
LUQUILLO, PUERTO RICO.
>>> THE DESPERATE
SEARCH FOR BURIED
SURVIVORS IS RUNNING
UP AGAINST THE CLOCK
IN MEXICO TONIGHT.
BUT MIRACLE RESCUES IN
THE RUBBLE ARE FUELING
SEARCHERS WITH HOPE
MORE THAN 72 HOURS
AFTER THE DEADLY QUAKE
HIT.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER
IS WITH THE SEARCH
TEAMS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
DESPERATION AND
DETERMINATION.
THIS IS THE FRANTIC
RACE TO BRING THE
BURIED BACK TO LIFE.
IT HAPPENS AGAIN AND
AGAIN.
MORE THAN 100 RESCUED.
MANY STILL MISSING.
>> WE NEED
INFORMATION.
ANY TYPE OF
INFORMATION BUT WE
NEED REAL INFORMATION.
>> Reporter: MARIA
MENDOZA IS LOOKING FOR
IVAN FERNANDEZ, BURIED
UNDER SIX STORIES OF
STEEL, CONCRETE AND
REBAR.
>> MY COUSIN'S THERE.
HE'S 27 YEARS OLD.
>> Reporter: AT THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
WHERE THE SEARCH
GRIPPED A NATION,
AUTHORITIES APOLOGIZE
FOR EARLIER REPORTS
THAT A GIRL WAS
TRAPPED BUT SAY THEY
STILL BELIEVE THERE
COULD BE A SURVIVOR IN
THE RUBBLE.
IT'S ALL HANDS ON DECK
INCLUDING FRIEDA, THE
LAB WORKING WITH THE
MEXICAN NAVY, SNIFFING
FOR THE MISSING.
AND THEN THERE'S THE
SEARCH AND RESCUE CREW
LOS TOPOS.
CHIEF HECTOR MENDES
FORMED HIS TEAM AFTER
THE 1985 QUAKE.
NOW NEEDED MORE THAN
EVER BEFORE.
>> WE ARE THE PEOPLE
WITH THE HEART TO
SUPPORT ALL THESE KIND
OF SITUATIONS.
>> Reporter: AT THE
LARGEST RESCUE SITES
ACROSS MEXICO, THIS IS
THE SCRAMBLE.
HUNDREDS ARE WORKING
AROUND THE CLOCK AND
THEY WON'T GIVE UP
HOPE.
MANY WHO SURVIVED HAVE
LITTLE LEFT.
CHRISTIAN CLAPS AND
WENDY ALVAREZ LIVE IN
A BUILDING THAT NO
LONGER STANDS.
"OUR WORST NIGHTMARE
HAS COME TRUE," SHE
SAYS.
TONIGHT THIS BROKEN
COUNTRY FIGHTING TO
GET BACK ON ITS FEET.
THE SEARCH FOR THE
MISSING ONLY PAUSES
FOR THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM.
♪
A COUNTRY THAT HAS
LOST SO MUCH WORKING
AROUND THE CLOCK TO
SAVE WHAT MATTERS
MOST.
AS SEARCH TEAMS ENTER
ANOTHER NIGHT OF
RESCUES, THEY SAY
SURVIVING BEYOND FOUR
DAYS IN THE RUBBLE IS
INCREDIBLY DIFFICULT,
BUT IN SOME CASES
VICTIMS HAVE MADE IT A
MONTH.
LESTER?
>> MIGUEL ALMAGUER, AS
THE WORK GOES ON IN
MEXICO, THANK YOU.
>>> THE WAR OF WORDS
BETWEEN PRESIDENT
TRUMP AND KIM JONG-UN
HAS TAKEN A VERY
PERSONAL TURN AS NORTH
KOREA THREATENS TO
TEST ANOTHER HYDROGEN
BOMB, THIS TIME OVER
THE PACIFIC.
HERE'S NBC WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT KRISTEN
WELKER.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP PROMPTING A NEW
LEVEL OF BRINKSMANSHIP
WITH NORTH KOREA TODAY
TWEETING "KIM JONG UN
OF NORTH KOREA, WHO IS
OBVIOUSLY A MADMAN,
WHO DOESN'T MIND
STARVING OR KILLING
HIS PEOPLE, WILL BE
TESTED LIKE NEVER
BEFORE."
THE PRESIDENT TALKING
TOUGH AT A RALLY IN
ALABAMA TONIGHT.
>> ROCKET MAN SHOULD
HAVE BEEN HANDLED A
LONG TIME AGO.
>> HE MAY BE SMART.
HE MAY BE STRATEGIC.
AND HE MAY BE TOTALLY
CRAZY.
BUT YOU KNOW WHAT?
NO MATTER WHAT HE IS
WE'RE GOING TO HANDLE
IT, FOLKS.
>> Reporter: LAST
NIGHT NORTH KOREA'S
LEADER TOOK AIM AT THE
PRESIDENT PERSONALLY
WARNING "I WILL SURELY
AND DEFINITELY TAME
THE MENTALLY DERANGED
U.S. DOTARD WITH
FIRE."
DOTARD A DISPARAGING
TERM FOR A SENILE
SENIOR.
STILL, IT'S NOT THOSE
WORDS BUT NORTH
KOREA'S THREAT TO TEST
A HYDROGEN BOMB OVER
THE PACIFIC THAT'S
RAISING ALARM BELLS.
>> ALL OF OUR MILITARY
OPTIONS, AS THE
PRESIDENT HAS SAID, IS
ON THE TABLE.
>> Reporter: SO FAR
NORTH KOREA HAS
CONDUCTED ALL ITS
NUCLEAR TESTS IN
UNDERGROUND TUNNELS.
THE LAST TIME A
NUCLEAR WEAPON WAS
TESTED IN THE EARTH'S
ATMOSPHERE WAS IN 1980
WHEN CHINA FIRED A
BALLISTIC MISSILE INTO
A DESERT.
EXPERTS SAY IF NORTH
KOREA WERE TO TAKE
SUCH AN ACTION NOW,
THE RESULTS COULD BE
CATASTROPHIC.
>> THE NORTH KOREANS
ARE PLAYING WITH FIRE
HERE.
THE DANGER IS IF NORTH
KOREA MISFIRES, IF
THEY CAN'T CONTROL THE
TEST, THEY KILL
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: IF NORTH
KOREA LAUNCHED A BOMB,
PENTAGON OFFICIALS SAY
UNDER ONE SCENARIO
ADVANCED RADARS AND
SATELLITES ALL OVER
THE WORLD WOULD DETECT
THE LAUNCH, GIVING THE
U.S. THE MILITARY
OPTIONS TO INTERCEPT
IT OR SHOOT IT DOWN
BEFORE ANY RADIOACTIVE
MATERIAL COULD DO
HARM.
BUT THERE ARE NO
GUARANTEES.
KRISTEN WELKER, NBC
NEWS, THE WHITE HOUSE.
>>> THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION TODAY
REVERSED A KEY POLICY
ON SEXUAL ASSAULTS ON
COLLEGE CAMPUSES,
ROLLING BACK ANOTHER
OBAMA-ERA RULE.
EDUCATION SECRETARY
BETSY DeVOS ISSUED NEW
INTERIM GUIDELINES
THAT WILL ALLOW
COLLEGES TO USE A
HIGHER STANDARD OF
EVIDENCE WHEN HANDLING
COMPLAINTS.
DeVOS SAID THAT WHILE
SCHOOLS MUST CONTINUE
TO CONFRONT THESE
CRIMES HEAD ON, TOO
MANY STUDENTS HAD BEEN
UNFAIRLY CHARGED WITH
SEXUAL MISCONDUCT.
>>> ANOTHER TRUMP
OFFICIAL IS FACING
CRITICISM TONIGHT FOR
HIS STYLE OF TRAVEL.
HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES SECRETARY TOM
PRICE IS BEING
INVESTIGATED FOR
REPORTEDLY TAKING
DOZENS OF PRIVATE
PLANES FOR GOVERNMENT
WORK AT TAXPAYERS'
EXPENSE.
CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HALLIE
JACKSON HAS MORE ON
THAT FOR US TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THE HEAD
OF THE HEALTH AGENCY
HITTING TURBULENCE
WITH THE PRICE OF HIS
PRIVATE TRAVEL FOR
GOVERNMENT BUSINESS
NOW UNDER REVIEW BY
FEDERAL INVESTIGATORS.
HHS SECRETARY TOM
PRICE RACKED UP A BILL
OF MORE THAN $300,000
ON AT LEAST TWO DOZEN
CHARTER FLIGHTS THIS
YEAR, ACCORDING TO
POLITICO, INCLUDING
ONE TRIP FROM D.C. TO
PHILADELPHIA FOR A
CONFERENCE ON OPIOIDS.
THAT'S ABOUT 300 MILES
ROUND TRIP, ROUGHLY 90
BUCKS BY CAR, 550 FOR
THE TRAIN AND UP TO
$725 ON A COMMERCIAL
FLIGHT.
BUT PRICE PICKED THE
PRIVATE OPTION,
HOPPING A CHARTER FOR
AN ESTIMATED $25,000.
>> HE'S WASTING
TAXPAYER MONEY.
AND FOR A GROUP OF
PEOPLE WHO CALL
THEMSELVES FISCAL
CONSERVATIVES, THIS IS
AN EMBARRASSMENT.
>> Reporter: AN HHS
SPOKESPERSON DEFENDED
PRICE'S USE OF PRIVATE
PLANES AS MORE
EFFICIENT AND
EFFECTIVE GIVEN HIS
BUSY SCHEDULE.
TELLING NBC NEWS, "THE
DEMANDS ON HIS TIME
ARE TREMENDOUS."
IN 2009 WHEN PRICE WAS
A MEMBER OF CONGRESS
HE RAILED AGAINST THE
USE OF PRIVATE FLIGHTS
BY OTHER LAWMAKERS.
>> THIS IS JUST
ANOTHER EXAMPLE OF
FISCAL
IRRESPONSIBILITY RUN
AMOK IN CONGRESS RIGHT
NOW.
>> Reporter: JUST LAST
MONTH ANOTHER CABINET
MEMBER ALSO FACED
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS
TRAVEL HABITS AFTER
THE TREASURY SECRETARY
EXPLORED USING A
GOVERNMENT PLANE FOR
HIS HONEYMOON TRIP TO
EUROPE, HE SAYS FOR
SECURITY REASONS.
FOR THE
ADMINISTRATION, ALL
PART OF A BUMPY RIDE.
HALLIE JACKSON, NBC
NEWS, THE WHITE HOUSE.
>>> BOB DOLE HAS BEEN
HOSPITALIZED.
THE FORMER REPUBLICAN
PRESIDENTIAL CANDIDATE
WAS ADMITTED TO WALTER
REED MEDICAL CENTER
LAST WEEK FOR LOW
BLOOD PRESSURE.
A SPOKESWOMAN SAYS HIS
CONDITION IS BEING
CORRECTED WITH
MEDICATION.
IN A TWEET, THE
94-YEAR-OLD DOLE
THANKED PEOPLE FOR
THEIR PRAYERS AND SAID
HE HOPES TO BE HOME
SIPPING A COSMO IN A
FEW DAYS.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, WHAT HAPPENS
WHEN THE EMERGENCY IS
WITH 911 ITSELF?
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE
YOU TO A BIG CITY
WHERE DESPERATE CALLS
FOR HELP HAVE GONE
UNANSWERED.
>>> ALSO, THE DRIVER
HAILED AS A HERO AFTER
A SCHOOL BUS ERUPTS IN
FLAMES.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH A CRITICAL
PROBLEM PLAGUING A
MAJOR AMERICAN CITY.
IN CINCINNATI A SERIES
OF 911 OUTAGES HAVE
LEFT CALLERS TO FEND
FOR THEMSELVES.
SO WHY IS IT
HAPPENING?
NBC NEWS NATIONAL
INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT JEFF
ROSSEN IS GETTING
ANSWERS IN TONIGHT'S
"ROSSEN REPORTS."
>> Reporter: IN
CINCINNATI A PUBLIC
SAFETY CRISIS.
CALLERS UNABLE TO GET
THROUGH TO 911.
>> I WAS DRIVING HOME,
AND I SAW A CAR SMASH
UP AGAINST A POLE.
>> Reporter: WOW.
>> SO I CALLED 911
TWO, THREE TIMES AND
THEY NEVER ANSWERED.
IT JUST RANG AND RANG.
>> Reporter: YOU'RE
TRYING TO HELP THAT
DRIVER WHO MAY HAVE
NEEDED IMMEDIATE
MEDICAL ATTENTION?
>> CORRECT.
>> Reporter: AND
COUNTLESS OTHERS.
>> WE CALLED THEM
THREE TIMES AND NO
RESPONSE.
>> IT RANG AND RANG
AND RANG.
NO ONE ANSWERED.
>> Reporter: 911
OPERATORS EVENTUALLY
CALLED BACK, BUT IN AN
EMERGENCY IT COULD BE
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
LIFE AND DEATH.
ACCORDING TO AN
INTERNAL CITY DOCUMENT
OBTAINED BY NBC NEWS,
THERE HAVE BEEN TEN
911 OUTAGES SINCE JUNE
OF 2016.
THE LATEST ONE JUST
THIS SUMMER LASTING 3
HOURS AND 30 MINUTES.
CITY OFFICIALS SAY THE
SYSTEM CAN'T HANDLE
THE VOLUME OF WIRELESS
CALLS, PUTTING MOST OF
THE BLAME ON A PRIVATE
COMPANY CALLED COMTECH
THAT RUNS CINCINNATI'S
911 SYSTEM.
>> WE'VE GOT A SERVICE
PROVIDER AT THAT LEVEL
WHO HAS NOT BEEN AS
RELIABLE AND
DEPENDABLE AS WE
NEEDED THEM TO BE.
>> Reporter: YOU'RE
GETTING RID OF
COMTECH?
>> BASICALLY.
>> Reporter: THE CITY
IS NOW TAKING OVER 911
OPERATIONS ITSELF, BUT
TURNS OUT COMTECH IS A
MAJOR PLAYER IN THE
NATION'S 911 SYSTEM.
ACCORDING TO THE
COMPANY'S S.E.C.
FILINGS, THEY ARE
UTILIZED BY LITERALLY
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE IN
MORE THAN 30 STATES.
AND CINCINNATI ISN'T
THE ONLY PLACE
EXPERIENCING PROBLEMS.
IN CONNECTICUT,
OFFICIALS REPLACED
COMTECH'S SYSTEM WITH
A NEW COMPANY AFTER A
THREE-HOUR 911 OUTAGE
HIT 52 CALL-TAKING
SITES.
AND IN SOUTH DAKOTA
THIS YEAR OFFICIALS
TEMPORARILY SUSPENDED
PAYMENTS TO COMTECH
SAYING THE COMPANY WAS
SLOW TO FIX SEVERAL
RECURRING PROBLEMS
FOUND WITHIN THE
SYSTEM.
COMTECH DIDN'T RESPOND
TO MULTIPLE CALLS AND
E-MAILS FROM NBC NEWS.
SO I PAID THEM A VISIT
AT THEIR NEW YORK
HEADQUARTERS, AND WE
SEE THE COMPANY'S CFO.
WE'RE FROM NBC NEWS
DOING A STORY ABOUT
THE 911 SYSTEM.
>> LET ME JUST GET --
>> Reporter: OUTAGES
IN CINCINNATI.
WE HAVEN'T HAD ANY OF
OUR CALLS OR E-MAILS
RETURNED.
WE JUST WANTED TO GET
SOME ANSWERS.
WE WAIT AND WAIT FOR
MORE THAN 15 MINUTES,
BUT HE NEVER
RE-EMERGES.
INSTEAD, SENDING OUT
THE RECEPTIONIST.
>> THEY'RE NOT COMING
OUT.
>> Reporter: THEY'RE
NOT GOING TO COME OUT?
>> NO.
>> Reporter: AS FOR
CINCINNATI, IT WILL
TAKE MONTHS TO GET THE
NEW SYSTEM UP AND
RUNNING, LEAVING
LOCALS TO WONDER WHAT
HAPPENS DURING AN
EMERGENCY TONIGHT.
JEFF ROSSEN, NBC NEWS,
CINCINNATI.
>>> THERE'S MORE TO
TELL YOU ABOUT
TONIGHT.
WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT
WITH WHY ONE MAJOR
CITY IS PUTTING THE
BRAKES ON UBER.
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>>> THIS IS THE SCARY
SCENE IN KANSAS CITY.
A SCHOOL BUS ENGULFED
IN FLAMES AFTER ITS
ENGINE CAUGHT FIRE.
FORTUNATELY, THE
DRIVER QUICKLY GOT ALL
THE KIDS OFF THE BUS
THROUGH THE REAR DOOR,
AND NO ONE WAS
INJURED.
A WITNESS SAID IT WAS
A MIRACLE THAT
EVERYONE ESCAPED IN
TIME.
THE SCHOOL DISTRICT IS
CALLING THAT DRIVER A
HERO.
>>> IF YOU'RE PLANNING
A TRIP TO LONDON, YOU
MAY NOT BE ABLE TO
COUNT ON UBER TO GET
AROUND.
UBER IS LOSING ITS
LICENSE TO OPERATE IN
LONDON NEXT MONTH.
CITY OFFICIALS
DECLARED THE RIDE
SHARING GIANT UNFIT TO
RUN A TAXI SERVICE,
CLAIMING A LACK OF
CORPORATE
RESPONSIBILITY.
UBER CAN STILL OPERATE
IN LONDON WHILE IT
APPEALS THAT RULING.
>>> SHE WAS ONE OF
THREE AFRICAN-AMERICAN
WOMEN WHOSE
LITTLE-KNOWN WORK
CRUNCHING NUMBERS FOR
NASA HELPED EARLY
SPACE MISSIONS SUCCEED
AND INSPIRED THE BOOK
AND MOVIE "HIDDEN
FIGURES."
TODAY IN VIRGINIA
99-YEAR-OLD KATHERINE
JOHNSON HELPED OPEN A
NEW NASA BUILDING
NAMED IN HER HONOR,
THE KATHERINE G.
JOHNSON COMPUTATION
RESEARCH FACILITY.
TODAY SHE GAVE CREDIT
TO EVERYONE WHO HELPED
IN HER MATHEMATICAL
MISSION.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
WE'LL MEET SOME WOMEN
WHO HAVE RISEN TO THE
TOP IN LAW ENFORCEMENT
AND ARE INSPIRING
AMERICA.
NEXT AT 6: WILL THE WARRIORS GO
TO THE WHITE HOUSE?
===JESS VO===
HEAR WHAT STEPH CURRY THINKS AND
HOW THE FINAL DECISION WILL BE
MADE.
===RAJ /TAKE VO===
PLUS, "FEEL THE BERN". SENATOR
SANDERS COMES TO THE BAY AREA.
THE CHANGE HE )S PUSHING FOR...
TO SAVE COUNTLESS LIVES.
===NEXT CLOSE===
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
WHILE THE NUMBER OF
WOMEN WHO ARE POLICE
OFFICERS HAS GROWN,
THEY'RE STILL A SMALL
MINORITY IN THIS
COUNTRY AND EVEN FEWER
WOMEN ARE IN
LEADERSHIP ROLES.
BUT IN DALLAS THAT'S
CHANGING, ESPECIALLY
AT THE TOP.
REHEMA ELLIS HAS
TONIGHT'S "INSPIRING
AMERICA" REPORT.
>> SO I DID TALK TO --
>> Reporter: RENEE
HALL IS TAKING CHARGE
IN DALLAS LIKE NO
WOMAN HAS EVER DONE
BEFORE.
SHE'S THE CITY'S FIRST
FEMALE POLICE CHIEF,
COMMANDING A FORCE
THAT'S 80% MALE,
MAKING HER LIKELY TO
FACE UNPRECEDENTED
SCRUTINY.
DO YOU SEE A DOUBLE
STANDARD?
>> I THINK IT'S A
DOUBLE STANDARD, BUT I
DON'T THINK WE HAVE TO
ACCEPT IT.
YOU CAN'T JUDGE EVERY
WOMAN BY ME NO MORE
THAN I CAN JUDGE EVERY
MAN BY YOU.
>> Reporter: THE
18-YEAR VETERAN OF THE
DETROIT POLICE
DEPARTMENT IS TAKING
OVER IN DALLAS AT A
TOUGH TIME.
FIVE OFFICERS WERE
GUNNED DOWN LAST YEAR.
>> WE HAVE TO BE OKAY
WITH BEING EMOTIONAL
ABOUT THE THINGS THAT
WE SEE.
>> Reporter: SHE'S NOT
ALONE.
DALLAS NOW HAS THREE
WOMEN AT THE TOP LAW
ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES,
A FIRST IN THE CITY
AND RARE NATIONWIDE.
>> SO HOW IS IT GOING
DOWN HERE?
>> Reporter: FAITH
JOHNSON IS THE DALLAS
COUNTY DISTRICT
ATTORNEY.
>> WE ARE NOT HERE
BECAUSE WE'RE WOMEN.
WE ARE HERE BECAUSE WE
ARE CAPABLE,
QUALIFIED, EDUCATED,
TRAINED TO DO AN
OUTSTANDING JOB.
>> AND JUST HAPPEN TO
BE WOMEN.
>> Reporter: LUPE
VALDEZ IS THE COUNTY
SHERIFF.
AND THE FIRST OPENLY
GAY LATINA SHERIFF
EVER ELECTED IN TEXAS.
>> IT'S LONELY AT THE
TOP.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO
MAKE A PATH EASIER FOR
OTHERS TO COME UP.
>> Reporter: GIRLS
COULDN'T BE MORE
PROUD.
>> IT MEANS THAT WE'RE
BECOMING REPRESENTED,
ESPECIALLY WOMEN BUT
ALSO PEOPLE OF COLOR,
AND THAT'S AMAZING.
>> WE CAN BE WHAT THEY
ARE.
WE CAN BE IN THE TOP
JUST AS THEY ARE.
>> WE DON'T WANT THEM
TO STOP JUST THERE.
YOU NEED TO GO BEYOND
FROM WHERE WE ARE AND
GO TO THE TOP.
>> Reporter: THREE
EXTRAORDINARY WOMEN
BRINGING A NEW LOOK TO
LAW ENFORCEMENT AND
CHANGING THE CULTURE
OF EXPECTATIONS.
REHEMA ELLIS, NBC
NEWS, DALLAS.
>>> WE APPRECIATE YOU
SPENDING PART OF YOUR
EVENING WITH US.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
THE MIXED MESSAGES ABOUT FREE
SPEECH WE A
>>> IF THE SPEAKERS COME WE'LL
BE READY.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, IS IT ON
OR OFF?
THE MIXED MESSAGES ABOUT FREE
SPEECH WEEK AT CAL.
HIGH LEVEL CONSERVATIVES MAKING
LAST MINUTE DECISIONS.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD EVENING AND THANKS FOR
BEING WITH US ON THIS FRIDAY.
RAJ MATHAI.
>> JESSICA AGUIRRE.
CONFUSION TONIGHT OVER FREE
SPEECH WEEK AT CAL.
HERE IS WHAT WE KNOW.
ALL RIGHT PROSKT FEWER MILO
YIANNOPOULOS IS IN THE BAY AREA.
HE LANDED TODAY AND WILL HOLDZ
NEWS CONFERENCE TOMORROW AT
TREASURE ISLAND ANN COULTER.
SHE IS OUT.
CONSERVATIVE COMMENTATOR SENT AN
EMAIL TO THE ASSOCIATED PRESS
SAYING SHE IS NOT COMING TO CAL.
BUT WHAT ABOUT STEVE BANNON?
FORMER WHITE HOUSE CHIEF
STRATEGIST HAS NOT CONFIRMED NOR
DENIED HIS PARTICIPATION.
NBC BAY AREA JODI HERNANDEZ
JOINS US LIVE WITH THE LATEST
REACTION FROM THE FREE SPEECH
WEEK ORGANIZERS AND THE
UNIVERSITY THIS THIS JUST GOES
ON AND ON JODI.
>> Reporter: IT DOES.
BERKELEY PATRIOT MEMBERS TELL ME
THEY ARE FINALIZING THE LIST OF
SPEAKERS.
BUT THEY INSIST THE EVENT WILL
TAKE PLACE AND THE UNIVERSITY
SAYS THEY'LL BE READY.
AS CAL STUDENTS GEAR UP FOR
TOMORROW'S BIG FOOTBALL GAME
AGAINST USC THEY ARE ALSO
BRACING FOR WHAT'S EXPECTED TO
BE AN BIGGER EVENT ON CAMPUS.
FOUR DAYS OF CONTROVERSIAL
ULTRACONSERVATIVE SPEAKERS,
INCLUDING MILO YIANNOPOULOS.
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF OUTSIDE
ORGANIZATIONS FROM OUR SCHOOL
COMING IN.
AND THEY'RE DISRUPTING