>>> ON THIS SATURDAY NIGHT,
STATE OF EMERGENCY.
THE MASSIVE WILDFIRE THREATENING
YOSEMITE DOUBLES IN SIZE
OVERNIGHT.
WE'RE ON THE FRONT LINES AS HOT
SHOT CREWS BATTLE THIS
FAST-MOVING BLAZE, NOW
THREATENING SAN FRANCISCO'S
POWER SUPPLY.
>>> SEARCHING FOR A SERIOUS
STRATEGY.
WITH U.S. WARSHIPS ON ALERT IN
THE MEDITERRANEAN, THE PRESIDENT
LOOKS FOR OPTIONS AFTER DOCTORS
INSIDE SYRIA CONFIRM THOUSANDS
WERE TREATED FOR SYMPTOMS OF A
CHEMICAL ATTACK.
>>> A MANHUNT IS UNDER WAY FOR
THE TEEN WHO ALLEGEDLY KILLED A
BELOVED WORLD WAR II VETERAN.
>>> MARCHING AGAIN, HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS RALLY FOR JOBS AND
JUSTICE TODAY IN WASHINGTON,
JUST AS THEY DID 50 YEARS AGO TO
HEAR DR. KING'S HISTORIC "I HAVE
A DREAM" ADDRESS.
>>> AND A MAYOR'S MISSION TO
REVITALIZE GARY, INDIANA, A TOWN
THAT HAS LONG BEEN DOWN ON ITS
LUCK, NOW SIGNS OF HOPE AND
HEALING ARE EVERYWHERE.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THAT HUGE WILDFIRE BURNING IN
CENTRAL CALIFORNIA IS GROWING
VIRTUALLY UNCHECKED TONIGHT AS
ITS IMPACT IS BEING FELT MORE
THAN 100 MILES AWAY.
FAR FROM THE FIREFIGHT, THE CITY
OF SAN FRANCISCO IS UNDER A
STATE OF EMERGENCY TONIGHT
BECAUSE ITS WATER SUPPLY AND
HYDROELECTRIC POWER COME FROM A
RESERVOIR NEAR THE FIRE ZONE.
2,700 FIREFIGHTERS ARE NOW ON
THE LINES BACKED BY A RELENTLESS
AIR ASSAULT, BUT WORKING AGAIN
TO RUGGED LANDSCAPE AND
EXHAUSTION.
THEY HAVE MANAGED TO CONTAIN
ONLY A TIE KNEE PIECE OF THIS
FIRE.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO IS IN
GROVELAND, CALIFORNIA, TO BRING
US THE VERY LATEST.
TOM, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: HI, LESTER.
PUBLIC UTILITY CREWS SAY THAT
THEY ARE CONFIDENT THEY CAN
MAINTAIN WATER AND POWER TO SAN
FRANCISCO.
THIS FIRE STATION BEHIND ME IS
SERVING AS AN INFORMATION POINT
SO RESIDENTS CAN GET REAL TIME
UPTATES ON EXACTLY WHAT THE
FIRE'S STATUS IS NOW.
5,500 HOMES REMAIN THREATENED
AND THIS FIRE IS IN VERY STEEP
TERRAIN.
>> STILL HOLDING OUT.
>> Reporter: FROM THE COCKPIT OF
A NATIONAL GUARD C-130.
>> GOT YOU IN SIGHT, COMING IN
POSITION BEHIND YOU.
>> Reporter: TO BLACK HAWK
HELICOPTERS, THE VIEW OF THE
DOWN-TO-DUSK AERIAL MISSION TO
ATTACK A FIRE THAT HAS GROWN
INTO ONE THE COUNTRY'S MOST
SERIOUS, THE CHALLENGE GETTING
THE WATER DROP FROM SO-CALLED
BAMBI BUCKETS ON JUST THE RIGHT
SPOT TO GIVE THE GROUND CREWS A
QUICK ADVANTAGE.
MEANWHILE ON THE GROUND,
HOMEOWNERS LIKE CAREEN AND MATT
ARE ON THE EDGE, LEAVING ON
THEIR OWN WHEN THE FLAMES GET
TOO CLOSE, AND RETURNING HOME
WHEN THE WINDS SEEM TO BE IN
THEIR FAVOR.
>> TWICE WE WENT WITH FRIENDS
AND WE GOT BACK TO PINE MOUNTAIN
LAKE AND THEN BACK AGAIN.
>> Reporter: THIS FAMILY
VISITING FROM GERMANY DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND THE RADIO REPORTS
UNTIL THEY GOT HERE.
>> WE HEADED OUT AND ASKED
SOMEBODY AND THEY TOLD US THAT
IN THE NORTH I THINK THERE IS A
FOREST FIRE.
>> Reporter: THICK SMOKE HAS NOW
DRIFTED ALL THE WAY TO RENO,
NEVADA, FORCING THE CANCELLATION
OF SOME OUTDOOR EVENTS.
AT 200 SQUARE MILES, THE RIM
FIRE IS MOSTLY CENTERED IN THE
STANDIS LASS NATIONAL FOREST AND
A REMOTE CORNER OF YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK.
HIGHWAY 120 INTO AND OUT OF THE
PARK IS CLOSED.
THE BURN AREA SO LARGE, IT'S
VISIBLE FROM SPACE.
THIS FIRE IS MOVING THROUGH
THESE FORESTS AT ABOUT 2,000
DEGREES, INCINERATING ALL THE
VEGETATION AND TURNING THE
GROUND INTO THIS WHITE-GRAY ASH.
IT WILL TAKE DECADES FOR THIS
FOREST TO GROW BACK.
>> THERE'S A LOT OF HEAT ON THAT
ROAD --
>> Reporter: AT 3:00 A.M., WE
CAUGHT UP WITH SACRAMENTO
FIREFIGHTERS, 14 HOURS INTO A
24-HOUR SHIFT.
FRANK BLACK WAS EXHAUSTED.
>> THE ANXIETY LEVEL IS JUST UP,
SO IT'S JUST HARD TO SLEEP, AT
LEAST FOR ME IT IS.
>> Reporter: WHILE BASE CAMP
OFFERS HOT FOOD, SHOWERS AND
BEDS 24/7, FIREFIGHTERS ARE
TONIGHT WONDERING HOW LONG IT
WILL TAKE TO CONTAIN A 200
SQUARE MILE FIRE.
AT THE MOMENT THIS FIRE IS ONLY
5% CONTAINED.
FIRE COMMANDERS CONTINUE TO TELL
US THEY ARE CONFIDENT THAT THEY
WILL KEEP THIS FIRE AWAY FROM
THE TOURIST AREAS OF YOSEMITE,
THAT AND YOSEMITE VALLEY.
THE FIRE LINE IS ABOUT 20 MILES
FROM THAT AREA.
LESTER, BACK TO YOU.
>> TOM COSTELLO TONIGHT, THANKS.
>>> TO THE CRISIS IN SYRIA NOW.
THE WHITE HOUSE IS WEIGHING ITS
OPTIONS AGAINST THE ASSAD REGIME
AFTER REPORTS THAT SYRIA'S ARMY
USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON ITS
CITIZENS.
DOCTORS WITHOUT BORDERS, WHICH
HAS TEAMS IN SYRIA, CONFIRMS
THAT THOUSANDS HAVE BEEN TREATED
FOR SYMPTOMS OF EXPOSURE TO A
CHEMICAL AGENT.
TONIGHT AS THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION CONSIDERS ITS
RESPONSE, U.S. WARSHIPS ARE ON
ALERT IN THE MEDITERRANEAN NEAR
SYRIA.
WE HAVE TWO REPORTS BEGINNING
WITH NBC'S EAMON MOHYELDIN IN
CAIRO.
>> Reporter: DOCTORS TREATED
MORE THAN 3,600 PATIENTS
WEDNESDAY, THE DAY OF THE
CHEMICALS WEAPONS ATTACK, OUT OF
WHICH MORE THAN 350 DIED AS A
RESULT.
NOW ALL OF THEM THEY SAY
DISPLAYED SYMPTOMS OF
NEUROTOXICITY, AN INDICATION
THAT PERHAPS CHEMICAL WEAPONS
WERE ACTUALLY USED.
THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT HAS DENIED
ANY RESPONSIBILITY AND DENIED
THAT IT USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS,
MORE IMPORTANTLY TODAY ON SYRIAN
STATE TELEVISION THEY SHOWED
IMAGES OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS THAT
WERE ALLEGEDLY FOUND IN AREAS
THAT WERE CONTROLLED BY SYRIAN
REBELS, AN INDICATION THAT
PERHAPS IT WAS THE REBELS THAT
WERE RESPONSIBLE FOR LAUNCHING
THESE WEAPONS.
MEANWHILE, THE TOP U.N.
DISARMAMENT CHIEF, THE
UNDERSECRETARY-GENERAL FOR THE
UNITED NATIONS ARRIVED TODAY IN
DAMASCUS.
SHE'S BEEN TRYING TO PRESS THE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT TO GIVE U.N.
INSPECTORS ACCESS TO THE SITE OF
ATTACKS SO THAT THEY CAN
DETERMINE EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED.
AS THE U.S. AND OTHER COUNTRIES
WEIGH A POSSIBLE MILITARY OPTION
AGAINST SYRIA, A SENIOR IRANIAN
LAWMAKER TODAY WARNED THAT ANY
MILITARY INTERVENTION INSIDE
SYRIA WOULD RESULT IN A REGIONAL
WAR THAT WOULD NOT END FAVORABLY
TO THE UNITED STATES OR TO
ALLIES ACROSS THE REGION.
LESTER?
>> EAMON MOHYELDIN IN CAIRO,
THANKS.
>>> WE TURN TO NBC'S DAVID
GREGORY IN WASHINGTON.
THE PRESIDENT MET WITH HIS
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISERS
TODAY, DAVID, WHAT ARE WE
LEARNING?
>> WHAT'S CLEAR, LESTER, THERE
IS A NEW SENSE OF URGENCY IN THE
WHITE HOUSE AFTER THIS ATTACK.
THE HUMAN COSTS IN SYRIA HAVE
BECOME JUST TOO HIGH TO BEAR.
DESPITE THAT, THERE IS
DISAGREEMENT I CAN TELL YOU
AMONG THE PRESIDENT'S ADVISERS
ABOUT WHAT SHOULD COME NEXT.
AMONG THE QUESTIONS, WHAT IS THE
LEGAL JUSTIFICATION FOR MILITARY
ACTION AND WHAT WOULD AN ATTACK
ACCOMPLISH?
THE INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY IS
TRYING TO VERIFY FACTS ON THE
GROUND AND AT THIS POINT THE
WHITE HOUSE IS SAYING LITTLE,
ONLY STRESSING THAT WHILE THE
U.S. HAS A RANGE OF OPTIONS
AVAILABLE, THE PRESIDENT WILL
MAKE AN INFORMED DECISION IN A
DELIBERATE WAY RATHER THAN
PURSUE QUICK ACTION BEFORE ALL
THE FACTS ARE KNOWN.
THE PRESIDENT DESCRIBED THIS
WEEK'S ALLEGED CHEMICAL ATTACK
AS A "BIG EVENT WITH GRAVE
CONCERN."
RIGHT NOW THE U.S. NAVY HAS FOUR
GUIDED MISSILE DESTROYERS IN THE
MEDITERRANEAN, TWO WELL WITHIN
FIRING RANGE OF ANY TARGETS IN
SYRIA.
DEFENSE SECRETARY HAGEL DECLINED
TO DISCUSS ANY SPECIFIC FORCED
MOVEMENTS, BUT HE LEFT LITTLE
DOUBT HE THINKS CHEMICAL WEAPONS
WERE INVOLVED SAYING, "IT
APPEARS TO BE WHAT HAPPENED, USE
OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS."
ON THE TABLE LIMITED AIR
STRIKES, MOST LIKELY CRUISE
MISSILES LAUNCHED FROM THOSE
DESTROYERS, TARGETING KEY ASSAD
MILITARY COMMAND POSTS.
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS TELLING US
THE CASE FOR MILITARY ACTION IS
TAKING SHAPE.
MILITARY OFFICIALS ARE WARNING
THAT EXTREMIST FIGURES LIKE AL
QAEDA ARE BEING DRAWN TO THE
CHAOS IN SYRIA LIKE "MOTHS TO A
FLAME."
YOU ADD CHEMICAL WEAPONS TO THE
PICTURE, AND THAT'S WHY YOU HEAR
THE PRESIDENT TALK ABOUT CORE
NATIONAL INTERESTS BEING AT
STAKE HERE.
LESTER?
>> DAVID GREGORY, DAVID, THANKS.
>>> NOW TO SPOKANE WHERE FOLKS
ARE SHAKING THEIR HEADS IN
DISGUST AND SADNESS AFTER THE
BRUTAL KILLING THIS WEEK OF A
MAN WHO SERVED HIS COUNTRY IN
WORLD WAR II, AND WAS ALWAYS
THERE FOR HIS NEIGHBORS, TOO.
AS MUCH AS THEY TRIED TO, THERE
IS JUST NO MAKING SENSE OF WHAT
TWO TEENAGED BOYS WOULD
ALLEGEDLY BEAT THE ELDERLY MAN,
WHO WAS BELOVED BY NEARLY
EVERYONE HE MET.
NBC'S MICHELLE FRANZEN HAS THE
STORY.
>> Reporter: DURING HIS 88
YEARS, FRIENDS AND FAMILY SAY
DELBERT "SHORTY" BELTON, ALWAYS
EMBRACED LIFE, WHETHER AS A
WORLD WAR II VETERAN, FAMILY
MAN, OR FRIEND.
>> ANY TIME I NEEDED ANYTHING,
HE WAS ALWAYS THERE.
>> Reporter: IN SPOKANE,
WASHINGTON, THIS PAST WEEK,
BELTON WAS ROBBED OF HIS LIFE IN
WHAT POLICE SAY WAS A BRUTAL AND
RANDOM BEATING AT THE HANDS OF
TWO 16-YEAR-OLDS.
>> THEY ROBBED HIM, THEY BEAT
HIM AND THEY KILLED HIM.
>> Reporter: ONE OF THE TEEN
SUSPECTS TURNED HIMSELF IN
THURSDAY AND IS BEING CHARGED AS
AN ADULT WITH FIRST-DEGREE
MURDER AND ROBBERY.
THE SEARCH IS STILL ON FOR THE
SECOND SUSPECT.
FRIEND NATALIE FIOM SAYS BELTON
WAS WAITING FOR HER OUTSIDE THE
EAGLES LODGE WHEN HE WAS
ATTACKED.
>> THE REASON HE WAS IN THE CAR
WAS BECAUSE HE WAS WAITING FOR
ME, BECAUSE HE'S A RESPECTFUL
GENTLEMAN.
>> Reporter: AT 18, BELTON WAS
DRAFTED.
FAMILY AND FRIENDS SAY HE WAS
INJURED IN THE BATTLE FOR
OKINAWA.
>> HE'S ALWAYS HELPED PEOPLE.
HE'S FOUGHT FOR OUR COUNTRY.
THERE'S NO EXCUSE FOR THE WAY HE
DIED.
>> Reporter: NEPHEW ALAN HILLS
REMEMBERS HOW BELTON HELPED HIM.
>> HE WASN'T JUST MY GREAT
UNCLE.
HE WAS A GREAT PERSON.
>> Reporter: A GREAT PERSON,
HILL SAYS, WHO LOVED TO RESTORE
OLD CARS AND GAVE HIM A CAR WHEN
HE WAS UNEMPLOYED.
>> IT SEEMS TRIVIAL BUT HE
REALLY DID SAVE MY LIFE.
HE MADE IT POSSIBLE FOR ME TO GO
GET A JOB, FIND WORK.
>> Reporter: ACTS OF KINDNESS
AND BRAVERY THAT DEFINED
BELTON'S LIFE.
FRIDAY NIGHT, A VIGIL WAS HELD
IN HIS HONOR AND A MAKESHIFT
MEMORIAL GROWS AS THIS COMMUNITY
MOURNS THE LOSS OF A HERO.
MICHELLE FRANZEN, NBC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>>> 50 YEARS AGO, A QUARTER OF A
MILLION PEOPLE STREAMED ONTO THE
NATIONAL MALL FOR A MARCH THAT
WOULD ENERGIZE THE PASSAGE OF
THE 1964 CIVIL RIGHTS ACT AND
THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT ONE YEAR
LATER.
THEY HEARD THE REVEREND DR.
MARTIN LUTHER KING DELIVER  ONE
OF THE MOST FAMOUS SPEECHES IN
AMERICAN HISTORY.
TODAY THOSE WHO WERE THERE
CONVERGED AGAIN TO GALVANIZE A
NEW GENERATION.
NBC'S KRISTEN WELKER IS ON THE
MALL FOR THIS DRAMATIC DAY.
KRISTEN, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER, GOOD
EVENING TO YOU.
TODAY THE MALL WAS FILLED WITH
MORE THAN 200,000 PEOPLE, ALL
HERE TO REMEMBER AND TO CONTINUE
THE FIGHT THAT GAINED NEW GROUND
HERE A HALF A CENTURY AGO.
MARCHING IN UNITY, ANOTHER STEP
THESE FOLKS SAY IN THE NATION'S
LONG JOURNEY TOWARD CIVIL
RIGHTS.
>> WE DO STILL CARE ABOUT OUR
RIGHTS AND OUR CIVIL RIGHTS.
>> Reporter: TODAY A SEA OF
PEOPLE CAME FROM ALL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY, INCLUDING RUSSELL GRADY
WHO BOARDED A BUS EARLY THIS
MORNING IN PATTERSON, NEW
JERSEY.
>> I'M ENERGIZED.
>> Reporter: THE 82-YEAR-OLD
TOOK PART IN THE MARCH ON
Z WASHINGTON NEARLY 50 YEARS
AGO.
>> MY GUT FEELING THEN IT, WE
DIDN'T KNOW IF WE COULD MAKE THE
PROGRESS THAT WE'VE MADE.
BUT TODAY I CAN SAY THAT WE'VE
MADE A LOT OF PROGRESS.
>> FREE AT LAST.
FREE AT LAST!
>> Reporter: ON THAT DAY DR.
MARTIN LUTHER KING JR. DELIVERED
WORDS THAT MADE HISTORY.
>> BECAUSE I HAVE A DREAM.
>> Reporter: AND TOGETHER, THESE
AMERICANS, 250,000 STRONG,
FORCED ACTION.
>> A YEAR LATER, OF COURSE,
CONGRESS PASSED IN 1964 THE
CIVIL RIGHTS RIGHT.
>> Reporter: D.C. DELEGATE
ELEANOR HOLMES NORTON WAS A
LAW STUDENT IN HER 20s AT THE
TIME, A NONVIOLENT ACTIVIST AND
ONE OF THE MARCH'S FEW FEMALE
ORGANIZERS.
>> THIS WAS A MARCH IN THE
SPIRIT OF NON-VIOLENCE IN EVERY
SENSE OF THE WORD.
IT WAS FULL OF JOY AND
EXALTATION.
FINALLY THIS WAS HAPPENING.
>> Reporter: DAVID BLAHA WAS
AMONG A QUARTER OF THE MARCHERS
WHO WERE WHITE.
TODAY HE CAME BACK WITH HIS
FAMILY INCLUDING HIS
GRANDDAUGHTER, WHO IS 11 YEARS
OLD, THE SAME AGE HE WAS ON THAT
HISTORIC DAY.
WHAT IS THAT LIKE FOR YOU AS A
GRANDFATHER?
>> WELL, I'M -- IT'S VERY
EMOTIONAL.
BECAUSE I'M THINKING WHEN SHE'S
MY AGE, SHE'LL HAVE HER
GRANDCHILDREN AT THE 100th.
>> WHILE THE COUNTRY HAS MADE
PROGRESS, THESE MARCHERS SAY
THERE IS MORE WORK TO DO IN THE
WAKE OF TRAYVON MARTIN, THE
SUPREME COURT'S DECISION TO
SCALE BACK THE VOTING RIGHTS ACT
AND WITH THE BLACK UNEMPLOYMENT
RATE SOARING.
MSNBC HOST REVEREND AL SHARPTON
ORGANIZED TODAY'S EVENT ALONG
WITH DR. KING'S SON.
>> THEY CAME TO WASHINGTON SO WE
COULD COME TODAY.
>> WE KNOW THAT THE DREAM IS FAR
FROM BEING REALIZED.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO STAND UP, SPEAK
UP, SPEAK OUT, AND GET IN THE
WAY!
MAKE SOME NOISE!
>> Reporter: AND NOW IN THE
SHADOW OF AMERICA'S COMPLICATED
RACIAL HISTORY, NEW DREAMS ARE
GIVING WAY.
>> I HAVE A DREAM THAT ONE DAY
16-YEAR-OLD KIDS DON'T HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT BEING KILLED WHEN
THEY'RE WALKING HOME FROM
7-ELEVEN.
>> I HAVE A DREAM THAT THE
AFRICAN-AMERICAN STORY WILL
BECOME A STORY OF THE WORLD.
>> THAT DR. KING'S DREAM, HIS
LEGACY WILL NEVER BE FORGOTTEN.
>> Reporter: NOW THE ACTUAL
ANNIVERSARY IS ON WEDNESDAY.
ON THAT DAY, PRESIDENT OBAMA
WILL DELIVER A SPEECH FROM THE
STEPS OF THE LINCOLN MEMORIAL,
THE SAME EXACT SPOT THAT DR.
MARTIN LUTHER KING DELIVERED HIS
"I HAVE A DREAM" SPEECH 50 YEARS
AGO.
LESTER?
>> NBC'S KRISTEN WELKER IN
WASHINGTON, THANKS.
>>> NBC WANTS TO HEAR FROM YOU
SHARE YOUR DREAM WITH YOUR
FELLOW AMERICANS.
SIMPLY RECORD A SHORT VIDEO
SAYING "I HAVE A DREAM THAT,"
AND FILL IN THE BLANK.
POST IT ON TWITTER AND FACEBOOK
USING #DREAMDAY, AND LET YOUR
VOICE BE HEARD.
AND THIS PROGRAM NOTE TOMORROW,
"MEET THE PRESS" WILL
REBROADCAST AN HOUR-LONG
INTERVIEW WITH DR. KING RECORDED
AUGUST 25th, 1963, THREE DAYS
BEFORE THE "I HAVE A DREAM"
SPEECH.
A SECOND HOUR WITH HOST DAVID
GREGORY WILL ADDRESS WHERE THAT
DREAM IS TODAY.
>>> WHEN "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
CONTINUES FOR THIS SATURDAY, THE
CAN DO SPIRIT OF GARY, INDIANA'S
MAYOR ON A MISSION.
A CITY ON THE ROPES NOW POISED
FOR A REBOUND.
>>> AND YOU MIGHT BE SURPRISED
WHAT'S WAITING FOR YOU AT YOUR
LOCAL LIBRARY THESE DAYS.
>>> TODAY, GARY, INDIANA, IS A
FAR CRY FROM ITS GLORY DAYS WHEN
IT WAS A THRIVING STEEL TOWN.
TODAY THE OFFICIAL UNEMPLOYMENT
NUMBER IS CLOSE TO 10%.
CONTINUING OUR SERIES "IN PLAIN
SIGHT" WHICH FOCUSES ON POVERTY
IN AMERICA, SUPPORTED BY THE
FORD FOUNDATION, HARRY SMITH
INTRODUCES US TO ITS
INSPIRATIONAL MAYOR, WHO IS ON A
MISSION TO SAVE HER CITIZENS.
>> Reporter: GARY, INDIANA, ONE
OF THE FIRST NOTCHES ON
AMERICA'S RUST BELT, A TOWN SO
LONG PAST ITS PRIME THE
DEMOLITION OF ONE OF ITS
THOUSANDS OF ABANDONED BUILDINGS
IS ACTUALLY A SMALL SIGN OF
PROGRESS.
GARY'S POPULATION IS LESS THAN
HALF OF WHAT IT ONCE WAS.
SOME OF ITS NEIGHBORHOODS ARE
RIDDLED WITH CRIME AND THE
PEOPLE WHO ARE LEFT HERE HAVE
HEARD EVERY POLITICAL PROMISE IN
THE BOOK.
IF EVER THERE WAS A CITY IN NEED
OF A SAVIOR, IT'S GARY.
>> HEY, WHAT'S UP?
GOOD MORNING, HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> Reporter: AND IT MIGHT JUST
BE THIS ONE, MAYOR KAREN
FREEMAN-WILSON.
>> I GREW UP HERE, WENT TO
PUBLIC SCHOOLS AND THEN WENT TO
HARVARD COLLEGE AND HARVARD LAW
SCHOOL.
COULDN'T WAIT TO GET BACK.
>> Reporter: COULDN'T WAIT TO
GET BACK?
>> I COULD NOT WAIT TO GET BACK
TO GARY, INDIANA.
>> Reporter: HER FATHER AND
GRANDFATHER BOTH WORKED IN THE
STEEL MILLS AND SHE HERSELF
SEEMS UNAFRAID OF PUTTING A
LITTLE ELBOW GREASE INTO
CLEANING UP HER TOWN.
MADAM MAYOR, YOU PICKING UP
TRASH, IS THIS GOING TO HELP
SAVE THE CITY OF GARY?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
IT'S BECAUSE IT'S -- YOU KNOW,
SOMETIMES YOU HAVE TO LEAD BY
EXAMPLE.
>> Reporter: IT SEEMS SIMPLE,
MAYBE EVEN SIMPLISTIC, BUT BY
EXAMPLE, THE MAYOR IS TRYING TO
SHOW THE PEOPLE OF GARY THEY
HAVE SOMETHING WORTH SAVING.
WHAT'S THE BIGGEST PROBLEM
YOU'VE GOT?
>> REALLY GETTING PEOPLE TO
BELIEVE AGAIN.
PEOPLE HAVE SEEN GARY IN A
CERTAIN WAY FOR SO LONG THAT
IT'S HARD FOR THEM TO UNDERSTAND
THAT IT CAN GET BETTER, THAT IT
WILL GET BETTER.
>> Reporter: THE MAYOR BELIEVES
GARY HAS ASSETS WORTH INVESTING
IN, SO THE AIRPORT'S GETTING A
NEW RUNWAY, MILLIONS HAVE BEEN
SPENT SPIFFING UP GARY'S
GLORIOUS LAKEFRONT, AND TO FILL
GARY'S EMPTY HOUSES, THE CITY
WILL BE HAPPY TO SELL ONE TO YOU
FOR $1.
YEP, ONE BUCK.
>> I SEE YOU WORKING ON YOUR
FLOWERS THERE.
>> Reporter: THE FORMER HIGH
SCHOOL AND COLLEGE POINT GUARD
SEEMS TO HAVE A KNACK FOR
RUNNING GARY'S OFFENSE.
YOU DON'T SEEM LIKE A POLITICIAN
TO ME.
>> THAT'S BECAUSE I'M NOT.
I'M A PUBLIC SERVANT.
THERE IS A DIFFERENCE.
>> Reporter: AND MAYBE IT'S THE
LITTLE THINGS THAT WILL END UP
MAKING A BIG DIFFERENCE.
>> THE PICKUP'S GOTTEN BETTER,
CLEANUP'S GOTTEN BETTER.
>> YOU CAN SEE A LOT OF THINGS
BEING RENOVATED, A LOT OF HOUSES
BEING TORN DOWN, THINGS THAT'S
SUPPOSED TO BE DONE IS BEING
DONE NOW.
>> Reporter: GREEN GRASS AND
IMPATIENS ON THE PORCH.
IN GARY, THOSE ARE SIGNS OF
REBIRTH.
HARRY SMITH, NBC NEWS, GARY,
INDIANA.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE BEACH
ALONG FLORIDA'S ATLANTIC COAST,
ANYBODY GOT ANY SAND TO SPARE?
S FROM
>>> FLORIDA'S ATLANTIC COAST,
FAMOUS FOR ITS SURF AND SANDY
BEACHES, BUT TONIGHT THE SANDS
OF TIME ARE WORKING AGAINST THE
STATE'S FAMOUS BEACHES.
HERE'S KERRY SANDERS.
>> Reporter: FLORIDA'S
COASTLINE, 663 MILES OF
SIGNATURE BEACHES, BUT IN SOUTH
FLORIDA, A CRISIS.
THANKS TO STORMS AND
DEVELOPMENT, THE SAND IS
DISAPPEARING.
>> IT IS QUITE A CONCEPT, BUT
UNFORTUNATELY IT'S TRUE.
>> Reporter: AND UNLIKE BEFORE,
PUMPING SAND FROM OFFSHORE BACK
ON TO THE BEACHES HERE IS NO
LONGER AN OPTION.
>> THE PROBLEM IS WE'RE RUNNING
OUT OF SAND OFFSHORE.
WE PRETTY MUCH VACUUMED
EVERYTHING UP.
>> Reporter: OFFICIALLY
MIAMI-DADE RUNS OUT OF OFFSHORE
SAND NEXT MONTH.
IN GOVERNMENT MEETINGS, ONE
OPTION DISCUSSED IS SHIPPING
SAND IN FROM THE BAHAMAS OR THE
TURKS AND CAICOS ISLANDS BUT
SHIPPING SAND FROM THE ISLANDS
IS NOT CHEAP.
ONE OTHER IDEA BEGINS WITH A
BOTTLE.
WHEN THEY'RE EMPTY, THIS GLASS
CAN BE CRUSHED AND WHAT DOES
CRUSHED GLASS LOOKS LIKE?
LOOKS AND FEELS LIKE SAND.
>> IT'S FINE.
IT'S HOMOGENOUS.
IT'S NOT STICKY OR ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: ERIC MYERS SAID IT
WOULD NOT ONLY WORK BUT BE THE
ULTIMATE RECYCLING EFFORT.
>> IT'S RECYCLING IN ITS PURIST.
>> Reporter: BECAUSE GLASS COMES
FROM?
>> GLASS COMES FROM SAND.
>> Reporter: BEACH GOERS CAN
BARELY TELL THE DIFFERENCE.
>> DOESN'T FEEL LIKE GLASS.
>> IF YOU WANT TO SAY IT'S GLASS
OR SOMETHING, I REALLY THOUGHT
IT WAS SAND.
I THINK THAT'S GREAT.
>> Reporter: FLORIDA'S BEACHES
PERHAPS GIVING NEW MEANING TO
WALKING ON BROKEN GLASS.
KERRY SANDERS, NBC NEWS, FT.
LAUDERDALE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, SOME
LIBRARIES SHOWING A NEW KIND OF
BOOK SMARTS.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, KINDLES AND
iPADS HAVE GIVEN US NEW WAYS TO
READ BOOKS AND THAT'S GOT SOME
LOCAL LIBRARIES HAVING TO
REINVENT THEMSELVES.
TONIGHT JOHN YANG WITH CHANGES
AT THE CHECKOUT DESK.
>> Reporter: WHEN RALPH
MANDARINO GOES TO THE GROSSE
POINT PUBLIC LIBRARY OUTSIDE OF
DETROIT IT'S NOT ALWAYS FOR A
BOOK.
>> I HAVE A TOOL THAT'S ON
RESERVE.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
TOOL, A TREE TRIMMER.
HE SAYS IT'S A BETTER TOOL THAN
OWNING ONE.
IF I BOUGHT THAT HOW OFTEN WOULD
YOU USE IT.
>> THAT'S THE POINT.
YOU'D ONLY USE IT MAYBE ONCE A
YEAR.
>> Reporter: HERE AT THE GROSSE
POINT LIBRARY THERE ARE 285
TOOLS TO BORROW, EVERYTHING FROM
"A" ON ADJUSTABLE WRENCH TO "X"
AN XACTO KNIFE.
THEY'RE STILL LOOKING FOR "Y"
AND "Z."
LIBRARIES AREN'T JUST FOR BOOKS
ANYMORE.
DVDs ARE COMMON ON LIBRARY
SHELVES BUT THE SKOKIE,
ILLINOIS, LIBRARY, HAS THINGS TO
MAKE DIGITAL VIDEOS, FLIP CAMS,
LAPTOPS AND SMALL VIDEO CAMERAS.
>> SO I CAN PUT IT ON MY HEAD.
>> Reporter: THAT YOU CAN WEAR.
>> WE HAVE PEOPLE USING A GO PRO
CAMERA FOR EXTREME STUFF.
>> Reporter: LIBRARIANS SAY IT'S
ALL ABOUT MEETING THE NEEDS OF
THEIR COMMUNITIES IN A WORLD
THAT'S SHIFTING FROM THE PRINTED
WORLD TO DIGITAL CONTENT.
IN ANN ARBOR, MICHIGAN, IT MEANS
OFFERING THINGS THAT CAN'T BE
DOWNLOADED, LIKE TELESCOPES AND
STEEL DRUMS.
♪
KIDS ARE DRAWN TO THE MUSICAL
TOOLS LIKE ELECTRONIC
SYNTHESIZERS.
SOME CHICAGO PUBLIC LIBRARIES
OFFER A QUIETER ATTRACTION FOR
KIDS, FISHING POLES.
AT THE SHERMAN PARK BRANCH ON
THE CITY'S SOUTH SIDE, CAMERON
AND JEREMIAH COOK DON'T HAVE TO
GO FAR TO USE THEM.
THE LAGOON BEHIND THE LIBRARY IS
STOCKED WITH CATFISH AND BLUE
GILL.
>> I LIKE COMING TO FISH HERE
BECAUSE IT'S QUIET AND NICE AND
RELAXING.
>> Reporter: BUT AT THE SAME
TIME, EXCITING.
>> IT'S LIKE A RUSH THROUGH YOUR
BLOOD.
IT'S LIKE YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING TO HAPPEN NEXT.
>> Reporter: JUST LIKE READING A
GOOD BOOK.
>> COME ON, YOU GOT A BITE.
>> I GOT A BITE!
>> Reporter: JOHN YANG, NBC
NEWS, GROSSE POINT FARMS,
MICHIGAN.
>>> THAT'S "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS SATURDAY.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
WE LEAVE YOU WITH MORE IMAGES
FROM TODAY'S HISTORIC EVENTS IN
WASHINGTON, D.C.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC NEWS, GOOD
NIGHT.
>>> GOOD EVENING, I'M DIANE
DWYER.
DEVELOPING STORY IN THE SOUTH
BAY.
POLICE SEARCHING FOR A GUNMAN
WHO SHOT AND KALD MAN IN
DOWNTOWN SAN JOSE 1:00, NEAR
THIRD AND JULIAN STREET, NOT FAR
FROM ST. JAMES PARK.
PEOPLE WHO LIVE NEARBY SAY IT
WAS DISTURBING TO HEAR GUNFIRE,
ESPECIALLY IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
DAY.
>> IT'S JUST CRAZY THAT THIS CAN
HAPPEN IN DOWNTOWN SAN JOSE IN
BROAD DAYLIGHT.
I LIVE ON THE CORNER.
A FRIEND WAS WALKING BACK THIS
DIRECTION AS I WAS GOING TOWARD
DOWNTOWN WHEN THE SHOOTING
OCCURRED.
WHILE I WAS READING ABOUT IT, I
WAS WONDERING IF THAT PERSON GOT
HURT OR NOT.
>> THE MAN SHOT WAS RUSHED TO
THE HOSPITAL AND PRONOUNCED DEAD
A SHORT TIME LATER.
INVESTIGATES DON'T KNOW WHAT LED
UP TO THE SHOOTING OR WHETHER
IT'S GANG RELATED.
THEY ARE WORKING ON PUTTING
TOGETHER A DESCRIPTION OF THE
GUNMAN.
THIS IS SAN JOSE'S 33rd KILLING
OF THE YEAR.
SAN JOSE HAD 46 IN ALL OF LAST
YEAR.
>>> WE HAVE BREAKING NEWS OUT OF
ELDORADO COUNTY.
NEW FIRE BURNING IN GEORGETOWN,