TOMORROW.
BEAUTIFUL.
>> DEFINITELY THE COLOR OF THE
DAY.
>> YES.
>> THANK YOU FOR JOINING US SEE
YOU BACK HERE AT 6:00.
BYE-BYE.
>>> TONIGHT, TEN MINUTES OF
TERROR.
DRAMATIC NEW TAPE AND A NEW TIME
LINE.
>> RUN, KEEP YOUR HEAD DOWN.
>> DID THE KILLER PLAN TO TARGET
OTHER CITIES BEFORE TAKING AIM
AT LAS VEGAS?
AND TONIGHT IS THE NRA OPENING
THE DOOR TO A BAN ON BUMP
STOCKS?
NBC NEWS EXCLUSIVE SAYS
PRESIDENT UMP WAS FURIOUS AT
HIS SECRETARY OF STATE AFTER OUR
REPORT ABOUT REX TILLERSON
REFERRING TO THE PRESIDENT AS A
MORON.
A SHOWDOWN INSIDE THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>>> AMERICANS AMBUSHED,
OVERWHELMED BY ISLAMIC MILITA  S
MILITANTS, THREE GREEN BERETS
KILLED.
>>> A CONGRESSMAN WHO PRESSURED
HIS MISTRESS TO GET AN ABORTION.
>>> EYES OFF THE ROAD.
A STARTLING DEVELOPMENT ABOUT
TECHNOLOGY BEHIND THE WHEEL.
NIGHTLY NEWS BEGINS NOW.
>> ANNOUNCER:  FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK,
THIS IS NBC NIGHTLY NEWS WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>> GOOD EVENING AND THANK YOU
FOR BEING WITH US TONIGHT.
THE HORROR AND INTENSITY OF LAST
SUNDAY NIGHT'S ATTACK IN LAS
VEGAS SEEN IN SNIPPETS OF VIDEO
UP TO THIS POINT IS COMING INTO
SHARPER FOCUS TONIGHT AS YET
ANOTHER NEW VIDEO EMERGES, THIS
TIME CAPTURING THE ENTIRE
[ INAUDIBLE ] UNDERSTAND WHY
THOSE IN THE LINE OF FIRE FELT
LIKE IT WENT ON FOREVER.
>> GO, GO!
EVERYBODY GO!
>> WE'LL TAKE YOU THROUGH MORE
OF THAT VIDEO IN A MOMENT AND
WHAT IT TELLS INVESTIGATORS.
BUT FIRST NEW INFORMATION ABOUT
THE SHOOTER STEPHEN PADDOCK AND
WHY POLICE SUSPECT HE HAD ALSO
CONSIDERED ATTACKS ON CROWDS AT
BIG EVENTS IN CHICAGO AND
BOSTON.
OUR JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS JOINS US NOW WITH LATE
DETAILS.
PETE?
>> Reporter: LESTER, GOOD
EVENING.
INVESTIGATORS SAY THIS NEW
INFORMATION COMES FROM WHAT
AUTHORITIES HOPE WILL BE ONE OF
THE MOST PRODUCTIVE SEARCHES NOW
UNDERWAY, OF HIS ELECTRONIC
TRAIL FROM THE HALF DOZEN PHONES
AND COMPUTERS HE LEFT BEHIND.
OFFICIALS SAY STEPHEN PADDOCK
DID INTERNET RESEARCH EARLIER
THIS YEAR ON LA LA PALOOZA, THE
SUMMER MUSIC FESTIVAL IN
CHICAGO'S GRANT PARK.
THEY SAY HE EVEN RESERVED ROOMS
IN A HOTEL THAT OVERLOOKS THE
PARK FOR A FEW DAYS BEFORE THE
EVENT THOUGH HE NEVER SHOWED UP.
HE ALSO RESEARCHED EVENTS AT
BOSTON'S FENWAY PARK AND NEARBY
HOTELS, OFFICIALS SAY.
SEARCHES OF ELECTRONIC DEVICES
FOUND IN HIS HOME AND HIS
INTERNET BROWSING HISTORY, A
SIGN, THEY SAY, PADDOCK WAS
THINKING OF ATTACKING LARGE
CROWDS MONTHS BEFORE THE LAS
VEGAS SHOOTING RAMPAGE.
BUT SO FAR INVESTIGATORS ARE
STUMPED OVER HOW STEPHEN PADDOCK
WENT FROM BEING A VARSITY TENNIS
PLAYER AND SOCIABLE HIGH SCHOOL
STUDENT IN CALIFORNIA TO THE
ANTI-SOCIAL FORMER ACCOUNTANT
WHO BECAME A MASS MURDERER.
HIS BROTHER ERIC SAYS HE KNOWS
OF NO SERIOUS HEALTH PROBLEMS
THAT WOULD HAVE MADE SUCH A
PROFOUND CHANGE.
>> SOMETHING HAPPENED IN HIS
HEAD THAT THE STEVE I KNEW TWO
WEEKS AGO NO LONGER THE GUY WHO
DID THAT.
>> Reporter: AND OFFICIALS SAY
HIS GIRLFRIEND MARILOU DANLEY
HAS TOLD AUTHORITIES PADDOCK HAD
SOME MENTAL HEALTH ISSUES AND
WOULD SOMETIMES LIE IN BED
CRYING OUT, OH, MY GOD.
BUT INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY HAVE
YET TO FIND ANY HEALTH PROBLEMS,
PHYSICAL OR MENTAL, GRAVE ENOUGH
TO PUSH HIM INTO BECOMING A
KILLER.
>>> AS FOR POLICE SAYING HE
MIGHT HAVE HAD AN ESCAPE PLAN,
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEY FOUND NO
HARD EVIDENCE OF THAT OR OF HELP
FROM ANYONE ELSE IN PLANNING OR
CARRYING OUT THE ATTACK.
AND DESPITE TIPS THAT PADDOCK
WAS WITH A WOMAN THE DAY OF THE
SHOOTING, NO SUCH PERSON HAS YET
BEEN FOUND.
PETE WILLIAMS, NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: I'M MIGUEL
ALMAGUER.
TONIGHT THIS NEW PERSPECTIVE.
>> RUN.
>> Reporter: OF THE CARNAGE AND
CHAOS ON THE VEGAS STRIP.
>> YOU'VE BEEN SHOT?
>> Reporter: FOR TEN MINUTES,
EMPLOYEE RAYMOND PAGE RECORDS
THIS HEART POUNDING SCENE,
CONCERT GOERS RUNNING FOR THEIR
LIVES.
>> GET DOWN!
>> Reporter: TODAY A NEW LOOK AT
THE CRIME SCENE AND A TIME LINE
OF THE BLOOD SHED.
10:05:00 P.M., FROM HIS DEADLY
PERCH, STEPHEN PADDOCK UNLEASHES
A FURY OF GUN FIRE.
10:15, THE SHOTS ARE OVER, BUT
PANIC OVER WHELMS THE STREETS
AND FIRST RESPONDERS.
>> IT WAS JUST MASS CHAOS.
IT WAS VICTIMS WHO WERE ROLLING
UP TO US IN TRUCKS, IN THE BEDS
OF THE TRUCKS JUST LOADED UP.
>> Reporter: 10:18, PADDOCK
FIRES 2 ROUNDS AT A SECURITY
GUARD WHO APPROACHES HIS ROOM.
SHOT IN THE LEG THE GUARD STILL
LEADS POLICE TO THE SOOEP WHERE
AT 11:20 THEY FIND PADDOCK DEAD.
>> HE METICULOUSLY PLANNED ON
THE WORST DOMESTIC ATTACK IN THE
UNITED STATES HISTORY.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS
DISCOVER PADDOCK'S CAR, LOADED
WITH 1600 ROUNDS OF AMMUNITION
AND 50 POUNDS OF EXPLOSIVES.
TONIGHT, INVESTIGATORS QUESTION,
DID HE HAVE AN ESCAPE PLAN AND
POSSIBLY HELP?
>> YOU HAVE TO MAKE THE
ASSUMPTION HE HAD TO HAVE SOME
HELP AT SOME POINT.
>> Reporter: IN THESE HARROWING
MOMENTS AFTER THE MASSACRE,
[ INAUDIBLE ] BEGAN LOADING THE
WOUNDED INTO HIS TRUCK.
>> ANYBODY ELSE?
>> Reporter: HE RESCUED AT LEAST
HALF A DOZEN.
BUT FOUR DAYS AFTER THE
MASSACRE, DID THEY SURVIVE?
THE NIGHT THERE IS SO MUCH
UNCERTAINTY AND PAIN.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER, NBC NEWS, LAS
VEGAS.
>> WE WILL TAKE A TURN NOW TO
NEW FALLOUT FROM OUR EXCLUSIVE
REPORT IN THE FEUD BETWEEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND SECRETARY OF
STATE REX TILLERSON.
NEW REVELATIONS TONIGHT ABOUT
JUST HOW FURIOUS THE PRESIDENT
WAS AFTER OUR REPORTING
YESTERDAY, ACCORDING TO SENIOR
OFFICIALS.
HERE'S NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL
WITH THAT.
>> Reporter: ALL THE PRESIDENT'S
MEN IN DAMAGE CONTROL TODAY.
THE SECRETARY OF STATE AND THE
VICE-PRESIDENT MAKING A PUBLIC
DISPLAY OF PLAYING NICE.
>> WITH THAT, SECRETARY OF
STATE, REX TILLERSON.
>> Reporter: BUT NEW DETAILS
TONIGHT ABOUT AN ANGRY SHOWDOWN
IN THE WHITE HOUSE WEDNESDAY
OVER THE NBC NEWS REPORT.
THE PRESIDENT, ACCORDING TO FIVE
SENIOR ADMINISTRATION OFFICIALS,
FURIOUS AT HIS SECRETARY OF
STATE.
CHIEF OF STAFF JOHN KELLY THEN
ABRUPTLY SCRAPPING PLANS TO
TRAVEL TO LAS VEGAS WITH THE
PRESIDENT SO HE COULD TRY TO
CONTAIN HIS BOSS'S FURY AND
MANAGE THE FALLOUT.
VICE-PRESIDENT MIKE PENCE ALSO
FUMING, ACCORDING TO SEVEN
SENIOR O
SENIOR OFFICIALS.
HE AND TILLERSON TALKED LEADING
TO THE NEWS CONFOR INSTANCE.
>> THE VICE-PRESIDENT HAS NEVER
HAD PERSUADE ME TO REMAIN THE
SECRETARY OF STATE BECAUSE I
HAVE NEVER CONSIDERED LEAVING
THIS POST.
>> Reporter: KELLY THEN
SUMMONING TILLERSON ASK THEIR
ALLY DEFENSE SECRETARY JAMES
MATTIS TO THE WHITE HOUSE.
ACCORDING TO THREE OFFICIALS
WHERE THEY HUDDLED TO DISCUSS
HOW TO GO FORWARD.
TODAY THE WHITE HOUSE PRESS
SECRETARY REJECTING THE IDEA
THAT THE PRESIDENT HAS UNDERCUT
HIS TOP DIPLOMAT BY REPEATEDLY
CONTRADICTING HIM.
>> THE PREMISE OF THAT QUESTION
IS ABSOLUTELY RIDICULOUS.
THE PRESIDENT CAN'T UNDERCUT HIS
OWN CABINET.
THE PRESIDENT IS THE LEADER OF
THE CABINET.
>> Reporter: CRITICS SAY THAT
LEAVES THE SECRETARY OF STATE
MORTALLY WEAKENED WITH FOREIGN
LEADERS.
>> OUR SECRETARY OF STATE HAS TO
BE ABLE TO GO INTO THE KREMLIN
AND MEET ONE ON ONE WITH
VLADIMIR PUTIN OR GO TO BEIJING
AS SECRETARY TILLERSON DID LAST
WEEK AND MEET WITH XI JINPING.
THOSE PEOPLE ARE NOT GOING TO
TAKE HIM SERIOUSLY IF HE DOESN'T
APPEAR TO HAVE THE CONFIDENCE OF
THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES.
>> Reporter: ASKED TO RESPOND
TONIGHT, WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS
DOWN PLAYING KELLY'S DECISION TO
STAY BEHIND, SAYING HE DECIDED
NOT TO GO TO LAS VEGAS IN ORDER
TO MANAGE DAY TO DAY NEEDS AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
LESTER?
>> ANDREA MITCHELL IN
WASHINGTON, THANK YOU.
OVERSEAS THIS EVENING, AN ACTIVE
U.S. MILITARY OPERATION IS
UNDERWAY IN WEST AFRICA AFTER
THREE ELITE GREEN BERETS WERE
KILLED IN AN AMBUSH AND FIRE
FIGHT WITH ISLAMIC MILITANTS IN
NIGERIAER.
NBC CORRESPONDENT HANS NICHOLS
HAS THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: PENTAGON OFFICIALS
TELL NBC NEWS ISIS MAY HAVE BEEN
BEHIND THE DEADLY AMBUSH OF U.S.
SPECIAL FORCES.
TONIGHT AMERICAN TROOPS ARE
STILL ON THE GROUND.
>> LAST NIGHT WE DID LOSE THREE
SERVICE MEMBERS, AND IT'S WITH A
VERY DYNAMIC SITUATION AND WE
STILL ONGOING OPERATIONS.
>> Reporter: IT HAPPENED IN THE
WEST AFRICAN NATION NIGER.
THE AMERICANS WERE ON A TRAINING
MISSION DESCRIBED AS ROUTINE.
LESS THAN A DOZEN U.S. AND
FORCES WERE ON FOOT WHEN THEY
WERE AMBUSHED BY A LARGER GROUP
OF ISLAMIC MILITANTS.
ACCORDING TO MILITARY OFFICIALS,
THE GREEN BERETS AND
NIGERIAERIANS WERE OVERWHELMED.
A HELICOPTER ARRIVING LATER TO
RESCUE THEM.
IN ADDITION TO THE THREE KILLED,
TWO WERE INJURED.
HOME TO SOME 800 U.S. TROOPS AND
DRONE BASES, THE MISSION TO KEEP
EYES ON TERRORIST GROUPS FROM
ISIS TO BOKO HARAM.
>> ARE THESE U.S. FORCES LOOKING
TO ENGAGE ISLAMIC MILITANTS?
>> NO, WE ARE ON A MISSION.
>> Reporter: THE BRAZEN AMBUSH
COULD MARK A NEW BATTLE AGAINST
ISIS IN AFRICA AS ISIS FIGHTERS
LOSE TERRITORY IN SYRIA AND
IRAQ.
LESTER?
>> HANS NICHOLS TONIGHT, THANK
YOU.
IN WASHINGTON THIS EVENING SIGNS
THE DOOR MAY BE OPENING SLIGHTLY
FROM REPUBLICANS IN CONGRESS AND
POSSIBLY FROM THE NRA TO NEW
RESTRICTIONS ON BUMP STOCKS, THE
DEVICES USED BY THE LAS VEGAS
KILLER TO TURN HIS SEMIAUTOMATIC
WEAPONS INTO AUTOMATIC MACHINE
GUNS.
NBC'S HALLE JACKSON HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: AFTER DECADES OF
REPUBLICAN RESISTANCE ON GUN
CONTROL, TONIGHT A NEW NARROW
OPENING ON BUMP STOCKS WHICH
LETS SEMIAUTOMATIC GUNS FIRE
FASTER.
>> APPARENTLY THIS ALLOWS YOU TO
TAKE A SEMIAUTOMATIC TURN INTO A
FULL AUTOMATIC.
IT IS SOMETHING WE NEED TO BEING
LOOK INTO.
>> Reporter: NOT JUST HOUSE
SPEAKER PAUL RYAN, BUT ONE OF
THE HIGHEST RANKING SENATORS
JOHN CORNYN.
>> I THINK IT'S WORTH SERIOUS
CONSIDERATION.
>> Reporter: AND THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF WILLING TO CONSIDER NEW
REGULATIONS.
>> WE ARE OPEN TO HAVING THAT
CONVERSATION.
WE THINK THAT WE SHOULD HAVE
THAT CONVERSATION AND WE WANT TO
BE PART OF IT MOVING FORWARD.
>> Reporter: THE WILD CARD
THROUGH ALL THIS HAS BEEN THE
NRA, SILENT SINCE SUNDAY'S
SHOOTING.
TODAY, SURPRISINGLY SUPPORTING
STRICTER RULES.
IN A STATEMENT SAYING, QUOTE,
DEVICES DESIGNED TO ALLOW
SEMIAUTOMATIC RIFLES TO FUNCTION
LIKE FULLY AUTOMATE I CAN RIFLES
SHOULD BE SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL
REGULATIONS, ASKING THE ATF TO
REVIEW BUMP STOCKS.
BUT IN 2010 THAT AGENCY
DETERMINED THE DEVICES ARE
ALLOWED BASED ON FEDERAL LAW.
MEANING IT WOULD BE UP TO
CONGRESS TO CHANGE THAT LAW FROM
CAPITOL HILL.
THAT'S WHERE STEVE SCALISE IS
JUST BACK TO WORK AFTER GETTING
SHOT THIS SUMMER AT A
CONGRESSIONAL BASEBALL PARTLY
CLOUDY ADVERTISE TALKING NOW
WITH INNOCENCE'S CHUCK TODD.
>> I DO THINK IT'S A LITTLE BIT
EARLY TO STAY PEOPLE KNOW WHAT
TO DO TO FIX THIS PROBLEM.
>> Reporter: IN THE HOUSE, A NEW
BIPARTISAN BILL WOULD BAN BUMP
STOCKS.
>> IF I KEEP A CONSTANT FORWARD
PRESSURE ON THIS, IT SIMULATES
FULL AUTO.
>> Reporter: UNTIL THIS WEEK
THEY'VE BEEN SEEN MOSTLY AS A
TARGET PRACTICE NOVELTY.
LEGAL NOW, BUT MAYBE NOT FOR
LONG.
HALLE JACKSON, NBC NEWS, THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>> NOW TO LATE WORD THAT
CONGRESSMAN TIM MURPHY A
REPUBLICAN FROM PENNSYLVANIA IS
RESIGNING AFTER HE WAS CAUGHT UP
IN A SEX SCANDAL AND REPORTEDLY
URGED HIS MISTRESS TO HAVE AN
ABORTION WHEN HE THOUGHT SHE WAS
PREGNANT.
DESPITE HIS WELL KNOWN
ANTI-ABORTION VIEWS.
HERE'S NBC'S KASIE HUNT.
>> Reporter: REPUBLICAN
CONGRESSMAN TIM MURPHY RESIGNING
IN DISGRACE IN THE WAKE OF A
BOMBSHELL REPORT HE ASKED A
MISTRESS TO TERMINATE A
SUSPECTED PREGNANCY.
EVEN AS HE PUSHED ANTI-ABORTION
LEGISLATION IN CONGRESS.
>> I SAY WHAT WE OUGHT TO DO IS
LET THESE CHILDREN LIVE SO THEY
HAVE A CHANCE FOR A BETTER
FUTURE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> Reporter: AFTER THE STORY
BROKE TUESDAY, MURPHY VOTED TO
BUO
TO BAN ABORTIONS AFTER 20 WEEKS.
HOURS LATER HE SAID HE WOULDN'T
RUN FOR REELECTION IN 2018.
UNDER PRESSURE FROM REPUBLICAN
LEADERS HE RESIGNED TODAY
EFFECTIVE OCTOBER 21st.
>> I THINK IT'S APPROPRIATE HE
MOVES ON TO THE NEXT CHAPTER OF
HIS LIFE.
>> Reporter: MURPHY ACKNOWLEDGED
HIS AFFAIR WITH SHANNON EDWARDS
A FORENSIC PSYCHOLOGIST WEEKS
AGO.
IT IS THE TEXT MESSAGES ABOUT
HER PREGNANCY SCARE THAT EXPOSED
HIM TO CHARGES OF HYPOCRISY.
YOU HAVE ZERO ISSUE POSTING YOUR
PRO-LIFE STANCE ALL OVER THE
PLACE WHEN YOU HAD NO ISSUE
ASKING ME TO ABORT OUR UNBORN
CHILD, SHE WROTE, ACCORDING TO
TEXT MESSAGES OBTAINED BY THE
PITTSBURGH POST GAZETTE.
THE CONGRESSMAN WROTE BACK
DENYING HE WROTE THE
ANTIABORTION MESSAGES.
I'VE NEVER WRITTEN THEM.
STAFF WROTE THEM.
I READ THEM AND WINCED A
SIX-PAGE MEMO OF HIM CREATING A
HOSTILE WORK ENVIRONMENT,
DESCRIBING HIM AS ERRATIC,
UNSTABLE, ANGRY AND ABUSIVE.
HIS OFFICE HASN'T CONFIRMED OR
DENIED THE AUTHENTICITY OF THE
TEXT OR MEMO.
CA
KASIE HUNT, NBC NEWS, THE
CAPITAL.
>> THE NEW ORLEANS HAS DECLARED
A STATE OF EMERGENCY AS TROPICAL
STORM NATE BARRELS TOWARDS THE
GULF COAST.
AL ROKER IS HERE WITH THE
FORECAST.
WHAT IS THE LATEST ON THIS ONE?
>> LESTER, THIS IS THE LATEST.
WEST VIRGINIA TROPICAL STORM
NATE 40 MILES SOUTHWEST OF
HONDURAS, 40 MILE PER HOUR WINDS
MOVING NORTH, NORTHWEST AT TEN
MILES PER HOUR.
YESTERDAY WE THOUGHT AT 7:00
A.M. HERE'S WHERE WE WOULD SEE
ON SUNDAY.
THE USA MODEL, THE NATIONAL
HURRICANE CENTER MODEL AND
EUROPEAN MODEL.
BUT AS WE GET THE LATEST IN, YOU
CAN SEE THE EUROPEAN MODEL RIGHT
NOW ON TOP OF NEW ORLEANS, THE
USA MODEL TO THE WEST AND THE
NEW ORLEANS MODEL FOR THE
NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER RIGHT
THERE AS WELL.
HERE'S WHAT WE LOOK FOR AS FAR
AS THE LATEST, THE POTENTIAL
IMPACTS, HEAVY RAIN, FLASH
FLOODING, TROPICAL FORCE WINDS,
STRONG WINDS AND ROUGH SURF.
>> WE KNOW YOU'LL KEEP AN EYE ON
IT, THANK YOU.
A WARNING ABOUT THE RISK OF
SO-CALLED INFO TANMENT SYSTEMS
IS WHAT THEY ARE POSED WHEN
YOU'RE BEHIND THE WHEEL.
ALSO OUT OF BOUNDS, FIRE STORM
ERUPTING OVER WHAT AN NFL
SUPERSTAR SAID TO A FEMALE
REPORTER.
WE'LL BE BACK.
OLLAPALOOZA
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH A WARNING
NOW ABOUT ALL THE INFOTAINMENT
TECHNOLOGY THAT COMES WITH NEW
CARS THESE DAYS, FROM GPS
SYSTEMS TO TEXT MESSAGING AND
E-MAILING.
BUT WITH SOMEONE DYING EVERY
2 1/2 HOURS AND DISTRACTED
DRIVING ACCIDENTS, NEW RESEARCH
FROM AAA SUGGESTS ALL THOSE
HIGH-TECH BELLS AND WHISTLES
COULD MAKE MATTERS WORSE.
HERE'S NBC'S TOM COSTELLO.
>> Reporter: FROM SALT LAKE CITY
POLICE, DASHCAM VIDEO OF A
HEAD-ON CRASH, THE OTHER DRIVER
ALLEGEDLY DISTRACTED.
NOW NEW RESEARCH SUGGESTS THE
NEWEST IN-CAR TECHNOLOGY MAY
ONLY BE CREATING GREATER
DISTRACTIONS.
>> PICK AN ADDRESS IN THE UNITED
STATES.
>> Reporter: NO MORE SIMPLE
BUTTONS AND KNOBS.
TODAY AS THE IT UP SCREEN, TALK
TO TEXT, E-MAIL, MUSIC,
NAVIGATION, PHONE CALLS, AND
WI-FI.
AAA AND THE UNIVERSITY OF UTAH
STUDIED 120 DRIVERS TRYING TO
USE THE TECHNOLOGY IN 2017
MODELS.
LIKE THIS DRIVER TUNING HIS RAID
DWROE.
>> TUNE A.M. 830.
>> Reporter: THEN WEAVING TO
AVOID A WOMAN IN A CROSSWALK.
THIS ONE WAS USING A TOUCH
SCREEN.
OF THE 30 VEHICLES TESTED 23
DEMANDED HIGH OR VERY HIGH
DRIVER ATTENTION TO USE THE
TECHNOLOGY.
DRIVERS TYPING ADDRESSES INTO
THE GPS WERE DISTRACTED THE
MOST.
UP TO 40 SECONDS.
>> MY EYES ARE OFF THE ROAD AT
THE MOMENT.
>> Reporter: ON A CLOSED COURSE
IN MARYLAND, I WENT FOR A TEST
DRIVE WITH LEAD RESEARCHER DAVID
STRAYER.
HOW DO YOU CHANGE SCREENS FROM
A.M. TO F.M.?
I DIDN'T REALIZE MY EYES WERE
OFF THE ROAD FOR 20 SECONDS.
>> MUCH OF THE TECHNOLOGY HAS
NOTHING TO DO WITH DRIVING.
>> Reporter: IT IS MEANT TO
REPLACE PORTABLE DEVICES THAT
CAN BE A GREATER DISTRACTION.
HANDS ON THE WHEEL AND EYES ON
THE ROAD CONTINUE TO BE CRITICAL
TO SAFE DRIVING.
>> SEND GINETTE A TEXT MESSAGE.
>> Reporter: THE TECHNOLOGY MAY
BE TOO TEMPTING TO IGNORE.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>> STILL TO COME TONIGHT, IT'S
ALREADY COST HIM ONE SPONSOR.
WHAT NFL STAR CAM NEWTON SAID TO
A FEMALE REPORTER THAT HAS HIM
FACING SOME BACKLASH TONIGHT.
>>> BACK NOW WITH THE
CONTROVERSY SWIRLING AROUND A
BIG NFL STAR, CAROLINA PANTHERS
QUARTERBACK CAM NEWTON WHO HAS
BEEN WIDELY ACCUSED OF SEXISM
OVER HIS COMMENTS TO A FEMALE
REPORTER, THUS FAR HE HASN'T
APOLOGIZED PUBLICLY, BUT THE
UPROAR IS ALREADY COSTING HIM
SOME MONEY.
NBC'S KRISTIN DAHLGREN HAS MORE.
>> Reporter: TODAY CAM NEWTON
TAKING HARD HITS OFF THE FIELD
ABOUT A COMMENT TO JORDAN
RODRIGUE.
>> THE PHYSICALITY --
>> Reporter: IT'S FUNNY TO HEAR
A FEMALE TALK ABOUT ROUTES,
LIKE -- FUNNY.
>> Reporter: UNLIKE NEWTON,
RODRIGUE WASN'T AMUSED.
I DON'T THINK IT'S FUNNY TO BE A
FEMALE AND TALK ABOUT ROUTES.
I THINK IT'S MY JOB.
AN NFL SPOKESMAN CALLING THE
COMMENTS JUST PLAIN WRONG AND
DISRESPECTFUL.
TODAY THE TEAM'S COACH SAID
NEWTON SPOKE TO THE REPORTER
AFTERWARDS.
>> CAM MADE A MISTAKE.
I UNDERSTAND HE HAD A
CONVERSATION WHERE HE PRETTY
MUCH SAID THAT HE SHOULDN'T HAVE
SAID WHAT HE SAID.
>> WE ARE ABOUT TO HIT THE ROAD.
>> Reporter: BUT RODRIGUE WHO
HAS COVERED THE TEAM FOR THE
PAST YEAR SAYS HE DID NOT
APOLOGIZE.
ADDING HIS COMMENTS IN PRIVATE
WERE EVEN WORSE.
IN 2012 NEWTON CALLED ANOTHER
FEMALE REPORTER SWEETHEART.
>> ONLY THING I CAN SAY,
SWEETHEART, IT'S MYSELF.
>> IT'S NOT FUNNY, IT'S OUR JOB.
IT'S GOING TO HAVE TO BE HIS JOB
TO GET USED TO IT BECAUSE WE'RE
NOT GOING ANYWHERE.
>> Reporter: NOW RODRIGUE'S OWN
WORDS UNDER FIRE FOR TWEETS
CALLED RACIST.
TODAY TWEETING SHE'S DEEPLY
SORRY.
NEWTON REMAINED SILENT BUT ONE
SPONSOR SPEAKING OUT, DANNON
SEVERING TIES WITH THE STAR.
>> THE ROCK AND ROLL HALL OF
FAME, AMONG THIS YEAR'S
NOMINEES, RADIOHEAD.
RAGE AGAINST THE MACHINE.
BON JOVI.
AND L.L. COOL JAY.
ALSO JUDIST PRIEST.
MOODY BLUES, DIRE STRAITS, THE
CARS, AND ON AND ON.
19 ACTS IN ALL.
WE HAVE PUT THE FULL LIST ON OUR
WEBSITE.
THE INDUCT EASE WILL BE
ANNOUNCED IN DECEMBER.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, THE COUNTRY MUSIC SONG
GOING VIRAL TO HONOR ONE OF THE
VICTIMS.
A WOMAN HAS FALLEN FROM A
CLIFF IN SAN FRANCISCO... RIGHT
NOW SKYRANGER IS
OVER THE SCENE.
PLUS, CARS RIDDLED WITH
BULLETS ON THE PENINSULA.
BUT IT )S WHERE THE SHOTS CAME
FROM... THAT MAKES THIS
SO CONCERNING.
NEXT.
THE NEWS AT SIX
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT WE WANT TO
END ON THE MEMORIES, THE STORIES
AND THE EMOTIONAL TRIBUTES TO
THE LIVES LOST IN THE TRAGEDY IN
LAS VEGAS.
SO MANY MOMS AND DADS, SONS AND
DAUGHTERS, FRIENDS AND LOVED
ONES GONE NOW, BUT NEVER
FORGOTTEN.
HERE'S JOE FRYER.
♪
>> Reporter: YOU CAN HEAR
BRENDAN STEWART'S LOVE FOR
COUNTRY MUSIC IN THIS
PERFORMANCE OF THE SONG "YOU
SHOULD BE HERE" THE COVER THAT
WENT VIRAL AFTER HE WAS KILLED
SHIELDING HIS GIRLFRIEND.
>> THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS ARE WITH
YOU.
>> Reporter: THIS WEEK VEGAS
RADIO STATION HAS BEEN PLAYING
IT IN STEWART'S HONOR.
>> IT BREAKS MY HEART THAT
BRENDAN IS NOT AROUND TO HEAR US
PLAY HIS MUSIC, BUT WE KNOW HIS
FAMILY AND FRIENDS WERE ABLE TO
HEAR THAT.
>> Reporter: THE CORONER NOW
SAYS ALL 58 VICTIMS HAVE BEEN
IDENTIFIED AND IT IS CLEAR THE
IMPACT OF THIS TRAGEDY REACHES
FAR BEYOND VEGAS.
THE 58 VICTIMS WHO LOST THEIR
LIVES IN VEGAS CAME FROM ALL
ACROSS THE COUNTRY AND CANADA.
AT LEAST 30 OF THEM CALLED
CALIFORNIA HOME.
ANGIE GOMEZ OF RIVERSIDE LOVED
THEATER AND MAKING PEOPLE LAUGH.
>> SHE LIVED SO HUMBLY.
SHE'S SO UNASSUMING.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST TWO
TEACHERS DIED.
SANDY CASEY AND JENNY PARKS.
>> MS. PARKS WAS THE BEST
TEACHER IN THE WORLD.
>> Reporter: JUST 22 YEARS OLD,
CHRISTY DUARTE WORLD FOR THE
L.A. KINGS.
THEY WILL WEAR A STICKER WITH
HER INITIALS ON THE BACKS OF
THEIR HELMETS.
>> IT IS IMPORTANT FOR US TO
HONOR HER AND TO TELL THE WORLD
HOW GREAT OF A PERSON SHE WAS.
>> Reporter: THE MEMORIES OF THE
VICTIMS LIKE BRENDAN STEWART'S
PERFORMANCE LIVE ON.
JOE FRYER, NBC NEWS, LAS VEGAS.
>> WE APPRECIATE YOU SPENDING
PART OF YOUR EVENING WITH US.
THAT IS NIGHTLY NEWS FOR THIS
THURSDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC NEWS, THANK
YOU FOR WATCHING, AND GOOD
NIGHT.
NOW:
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I )M JANELLE WANG -- IN FOR RAJ
MATHAI.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> JESSICA AGUIRRE.
WE BEGIN WITH BREAKING NEWS OUT
OF SAN FRANCISCO.
FIREFIGHTERS ARE RUSHED TO WHERE
A WOMAN HAS FALLEN FROM A CLIFF.
HAPPENED WITHIN PAST HOUR.
WE'LL TAKE YOU OUTSIDE YOU CAN
SEE THE SKY RANGER ABOVE THE
SCENE AND THE CLIFF.
THERE ARE EMERGENCY VEHICLES
BELOW.
NOW THE SAN FRANCISCO FIRE
DEPARTMENT JUST TOLD US THAT THE
MEDICAL EXAMINER IS ON THE WAY
WHICH MEANS THAT THAT WOMAN IS
DEAD.
WE HAVE A CREW AT FT. CLEMSON
GATHERING INFORMATION.
WELL BRING YOU INFORMATION ON
THE DIGITAL PLATFORMS AS WELL
PROCESS.
>>> TO THE NEWS IN LAS VEGAS AND
THE LAS VEGAS MASSACRE
INVESTIGATION.
U.S. OFFICIALS SAY THE SHOOTER
MAY HAVE PLANNED PLOR ATTACKS
INCLUDING A WAR BOMBING.
THERE IS NO SOLID EVIDENCE BUT
LOOKING INTO THE POSSIBILITY.
ERT AUTHORITIES CONFIRM THAT THE
GUNMAN, STEPHEN PADDOCK LOOKED
AT OTHER CITY WAS HIGH RISES
OVERLOOKING OUTDOOR VENUE
PROCESSION.
INCLUDING IN BOSTON FENWAY PARK.
HE BOOKED ROOMS IN LAS VEGAS THE
WEEK OF LIFE IS BEAUTIFUL WHICH
IS OF AN ALTERNATIVE FESTIVAL.
IN CHICAGO DURING LA LA PLOOZA.
AFLT HE NEVER CHECKED IN THE WHO
WILLIE HOTEL IN CHICAGO.
>> WE ARE GET AGO TERRIFYING NEW
LOOK AT THE CHAOTIC MOMENTS
AFTER BULLETS RANG OUT.
A CITY EMPLOYEE WORKING ON A
STOPLIGHT SAW WHAT WAS HAPPENING
AND WALKED INTO THE LINE OF
FIRE.
ACCORDING TO THE VIDEO, THE
ENTIRE TIME.
>> SAM BROCK JOINS US WITH WHATS