THEN MORE LOCAL NEWS AT 6:00.
WE WILL SEE YOU THEN.
GOOD NIGHT!
>>> ON THIS SUNDAY NIGHT -- HIGH
ALERT.
SEVERE WEATHER BREAKING OUT
RIGHT NOW FROM THE PLAINS TO THE
GREAT LAKES.
>> WOW!
LOOK AT THE ROTATION!
>> DAMAGING WINDS, TORNADOES AND
FLOODING.
TONIGHT WHY CLOSE TO HALF THE
U.S. POPULATION COULD BE AT RISK
FROM DANGEROUS STORMS BEFORE IT
IS OVER.
>>> COLLISION COURSE.
DRAMATIC NEW IMAGES OF A
COMMUTER TRAIN CRASH JUST
MOMENTS AFTER IMPACT AMORE
THAN 100,000 IN THE NORTHEAST
BRACE FOR WHAT COULD AND
NIGHTMARE COMMUTE.
>>> STATE OF MIND.
THE NEW GUIDELINES TO HELP
MENTAL HEALTH PROFESSIONALS
DIAGNOSIS DISORDERS.
BUT SOME OF THEM ARE CAUSING
CONTROVERSY AND CONCERN.
>>> VOICE OF EXPERIENCE.
THE PRESIDENT TELLS GRADUATES TO
SET AN EXAMPLE AND POINTS TO HIS
OWN STRUGGLES AS A MAN OF COLOR.
>>> AND -- JACKPOT.
MORE THAN HALF A BILLION DOLLARS
AND TONIGHT SOMEONE HAS THE
WINNING POWERBALL TICKET.
FROM A TINY TOWN IN FLORIDA THAT
WAITS FOR THE WINNER TO CLAIM
THE PRIZE.
>> FROM NBC NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS
IS "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AS WE START HERE TONIGHT,
DANGEROUS STORMS ARE BREAKING
OUT ACROSS A WIDE SWATH OF THE
COUNTRY FROM OKLAHOMA INTO
KANSAS, ON UP INTO MINNESOTA.
SEVERE THUNDERSTORM WARNINGS AND
TORNADO WATCHES ARE UP IN AT
LEAST SIX STATES TONIGHT.
IN OKLAHOMA CITY, AN OMINOUS
WALL CLOUD APPEARED LATE THIS
AFTERNOON AS ALL EYES TURNED TO
THE THREATENING SKIES AMID A
FLURRY OF WARNINGS.
ALREADY THERE HAD BEEN A NUMBER
OF TORNADOES THAT HAVE TOUCHED
DOWN IN OKLAHOMA, INCLUDING THIS
ONE WE SAW A BIT EARLIER IN
EDMOND.
THIS HAS BEEN A TOPSY-TURVY
WEEKEND FOR A LOT OF PEOPLE IN
THE COUNTRY'S MIDSECTION AND
THIS DANGEROUS WEATHER SYSTEM IS
ON THE MOVE.
TONIGHT THE NATIONAL WEATHER
SERVICE SAYS 148 MILLION PEOPLE
ARE AT RISK FOR SEVERE WEATHER
FROM NOW INTO TUESDAY.
THAT'S HALF THE U.S. POPULATION.
WE WATCHED AS THIS ALL UNFOLDED
IN OKLAHOMA JUST MOMENTS AGO.
TAKE A LISTEN.
>> GO LEFT!
>> BIG-GUN TORNADO COMING DOWN!
WHOA, WHOA, WHOA.
STAY ON THE STREET.
>> FOLKS, LOOK AT THAT.
THAT'S VIOLENT.
>> VIOLENT TORNADO!
OFF TO THE RIGHT.
BIG-TIME DEBRIS CLOUD.
THERE IS LARGE STRUCTURAL
DEBRIS.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE HEADING
FOR --
>> RIGHT IN FRONT OF US!
>> DOBBS ROAD.
>> IT'S VERY DANGEROUS!
>> BASEBALL-SIZED HAIL.
THAT IS APPROACHING DOBBS ROAD.
ONE MILE SOUTH OF WATERLOO ROAD.
YOU FOLKS IN RURAL AREAS UP
THERE, THIS IS A LIFE
THREATENING, DAMAGING TORNADO
HERE.
IT IS LARGE AND MULTI-VORTEX.
>> AS THEY REPORTED IN OKLAHOMA
A SHORT WHILE AGO, OUR TEAM IS
IN PLACE TO COVER IT ALL,
INCLUDING NBC'S JANET SHAMLIAN
IN OKLAHOMA CITY WHO SPENT SOME
TIME HERSELF TAKING SHELTER
TODAY.
JANET?
>> YEAH, THAT'S RIGHT, LESTER.
THE POWER LINES ARE STILL DOWN
FROM LAST NIGHT'S STORM AND HERE
WE GO AGAIN.
CONDITIONS HAVE GOTTEN WORSE
VERY QUICKLY HERE.
JUST WITHIN THE LAST HOUR WE
HEARD THE TORNADO SIRENS
MULTIPLE TIMES.
AS YOU INDICATED, FOR THE WHILE
WE WERE IN THE BACK AFTER TARGET
STORE ABOUT 100 YARDS FROM WHERE
I AM STANDING WITH SEVERAL DOZEN
OTHER PEOPLE TAKING SHELTER.
THE PICTURES ARE VERY DRAMATIC,
AND A LOT OF PEOPLE WATCHED THIS
UNFOLD LIVE ON THE WEATHER
CHANNEL.
>> WE GOT A TORNADO, GUYS.
>> WE GOT A TORNADO?
>> GOT A TORNADO ON THE GROUND
RIGHT NOW, GUYS.
>> THERE IS SOME LARGE DEBRIS IN
THE AIR RIGHT HERE.
>> HERE HAD COMES.
HOLY SMOKES.
>> Reporter: HEAVY RAINS,
WHIPPING WINDS AN TORNADOES
PUMMELING THE CENTRAL PLAINS.
>> OH!
LIGHTNING BOLT.
>> THIS ONE WAS ON TOP OF THE
WEATHER CHANNEL'S TORNADO HUNT
TEAM.
>> WE ARE ALMOST RIGHT UNDER THE
TORNADO AT THIS POINT.
WE CAN HEAR THE ROAR.
IT IS RIGHT OVER US BUT WE CAN
STILL SEE IN CONTACT WITH THE
GROUND FARTHER OFF TOWARD THE
NORTHEAST.
>> Reporter: ACROSS THE REGION
TONIGHT, MORE THAN 30 MILLION
PEOPLE ARE IN THE PATH OF THE
STORMS.
IN OKLAHOMA CITY,
70-MILE-AN-HOUR WINDS TOOK DOWN
BLOCK AFTER BLOCK OF POWER
LINES.
>> WE HAVE MORE STORMS COMING IN
TONIGHT.
THEY'RE GOING TO BE SEVERE SO WE
WOULD LIKE TO GET THIS UP AND
MAKE SURE IT IS IN PLACE BEFORE
ANOTHER STORM COMES THROUGH.
>> Reporter: 2013 HAD BEEN ONE
OF THE QUIETEST TORNADO SEASONS
ON RECORD DUE TO A COLD SPRING.
BUT THAT ENDED WITH LAST WEEK'S
ASSAULT ON TEXAS WHERE SIX
PEOPLE DIED IN GRANBURY NEAR FT.
WORTH.
>> WE HAVE ONE OF OUR STRONGER
UPPER AIR DISTURBANCES FROM THE
SPRING THAT'S COME IN FROM THE
PACIFIC NORTHWEST, PUSHED ITS
WAY SOUTHEAST AND NOW IT IS
GATHERING UP SOME OF THAT GULF
OF MEXICO MOISTURE.
WE HAVE WINDS FROM THE SOUTHEAST
THAT ARE MOIST AND WARM, WINDS
ALOFT FROM THE SOUTHWEST.
SO THE TURNING OF THOSE WINDS
ALLOWS THE STORMS TO DEVELOP
ROTATION.
WE CALL THEM SUPER CELL
THUNDERSTORMS AND THOSE ARE THE
ONES THAT PRODUCE LOTS OF
DANGEROUS TORNADOES.
>> Reporter: BY AN EARLY COUNT,
SOME 22 TORNADOES SATURDAY.
19 IN KANSAS, THREE IN NEBRASKA.
ALL WITHIN TWO HOURS.
RESIDENTS ARE AWARE TONIGHT AND
MONDAY COULD BE EVEN WORSE.
>> I PROBABLY DRIVE BACK CLOSE
TO OKLAHOMA CITY AND JUST STAY
IN THAT UNDERGROUND PARKING
GARAGE FOR A WHILE.
I JUST DON'T TAKE CHANCES WITH
TORNADOES.
>> Reporter: AND NO ONE SHOULD,
AUTHORITIES SAY.
A TORNADO ALSO TOUCHED DOWN IN
WICHITA TONIGHT BUT NO REPORTS
OF INJURIES.
THERE IS A CLEARING NOW BUT
LESTER, WE'RE TOLD THE VERY
WORST OF THIS STORM COULD BE
STILL TO COME TONIGHT AND INTO
TOMORROW.
BACK TO YOU.
>> JANET SHAMLIAN, HANG IN
THERE, THANKS.
WEATHER CHANNEL METEOROLOGIST
KELLY CASS IS TRACKING THE
STORMS.
KELLY, WHAT AREAS ARE ON ALERT?
>> WE STILL HAVE A HIGH TORNADO
THREAT AS WE GO LATE INTO THE
EVENING TONIGHT, ALL ACROSS THE
UPPER MIDWEST, STRETCHING ON
DOWN TOWARDS OKLAHOMA.
TAKE A LOOK AT THE TORNADO
WATCHES FROM GO FROM WISCONSIN
AS WELL AS THE TWIN CITIES, DOWN
INTO TULSA.
AND WE ALSO ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
SOME LARGE HAIL.
WE ALREADY HAD REPORTS OF
SOFTBALL-SIZED HAIL.
ACTIVE TORNADO WARNINGS.
WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING THEM AROUND
THE OKLAHOMA CITY AREA,
STRETCHING ON UP INTO KANSAS,
WARNINGS GALORE.
WE'RE ALSO LOOKING AT FLASH
FLOODING IN A LOT OF THE
SLOW-MOVING THUNDERSTORMS AS
WELL.
TONIGHT THE RED ZONE.
MINNEAPOLIS TO KANSAS CITY,
RIGHT ON DOWN TOWARDS TULSA AND
OKLAHOMA CITY.
TORNADOES ARE LIKELY.
THEY COULD BE LARGE AND
LONG-LIVED, THAT MEANS LASTING
FOR MILES ON THE GROUND.
AND THEN TOMORROW STILL MORE
SEVERE WEATHER FROM OKLAHOMA
CITY ON UP TOWARDS CHICAGO.
SO EVEN MORE PEOPLE WILL BE
INCLUDED IN THOSE WARNINGS.
BACK TO YOU.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG
NIGHT.
KELLY CASS, THANKS.
REMIND FOLKS THE WEATHER CHANNEL
IS COVERING THIS ONLINE AND ON
CABLE.
NOW FOR THE TRAIN DERAIL THAT
SNARLED TRAFFIC INTO THE
NORTHEAST CORRIDOR.
THE NTSB CONTINUED ITS
INVESTIGATION TODAY AS TENSE OF
THOUSANDS OF PASSENGERS BRACE
FOR A DIFFICULT COMMUTE
TOMORROW.
NBC'S MICHELLE FRANZEN IS IN
BRIDGEPORT, CONNECTICUT FOR US
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: A NEW VIDEO POSTED
ON YOUTUBE CAPTURES THE FRANTIC
MOMENTS AFTER FRIDAY'S TRAIN
COLLISION IN BRIDGEPORT,
CONNECTICUT.
>> STEP OVER THIS.
>> Reporter: SHOCKED PASSENGERS
MAKING THEIR WAY TO SAFETY JUST
MOMENTS AFTER IMPACT.
NBC NEWS HAS NOT AUTHENTICATED
THE VIDEO.
TODAY CREWS SEPARATED MORE THAN
A DOZEN RAIL CARS AT THE
COLLISION SITE AND HEAVILY
DAMAGED TRAIN CARS WERE MOVED.
A SLOW TOW TO A NEARBY RAIL
YARD.
THE NTSB IS FOCUSING ON TWO
SECTIONS OF TRACK WITH SIGNS OF
POSSIBLE FRACTURES.
THEY WERE SENT TO THE AGENCY'S
LAB IN WASHINGTON, D.C. FOR
ANALYSIS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY DATA RECORDER
SHOW THE TRAINS WERE TRAVELING
AROUND 70 MILES PER HOUR AT THE
TIME OF THE COLLISION.
>> THEY WERE GOING 70 MILES PER
HOUR JUST PRIOR TO THE IMPACT.
>> Reporter: THE ACCIDENT
OCCURRED IN AN AREA UNDER
LONG-TERM CONSTRUCTION WHERE
ONLY TWO OF THE FOUR TRACKS WERE
OPERATIONAL.
>> WE DON'T KNOW THE CAUSE YET.
BUT CERTAINLY, IT IS A WAKE-UP
CALL FOR PAYING ATTENTION TO THE
QUALITY AND EFFICIENCY OF OUR
RAIL SYSTEM.
>> Reporter: IT IS ALSO NEAR THE
SITE OF A TRAIN WRECK IN 1911.
INDUSTRY EXPERTS SAY THE
NORTHEAST CORRIDOR IS THE
BUSIEST TRAIN ROUTE IN THE
COUNTRY.
A 457-MILE STRETCH FROM
WASHINGTON, D.C. TO BOSTON.
IN CONNECTICUT ALONE, ABOUT
125,000 PASSENGERS TRAVEL PER
DAY THROUGH THE AREA WHERE THE
DERAILMENT OCCURRED.
ABOUT 30,000 PEOPLE USE THE
STATIONS WHERE SERVICE IS
CLOSED.
AND OFFICIALS WILL BE PROVIDING
SHUTTLE BUSES FOR THOSE 30,000
RESIDENTS AND ARE ALSO
ENCOURAGING THEM TO TAKE
ALTERNATIVE TRANSPORTATION AND
CAR POOLING.
MEANTIME, REPAIRS ON THOSE
DAMAGED TRACKS HAS ALREADY
BEGUN.
LESTER?
>> MICHELLE FRANZEN TONIGHT,
THANK YOU.
>>> AFTER A TURBULENT WEEK FOR
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION, THE
WHITE HOUSE WENT ON THE
DEFENSIVE TODAY.
THOUGH THE PRESIDENT HIMSELF
STEERED CLEAR OF THE
CONTROVERSIES.
NBC'S PETER ALEXANDER HAS THE
LATEST.
>> OBAMA, OBAMA!
>> Reporter: WITH THE PRESIDENT
ADDRESSING GRADUATES AT THE
HISTORICALLY BLACK MOREHOUSE
COLLEGE IN ATLANTA TODAY, NO
MENTION OF THE CONVERGENCE OF
CONTROVERSIES STILL BREWING IN
WASHINGTON.
STILL, THE WHITE HOUSE IS
AGGRESSIVELY RESPONDING, CALLING
ACCUSATIONS OF MISMANAGEMENT
OFFENSIVE AND ABSURD.
ON THE IRS ISSUE --
>> THERE IS NO QUESTION THAT
REPUBLICANS ARE TRYING TO MAKE
POLITICAL HAY HERE.
>> Reporter: A SENIOR ADVISOR
SPEAKING OUT ON ALL FIVE SUNDAY
MORNING TALK SHOWS.
>> WHEN THEY WANT TO DO WHEN
LACKING A POSITIVE AGENDA IS TRY
TO DRAG WASHINGTON INTO A SWAMP
OF PARTISAN FISHING EXPEDITIONS
TRUMPED UP HEARINGS AND FALSE
ALLEGATIONS.
WE'RE NOT GOING TO LET THAT
HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
TEAM PROMISING ACCOUNTABILITY AT
THE IRS.
STILL, REPUBLICANS AREN'T
SATISFIED.
>> THERE IS A CULTURE OF
INTIMIDATION THROUGHOUT THE
ADMINISTRATION.
IT IS NO WONDER THAT THE AGENTS
AND THE IRS SORT OF GET THE
MESSAGE.
THE PRESIDENT DEMONIZES HIS
OPPONENTS.
>> Reporter: BUT GOP LEADERS
CONCEDE THERE IS NO EVIDENCE THE
WHITE HOUSE ORDERED THE
TARGETING OF CONSERVATIVES.
>> WE DON'T HAVE ANYTHING TO SAY
THAT THE PRESIDENT KNEW ABOUT
THIS.
>> THE INVESTIGATION HAS JUST
BEGUN SO I'M NOT GOING TO REACH
A CONCLUSION ABOUT WHAT WE MAY
FIND.
>> Reporter: AFTER WHAT MAY HAVE
BEEN AMONG THE TOUGHEST WEEKS OF
THE OBAMA PRESIDENCY, A
JUST-RELEASED POLL SHOWS THE
PRESIDENT'S APPROVAL RATING
LARGELY UNAFFECTED.
STILL THE MAJORITY OF AMERICANS
VIEW ALL THREE ISSUES AS VERY
IMPORTANT TO THE NATION.
DESPITE WHITE HOUSE CLAIMS THAT
SOME CONGRESSIONAL REPUBLICANS
ARE OVERPLAYING THEIR HAND.
>> THIS IS NOT WATERGATE, BUT
THERE ARE SOME PEOPLE IN THE
ADMINISTRATION WHO HAVE ACTED AS
IF THEY WANT TO BE NIXONIAN.
AND THAT'S A VERY BIG PROBLEM.
>> WHAT UNITES ALL THESE THINGS,
IT UNDERMINES THE CREDIBILITY OF
THE ADMINISTRATION AND THE
PRESIDENT AND THE COMPETENCE OF
GOVERNMENT.
THIS IS A TIME WHEN WE HAVE A
PRESIDENT WHO IS REALLY TRYING
HARD TO PROVE THAT GOVERNMENT
CAN IMPROVE OUR LIVES.
>> Reporter: AT AN EVENT THIS
AFTERNOON, PRESIDENT OBAMA
COMPLAINED THAT PARTISAN BATTLES
ARE KEEPING THIS COUNTRY'S
ECONOMY FROM GETTING STRONGER.
LESTER, THERE ARE MORE BATTLES
ON TAP THIS WEEK.
FORMER IRS COMMISSIONER DOUG
SCHULMAN IS SCHEDULED TO TESTIFY
BEFORE CONGRESS WEDNESDAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, PETER.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE NOW KNOW WHERE BUT WE
STILL DON'T KNOW WHO.
WE'RE TALKING OF COURSE ABOUT
THE HUGE POWERBALL JACKPOT AND
THAT ONE WINNING TICKET THAT
SOMEONE BOUGHT IN A SMALL TOWN
IN CENTRAL FLORIDA.
NBC'S KERRY SANDERS IS THERE
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: IN ZEPHYRHILLS,
FLORIDA, POPULATION 13,337, WE
KNOW WHO DIDN'T WIN.
>> WARREN CONNELLY FROM
ZEPHYRHILLS.
>> Reporter: A LOSER?
>> A LOSER.
>> Reporter: THE ONE AND ONLY
WINNING TICKET WAS SOLD AT THIS
PUBLIX GROCERY STORE.
THE CHANCES OF WINNING -- 1 IN
175 MILLION.
>> WOW.
I SHOULD HAVE WENT TO PUBLIX.
>> Reporter: WHILE IT IS
BELIEVED A RESIDENT OF THIS TOWN
FAMOUS FOR ZEPHYRHILLS SPRINGS
BOTTLED WATER IS THE WINNER,
IT'S POSSIBLE THE TICKET HOLDER
COULD HAVE PARACHUTED IN FROM
ELSEWHERE.
TENS OF THOUSANDS COME TO
ZEPHYRHILLS FOR ITS DROP ZONE,
ONE OF THE MOST POPULAR SKY
DIVING SPOTS IN THE UNITED
STATES.
ANNEMARIE HAMMOND BOUGHT A
POWERBALL TICKET AT THAT PUBLIX
GROCERY STORE LAST NIGHT.
>> THIS MORNING WHEN WE HEARD
THE THING ON THE NEWS -- I RAN
TO MY PURSE.
I WAS LIKE -- AW.
>> Reporter: THE WINNING TICKET
IS WORTH $590.5 MILLION.
$148 MILLION GOES RIGHT TO THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT IN TAXES.
IF THE WINNER TAKES THE LUMP
SUM, IT WILL BE A $370 MILLION
PAYDAY.
THE SECOND LARGEST LOTTERY
WINNINGS IN THE UNITED STATES,
EVER.
>> TONIGHT WE HAD THE BIGGEST
JACKPOT IN POWERBALL HISTORY.
>> Reporter: THE $590 MILLION
JACKPOT IS SO LARGE, IT COULD
FUND THE CITY OF ZEPHYRHILLS'
ENTIRE GOVERNMENT BUDGET FOR THE
NEXT 12 YEARS.
>> I DON'T SEE HOW ONE PERSON
COULD EVER SPEND THAT KIND OF
MONEY.
IN THEM, THEIR CHILDREN AND
THEIR GRANDCHILDREN COULDN'T
SPEND THAT KIND OF MONEY.
>> Reporter: WHILE WE'RE HERE
WAITING TO FIND OUT WHO WON THE
POWERBALL, IN VIRGINIA AND NEW
JERSEY, THERE WERE TWO WINNING
TICKETS SOLD IN THE MEGA
MILLIONS.
THE IDENTITIES OF THOSE WINNING
TICKETS OWNERS ARE YET TO COME
FORWARD.
BUT BY COMPARISON TO THE $590
MILLION IN THE POWERBALL, THE
MEGA MILLION WINNERS ARE GOING
TO HAVE TO SPLIT A MEASLY $190
MILLION.
LESTER?
>> TOUGH TIMES INDEED, KERRY
SANDERS, THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> YOU MAY FEEL LIKE YOU NEED A
LOTTERY JACKPOT WHEN YOU HEAR
THE LATEST NEWS AT THE PUMP.
AAA SAYS THE COST OF A GALLON OF
GAS HAS JUMPED 14 CENTS FROM A
MONTH AGO.
THE AVERAGE PRICE OF A GALLON OF
REGULAR IS NOW $3.65.
PRICES ARE HIGHEST IN
MINNEAPOLIS AND LOWEST IN
TUCSON.
>>> OFF ALASKA'S MAINLAND
TONIGHT, THE PAVLOV VOLCANO
CONTINUES TO ERUPT BILLOWING ASH
22,000 FEET HIGH.
SCIENTISTS TRACKING THE VOLCANO
IN ALASKA'S REMOTE ALEUTIAN
ISLANDS CHAIN SAY ITS STEAM AND
ASH PLUM IS THINNING AND IS NO
LONGER A THREAT TO INTERNATIONAL
AIR TRAFFIC.
>>> WHEN "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
CONTINUES FOR THIS SUNDAY, NEW
DIAGNOSIS GUIDELINES FOR MENTAL
HEALTH PROFESSIONALS CAUSING
CONTROVERSY.
>>> AND LATER, A TIME HONORED
TRADITION AND WHY THE OLD
MACHINES ARE ONCE AGAIN THE
RIGHT STUFF.
>>> FROM THE FDA TONIGHT -- A
WARNING TO HEALTH CARE PROVIDERS
ABOUT STERILE PRODUCTS MADE BY A
LEADING COMPOUNDING PHARMACY.
THE GOVERNMENT SAYS THE PRODUCTS
MADE BY THE DALLAS-BASED
NUVISION PHARMACY MAY HAVE BEEN
CONTAMINATED AND COULD PUT
PATIENTS AT RICK OF INFECTION.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO MENTAL HEALTH
AND NEW GUIDELINES TO HELP
PROFESSIONALS DIAGNOSE SOME
COMMON DISORDERS.
NBC'S CHIEF MEDICAL EDITOR DR.
NANCY SNYDERMAN SAYS FOR SOME
THE NEW CLASSIFICATIONS ARE
CAUSING CONTROVERSY.
>> Reporter: AT 5 YEARS OLD,
SCOTT FINKELSTEIN WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH ASPERGER'S SYNDROME.
NOW, 23, HE'S LIVED WITH THE
DISORDER FOR AS LONG AS HE CAN
REMEMBER.
>> IT JUST MAKES ME UNABLE TO
READ PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: PEOPLE WITH
ASPERGER'S LIKE SCOTT HAVE OFTEN
RELIED ON ASSISTANCE FROM HEALTH
SERVICES AND EARLY INTERVENTION,
RECEIVED BECAUSE OF THEIR
DIAGNOSIS.
MANY FAMILIES WORRY THIS
CRITICAL AID WILL BE IN JEOPARDY
AFTER THE RELEASE OF A NEW
HANDBOOK.
>> IT IS A VERY SCARY THING FOR
US AND FOR FAMILIES WHO HAVE
CHILDREN ON THE AUTISM SPECTRUM
THAT NEED SERVICES.
>> Reporter: THAT HANDBOOK, THE
DIAGNOSTIC AND STATISTICAL
MANUAL OF MENTAL DISORDERS, OR
THE DSM, IS THE GOLD STANDARD
USED BY PSYCHIATRISTS FOR MORE
THAN 60 YEARS TO GUIDE THEM WHEN
DIAGNOSING MENTAL DISORDERS.
>> THERE IS CONSIDERABLE AMOUNT
OF RESEARCH AND CLINICAL
EXPERTISE AND ADVANCES THAT MADE
IT VERY APPROPRIATE FOR US TO
ISSUE A DSM-5.
>> Reporter: UNDER THE NEW
GUIDELINES, THOSE WHO HAD ONCE
BEEN DIAGNOSED WITH ASPERGER'S
NOW FALL UNDER THE BROADER
UMBRELLA OF AUTISM SPECTRUM
DISORDER.
NEW DIAGNOSES, SUCH AS HOARDING
DISORDER AND BINGE EATING
DISORDER HAVE ALSO BEEN ADDED TO
THE MANUAL.
CHANGES THAT HAVE CREATED
CONTROVERSY.
>> DSM-5 HAS BEEN TOO INNOVATIVE
ALLOWING TOO MANY OPENINGS FOR
UNINTENDED CONSEQUENCES THAT
WILL LEAD TO EXCESSIVE AND
HARMFUL TREATMENT.
>> Reporter: DESPITE THE DEBATE,
SOME EXPERTS SAY THAT WHILE
DISORDER CLASSIFICATION WILL
CHANGE, TREATMENT OPTIONS WILL
REMAIN THE SAME.
SO DOES THE NEW DSM GIVE DOCS
MORE FREEDOM TO JUST SAY IT I'LL
JUST FIX IT WITH A PILL?
>> NO.
THE NEW MANUAL DOESN'T GIVE THAT
KIND OF PERMISSION TO FIX IT
WITH A PILL AT ALL.
IT IS NOT A TREATMENT DOCUMENT.
NEVER WAS.
IT'S A COMMUNICATION DOCUMENT.
>> MAYBE WE CAN THINK ABOUT IT
DIFFERENTLY.
>> Reporter: A BRIGHT SPOT FOR
FAMILIES LIKE THE FINKLESTEINS,
TRYING TO MAKE SURE LOVED ONES
WITH MENTAL DISORDERS GET THE
NECESSARY CARE.
>> JUST BECAUSE IT'S GONE AWAY
IN THE BOOK DOESN'T MEAN IT IS
GOING AWAY IN REAL LIFE.
>> Reporter: NO MATTER HOW THOSE
DISORDERS ARE DEFINED.
DR. NANCY SNYDERMAN, NBC NEWS,
NEW YORK.
>>> IN JUST A MOMENT, A VOICE OF
EXPERIENCE.
THE PRESIDENT SPEAKING
PERSONALLY ABOUT RACE AND
RESPONSIBILITY.
>>> AT HIS COMMENCEMENT SPEECH
AT MOREHOUSE COLLEGE IN ATLANTA
TODAY, PRESIDENT OBAMA PAID
TRIBUTE TO THE ALMA MATER OF THE
REVEREND DR. MARTIN LUTHER KING
JR.
THE PRESIDENT SPOKE IN VERY
PERSONAL TERMS TYING DR. KING'S
JOURNEY TO HIS OWN STRUGGLES
GROWING UP.
>> WE KNOW THAT TOO MANY YOUNG
MEN IN OUR COMMUNITY CONTINUE TO
MAKE BAD CHOICES AND I HAVE TO
SAY, GROWING UP, I MADE QUITE A
FEW MYSELF.
SOMETIMES I WROTE OFF MY OWN
FAILINGS AS JUST ANOTHER EXAMPLE
OF THE WORLD TRYING TO KEEP A
BLACK MAN DOWN.
I HAD A TENDENCY SOMETIMES TO
MAKE EXCUSES FOR ME NOT DOING
THE RIGHT THING.
BUT ONE OF THE THINGS THAT ALL
OF YOU HAVE LEARNED OVER THE
LAST FOUR YEARS IS THERE'S NO
LONGER ANY ROOM FOR EXCUSES.
BE THE BEST HUSBAND TO YOUR
WIFE, OR YOUR BOYFRIEND OR YOUR
PARTNER.
BE THE BEST FATHER YOU CAN BE TO
YOUR CHILDREN.
BECAUSE NOTHING'S MORE
IMPORTANT.
WHATEVER SUCCESS I HAVE
ACHIEVED, WHATEVER POSITIONS OF
LEADERSHIP I HAVE HELD, HAVE
DEPENDED LESS ON IVY LEAGUE
DEGREES OR S.A.T. SCORES OR GPAs
AND HAVE INSTEAD BEEN DUE TO
THAT SENSE OF CONNECTION AND
EMPATHY.
THE SPECIAL OBLIGATION I FELT AS
A BLACK MAN, LIKE YOU, TO HELP
THOSE WHO NEED IT MOST, PEOPLE
WHO DIDN'T HAVE THE
OPPORTUNITIES THAT I HAD.
BECAUSE THERE BUT FOR THE GRACE
OF GOD GO I, I MIGHT HAVE BEEN
IN THEIR SHOES.
I MIGHT HAVE BEEN IN PRISON.
I MIGHT HAVE BEEN UNEMPLOYED.
I MIGHT NOT HAVE BEEN ABLE TO
SUPPORT A FAMILY.
AND THAT MOTIVATES ME.
>> THE PRESIDENT IS SHARING IN A
WAY WE RARELY HEAR HIM AT
MOREHOUSE COLLEGE TODAY.
>>> "SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE" SAID
FAREWELL TO SOME OF ITS
SIGNATURE STARS LAST NIGHT ON A
NIGHT OF SWAN SONGS.
BILL HADER MADE HIS FINAL
APPEARANCE AS THE NIGHTCLUB
STEFAN.
SETH MEYERS ANNOUNCED HE'S
LEAVING THE SHOW WHEN HE TAKES
OVER "LATE NIGHT" HERE ON NBC.
>> GOODNIGHT!
>> FRED ARMISEN ALSO REPORTED
LEAVING.
HE PERFORMED LAST NIGHT AS THE
PUNK ROCKER IAN RUBBISH.
BIG SHOES TO FILL WHEN THE SHOW
STARTS ITS 39th SEASON IN
SEPTEMBER.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, WHY
TYPEWRITERS ARE SUDDENLY HIP
AGAIN.
>>> SEEMS LIKE EVERYTHING THESE
DAYS IS DIGITAL.
AND SO A STORY ABOUT
COMMUNICATING IN A SIMPLER WAY
FROM A SIMPLER TIME ALMOST MAKES
US FEEL SENTIMENTAL.
NBC'S STEPHANIE GOSK NOW ON THE
RETURN OF THE TYPEWRITER.
>> Reporter: NOT THAT LONG AGO,
THIS WAS THE SOUND OF THE
WORKPLACE.
THE AGE OF THE TYPEWRITER.
THE BRAND NAMES HAD GRAVITAS.
SMITH CORONA.
ROYAL STANDARD.
AND THE OILED BLICKENSDERFER.
AS GREAT AS THEY WERE, THESE
MARVELS OF MECHANICS STOOD NO
CHANCE AGAINST THE DIGITAL AGE,
OR DID THEY?
AT THE MESA TYPEWRITER EXCHANGE
IN ARIZONA, THEIR REPAIRMAN BILL
WALD IS NOTICING A CHANGE.
>> NOW PEOPLE USING TYPEWRITERS
ARE A DIFFERENT GROUP, AND THEY
LOVE THEIR TYPEWRITERS.
IN THE LAST FEW YEARS I'VE HAD
MORE AND MORE INTEREST FROM
YOUNGER PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: NOT FAR FROM THEIR
ENGLISH TEACHER HAS HIS
OPPORTUNITIES WRITE ENTIRELY ON
TYPEWRITERS.
>> IT HELPS YOU CONCENTRATE
MORE.
BECAUSE ON A COMPUTER, THERE IS
OTHER DISTRACTIONS.
>> Reporter: THERE'S NO
BACKSPACE, AUTO CORRECT OR
SPELL-CHECK.
>> YOU GOT TO KNOW WHAT YOU'RE
GOING TO SAY, YOU GOT TO MAKE
SURE IT MAKES SENSE.
>> Reporter: THIS CLASSROOM IS
HOME TO DOZENS OF MACHINES.
>> 20 YEARS AGO IF YOU WERE
COLLECTING A TYPEWRITER, YOU
WERE A TOWN ECCENTRIC.
NOW YOU CAN FIND PEOPLE ACROSS
THE COUNTRY INTERESTED IN THE
SAME HOBBY.
>> Reporter: THEY'RE POPPING UP
IN UNLIKELY PLACES.
THERE ARE THE FAMOUS COLLECTORS,
THE HIGH-PROFILE USERS, AND THE
MODERN-DAY ENTHUSIASTS, LIKE
THIS GROUP IN NEW YORK TAKING
PART IN A TYPE-IN.
AN IDEA STARTED BY MIKE THAT'S
SPREAD AROUND THE WORLD.
TELL ME WHAT IT IS ABOUT
TYPEWRITERS THAT YOU LIKE SO
MUCH.
>> ONE, THEY'RE FINELY CRAFTED.
TWO, THEY'RE NOT MEANT TO BE
OBSOLETE.
THREE, THEY ONLY DO ONE THING.
>> Reporter: THEY TYPE.
THAT'S IT.
WITH A LITTLE PRACTICE, THIS IS
SO EASY.
I WAS READY FOR THE SPEED
CONTEST.
>> GO.
>> WHERE'S THE 1?
A ROUGH START.
I'M ALREADY LOSING.
A LOT HARDER THAN IT LOOKS.
OH, I RIPPED IT!
BUT I DID FINISH.
COLLEGE FRESHMAN MATTHEW SEDONI
WAS THE FASTEST.
THAT'S HIS COPY ON THE LEFT AND
MINE ON THE RIGHT.
>> WHEN YOU'RE SITTING AT ONE
YOU ALMOST FEEL LIKE YOU COULD
BE ERNEST HEMMINGWAY OR
SOMETHING.
>> Reporter: A REVIVAL OF THE
TYPEWRITER, PROVING ITS TIMELESS
APPEAL.
STEPHANIE GOSK, NBC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>>> AND THAT'S "NBC NIGHTLY
NEWS" FOR THIS SUNDAY.
BRIAN WILLIAMS WILL BE HERE
TOMORROW.
I'M LESTER HOLT REPORTING FROM
NEW YORK.
FOR ALL OF US HERE AT NBC NEWS,
GOODNIGHT.
I'M DIANE DWYER.
>>> RIGHT NOW FIREFIGHTERS ARE
BATTLING A FIRE FIGHT.
THERE IS A PRESCHOOL NEAR BY.
WITNESSES THEY HUGE PLUMES OF
SMOKE ARE FILLING THE AIR AND
THE FIRE DEPARTMENT TWEETED THAT
HOMES ARE THREATENED.
>> TONIGHT, REPORTS OF ANOTHER
SIGNIFICANT PROBLEM FOR THE NEW
EASTERN SPAN OF THE BAY