WERE ASSEMBLED INSIDE PRESSURE
COOKER POTS SIMILAR TO THIS ONE
PACKED WITH BBs, BALL BEARINGS
AND NAILS TO MAGNIFY THE INJURY.
AS THESE HOMELAND SECURITY
BULLETINS NOTE, PRESSURE COOKERS
HAVE BEEN USED FOR DECADES IN
TERROR BOMBINGS.
INSTRUCTIONS FOR MAKING THEM
APPEAR ON THE INTERNET INCLUDING
JUST LAST MONTH IN AN AL QAEDA
MAGAZINE "INSPIRE."
INVESTIGATORS SAY THE EXPLOSIVE
IN BOSTON WAS MOST LIKELY
SMOKELESS POWDER, GUNPOWDER LIKE
THIS, AVAILABLE AT SPORTING
GOODS STORES, NOT SOMETHING MORE
POWERFUL LIKE DYNAMITE.
AND THEY BELIEVE THE BOMBS WERE
CARRIED TO THE SCENE IN DARK
NYLON BAGS AND SET OFF BY
TIMERS.
THE FBI IS EXAMINING PHOTOS LIKE
THIS FROM NBC AFFILIATE WHDH TO
SEE IF NYLON BAGS MIGHT HAVE
BEEN PLACED IN TRASH BAGS ON THE
SIDEWALK TO APPEAR LESS
CONSPICUOUS.
A FORMER BOMB INVESTIGATOR SAYS
THE EXPERTS KNOW WHAT TO LOOK
FOR.
>> THEY ARE ABLE TO RECOGNIZE
THE MINUTE PIECES OF AN ARTICLE
THAT A CIVILIAN WOULDN'T EVEN
KNOW WHAT IT WAS, BUT A BOMB
INVESTIGATOR LIKE FBI OR ATF
WILL SAY, THAT'S FROM A CLOCK.
THAT'S FROM A BATTERY.
>> Reporter: BOSTON POLICE SAY
THE AREA WAS CHECKED TWICE FOR
BOMBS YESTERDAY, BUT THERE WAS
NO SECURITY SCREENING.
>> BECAUSE THERE IS UNRESTRICTED
ACCESS TO THE RACE COURSE,
SIMPLY BECAUSE IT'S 28 MILES
LONG, PEOPLE CAN COME AND GO AND
BRING ITEMS IN AND OUT.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES LAST
NIGHT SEARCHED THE APARTMENT OF
A FOREIGN STUDENT WHO WAS
INJURED IN THE BLAST AND SEEN
RUNNING AWAY, BUT THEY FOUND
NOTHING, AND HE IS NOT
CONSIDERED A SUSPECT.
INVESTIGATORS URGE ANYONE WHO
WAS AT THE SCENE YESTERDAY TO
SEND THEM PICTURES AND VIDEOS.
ONE PERSON RESPONDING, BEN
THORNDIKE, WHO WORKS IN A
BUILDING THAT OVERLOOKS THE
FINISH LINE.
HE SNAPPED THESE PICTURES IN
RAPID SEQUENCE IMMEDIATELY AFTER
THE FIRST EXPLOSION.
ONE PERSON CAN BE SEEN RUNNING
AWAY, CLOTHES TORN BY THE BLAST.
>> I JUST KEPT THE CAMERA UP,
JUST PUSHED THE RAPID SHUTTER
BUTTON DOWN AND JUST TOOK, YOU
KNOW, 25 PICTURES OVER THE
COURSE OF -- IF FELT LIKE A LONG
TIME, BUT I THINK IT WAS ONLY 15
OR 20 SECONDS.
>> Reporter: POLICE AND FEDERAL
AGENTS EVEN TOOK THE HIGHLY
UNUSUAL STEP OF ASKING PEOPLE
LEAVING BOSTON AT THE AIRPORT
TODAY IF THEY HAD PICTURES OF
VALUE, TOO.
AND THIS BREAKING NEWS ON
ANOTHER NOTE.
AN UNRELATED NOTE.
THE FBI IS ANALYZING AN ENVELOPE
SENT TO A U.S. SENATOR BUT
INTERCEPTED AT AN OFF-SITE MAIL
SITE.
A FIELD TEST INDICATED IT WAS
POSITIVE FOR THE POISON CALLED
RICIN.
IT'S NOW IN THE LAB TO SEE IF IT
REALLY IS THAT CHEMICAL.
BRIAN?
>> Reporter: PETE WILLIAMS IN
OUR WASHINGTON BUREAU TONIGHT.
PETE, THANKS.
AND AFTER THIS SAD, DEPRESSING
DAY IN BOSTON, LESTER HOLT, PART
OF OUR TEAM HERE, IS HERE
TONIGHT WITH THE NEWS OF THIS
DAY.
LESTER?
>> BRIAN, THIS HEAVY POLICE
PRESENCE WILL BE A WAY OF LIFE
FOR BOSTON RESIDENTS FOR SOME
TIME TO COME, BUT THERE WERE
THOUSANDS OF VISITORS HERE,
SPECTATORS, THEY CAME TO BEAR
WITNESS TO A GREAT SPORTING
EVENT.
INSTEAD THEY ARE FILING OUT OF
TOWN HAVING BEARED WITNESS TO
TERROR.
>> Reporter: A RUNNER, A CAMERA
STRAPPED TO HER BODY WITH A VIEW
OF THE FINISH LINE ON THE
HORIZON.
A VIEW THAT CHANGES IN AN
INSTANT.
IT IS ONE OF COUNTLESS IMAGES
THAT CAPTURED THE DAY, IMAGES
AUTHORITIES HOPE ALSO CAPTURED
THE BOMBERS.
>> SOMETHING JUST BLEW UP.
>> THERE HAS TO BE HUNDREDS, IF
NOT THOUSANDS, OF PHOTOGRAPHS OR
VIDEOS OR OBSERVATIONS THAT WERE
MADE DOWN AT THAT FINISH LINE
YESTERDAY.
AND THEY'RE SITTING OUT THERE
AMONGST EVERYONE THAT'S WATCHING
THIS EVENT THIS MORNING.
>> I NEED OFFICERS.
A SECONDARY DEVICE!
>> Reporter: RECORDINGS OF
EMERGENCY RADIO TRAFFIC HAVE
BEEN RELEASED.
>> THERE'S MULTIPLE PEOPLE DOWN!
>> Reporter: ILLUSTRATING THE
URGENCY OF YESTERDAY'S RESPONSE.
AND TODAY ANOTHER OF THE DEAD
WAS IDENTIFIED.
29-YEAR-OLD KRYSTLE CAMPBELL OF
MEDFORD, MASSACHUSETTS.
>> EVERYBODY THAT KNEW HER LOVED
HER.
SHE LOVED HER JOB.
SHE HAD A HEART OF GOLD.
SHE WOULD ALWAYS SMILE.
YOU COULDN'T ASK FOR A BETTER
DAUGHTER.
I CAN'T BELIEVE THIS HAS
HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: ALLEN PANZER, A
NORTH CAROLINA EMERGENCY ROOM
PHYSICIAN, WAS WAITING FOR HIS
WIFE TO CROSS THE FINISH LINE.
HE SAW THE EXPLOSION AND
ATTENDED TO THE MOST SERIOUSLY
WOUNDED.
>> IT WAS BLAST INJURIES TO THE
LOWER EXTREMITIES FOR THE MOST
PART.
ONE GENTLEMAN HAD NO LEGS BELOW
THE KNEES.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS SAY
THE BOMBS WERE PLACED AMONG THE
CROWD DOWN THE BLOCK FROM EACH
OTHER, DETONATING JUST OVER TEN
SECONDS APART.
OFFICIALLY, IT WAS BACK TO
BUSINESS IN MOST OF BOSTON
TODAY.
BUT REMINDERS ARE EVERYWHERE
THAT THINGS ARE NOT BACK TO
NORMAL.
>> YOU SEE PEOPLE, AND THEIR
FACES ARE REALLY SOBER, JUST
WALKING AROUND.
IT'S KIND OF AN EERIE FEELING IN
THE AIR.
>> Reporter: TODAY RUNNERS WERE
ABLE TO RETURN TO THE ROUTE TO
COLLECT BELONGINGS THAT WERE
LEFT IN THE HASTE OF YESTERDAY'S
FLEE TO SAFETY.
SOME WERE GIVEN MEDALS FOR A
RACE THEY WERE UNABLE TO
COMPLETE.
MEDALS HOPELESSLY TARNISHED BY
TRAGEDY.
>> I RAN 22 MILES THINKING ABOUT
THE MINUTE WHEN I WAS GOING TO
COME DOWN THE STREET AND GET
THIS MEDAL.
AND IT'S, LIKE, THIS IS NOT HOW
I WANTED IT, BUT IT'S AROUND MY
NECK, AND I WAS A PART OF THIS
DAY.
>> Reporter: THERE ARE ANY
NUMBER OF STORIES THAT WILL
BREAK YOUR HEART HERE INCLUDING
THE STORY OF THE SECOND VICTIM,
KRYSTLE CAMPBELL.
HER PARENTS WERE FIRST TOLD THAT
IT WAS HER FRIEND WHO DIED,
BRIAN, BUT DOCTORS HAD TO RETURN
AND TELL THEM IT WAS KRYSTLE WHO
PASSED AWAY.
>> LESTER HOLT HERE WITH US IN
BOSTON, THANKS.
YOU HEAR THE CHURCH BELLS BEHIND
US.
THEY STARTED OFF WITH "GOD BLESS
AMERICA" A FEW MINUTES BACK.
THIS ENTIRE CITY, OF COURSE,
CONSUMED WITH WHAT HAPPENED
YESTERDAY.
AND SO MANY QUESTIONS AND
STORIES ABOUT THE VICTIMS OF
THIS.
KATY TUR, PART OF OUR TEAM HERE
AS WELL, SHE'S BEEN LOOKING INTO
THE VICTIMS ALL DAY.
GOOD EVENING.
>> BRIAN, THEY WERE STANDING ON
THE SIDELINES CHEERING ON LOVED
ONES, FRIENDS AND EVEN
STRANGERS.
THEN ALL OF A SUDDEN CHAOS.
TONIGHT WE'RE LEARNING MORE
ABOUT THE TRAUMA OF THOSE FIRST
FEW MOMENTS INCLUDING THE
VICTIMS.
AND AN 8-YEAR-OLD BOY EXCITED TO
SEE A MARATHON.
>> Reporter: TODAY NEIGHBORS
REMEMBERED 8-YEAR-OLD MARTIN
RICHARD, THE YOUNGEST OF THE
VICTIMS.
>> TO KNOW THAT THAT LITTLE BOY
WILL NEVER COME HOME AGAIN IS --
IT KEPT ME UP TONIGHT, AND IT
WILL PROBABLY KEEP ME UP MORE
NIGHTS.
>> Reporter: MARTIN WAS IN THE
CROWD WATCHING THE MARATHON WITH
HIS PARENTS, 11-YEAR-OLD BROTHER
AND 5-YEAR-OLD SISTER CLOSE TO
WHERE THE BLAST WENT OFF.
HE WAS KILLED.
HIS MOM AND SISTER RIGHT NOW ARE
IN VERY BAD SHAPE.
IN A STATEMENT, HIS FATHER, BILL
RICHARD, WROTE, "MY DEAR SON
MARTIN HAS DIED FROM INJURIES
SUSTAINED IN THE ATTACK ON
BOSTON.
MY WIFE AND DAUGHTER ARE BOTH
RECOVERING FROM SERIOUS
INJURIES.
WE THANK OUR FAMILY AND FRIENDS,
THOSE WE KNOW AND THOSE WE HAVE
NEVER MET, FOR THEIR THOUGHTS
AND PRAYERS."
>> WE'RE A VERY CLOSE COMMUNITY,
AND WE ARE ALL DEVASTATED.
>> Reporter: THE DRAWING HE MADE
IN FRONT OF HIS HOME OVER THE
WEEKEND DREW NEIGHBORS AND
FRIENDS WHO LEFT FLOWERS AND
CANDLES IN REMEMBRANCE OF THE
YOUNG BOY.
AT THE FINISH LINE IT ONLY TOOK
MOMENTS FOR A JOYOUS
ACCOMPLISHMENT TO TURN TO
TERRIFYING CONFUSION.
78-YEAR-OLD BILL IFFRIG WAS JUST
FEET FROM THE EXPLOSION, ABOUT
TO FINISH HIS 45th MARATHON.
WHAT DID IT SOUND LIKE?
WHAT DID IT FEEL LIKE?
>> IT WAS SO LOUD.
BOOM!
>> Reporter: WHAT HAVE YOUR KIDS
SAID TO YOU?
>> THEY SAID, DAD, YOU ARE SO
LUCKY.
YEAH, I WAS REALLY LUCKY THAT IT
ENDED UP LIKE IT DID.
>> Reporter: THE FAMILIES OF
NEWTOWN SHOOTING VICTIMS WERE AT
THE RACE, BUT NONE WERE INJURED.
STILL MANY OTHERS WERE.
>> IT WAS AN EXTRAORDINARY
HORRIBLE SCENE, AND WHAT WE WERE
ABLE TO DO IS PULL TOGETHER WHAT
WE NEEDED TO PULL TOGETHER IN A
VERY SHORT PERIOD OF TIME.
>> JUST DIDN'T SEEM REAL.
>> Reporter: LEEANN AND NICHOLAS
WERE WATCHING THE RACE.
SHE WAS LEFT WITH SHRAPNEL IN
HER LEG AND A SHATTERED FEMUR.
NOW SHE REMEMBERS THE COMPASSION
OF THOSE WHO RUSHED TO HELP.
>> I HAD A WOMAN WHO I DON'T
KNOW CAME AND HELD MY HAND.
>> Reporter: 30 CODE RED VICTIMS
WITH LIFE-THREATENING INJURIES
TAKEN TO HOSPITALS.
THEY AND DOZENS OF OTHERS ARE
TRYING TO RECOVER TONIGHT.
AND RIGHT NOW 24 REMAIN IN
CRITICAL CONDITION.
REGIONAL BLOOD BANKS ARE ASKING
FOR DONATIONS FROM SURROUNDING
STATES, BRIAN, AS BOSTON HAS
DEPLETED ALL OF THEIR SUPPLIES.
>> AS WE SAID, IT'S CONSUMED
THIS ENTIRE CITY.
KATY TUR HERE WITH US IN BOSTON.
THANKS.
>>> AND TONIGHT, GOVERNOR OF
MASSACHUSETTS DEVAL PATRICK IS
WITH US FROM THE COMMAND POST AT
THE WESTIN HOTEL NOT FAR FROM US
HERE.
GOVERNOR, THANK YOU FOR BEING
WITH US.
FIRST OF ALL, IS THERE ANYTHING
YOU'VE BEEN ON THE INSIDE ALL
DAY, ANYTHING YOU'VE LEARNED?
ANY IMAGERY YOU'VE SEEN THAT
WOULD LEAD US TO BELIEVE THEY'RE
ANY FURTHER DOWN THE ROAD?
>> WELL, I THINK YOUR REPORTS
ABOUT THE STATUS OF THE
INVESTIGATION ARE PRETTY
THOROUGH.
WHAT WE KNOW, WE HAVE MADE
PUBLIC OR MOST OF IT ANYHOW.
THE INVESTIGATORS AT THE
FEDERAL, STATE AND LOCAL LEVEL
ARE COORDINATING BEAUTIFULLY,
AND WE HAVE EVERY CONCEIVABLE
ASSET ON THE GROUND, AND THEY
ARE LITERALLY COMBING THE BLAST
SITE WITH A FINE-TOOTH COMB TO
PIECE TOGETHER WHAT HAPPENED AND
ULTIMATELY THE STORY OF HOW AND
BRING WHOMEVER IS RESPONSIBLE TO
JUSTICE.
IT'S A SLOW PROCESS.
IT'S A PAINFUL ONE.
BUT THERE ARE ALSO ALONGSIDE
THIS, BRIAN, SOME EXTRAORDINARY
STORIES OF GRACE AND KINDNESS
THAT PEOPLE HAVE SHOWN, BOTH
NEIGHBORS FROM MASSACHUSETTS AND
VISITORS FROM OUTSIDE OF THE
CITY AND THE STATE.
>> I HEARD YOUR PUBLIC PLEA,
GOVERNOR, A YOUNG WOMAN WHO WAS
HELPED BY AN ARMY SERGEANT JUST
BACK FROM AFGHANISTAN.
YOU'RE HELPING TO FIND HIM TO
REUNITE HIM WITH HER.
ONE FINAL QUESTION BEFORE WE
LOSE YOU.
AND THAT IS, IT WAS STRIKING
YESTERDAY, THIS HAPPENED WITH
BOSTON PD OFFICERS IN THE
FOREGROUND, MEANING IF YOU CAN
GET A DEVICE INTO AN ALREADY
SECURED AREA, WHAT'S THAT GOING
TO MEAN FOR DEFENDING CITIES
LIKE BOSTON?
>> WELL, I THINK THE THING TO
REMEMBER HERE -- MAYBE TWO
THINGS TO REMEMBER.
FIRST OF ALL, THE FIRST JOB OF
EVERYBODY IS TO FIGURE OUT WHO
IS RESPONSIBLE FOR WHAT HAPPENED
AND PRECISELY WHAT HAPPENED AND
TO BRING THAT PERSON OR PERSONS
TO JUSTICE.
AND THAT'S WHAT LAW ENFORCEMENT
IS FOCUSED ON.
THE SECOND THING, THEN, IS TO
SORT OUT HOW THIS COULD HAVE
HAPPENED.
YOU KNOW, WE'VE HAD 116 YEARS OF
INCIDENT-FREE MARATHONS.
AND EVERY YEAR WE HAVE LEARNED
LESSONS FROM THE ONE BEFORE.
IT'S A TERRIBLE, TERRIBLE AND
BLOODY LESSON WE'RE HAVING TO
LEARN THIS TIME.
BUT I AM ALSO CONFIDENT THAT WE
WILL LEARN WHAT LESSONS THERE
ARE TO BE LEARNED, AND NEXT
YEAR'S MARATHON WILL BE BIGGER
AND BETTER THAN EVER.
>> THE GOVERNOR OF THE
COMMONWEALTH OF MASSACHUSETTS,
DEVAL PATRICK, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH FOR BEING WITH US.
WE'LL BE BACK WITH MORE NEWS
FROM BOSTON AND ELSEWHERE RIGHT
AFTER THIS.
>>> WE'RE BACK AT THE CORNER OF
THE PUBLIC GARDEN HERE IN
BOSTON.
THE NEXT MAJOR MARATHON IS THIS
SUNDAY IN LONDON.
FOR THAT MATTER THERE'S A MAJOR
SPORTING EVENT EVERY DAY ALL
YEAR ALL AROUND THE WORLD.
AND THIS RAISES QUESTIONS ABOUT
HOW TO DEFEND AND SECURE THOSE.
TOM COSTELLO IS AT THE VERIZON
CENTER IN WASHINGTON WHERE
THERE'S AN NHL GAME TONIGHT.
THE CAPITALS PLAYING THE TORONTO
MAPLE LEAFS.
TOM, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: HI, BRIAN.
AND THE ATTACK ON BOSTON VERY
MUCH ON THE MINDS OF PEOPLE HERE
AS WELL AS AT SPORTING EVENTS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
BUT THERE IS ALSO A
DETERMINATION NOT TO BOW TO
TERRORISTS.
ON THIS DAY AFTER, MANY
AMERICANS FELT ON EDGE LIKE THEY
HAVEN'T IN YEARS.
SUSPICIOUS PACKAGES BROUGHT
BOSTON'S LOGAN AND NEW YORK'S
LaGUARDIA AIRPORTS TO A CRAWL
TODAY.
BOTH WERE LATER DEEMED SAFE.
IN WASHINGTON, A HEAVY POLICE
PRESENCE IN THE SUBWAYS.
PEDESTRIAN TRAFFIC IN FRONT OF
THE WHITE HOUSE SHUT DOWN.
CAPITOL POLICE CHECKED EVERY
TRASH CAN FOR EXPLOSIVES.
WHILE AT THE EMANCIPATION DAY
PARADE, BOTH UNEASE --
>> I WAS KIND OF CONCERNED AS TO
WHO'S HERE, YOU KNOW, WHY
THEY'RE HERE, IF ANYTHING'S
GOING TO HAPPEN.
ARE WE SAFE?
>> Reporter: -- AND DEFIANCE.
>> I CAME DOWN.
I'M NOT GOING TO BE AFRAID.
THIS IS MY HOME.
>> Reporter: ACROSS THE COUNTRY,
POLICE DEPARTMENTS WERE SHOWING
THE BADGE TODAY.
THE TSA ALSO STUFFING UP
PASSENGER SCREENINGS.
MEANWHILE, EVENT ORGANIZERS
BEGAN REVISITING SECURITY PLANS
FOR BIG UPCOMING GATHERINGS.
THE OKLAHOMA CITY MARATHON, A
BIKE RACE IN HOUSTON, A 10K IN
MIAMI, NASCAR IN VIRGINIA, EVEN
THE KENTUCKY DERBY AND INDY 500
GETTING A SECOND LOOK.
>> I THINK THE EVENT IN BOSTON
YESTERDAY WILL RAISE ONCE AGAIN
THE CONSCIOUSNESS THAT THERE IS
A REASON, THERE IS A NEED FOR
THE EXTRA SECURITY THAT THEY
ENCOUNTER.
>> Reporter: SINCE 9/11, THERE'S
BEEN A DRAMATIC INCREASE IN THE
USE OF SECURITY CAMERAS.
TODAY AN INFLUENTIAL REPUBLICAN
CALLED FOR EVEN MORE.
>> OUT ON THE STREET, THERE'S
NOT AN EXPECTATION OF PRIVACY.
>> Reporter: AT THE LAPD
INTELLIGENCE NERVE CENTER, THE
POLICE CHIEF INSISTED HIS
CAMERAS AND OFFICERS CAN'T DO IT
ALONE.
>> THERE IS NO WAY THAT 10,000
LOS ANGELES POLICE OFFICERS CAN
WATCH OVER A CITY OF 4 MILLION
PEOPLE.
WITHOUT THE HELP OF THE PEOPLE
THAT THEY'RE WATCHING.
>> Reporter: THE MESSAGE SINCE
9/11, IF YOU SEE SOMETHING, SAY
SOMETHING.
POLICE AND SECURITY EXPERTS ARE
REITERATED TO US TODAY THAT THEY
REALLY WANT PEOPLE TO CALL IN
WITH TIPS AND WITH EVEN THE
SMALLEST BITS OF INFORMATION.
THEY POINT OUT THAT IN THE PAST,
THOSE SMALL CLUES HAVE VERY
OFTEN BEEN THE KEY TO TRACKING
DOWN A CRIMINAL OR BREAKING A
TERROR SUSPECT OR CELL.
BRIAN?
>> TOM COSTELLO AT THE
CAPS/MAPLE LEAFS GAME, THANKS.
>>> THERE WAS OTHER NEWS TODAY.
WE'LL BE BACK WITH THAT RIGHT
AFTER THIS.
>>> A HUGE STORY, A COMPUTER
PROBLEM TOOK DOWN THE AMERICAN
AIRLINES RESERVATIONS AND CHECK
IN SYSTEM.
FOR A TIME, THE ENTIRE AIRLINE
GROUNDED ITS FLEET.
THEY SAID IT WAS A GLITCH AND
NOT A HACK.
AMERICAN TERMINALS AROUND THE
COUNTRY WERE JAMMED WITH DELAYED
PASSENGERS AND ARRIVING
AIRCRAFT.
LANDING UNANNOUNCED IN MANY
CASES AT AIRPORTS ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
THEY WERE FORCED TO SIT ON
TARMACS WITH NO GATES AVAILABLE
TO OFFLOAD PASSENGERS.
MORE THAN 700 FLIGHTS WERE
CANCELED.
NEARLY 1,000 DELAYED BEFORE
THINGS GOT STRAIGHTENED OUT.
BUT A VERY BAD DAY AT AMERICAN
AIRLINES.
>>> THIS NEXT STORY WOULD HAVE
RECEIVED BROAD COVERAGE WERE IT
NOT FOR THIS TERRORIST BOMBING
IN BOSTON.
A BIPARTISAN REVIEW BOARD HAS
FOUND IT INDISPUTABLE IN THEIR
WORDS THAT THE UNITED STATES HAS
ENGAGED IN THE PRACTICE OF
TORTURE SINCE 9/11.
THEY SAY THE HIGHEST OFFICIALS
IN OUR COUNTRY BEAR
RESPONSIBILITY AND SHARE
RESPONSIBILITY FOR IT.
THE REPORT SAYS TORTURE HAS
DAMAGED THE STANDING OF OUR
NATION.
ON TOP OF POTENTIALLY INCREASING
THE DANGER TO U.S. MILITARY
PERSONNEL TAKEN CAPTIVE, ON TOP
OF ALL OF IT, THE COMMISSION
FOUND NO EVIDENCE THAT TORTURE
EVER YIELDED ANY KEY
INFORMATION.
NO INFORMATION THAT WE ARE ANY
SAFER BECAUSE OF IT.
>>> AND WE LEARNED LATE TODAY,
PAT SUMMERALL HAS DIED.
HE WAS A VETERAN KICKER IN THE
NFL BUT MOST OF US CAME TO KNOW
HIM AS THE VOICE OF THE NFL.
FIRST WITH HIS PARTNER, TOM
BROOKSHIRE AND FOR YEARS WITH
THE GREAT JOHN MADDEN.
HE CALLED 16 SUPER BOWLS.
HE WAS IN THE BOOTH FOR FOUR
DECADES.
AFTER A LIFE SPENT ON THE ROAD,
HE WENT PUBLIC ABOUT HIS OWN
ALCOHOLISM.
YEARS AGO HE UNDERWENT
SUCCESSFUL REHAB.
HE HELPED SET THE MODERN DAY
STANDARD FOR MAY BY PLAY AS AN
ART FORM.
HE DIED IN DALLAS, TEXAS, AT THE
AGE OF 82.
WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH SOME
OF THE STORIES THAT EMERGED
TODAY HERE IN BOSTON.
THOSE WHO STEPPED UP AT AN AWFUL
MOMENT YESTERDAY.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT FROM BOSTON,
INEVITABLY WHEN SOMETHING BAD
LIKE THIS HAPPENS, TERRIFIC
STORIES OF HEROISM AND KINDNESS
EMERGE.
NBC'S ANNE THOMPSON WHOSE ROOTS
ARE HERE HAS THE STORY OF THIS
CITY TODAY.
>> Reporter: IF CRISIS REVEALS
CHARACTER, THEN CALL BOSTON
COURAGEOUS.
CARLOS ARREDONDO, THE MAN IN THE
COWBOY HAT, IS ONE OF MANY WHO
RAN TO HELP INSTEAD OF RUNNING
AWAY.
>> I WAS CARRYING SOMEONE WHO
LOST BOTH OF THEIR LEGS.
>> Reporter: IN THE MIDST OF THE
HORROR, HE REMEMBERED HIS LOWEST
POINT, WHEN HE LEARNED HIS SON
ALEX, A MARINE, HAD BEEN KILLED
IN IRAQ.
GRIEF STRICKEN, HE SET HIMSELF
ON FIRE AND WAS RESCUED.
HE RECALLED HIS WIFE'S WORDS OF
COMFORT AS HE CALMED JEFF
BAUMANN JR.
BAUMANN LOST HIS LOWER LEGS BUT
SURVIVED.
>> WHAT I EXPERIENCED MYSELF, I
GIVE SOMETHING TO COMFORT HIM
AND GIVE HIM HOPE AND GET HIM
OUT OF THERE AS SOON AS WE
COULD.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN CALL BOSTON
KIND.
PETER DEANDRADE LIVES TWO BLOCKS
FROM WHERE THE BOMBS WENT OFF.
LEFTOVERS FROM HIS PRE-RACE
PARTY WERE POST-RACE SUSTENANCE
TO CONFUSED RUNNERS.
>> WE CARRIED EVERYTHING OUT ON
PLATTERS AND STARTED FEEDING
PEOPLE AND BROUGHT OUT COFFEE.
THE LITTLE THINGS WE COULD DO,
MY FRIENDS AND I, TO HELP PEOPLE
OUT IN THIS TRAGEDY.
>> Reporter: BOSTON AT TIMES HAS
BEEN DIVIDED BY CLASS, ETHNICITY
AND RACE, BUT IT'S ALWAYS COME
TOGETHER ON MARATHON DAY, NEVER
MORE THAN IN 2013 WHEN NEARLY
6,000 PEOPLE OFFERED THEIR HOMES
ONLINE TO STRANDED RUNNERS.
YES, YOU CAN CALL BOSTON
GENEROUS.
MARGUERITE SMITH INVITED THREE
RUNNERS AND THEIR FIVE FRIENDS
INTO HER HOME AND FED THE
SHIVERING GROUP FROM KANSAS
CITY.
>> THEY WERE SITTING THERE NOT
ABLE TO GET INTO THEIR HOTEL,
NOT HAVING EATEN, AND THEY
WEREN'T COMPLAINING.
THEY WERE JUST VERY CHARMING.
>> Reporter: ONE OF THE RUNNERS,
ALLIE HATFIELD, POSTED PICTURES
ON HER BLOG WRITING "PEOPLE ARE
GOOD."
AND TONIGHT YOU CAN SAY THAT
ABOUT BOSTON, TOO.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC NEWS, BOSTON.
>>> AND ONE MORE NOTE BEFORE WE
GO.
IT TAKES SOMETHING BIG FOR THIS
TO HAPPEN.
THE YANKEES AND RED SOX LOGOS
SIDE BY SIDE RIGHT THERE ON THE
SIDE OF YANKEE STADIUM IN THE
BRONX WHERE TONIGHT THE YANKEES
WILL PAUSE TO PLAY THE FENWAY
ANTHEM "SWEET CAROLINE" AS THE
ULTIMATE SHOW OF SUPPORT FOR
BOSTON.
THE RIVALRY TAKES A BREAK.
IT WILL BE BACK.
THAT IS OUR BROADCAST FOR THIS
TUESDAY NIGHT FROM BOSTON.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE WITH
US.
I'M BRIAN WILLIAMS.
WE'LL LOOK FOR YOU BACK IN NEW
YORK TOMORROW NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT.
♪
>>> IT SHOWS THAT THE CULTURE
THAT THE ISSUE OF SAFETY IS
SOMETHING THAT HAS NOT BEEN A
PRIORITY.
>> WE INVESTIGATED, NOW A STATE
LAWMAKER IS DEMANDING ACTION
FROM THE GOVERNOR.
RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, THE SHAKEUP
HE'S CALLING FOR AT THE
CALIFORNIA PUBLIC UTILITIES
COMMISSION.
>>> PLUS A HIGHLY ANTICIPATED
HEARING FOR THE SOUTH BAY TEENS
ACCUSED OF SEXUALLY ASSAULTING
15-YEAR-OLD AUDRIE POTT.
>> FRANTIC MOMENTS FOR A FATHER
AND SON WHO WERE AT THE FINISH
LINE AT THE BOSTON MARATHON WHEN
THE BOMB WENT OFF.
>>> GOOD TUESDAY EVENING.
I'M JANELLE WANG.
RAJ MATHAI IS ON ASSIGNMENT.
>> I'M JESSICA AGUIRRE.
TONIGHT MORE BAY AREA FAMILIES
ARE SHARING THEIR STORIES OF
TERROR IN BOSTON.
WHAT WAS SUPPOSED TO BE THE
MEMORY OF A LIFETIME, CROSSING
THAT FINISH LINE AT THE HISTORIC
BOSTON MARATHON, TURNED INTO
PURE PANIC AND CONFUSION.
TERRY McSWEENEY JOINS US FROM
BOSTON WHERE HE SPOKE TO A
FATHER AND A SON FROM LOS ALTOS.
THEY WERE JUST LOOKING TO HAVE
THAT ULTIMATE RUNNING
EXPERIENCE, BUT REALLY THEY HAD
THE ULTIMATE BONDING EXPERIENCE.
>> Reporter: THAT'S TRUE.
YESTERDAY WAS GOING TO BE A VERY
MEMORABLE DAY FOR THE ANDERSON
FAMILY OF LOS ALTOS.
FATHER AND SON RUNNING TOGETHER
IN THE BOSTON MARATHON.
OBVIOUSLY IT'S A MEMORABLE DAY,
BUT NOT FOR THE REASON THEY HAD
HOPED.
HERE IN BOSTON TONIGHT MEMORIALS
LIKE THIS GOING UP HERE AND
THERE.
THIS ONE ON THE STREET WHERE THE
BOMBS WENT OFF.
PEOPLE STOPPING BY TO OFFER
THEIR PRAYERS AND THOUGHTS FOR
THE VICTIMS.
THE ANDERSONS, MEANWHILE, ARE
OFFERING THANKS FOR EACH OTHER.
>> THIS WAS GOING TO BE, YOU
KNOW, OUR MOMENT.
>> Reporter: AND IN A TRAGIC
WAY, IT WAS THE MOMENT FOR BOB
ANDERSON OF LOS ALTOS AND HIS
SON, MICHAEL.
THEY CAME TO BOSTON TO RUN THE
MARATHON.
BOB FINISHED BEFORE MICHAEL AND
WAS WAITING FOR HIS SON JUST
PAST THE FINISH LINE, JUST
BEFORE 2:00.
>> YOU COULD HEAR THE SOUND OF
THE BOMB AND THE SMOKE.
OH, MY GOD.
AT THAT MOMENT, I MEAN I DIDN'T
KNOW WHERE MY SON WAS.
MOMENTS LATER THERE WAS A SECOND
BOMBING OR EXPLOSION AND IT WAS
JUST -- IT WAS JUST
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> Reporter: POLICE WERE HERDING
PEOPLE AWAY.
BOB SAYS HE DIDN'T PANIC, BUT HE
KNEW HIS SON HOPED TO RUN ABOUT
A FOUR-HOUR MARATHON, AND THE
BOMBS WENT OUT SHORTLY AFTER
THAT MARK.
THE EMERGENCY MEETING PLACE FOR
THE ANDERSONS WAS THE HOTEL.
AND AFTER WHAT SEEMED LIKE DAYS,
MICHAEL TURNED UP THERE.
>> MIKE CAME IN AND WE BOTH JUST
HUGGED EACH OTHER.
I JUST SAID, MIKE, I LOVE YOU SO
MUCH.
ARE YOU OKAY?
AND THAT WAS IT.
I MEAN WE JUST -- WE HUGGED EACH
OTHER.
BUT IT'S -- IT'S JUST
UNBELIEVABLE.
>> Reporter: WHAT YOU'RE LOOKING
AT OUT HERE ON THE STREET WHERE
THE BOMBS WENT OFF IS ONE OF THE
MEDALS GIVEN TO THOSE WHO FINISH
THE BOSTON MARATHON.
SOMEONE OFFERING IT UP IN