PRONOUNCE THEM.
>> SO IMPRESSIVE.
>> THANK YOU FOR JOINING US AT
5:00.
WE HAVE NIGHTLY NEWS UP NEXT.
>>> TONIGHT, SHOCK
WAVES, NEW IMAGES OF
CHILDREN CAUGHT IN THE
HORRIFIC ATTACK IN
SYRIA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP
CALLING IT AN AFRONT
TO HUMANITY.
>>> TIME HAS RUN OUT
FOR NORTH KOREA.
>>> SHAKE-UP, TOP
TRUMP AIDE STEVE
BANNON SUDDENLY
REMOVED FROM A
POWERFUL SEAT AT THE
TABLE AS PRESIDENT
TRUMP WITHOUT ANY
EVIDENCE SAYS SUSAN
RICE MAY HAVE
COMMITTED A CRIME.
>>> O'REILLY REVOLT.
MORE ADVERTISERS BAIL
AS BILL O'REILLY GAINS
A POWERFUL DEFENDER.
>>> TORNADO EMERGENCY,
HOMES DEMOLISHED AS
SEVERE STORMS RUMBLE
ACROSS THE SOUTH.
ALERTS TONIGHT FOR
MILLIONS.
>> AMAZON REFUNDS, $70
MILLION COMING TO
CUSTOMERS.
WHO IS GETTING MONEY
BACK?
>>> AND FROM CENTER
FIELD TO CENTER STAGE,
A BELOVED BASEBALL
SLUGGER INSPIRING
AMERICA.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> FROM LOS ANGELES,
GOOD EVENING TO OUR
VIEWERS HERE IN THE
WEST.
TWO INFAMOUS DICTATORS
AND BOTH IN THE CROSS
HAIRS OF PRESIDENT
TRUMP TONIGHT RAISING
THE POTENTIAL OF
MILITARY RESPONSES
AFTER ACTS THAT ARE
DRAWING BROAD CONCERN
AND CONDEMNATION.
THE FIRST, SYRIA'S
LEADER ASSAD.
PRESIDENT TRUMP
HORRIFIED BY THE
DEADLY GAS ATTACK ON
CIVILIANS SAYING IT
CROSSES MANY LINES AND
OFFERING THE VAILED
WARNING THERE MAY BE A
NEW U.S. APPROACH TO
SYRIA.
THE PRESIDENT TRUMPING
UP HEAT ON NORTH
KOREA'S LEADER KIM
JONG-UN.
AHEAD OF A CRITICAL
MEETING TOMORROW.
AS WE SHOWED YOU
DURING THE BROADCAST
FROM SOUTH KOREA THIS
WEEK, AMERICA ARMED
FORCES ARE AT A HEIGHT
OF READINESS WITH
KIM'S RECENT THREATS.
WE HAVE TWO REPORTS
STARTING WITH THE
SYRIAN CRISIS AND
NBC'S RICHARD ENGEL.
>> Reporter: A DAY
AFTER AN ALLEGED
CHEMICAL ATTACK BY
ASSAD'S REGIME, THE
VICTIMS ARE STILL
STRUGGLING TO BREATHE.
QUIVERING
UNCONTROLLABLY.
DOCTORS SAY IT'S
CONSISTENT WITH
EXPOSURE TO A NERVE
AGENT LIKE SARIN GAS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID
THE IMAGES OF THE
VICTIMS MADE A DEEP
IMPRESSION ON HIM.
>> A CHEMICAL ATTACK
THAT WAS SO HORRIFIC
IN SYRIA AGAINST
INNOCENT PEOPLE
INCLUDING WOMEN, SMALL
CHILDREN, AND EVEN
BEAUTIFUL LITTLE
BABIES, THEIR DEATHS
WAS AN AFFRONT TO
HUMANITY.
THESE HEINOUS ACTIONS
BY THE ASSAD REGIME
CANNOT BE TOLERATED.
>> Reporter: IT'S A
BIG REVERSAL.
JUST TWO DAYS AGO
THE ADMINISTRATION
SEEMED WILLING TO
ACCOMMODATE ASSAD.
>> MY ATTITUDE TOWARD
SYRIA AND ASSAD
CHANGED VERY MUCH.
>> Reporter: AND
AFTER BLAMING FORMER
PRESIDENT OBAMA FOR
NOT TAKING ACTION
AFTER DRAWING A RED
LINE ON CHEMICAL
WEAPONS, TODAY THAT
CHANGED TOO.
>> I NOW HAVE
RESPONSIBILITY AND I
WILL HAVE THAT
RESPONSIBILITY AND
CARRY IT VERY PROUDLY.
>> Reporter: BUT
CONFRONTING ASSAD
MEANS CHALLENGING HIS
BIGGEST BACKER,
RUSSIA.
WHICH OFFERED TODAY A
VERY DIFFERENT
EXPLANATION FOR THE
VICTIMS, SAYING
ASSAD'S TROOPS BOMBED
A TERRORIST'S CHEMICAL
WEAPONS DEPOT.
BUT VIDEO OBTAINED BY
NBC NEWS OF WHAT
WITNESSES SAY IS THE
IMPACT SITE SHOWS A
CRATER IN AN OPEN
ROAD, NO DEPOT NEARBY.
AT THE U.N. SECURITY
COUNSEL AMBASSADOR
NIKKI HALEY MADE AN
EMOTIONAL ADDRESS.
>> LOOK AT THOSE
PICTURES.
HOW MANY MORE CHILDREN
HAVE TO DIE BEFORE
RUSSIA CARES?
>> Reporter: SO WILL
THE PRESIDENT RESPOND
WITH MILITARY ACTION?
HE LEFT OPEN THAT
POSSIBILITY.
>> I'M NOT SAYING I'M
DOING ANYTHING ONE WAY
OR THE OTHER.
>> Reporter: BUT THERE
ARE RISKS LIKE SYRIAN
AIR DEFENSES AND
POSSIBLE RUSSIAN
RESISTANCE.
PRESIDENT TRUMP, WHO
CAME TO OFFICE WITH A
PROMISE OF AMERICA
FIRST NOW SEEMS LIKE
HE WANTS TO BE MORE
INVOLVED IN WORLD
AFFAIRS.
HE'S BEEN CALLED AN
ISOLATIONIST, HE
DIDN'T SOUND LIKE ONE
TODAY.
LESTER?
>> RICHARD ENGEL IN
THE LONDON NEWSROOM,
THANK YOU.
>>> THE GLOBAL CRISIS
THE PRESIDENT
ADDRESSED.
NORTH KOREA FIRING YET
ANOTHER BALLISTIC
MISSILE INTO THE SEA
OF JAPAN.
CONTAINING KIM JONG
UN'S PROGRAM WILL BE
FRONT AND CENTER AS
PRESIDENT TRUMP
WELCOMES THE PRESIDENT
OF CHINA AT A
HIGH-STAKES SUMMIT AT
HIS FLORIDA ESTATE.
PETER ALEXANDER HAS
DETAILS.
>> I WILL DO WHATEVER
I HAVE TO DO.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN A
SHOWDOWN WITH NORTH
KOREA AND ITS ERRATIC
DICTATOR, KIM JONG-UN.
>> WE HAVE A BIG
PROBLEM.
WE HAVE SOMEBODY THAT
IS NOT DOING THE RIGHT
THING, AND THAT'S
GOING TO BE MY
RESPONSIBILITY.
>> Reporter: THAT
RESPONSIBILITY
HEIGHTENED BY ANOTHER
NORTH KOREAN MISSILE
TEST JUST 24 HOURS AGO
WITH A SENIOR WHITE
HOUSE OFFICIAL TELLING
NBC NEWS ALL OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE.
BUT DEALING WITH THE
ROGUE NATION'S GROWING
NUCLEAR THREAT ALSO
FALLS ON CHINA.
THE PRESIDENT THIS
WEEK WARNING IF THE
CHINESE DECIDE TO
HELP, THAT WILL BE
VERY GOOD FOR CHINA
AND IF THEY DON'T, IT
WON'T BE GOOD FOR
ANYONE.
>> CHINA IS THE ONLY
COUNTRY IN THE WORLD
THAT HAS PREDOMINANT
MATERIAL INFLUENCE ON
NORTH KOREA IN TRADE,
ENERGY, AND IN COAL.
IF CHINA PULLS THE
PLUG, NORTH KOREA HAS
NO OTHER OPTION.
>> Reporter: THE
URGENT ISSUE CERTAIN
TO DOMINANT TOMORROW'S
HIGH-STAKES SUMMIT
WITH CHINA'S PRESIDENT
THE FIRST FACE TO FACE
MEETING WITH COMPETING
AGENDAS.
>> THIS IS A TIME WHEN
THE UNITED STATES
ACTUALLY DEFINES ITS
RELATIONSHIP WITH
BEIJING, MAYBE NOT
ONLY FOR COMING
DECADES BUT FOR LONGER
THAN THAT.
>> Reporter: ONE TOOL
THE PRESIDENT IS
LIKELY TO LEAN INTO
WITH CHINA, TRADE,
PUNCTUATING A HUGE
CAMPAIGN USING BEIJING
AS A PUNCHING BAG.
>> WE CAN'T ALLOW
CHINA TO RAPE THE
COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP SAYING THEY ARE
MANIPULATING CURRENCY.
THE HISTORIC MEETING
AFTER RENEWED SCRUTINY
OF MR. TRUMP'S
PERSONAL TIES TO CHINA
INCLUDING A CHINESE
GOVERNMENT OWNED BANK
A TENANT IN TRUMP
TOWER, AND ANOTHER
LENDER ON A NEARLY
BILLION DOLLAR TRUMP
MORTGAGE.
THE PRESIDENT DENIES
ANY CONFLICTS OF
INTEREST BECAUSE HIS
SONS NOW RUN THE
FAMILY BUSINESS.
TONIGHT, THERE ARE
ALSO QUESTIONS ABOUT
IVANKA TRUMP'S
SIGNATURE LINE, MUCH
OF IT STILL MADE IN
CHINA WITH DOZENS OF
SHIPMENTS ARRIVING
SINCE THE ELECTION,
THREE IN JUST THE LAST
MONTH.
FOR HER PART, MS.
TRUMP SAYS SHE'S NO
LONGER INVOLVED WITH
HER COMPANY.
IT'S IN A TRUST RUN BY
HER BROTHER-IN-LAW AND
SISTER-IN-LAW, LESTER?
>> PETER ALEXANDER, AT
THE WHITE HOUSE,
THANKS.
>>> TO THE SUDDEN
POWER SHIFT AT THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL.
THE PRESIDENT'S TOP
AID STEVE BANNON IS
LOSING HIS SEAT AT THE
TABLE WEEKS AFTER HIS
APPOINTMENT TO THAT
POSION SPARKED
SURPRISE AND CRITICISM
AS PRESIDENT TRUMP
KICKED UP DUST OF HIS
OWN WITHOUT ANY
EVIDENCE SAYING SUSAN
RICE MAY HAVE
COMMITTED A CRIME.
NBC'S HALLIE JACKSON
HAS IT ALL COVERED.
>> THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT'S INNER
CIRCLE TODAY IN A
SINGLE FILE LINE WITH
THE NOTABLE EXCEPTION.
CHIEF STRATEGIST STEVE
BANNON, WHO'S BEEN AT
EVERY OTHER PRESS
CONFERENCE SO FAR.
A SOURCE FAMILIAR SAYS
BANNON WAS WORKING ON
HEALTH CARE BUT THE NO
SHOW CAME HOURS AFTER
HE WAS OUSTED FROM THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL.
>> STEVE BANNON RAISED
EYEBROWS AT FIRST
BECAUSE YOU DON'T PUT
POLITICAL PEOPLE ON A
NATIONAL SECURITY
COMMITTEE.
IT'S TOO SOON TO TELL
IF HE'S LOSING
INFLUENCE.
BUT HE'S CLEARLY BEEN
DIMINISHED.
>> Reporter: THE VICE
PRESIDENT INSISTING
IT'S NOT A DEMOTION.
>> THIS IS JUST A
NATURAL EVOLUTION TO
ENSURE THE NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNSEL IS
ORGANIZED IN A WAY
THAT BEST SERVES THE
PRESIDENT.
>> Reporter: THE MOVE,
WINNING BIPARTISAN
SUPPORT.
>> I'D BE VERY PLEASED
THAT HE'S NOT ON THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL.
MY HOPE IS THAT HE
WOULD HAVE NO ROLE IN
GOVERNMENT AT ALL.
>> Reporter: THAT'S
NOT HAPPENING.
WHILE BANNON IS NOT ON
THE NSC ANYMORE, HE
CAN ATTEND MEETINGS
AND HAS ONE OF THE
HIGHEST SECURITY
CLEARANCES IN THE WEST
WING.
A TOP WHITE HOUSE
OFFICIAL SAYS BANNON
WAS ORIGINALLY PUT ON
THE COMMITTEE AS A
CHECK AGAINST MICHAEL
FLYNN, THE NOW
DISMISSED NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISER.
BANNON'S GOAL
ORIGINALLY, TO BREAK
DOWN THE OBAMA ERA
STRUCTURE INSIDE THAT
NATIONAL SECURITY
TEAM, LED AT THE TIME
BY SUSAN RICE.
SHE'S IN THE
PRESIDENT'S CROSS
HAIRS NOW AS HE
ACCUSES RICE WITH NO
EVIDENCE OF COMMITTING
A CRIME BY REQUESTING
THE NAMES OF PEOPLE
CONNECTED BY THE TRUMP
TEAM BE UNMASKED.
>> THERE IS SIMPLY
NOTHING WRONG,
UNEXPECTED, ILLEGAL
ABOUT DOING THAT.
WHAT WOULD BE WRONG
AND ILLEGAL IS IF SHE
TOOK THAT NAME AND
THEN, YOU KNOW,
E-MAILED IT TO THE
PRESS.
>> I LEAKED NOTHING TO
NOBODY.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT, YET AGAIN,
MAKING AN
UNSUBSTANTIATED
SURVEILLANCE CLAIM
TELLING "THE NEW YORK
TIMES" IT'S QUOTE ONE
OF THE BIG STORIES OF
OUR TIME.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS
HE WILL EXPLAIN HIS
CLAIM AT THE RIGHT
TIME.
SUSAN RICE DECLINED TO
COMMENT ON WHAT HER
SPOKESPERSON IS
CALLING A LUDICROUS
CHARGE.
LESTER?
>> HALLIE JACKSON,
THANK YOU.
>>> TONIGHT THERE ARE
TORNADO WARNINGS
FIRING UP ACROSS THE
SOUTH.
HOMES DEMOLISHED AS
STORMS CONTINUE TO
THREATEN MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS.
IN A MOMENT AL ROKER
WILL BE HERE, BUT
FIRST, FROM KERRY
SANDERS ON THE GROUND
IN THE STORM ZONE.
>> Reporter: A
SUSPECTED TORNADO
TODAY IN WESTIN,
GEORGIA, TWISTED METAL
SCATTERED ACROSS
FIELDS, THIS HOME
COLLAPSED.
WIND RIPPING THESE
BUILDINGS APART.
NO SERIOUS INJURIES
REPORTED BUT HIGH
ANXIETY.
>> WE GATHERED DOWN
HERE, IT WAS REALLY
BAD BECAUSE THE TOP ON
THE WHOLE HOUSE
STARTED PEELING OFF.
WE KNEW IT WAS A VERY
SERIOUS STORM.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER
POSSIBLE TORNADO THIS
AFTERNOON IN HENRY
COUNTY, ALABAMA.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN IT
GOT REALLY, REALLY
CALM AND THE TREES
STARTED SPINNING AND
THE RAIN STARTED
POURING.
>> Reporter: ACROSS
THE SOUTH TODAY,
DAMAGING HAIL,
LIGHTNING STRIKES
IGNITING SEVERAL HOUSE
FIRES.
AND WIDE SPREAD
FLOODING.
SEVERAL FEET DEEP ON
THESE STREETS IN
COLUMBIA, SOUTH
CAROLINA.
IN SOME AREAS MORE
THAN TWO INCHES OF
RAIN AN HOUR.
IN AUGUSTA, GEORGIA,
WEATHER SUSPENDING PAR
THREE PLAY AT THE
MASTERS GOLF
TOURNAMENT FOR THE
FIRST TIME IN 53
YEARS.
TRAVEL ACROSS THE
COUNTRY IMPACTED WITH
MORE THAN 500 FLIGHTS
OUT OF ATLANTA
CANCELLED.
>> A LARGE EXTREMELY
DANGEROUS AND
POTENTIALLY DEADLY
TORNADO.
>> Reporter: IN TOTAL,
AT LEAST 61 MILLION
PEOPLE UNDER THREAT
TODAY AND INTO THE
EVENING.
IT'S ALL PART OF THE
SAME WEATHER SYSTEM
THAT PRODUCED THIS
TORNADO IN TINY
GOODMAN, MISSOURI ON
TUESDAY.
TODAY, THEY ARE
STARTING TO CLEAN UP
WHILE THE REGION
BRACES FOR ANOTHER
DANGEROUS NIGHT.
TONIGHT, AS WE LOOK
LIVE HERE IN RURAL
GEORGIA, THOSE INSIDE
HERE WHEN THE TORNADO
HIT SAY THEY ARE JUST
HAPPY TO HAVE ESCAPED
WHAT WERE SOME
HEART-POUNDING MOMENTS
ADDING IN TODAY'S
TORNADOS, IT'S BEEN A
BUSY SEASON SO FAR,
MORE THAN 350 TWISTERS
THIS YEAR.
LESTER?
>> OKAY.
KERRY SANDERS, THANKS.
AL ROKER IS TRACKING
THE STORMS FOR US.
WHERE IS THE DANGER
MOVING FORWARD?
>> LESTER, THE
SOUTHEAST.
WE'RE WATCHING THIS
RIGHT NOW.
20 MILLION PEOPLE
UNDER A TORNADO WATCH
AND CURRENTLY NOT JUST
A MAJOR RISK BUT A
HIGH RISK.
THE GREATEST THREAT
FOR STORMS AND
TORNADOS DOWN THROUGH
CENTRAL AND SOUTHERN
GEORGIA INTO CENTRAL
SOUTH CAROLINA.
AS THIS MOVES EAST,
THESE TORNADOS COULD
BE RAIN WRAPPED.
IT WILL BE DARK.
YOU WON'T BE ABLE TO
SEE THEM.
THAT WILL BE THE
DANGER.
THE STRONG STORMS MOVE
INTO THE NORTHEAST,
MID-ATLANTIC STATES
AND NEW ENGLAND,
BRINGING WITH IT HEAVY
FLOODING.
IN FACT, WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT 47 MILLION UNDER
A FLOOD THREAT THIS
EVENING ON INTO
TOMORROW.
LESTER?
>> AL ROKER, THANKS,
AL.
>>> NOW TO THE GROWING
BACKLASH AGAINST FOX
NEWS STAR BILL
O'REILLY.
NEARLY THREE DOZEN
ADVERTISERS HAVE NOW
ABANDONED O'REILLY'S
SHOW AFTER THE NETWORK
PAID OUT MILLIONS TO
SETTLE SEXUAL
HARASSMENT CLAIMS
AGAINST HIM.
TODAY, PRESIDENT TRUMP
HIMSELF CAME TO
O'REILLY'S DEFENSE.
ANNE THOMPSON HAS
MORE.
>> AND THE O'REILLY
FACTOR BEGINS NOW.
>> Reporter: AS
ADVERTISERS CONTINUE
TO FLEE, 35 AND
COUNTING TONIGHT,
ACCUSATIONS THE FOX
NEWS STAR ACTUALLY
HARASSED FEMALE
COLLEAGUES.
COMING TO HIS SIDE,
PRESIDENT DONALD
TRUMP.
IN AN INTERVIEW WITH
"THE NEW YORK TIMES",
TRUMP CALLED O'REILLY
A GOOD PERSON.
O'REILLY AND FOX NEWS
SETTLED CLAIMS FROM
FIVE WOMEN FOR $13
MILLION ACCORDING TO
THE TIMES BUT TRUMP
SAID, I THINK HE
SHOULDN'T HAVE SETTLED
ADDING I DON'T THINK
BILL DID ANYTHING
WRONG.
THAT DEFENSE OF
O'REILLY WHO TRUMP
KNOWS WELL INFURIATED
ATTORNEY LISA BLOOM.
>> I'VE BEEN FLOODED
BY CALLS FROM FOX NEWS
WOMEN ALL WEEK.
>> Reporter: NOW
REPRESENTING WENDY
WALSH, A FORMER FOX
CONTRIBUTOR WHO CLAIMS
O'REILLY HARASSED HER.
>> I SIMPLY SAID, I'M
SORRY, I CAN'T DO
THAT.
>> Reporter: TRUMP HAS
BEEN ACCUSED OF
UNWANTED SEXUAL
MISCONDUCT IN THE PAST
AND DENIED IT.
HIS COMMENTS TO AN
ACTRESS DURING HIS
"ACCESS HOLLYWOOD"
TAPING ALMOST DERAILED
HIS PRESIDENTIAL
CAMPAIGN.
TRUMP APOLOGIZED BUT
NO NEW WORDS FROM
O'REILLY.
A STATEMENT EARLIER
THIS WEEK HIS FAME
MADE HIM VULNERABLE TO
LAWSUITS AND HE
SETTLED TO PROTECT HIS
CHILDREN.
A CONTROVERSY IN THE
HEADLINES DURING
APRIL, WHAT THE
PRESIDENT HAS
PROCLAIMED AS NATIONAL
SEXUAL ASSAULT AND
PREVENTION MONTH.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, AMAZON
SHOPPERS, LISTEN UP,
WHY THE ONLINE
SHOPPING GIANT IS
REFUNDING $70 MILLION
TO PARENTS AND HOW YOU
MIGHT BE ABLE TO GET
YOUR SHARE OF IT.
>>> ALSO, BUBBLING
CONTROVERSY, HOW PEPSI
IS RESPONDING TO THE
BACKLASH OVER THE
LATEST ADVERTISEMENT.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH A CONSUMER ALERT.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
AMERICANS ARE ABOUT TO
GET REFUNDS FROM
AMAZON.
IT COMES AFTER A LONG
LEGAL BATTLE OVER
YOUNG CHILDREN RACKING
UP PURCHASES ON THEIR
PARENTS' AMAZON
ACCOUNTS, PARENTS
UNAWARE IT WAS
HAPPENING.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO HAS
DETAILS ON THE
SETTLEMENT.
>> Reporter: IT'S A
PRETTY SIMPLE CONCEPT,
A 4-YEAR-OLD CAN'T
CONSENT TO CHARGE A
PARENTS' CREDIT CARD
BUT YOUNG CHILDREN
WERE PLAYING POPULAR
KIDS' GAMES ON
AMAZON'S KIN DEL,
INCLUDING ICE AGE
STORY AND TAP ZOO AND
MORE.
SUDDENLY, UP POPPED AN
OPTION FOR THE CHILD
TO BUY MORE VIRTUAL
PETS, MORE GOLD COINS
OR STARS BUT FOR REAL
MONEY.
ANYWHERE FROM 99 CENTS
TO $99.
THE KIDS, OF COURSE,
QUICKLY AGREED.
>> SO WE ALLEGE THAT
PARENTS WERE BEING HIT
WITH THESE CHARGES,
MANY OF WHICH WERE
LARGE-DOLLAR CHARGES
AND LARGE NUMBERS OF
CONSUMERS COMPLAINED.
>> I WAS PRETTY
ASTONISHED.
I WAS QUITE ILL TO MY
STOMACH.
>> Reporter: JULIE
PANICKED AFTER THEN
8-YEAR-OLD HANNA SPENT
$10,000 BUYING VIRTUAL
FOOD FOR A VIRTUAL PET
ONLINE.
PUTTING THE FAMILY
TRIP TO YELLOWSTONE IN
JEOPARDY.
>> WE THOUGHT WE WERE
GOING TO HAVE TO
CHANGE OUR VACATION
PLANS OR CANCEL OUR
VACATION PLANS THAT WE
HAD WORKED ON FOR
MONTHS AND MONTHS OF
PLANNING.
>> Reporter:
THANKFULLY, AMAZON
REFUNDED THE $10,000.
NOW IT'S REACHING OUT
TO TENS OF THOUSANDS
OF CUSTOMERS REFUNDING
$70 MILLION BACK TO
THEIR CREDIT CARDS.
IT'S ALSO REQUIRING
PASSWORDS FOR
PURCHASES MADE IN
KIDS' GAMES AND
ENCOURAGING PARENTS TO
GO TO THE APP STORE
THEN GO INTO SETTINGS
AND IN-APP PURCHASES
AND SET PASSWORDS OR
PIN CODES.
THE TAKEAWAY, PAYING
CUSTOMERS DO HAVE TO
CONSENT BEFORE THEIR
CREDIT CARD IS
CHARGED.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC
NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A
MOMENT WITH A FIGHTER
JET GOING DOWN IN
FLAMES.
THE PILOT FORCED TO
MAKE A SPLIT-SECOND
DECISION.
>> OH MY GOD.
THANK GOD HE'S OKAY.
>>> A SCARE IN THE
SKIES OVER MARYLAND
TODAY AS A FIGHTER JET
WENT DOWN JUST A FEW
MILES FROM THE U.S.
CAPITOL.
THE PILOT ON AN AIR
NATIONAL GUARD
TRAINING MISSION
EJECTED SAFELY BUT WAS
INJURED.
PARACHUTING TO THE
GROUND AS THE F-16
CRASHED INTO A WOODED
AREA SOUTHWEST OF
JOINT BASE ANDREWS.
THOSE INJURIES WE'RE
TOLD THANKFULLY WERE
NOT LIFE-THREATENING.
>>> TO THE SODA AD
SPARKING A BIG
BACKLASH ON SOCIAL
MEDIA.
PEPSI HAS NOW PULLED
THE COMMERCIALS
FEATURING A REALITY TV
STAR AFTER CRITICS
CLAIMED IT WAS IN BAD
TASTE AND TRIVIALIZED
THE BLACK LIVES MATTER
MOVEMENT.
NBC'S GABE GUTIERREZ
EXPLAINS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
PEPSI IS IN DAMAGE
CONTROL AFTER BEING
ACCUSED OF EXPLODING
RACIAL PROTESTS TO
SELL SODA.
THE TWO AND A HALF
MINUTE AD RELEASED
TUESDAY ON YOUTUBE,
FEATURES MODEL AND
REALITY TV STAR
KENDALL JENNER HAPPILY
JOINING A GROUP OF
YOUNG PROTESTERS.
IT NEVER SPECIFICALLY
REFERENCES THE BLACK
LIVES MATTER MOVEMENT
BUT MANY CRITICS NOTED
THE STARK CONTRAST
BETWEEN THE IMAGE OF
JENNER HANDING A SOFT
DRINK TO AN OFFICER
AND PICTURES LIKE THIS
ONE OF RIOT POLICE
DETAINING A WOMAN IN
BATON ROUGE LAST
SUMMER.
>> THIS AD TRIVIALIZES
THE URGENCY OF THE
ISSUES AND IT
DIMINISHES THE
SERIOUSNESS AND THE
GRAVITY OF WHY WE GOT
INTO THE SITUATION IN
THE FIRST PLACE.
>> Reporter: ON SOCIAL
MEDIA, THE VIDEO
QUICKLY DREW ANGER AND
RIDICULE.
MARTIN LUTHER KING
JUNIOR'S DAUGHTER
BERNICE TWEETED IF
ONLY HER FATHER HAD
KNOWN ABOUT THE POWER
OF PEPSI.
>> I'VE NEVER SEEN
THIS AD GET NEGATIVE
RESPONSE SO QUICKLY
AND I THINK IT WILL
MAKE PEPSI RE-EVALUATE
WHAT THEY'RE DOING
WITH THEIR BRAND
QUICKLY.
>> Reporter: TODAY
PEPSI YANKED THE AD
SHOWING A GLOBAL
MESSAGE OF UNITY,
PEACE AND
UNDERSTANDING,
CLEARLY, WE MISSED THE
MARK AND WE APOLOGIZE.
♪
DECADES AGO, THIS
ICONIC COKE COMMERCIAL
DURING THE FLOWER
POWER MOVEMENT STRUCK
THE RIGHT TONE AT THE
RIGHT TIME.
AS PEPSI FOUND OUT,
TIMES HAVE CHANGED.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, MIAMI.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK
HERE TONIGHT, THE
BASEBALL SUPER STAR
USING HIS LIFE'S OTHER
PASSION TO CONNECT
WITH KIDS.
INSPIRING AMERICA IS
NEXT.
NE. AIC ASUS TY'RTANG  FIT BK I=
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT
WITH BASEBALL SEASON
IN FULL SWING A STORY
ABOUT A MAN OF MANY
TALENTS, NOT ONLY DOES
HE HAVE FOUR WORLD
SERIES CHAMPIONSHIPS
TO HIS NAME, HE'S ALSO
A LATIN GRAMMY
NOMINATED RECORDING
ARTIST.
AND NOW HE'S USING HIS
LOVE OF MUSIC TO GO TO
BAT FOR SCHOOLKIDS.
NBC'S REHEMA ELLIS HAS
MORE IN OUR INSPIRING
AMERICA REPORT.
>> HEY, KIDS.
>> Reporter: HE'S BEST
KNOWN AS A CHAMPION
BASEBALL PLAYER BUT
THESE KIDS ARE
CHEERING FOR THE OTHER
SIDE OF BERNIE
WILLIAMS.
♪
>> Reporter: WHAT CAME
FIRST?
YOUR LOVE OF BASEBALL
OR YOUR LOVE OF MUSIC?
>> THEY BOTH CAME
AROUND THE SAME TIME
IN MY LIFE.
>> Reporter: THE
FORMER NEW YORK YANKEE
AND LATIN GRAMMY
NOMINATED GUITARIST
GREW UP PLAYING
BASEBALL AND ATTENDING
A PERFORMING ARTS
SCHOOL.
HE'S NOW JOINED
ANOTHER TEAM CALLED
TURN AROUND ARTS, THAT
GIVES STUDENTS
SOMETHING HIS MOTHER
MADE SURE HE HAD.
>> SHE SAID, WELL, YOU
HAVE TO BE A
WELL-ROUNDED
INDIVIDUAL.
IN ORDER FOR YOU TO DO
THAT, YOU NEED TO BE
EXPOSED TO ARTS,
MUSIC, AND SPORTS.
>> Reporter: FUNDED
THROUGH A GRANT FROM
THE KENNEDY CENTER,
THE PROGRAM ALLOWS
SCHOOLS TO MIX THE
ARTS INTO ALL ACADEMIC
SUBJECTS, ACTING OUT
SCENES IN SCIENCE.
OR DRAWING AND
HISTORY.
AND IT'S WORKING.
IN 68 SCHOOLS
NATIONWIDE, WITH
TURNAROUND ARTS
PROGRAMS, MATH SCORES
ARE UP BY MORE THAN
22%, READING BY MORE
THAN 12%.
>> WHEN YOU BRING THE
ARTS INTO SCHOOL,
SCHOOLS GO FROM GREY
OF COLOR, PARENTS
BECOME MORE ENGAGED
AND ATTENDANCE STARTS
TO GO UP.
♪
>> Reporter: THIS
YEAR, JOSHUA WENT FROM
CHRONICALLY TARDY TO
HONOR ROLL.
>> YOU HAVE TO BE GOOD
TO BE IN BAND OR YOU
ARE NOT GOING TO BE
ALLOWED TO COME DOWN
AND PRACTICE.
>> Reporter: A LOT OF
THEM WILL HAVE TALENT
TO BECOME MUSICIANS
AND ARTISTS BUT THE
ONES THAT DON'T GOT
EXPERIENCE TO LEAD
THEM INTO WHATEVER
THEY DECIDE TO DO.
>> Reporter: FROM
CENTER FIELD TO
CLASSROOM, NOW HITTING
HOME RUNS WITH KIDS.
REHEMA ELLIS, NBC
NEWS, BRIDGEPORT,
CONNECTICUT.
>>> THAT'S GOING TO DO
IT FOR US ON A
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
RIT N AT: CLNerodyas d eughRU=0
>>>.
>>> I THINK EVERYBODY HAS HAD
ENOUGH.
>> RIGHT NOW, AT 6:00, CLEANING
UP IN A DANGER ZONE IN THE
BAY AREA'S LARGEST CITY.
WE HAVE THE EXCLUSIVE STORY.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I'M JANELLE WANG.
>> AND I'M RAJ MATHAI.
AN UNUSUAL TACTIC USED TO CRACK
DOWN IN A HOT SPOT FOR CRIME.
SAN JOSE P.D. HAS OPENED AN
OFFICE RIGHT IN THE HOT ZONE.
NBC BAY AREA DAMON TRUJILLO HAS
THE STORY.
>> Reporter: WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
FOUNTAIN ALLEY HERE IN DOWNTOWN
SAN JOSE AND LOOKING AT THE
POLICE STATS POSTED BY SAN JOSE
POLICE, THERE HAVE BEEN 60 CALLS
FOR SERVICE IN THIS AREA ALONE
IN THE LAST 30 DAYS.
THERE ARE POLICE OFFICERS ON THE
CORNER EVER FOUNTAIN ALALLEY, AD
BETWEEN FIRST AND SECOND.
POLICE ARE MOVING IN RIGHT HERE
FOR GOOD.
YOU NAME THE DRUG, AND YOU'LL
LIKELY FIND IT HERE ON FOUNTAIN
ALLEY.
CRIME HAPPENS HERE VIRTUALLY
DAILY.
>> WE SEE CRIMES, DRUG DEALING,
PROSTITUTION HERE AND THERE.
>> Reporter: THE CITY FISH
MARKET SAYS THE CRIME HAS
AFFECTED BUSINESS.
POLICE HAVE KNOWN ABOUT THIS
AALLEY FOR YEARS, THEY'LL MAKE
ARRESTS, BUT THAT HASN'T STOPPED
THE PROBLEM.
>> HOW IS CRIME HERE?
>> VER