CHILLY TEMPERATURES AHEAD OF
THIS WEEKEND.
>> IT'S LIKE A WINTER DAY.
THANKS FOR JOINING US AT 5:00.
LESTER HOLT JOINS US NEXT WITH
"NIGHTLY NEWS."
>>> TONIGHT, INSIDE
THE STRIKE FROM THE
WAR ROOM.
THE U.S. TOMAHAWK
ATTACK IN SYRIA, HOW
WILL ASSAD RESPOND?
TONIGHT A WAR OF WORDS
AS RUSSIA LASHES OUT
AND THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION WARNING
ITS PREPARED TO TAKE
FURTHER ACTION.
>>> NBC NEWS
EXCLUSIVE, THE
MILITARY OPTIONS FOR
NORTH KOREA PRESENTED
TO PRESIDENT TRUMP.
SOURCES SAY THEY
INCLUDE PLACING
NUCLEAR WEAPONS IN
SOUTH KOREA OR KILLING
KIM JONG-UN.
WE HAVE THE
CONTROVERSIAL PLANS.
>>> TRUCK ATTACK
TERROR SLAMMING INTO A
DEPARTMENT STORE, DEAD
AND INJURED IN THE
STREET.
WHO IS BEHIND THIS?
>>> SLASHING YOUR
BILLS BY HIRING
SOMEONE ELSE TO DO IT
FOR YOU.
HOW FAMILIES ARE
SAVING BIG.
>>> AND FANTASTIC
FOUR, WAIT UNTIL YOU
SEE WHAT THESE
COMPETITIVE
QUADRUPLETS
ACCOMPLISH.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING TO
OUR VIEWERS IN THE
WEST.
AFTERMATH.
THE U.S. TONIGHT
ASSESSING THE DAMAGE
AND MEASURING THE
REACTION AND FALLOUT
TO THE PUNISHING AIR
RAID ON SYRIA.
FOR SEVERAL LONG
MINUTES OVERNIGHT,
DOZENS OF AMERICAN
TOMAHAWK CRUISE
MISSILES RAINED DOWN
ON THE SYRIAN MILITARY
AIRFIELD THAT'S BEEN
LINKED TO THIS WEEK'S
DEADLY CHEMICAL ATTACK
ON CIVILIANS IN A
REBEL HELD AREA OF THE
COUNTRY.
SIX PEOPLE ON THE
GROUND WERE KILLED IN
THE OVERNIGHT MISSILE
STRIKE.
TONIGHT AS POST STRIKE
IMAGES OF THE AIR
FIELD EMERGED, WE HAVE
NEW DETAILS ON HOW THE
U.S. OPERATION
UNFOLDED, THE MESSAGE
SENT, AND QUESTIONS
OVER WHETHER THIS
OPENS A NEW CHAPTER IN
A CIVIL WAR PRESIDENT
TRUMP REPEATEDLY
PROMISED TO STEER
CLEAR OF.
WE HAVE TWO REPORTS,
FIRST RICHARD ENGEL ON
THE MISSILE ATTACK
ITSELF.
>> Reporter: NEW
IMAGES TONIGHT FROM
RUSSIAN TV OF THE
SYRIAN BASE ATTACK ON
ORDERS FROM PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
THEY SHOW LITTLE
DESTRUCTION.
RUSSIA APPARENTLY
TRYING TO DOWNPLAY THE
IMPACT OF THE STRIKES.
BUT THE U.S. MILITARY
LATE TODAY RELEASING
THESE PHOTOS, SHOWING
SIGNIFICANT DAMAGE TO
THE BASE, THE U.S.
SAYS THE SYRIAN REGIME
USED TO LAUNCH THIS
WEEK'S DEADLY CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
AT 7:40 P.M., TWO NAVY
DESTROYERS IN THE
MEDITERRANEAN LAUNCHED
60 CRUISE MISSILES.
TARGETING THE AIR
BASE.
ONE MISSILE MISFIRED
INTO THE SEA, THE REST
DIRECT HITS DESTROYING
20 SYRIAN AIRCRAFT AND
REINFORCED HANGARS AND
FUEL DEPOTS.
THE U.S. SAYS IT
AVOIDED TARGETING
CHEMICAL WILLS ON THE
BASE TO PREVENT
DISBURSING TOXINS.
BASHAR AL ASSAD'S
GOVERNMENT TODAY CALL
THE STRIKES FOOLISH
AND UNMOTIVATED.
>> THEY ATTACK US IN
ONE WAY OR ANOTHER TO
HELP THE TERRORIST
THEY THEIR GROUND.
>> Reporter: THE MORE
SERIOUS DISPUTE NOW IS
WITH SYRIA'S BACKER
RUSSIA.
THE U.S. MILITARY SAYS
IT INFORMED MOSCOW
BEFORE THE STRIKES TO
AVOID RUSSIAN
CASUALTIES ON THE
BASE.
NOW THE U.S. MILITARY
IS INVESTIGATING IF
RUSSIA WAS COMPLICIT
IN THE CHEMICAL ATTACK
OR MERELY FAILED TO
STOP IT.
A WAR OF WORDS TODAY
AT THE U.N. SECURITY
COUNSEL.
>> THE UNITED STATES
TOOK A VERY MEASURED
STEP LAST NIGHT.
WE ARE PREPARED TO DO
MORE.
BUT WE HOPE THAT WILL
NOT BE NECESSARY.
>> Translator: WE
DESCRIBE THAT ATTACK
AS A FRAGRANT
VIOLATION OF
INTERNATIONAL LAW AND
AN ACT OF AGGRESSION.
>> Reporter: PUTIN'S
SPOKESMAN CALLED THE
ATTACK A SIGNIFICANT
BLOW IN RELATIONS WITH
WASHINGTON.
BUT THIS ATTACK,
LIMITED AND APENANTLY
A ONE OFF, WAS NOT
ABOUT REDEFINING
RELATIONS WITH SYRIA
OR RUSSIA, BUT SENDING
A MESSAGE.
>> I THINK IT WAS A
WIN FOR THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.
I THINK THEY HAVE
DEMONSTRATED
FORCEFULNESS TO THE
INTERNATIONAL
COMMUNITY.
THE QUESTION IS, YOU
KNOW, THE OTHER SIDE
GETS A VOTE, WHAT WILL
THE IRANIAN
REVOLUTIONARY GUARDS
DO?
HEZBOLLAH MILITIAS AND
FOR THAT MATTER, ASSAD
HIMSELF.
>> Reporter: RUSSIA
SAID TODAY IT WILL
INCREASE ITS AIR
DEFENSES IN SYRIA.
THE U.S. MILITARY,
HOWEVER, SAYS THERE
ARE NO INDICATIONS
MOSCOW PLANS TO
RETALIATE.
AND A MEETING BETWEEN
PUTIN AND SECRETARY OF
STATE REX TILLERSON
SCHEDULED NEXT WEEK IN
MOSCOW IS STILL ON.
LESTER?
>> RICHARD, WE'RE
LEARNING MORE ABOUT
THE DRAMA BEHIND THE
SCENES IN THE MOMENTS
LEADING UP TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP
ORDERING THOSE STRIKES
ON SYRIA.
NBC'S CHIEF WHITE
HOUSE CORRESPONDENT
HALLIE JACKSON TAKES
US INSIDE THOSE
CRITICAL HOURS WHICH
HAVE ALSO LED TO
REPORTS OF A POTENTIAL
SHAKE-UP AMONG WHITE
HOUSE POWER PLAYERS.
>> Reporter: TODAY NO
RESPONSE FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP ASKED
ABOUT HIS STRIKE IN
SYRIA.
>> THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
>> Reporter: A
DECISION HE MADE AFTER
WHAT THE WHITE HOUSE
CALLS A 72-HOUR
EVOLUTION.
TUESDAY MORNING, THE
PRESIDENT IS BRIEFED
ON THE ATTACK, QUOTE
DISTURBED BY IT AND
ASKING FOR OPTIONS.
THAT TRIGGERS 48 HOURS
OF INTENSE MEETINGS
INCLUDING ONE ENROUTE
TO PALM BEACH.
BY THURSDAY AFTERNOON,
A DECISION, GREEN
LIGHTING THE STRIKE.
IN THE MEDITERRANEAN,
THE LAUNCH BEGINNING.
IN FLORIDA, THE
PRESIDENT HOSTING
CHINA'S LEADER FOR
STEAK AND SALAD.
90 MINUTES LATER, HE'S
BRIEFED IN THIS SECURE
ROOM AT MAR-A-LAGO.
THE MOOD INSIDE
CAUTIOUSLY CONFIDENT.
ACCORDING TO AN
ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIAL.
NOT LONG AFTER THE
PRESIDENT ADDRESSES
THE NATION.
>> EVEN BEAUTIFUL
BABIES WERE CRUELLY
MURDERED IN THIS VERY
BARBARIC ATTACK.
>> THIS NOW HAS
PROVIDED THE
ADMINISTRATION A
DEMONSTRATION MOMENTS
FOR THE REST OF THE
WORLD TO INCLUDE THE
CHINESE AND THE
RUSSIANS, TO
UNDERSTAND THAT
THERE'S A NEW SHERIFF
IN TOWN.
>> Reporter: IN
WASHINGTON TODAY,
LAWMAKERS BRIEFED ON
WHAT HAPPENED.
>> THE SIGNAL IS AS
IMPORTANT AS THE
ACTUAL DAMAGE THAT WAS
DONE.
>> Reporter: EVEN SOME
WHO BACK THE STRIKE
DON'T LIKE HOW THE
PRESIDENT CUT OUT
CONGRESS.
>> I THINK THE
PRESIDENT OWES IT TO
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE TO
COME TO CONGRESS AND
PRESENT A PLAN.
>> Reporter: THE
ADMINISTRATION ARGUES
THE COMMANDER IN CHIEF
CAN DECIDE ON HIS OWN
TO TAKE MILITARY
ACTION TO PROTECT THE
U.S.
BUT BY GETTING
INVOLVED IN SYRIA, THE
PRESIDENT REVERSED HIS
PAST POSITION.
AS THE WHITE HOUSE
INSISTS HE'S STILL
COMMITTED TO AMERICA
FIRST.
THAT'S THE POLICY
PUSHED BY STEVE
BANNON, RECENTLY
OUSTED FROM THE
POWERFUL NATIONAL
SECURITY COUNSEL
SPARKING SPECULATION
HE'S LOSING INFLUENCE.
THE WHITE HOUSE
PUSHING BACK ON
REPORTS OF AN IMMINENT
STAFF SHAKEUP THAT
COULD INCLUDE BANNON
AND CHIEF OF STAFF
REINCE PRIEBUS, CRISIS
ON FRONTS IN THE
AFTERMATH OF THE
PRESIDENT'S MOST
SIGNIFICANT MILITARY
MOMENT YET.
AND AT MAR-A-LAGO, AN
IMPORTANT DIPLOMATIC
MOMENT AS PRESIDENT
TRUMP WRAPS UP HIS
SUMMIT WITH THE
CHINESE PRESIDENT.
THE TWO COMMITTED TO
WORKING TOWARD A
DENUCLEARIZED KOREAN
PENINSULA, AND A 100
DAY ACTION PLAN ON
TRADE, WITH PRESIDENT
TRUMP ACCEPTING
PRESIDENT XI'S
INVITATION TO VISIT
CHINA.
THE DATES STILL BEING
WORKED OUT.
LESTER?
>> HALLIE, THANK YOU.
>>> NBC NEWS LEARNED
EXCLUSIVE DETAILS
ABOUT TOP SECRET U.S.
MILITARY OPTIONS
PRESENTED TO THE
PRESIDENT, SOME
THOUGHT WITH
CONTROVERSY IF ALL
ELSE FAILS IN REIGNING
NORTH CAROLINA IN.
WE GET THAT FROM NBC
NEWS CYNTHIA MCFADDEN.
>> Reporter: MULTIPLE
TOP RANKING
INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS
TELL NBC NEWS IF
DIPLOMACY FAILS WITH
NORTH KOREA, THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL HAS PRESENTED
HIM WITH SOME HIGHLY
CONTROVERSIAL COURSES
OF ACTION.
FIRST, PLACING U.S.
NUCLEAR WEAPONS IN
SOUTH KOREA AND
AGGRESSIVE SHOW OF
FORCE.
THE U.S. WITHDREW ALL
NUCLEAR WEAPONS FROM
THE KOREAN PENINSULA
25 YEARS AGO AT THE
END OF THE COLD WAR.
>> I DON'T THINK
THAT'S A GOOD IDEA.
I THINK THAT IT WILL
ONLY INFLAME THE VIEW
FROM PYONGYANG.
THE IDEA THAT WE WOULD
USE A NUKE LEER AR
WEAPON EVEN AGAINST
NORTH KOREA IS HIGHLY
UNLIKELY.
>> Reporter: HE ALSO
BELIEVES BRINGING BACK
NUKES TO SOUTH KOREA
IS A BAD IDEA.
BUT THAT IT IS VERY
MUCH BEING DISCUSSED
IN SEOUL.
>> IT'S AN INTERESTING
DEBATE IN SOUTH KOREA.
I WOULD SAY PUBLIC
SUPPORT FOR
REINTRODUCTION OF
TACTICAL NUCLEAR
WEAPONS IS CLIMBING.
SOME POLLS PUT IT WELL
OVER 50%.
>> Reporter: A SECOND
OPTION, TARGET AND
KILL NORTH KOREA'S
LEADER KIM JONG-UN AND
OTHER SENIOR LEADERS
IN CHARGE OF MISSILES
AND NUCLEAR WEAPONS.
>> DECAPITATION IS
ALWAYS A TEMPTING
STRATEGY WHEN YOU'RE
FACED WITH A HIGHLY
UNPREDICTABLE AND
HIGHLY DANGEROUS
LEADER.
THE QUESTION YOU HAVE
TO ASK YOURSELF IS
WHAT HAPPENS THE DAY
AFTER YOU DECAPITATE?
I THINK THAT IN NORTH
KOREA, IT'S AN
ENORMOUS UNKNOWN.
>> Reporter: PUSHING
FOR REGIME CHANGE
COULD ALSO CAUSE
TROUBLE WITH THE
CHINESE.
>> DISCUSSIONS OF
REGIME CHANGE AND
DECAPITATION TEND TO
CAUSE THE CHINESE
GREAT PAUSE OR CONCERN
AND TENDS TO HAVE THEM
MOVE IN THE OPPOSITE
DIRECTION.
>> Reporter: A THIRD
OPTION, COVERT ACTION.
INFILTRATING U.S. AND
SOUTH KOREAN SPECIAL
FORCES INTO NORTH
KOREA TO SABOTAGE OR
TAKE OUT KEY
INFRASTRUCTURE.
FOR INSTANCE, BLOWING
UP BRIDGES TO BLOCK
THE MOVEMENT OF MOBILE
MISSILES.
THE CIA THAT WOULD
OVERSEE OPERATIONS
TOLD NBC NEWS IT COULD
OFFER NO GUIDANCE ON
THIS OPTION.
>> THE BEST STRATEGY
WE COULD UNDER TAKE IF
FORCED TO REACH TO A
MILITARY OPERATION
WOULD BE SOME
COMBINATION OF SPECIAL
FORCES WITH SOUTH
KOREA AND CYBER.
>> Reporter: SHOULD
ALL OF THESE OPTIONS
BE UNDER DISCUSSION?
>> IT'S MANDATORY TO
PRESENT THE WIDEST
POSSIBLE ARRAY OF
OPTIONS.
THAT'S WHAT ENABLES
PRESIDENTS TO MAKE THE
RIGHT DECISIONS WHEN
THEY SEE ALL THE
OPTIONS ON THE TABLE
IN FRONT OF THEM.
>> Reporter: WHETHER
ANY OF THESE OPTIONS
ARE ADOPTED HINGES IN
LARGE PART WITH WHAT
HAPPENS WITH CHINA,
WHETHER THEY AGREE TO
PUT MORE PRESSURE ON
NORTH KOREA.
SENIOR OFFICIALS TELL
NBC NEWS FOR NOW IT'S
BEEN UP STAGED FOR
ACTION IN SYRIA BUT
SOON ENOUGH EXPECT IT
TO BE BACK FRONT AND
CENTER.
AT THE WHITE HOUSE THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
SPOKESMAN DECLINED TO
COMMENT.
LESTER?
>> SOBERING CHOICES
THERE.
CYNTHIA, THANK YOU.
>>> TONIGHT A MASSIVE
MANHUNT UNDERWAY IN
SWEDEN FOR THE PERSON
OR PERSONS BEHIND A
SUSPECTED TERROR
ATTACK IN STOCKHOLM.
A DRIVER PLOWING
THROUGH A CROWD
LEAVING BODIES IN THE
STREET BEFORE SLAMMING
INTO A DEPARTMENT
STORE.
NBC'S KEIR SIMMONS HAS
LATE DETAILS.
>> Reporter: PANIC AND
CONFUSION SEEN IN THIS
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO AS
A STOLEN TRUCK BARRELS
THROUGH THE CITY
CENTER AND INTO AN UP
SCALE DEPARTMENT
STORE.
>> I SAW EIGHT PEOPLE
GET DRIVED OVER.
>> BODIES LYING ON THE
STREET AND I COULD SEE
THE POLICE COVERING A
BODY WITH AN ORANGE
BLANKET.
>> Reporter: IT WAS
JUST BEFORE 3:00 P.M.
IN STOCKHOLM, SMOKE
BILLOWING OUT OF THE
WRECKAGE.
MORE THAN A DOZEN
PEOPLE INJURED, FOUR
KILLED.
>> POLICE SAID IF YOU
HAVE KIDS AND WANT TO
SEE THEM AGAIN, LEAVE
NOW.
>> Reporter: WITHIN
HOURS, THE COUNTRY'S
PRIME MINISTER TOOK TO
TWITTER SAYING ALL
INDICATIONS ARE THIS
IS AN ACT OF
TERRORISM.
>> THIS IS NOT A SAFE
PLACE.
>> Reporter: IN THE
CHAOS, POLICE
EVACUATED THE AREA AND
UNCERTAIN IF MORE
ATTACKS WERE IMMINENT
LAUNCHING A NATIONWIDE
MANHUNT FOR THOSE
RESPONSIBLE.
HOURS LATER ONE
SUSPECT ARRESTED AND
POLICE RELEASING A
PHOTO OF A MAN WANTED
FOR QUESTIONING.
TODAY'S BRAZEN ATTACK
IS THE LATEST USING A
VEHICLE TO KILL AND
CAUSE CHAOS.
IT'S SOMETHING EXPERTS
CALL LOW-TECH SOFT
TARGET TERRORISM.
JUST LAST MONTH IN
LONDON AN SUV MOWED
DOWN PEDESTRIANS ON
WESTMINSTER BRIDGE.
IN DECEMBER AT A
HOLIDAY MARKET IN
BERLIN, 12 DEAD,
DOZENS INJURED AND THE
HORRIFIC BASTILLE DAY
ATTACK IN FRANCE LAST
SUMMER.
86 PEOPLE KILLED.
TONIGHT, THE EIFFEL
TOWER DARK RECOGNIZING
THIS GRIM DAY.
A HORROR THAT COUNTRY
AND NOW SWEDEN KNOW
ALL TOO WELL.
SO FAR NO ORGANIZATION
HAS CLAIMED
RESPONSIBILITY FOR THE
ATTACK AND TONIGHT
POLICE HERE TELL NBC
NEWS THE DRIVER OF THE
TRUCK HAS NOT BEEN
ARRESTED.
A MANHUNT UNDERWAY
HERE TONIGHT.
LESTER?
>> KEIR SIMMONS IN
STOCKHOLM TONIGHT,
THANK YOU.
>>> TONIGHT BACK IN
THIS COUNTRY A BIG
VICTORY FOR
REPUBLICANS
CIRCUMVENTING A
DEMOCRATIC ROAD BLOCK
AND CELEBRATING THE
CONFIRMATION OF NEIL
GORSUCH TO THE SUPREME
COURT.
IT COMES AFTER A
VACANCY BATTLE THAT
LASTED WELL OVER A
YEAR, THROUGH TWO
ADMINISTRATIONS.
AND AS OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS REPORTS, HE
COULD HAVE AN
IMMEDIATE IMPACT.
>> Reporter: 66 DAYS
SINCE HE WAS NOMINATED
BY PRESIDENT TRUMP
APPEALS COURT JUDGE
NEIL GORSUCH WAS
CONFIRMED SLIGHTLY
FASTER THAN AVERAGE
AFTER PUNISHING
HEARINGS AND A CHANGE
IN SENATE RULES TO
ELIMINATE THE
FILIBUSTER.
>> HE WILL MAKE A
SUPERB JUSTICE.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS
FACE THE INEVITABLE
HOPING TO NO LONGER
BLOCK HIM.
>> WE ARE CHARGING
JUDGE GORSUCH TO BE
THE INDEPENDENT AND
FAIR-MINDED JUSTICE
AMERICA BADLY NEEDS.
>> Reporter: 54 TO 45.
INDIANA, NORTH DAKOTA
AND WEST VIRGINIA.
>> THE NOMINATION OF
NEIL M. GORSUCH OF
COLORADO TO BE AN
ASSOCIATE JUSTICE OF
THE SUPREME COURT OF
THE UNITED STATES IS
CONFIRMED.
>> THE MOST
CONSEQUENTIAL DECISION
I'VE EVER BEEN
INVOLVED IN WAS THE
DECISION TO LET THE
PRESIDENT BE ELECTED
LAST YEAR, PICKED THE
SUPREME COURT NOMINEE.
>> Reporter: NEIL
GORSUCH BECOMES A
JUSTICE MONDAY WHEN
HE'S SWORN IN WITH A
PUBLIC CEREMONY AT THE
WHITE HOUSE LIKE THE
ONE 11 YEARS AGO FOR
ALITO.
KAGAN AND SOTOMAYOR
WERE SWORN IN AT THE
COURT BECAUSE
PRESIDENT OBAMA
THOUGHT THAT
SYMBOLIZED JUDICIAL
INDEPENDENCE.
JUSTICE GORSUCH WILL
HEAR AND VOTE ON THE
FINAL CASES OF THE
TERM INCLUDING AN
IMPORTANT TEST OF
RELIGIOUS FREEDOM, A
LUTHERAN CHURCH DENIED
FUNDS TO RESURFACE THE
SCHOOL PLAYGROUND SAYS
THAT'S RELIGIOUS
DISCRIMINATION TURNING
IT DOWN WHILE PUBLIC
SCHOOLS GOT THE MONEY.
IT'S BEEN 14 MONTHS
SINCE JUSTICE SCALIA
DIED.
THEY ARE EAGER TO GET
BACK TO FULL STRENGTH,
LESTER?
>> PETE WILLIAMS,
THANK YOU.
>>> STILL AHEAD,
SAVING YOU MONEY.
THE NEGOTIATORS THAT
HAGGLE ON YOUR BEHALF
TO CUT DOWN THOSE BIG
MONTHLY BILLS.
ONE FAMILY SAYING THEY
SAVED OVER $2,000.
WE'LL BE BACK WITH
THEIR STORY.
>>> BACK NOW WITH A
CONSUMER ALERT, HOW
FAMILIES ACROSS THE
COUNTRY ARE FINDING A
NEW WAY TO SLASH THEIR
BILLS AND SAVE BIG BY
HIRING SOMEONE ELSE TO
DO IT FOR THEM AND YOU
CAN, TOO, IF YOU'RE
WILLING TO GIVE UP A
CUT OF THE SAVINGS.
NBC'S ANN THOMPSON
EXPLAINS.
>> Reporter: POPCORN
IS IT PAUL AND JULIE'S
BUSINESS.
>> WE HAVE WHITE
CHOCOLATE CRANBERRY
AND BLUEBERRIES AND
CREAM.
>> Reporter: OFFERING
80 FLAVORS AT THE
THREE STORES IN
COASTAL MAINE.
BUT WHAT THEY SPEND ON
WIRELESS INTERNET AND
CABLE SERVICES HAS
LEFT A SOUR TASTE.
>> ALMOST $500 A
MONTH.
>> ACTUALLY MORE THAN
$500 A MONTH.
IT'S ALMOST $600.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> Reporter: WE
INTRODUCED THEM TO
SHARKS, THE HUMAN
KIND.
>> IF YOU CAN MATCH
THAT, I'LL STAY WITH
YOU GUYS.
>> Reporter: BILL
SHARP, PROFESSIONAL
NEGOTIATORS THAT TAKE
40% OF THE SAVINGS
THEY WIN FOR
CUSTOMERS.
>> CONSUMERS DON'T PAY
ATTENTION TO PRICE
CREEP.
THIS WILL BE YOUR
PRICE GRADUALLY GOING
UP OR NEW FEES ADDED.
>> Reporter: THE
ROBERTS PUT THE
COMPANY TO THE TEST.
>> I'LL GO AHEAD AND
INSTALL IT NOW.
>> Reporter:
DOWNLOADING THE APP.
>> SNAP A PICTURE.
>> Reporter: AND
UPLOADING BILLS.
THE WHOLE PROCESS 12
MINUTES TO GET THE
SHARKS FISHING.
>> IT'S AN $80
DIFFERENCE.
>> Reporter: THIS
EXISTS BECAUSE MOST
CONSUMERS DON'T EVEN
REALIZE THEY CAN
NEGOTIATE OR IF THEY
DO, THEY DON'T WANT TO
SPEND THE TIME AND
THEY DON'T WANT
CONFRONTATION.
>> CONSUMERS CAN DO
EVERYTHING WE'RE DOING
HERE.
WE JUST DO IT BETTER.
>> Reporter: HOW MUCH
BETTER?
WE CALLED FOR THE
RESULTS.
>> WE SAVED YOU A
TOTAL OF $2,311.56.
>> HOLY SMOKES.
>> Reporter: ON HOME
INTERNET AND CABLE,
MORE THAN $1,000.
PERSONAL CELL PHONES,
$900 PLUS.
BUSINESS PHONES AND
INTERNET, MORE THAN
$300 SAVED.
>> THAT'S A VACATION.
I MEAN, THAT'S A WAY
FOR US TO TAKE THE
GIRLS AND GO
SOMEWHERE.
>> Reporter: MONEY IN
THE ROBERTS' POCKETS
BUT JUST THE BEGINNING
FOR COMPANIES LIKE
THIS.
>> THERE ARE 300
MILLION BILLS TO BE
NEGOTIATED AND ABOUT
50E $50 BILLION A YEAR
THAT CAN BE SAVED.
>> Reporter: AND THE
SHARKS ARE CIRCLING.
ANN THOMPSON, NBC
NEWS, MASSACHUSETTS.
>>> UP NEXT HERE
TONIGHT, THE FAMILY
BUSINESS SHUTTING DOWN
AFTER SIX DECADES PART
OF AN ALARMING
NATIONWIDE TREND THAT
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH TROUBLE IN STORE
FOR A BIG PART OF THE
AMERICAN ECONOMY.
THE NEW JOBS REPORT
SHOWED SOME CONTINUING
PROMISING SIGNS, A
DROP IN UNEMPLOYMENT
TO 4.5%.
EMPLOYERS ADDED JUST
98,000 NEW JOBS LAST
MONTH.
THAT'S HALF THE NUMBER
ECONOMISTS EXPECTED.
BUT PERHAPS THE
BIGGEST TROUBLE SPOT
IS IN RETAIL.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO HAS
DETAILS.
>> Reporter: IN
VIRGINIA THE FACES OF
DISAPPEARING RETAIL
JOBS UP CLOSE AND VERY
PERSONAL AS ERIC STERN
IS FORCED TO CLOSE HIS
FAMILY'S OUTDOOR STORE
AFTER 61 YEARS.
>> YOU CRY A LITTLE,
LAUGH A LITTLE AND HUG
IT OUT A LITTLE BIT.
>> Reporter: THE END
OF AN ERA COMING IN
LARGE PART BECAUSE OF
ONLINE COMPETITION.
TODAY NEWS THAT IN
FEBRUARY ALONE,
RETAILERS CUT 30,000
JOBS.
SOME OF THE BIGGEST
NAMES IN AMERICA ARE
SLASHING JOBS AND
CLOSING STORES.
PAYLESS SHOES, J.C.
PENNEY, MACY'S AND
SEARS, WALMART, EVEN
POLO.
WITH SO MANY BIG-NAME
ANCHOR STORES CUTTING
BACK OR SHUTTING DOWN,
ANOTHER AMERICAN
INSTITUTION SHOPPING
MALLS ARE BEING TORN
DOWN WITH 30% AT RISK
NATIONWIDE.
>> I DON'T THINK THE
RETAIL JOBS ARE COMING
BACK.
I THINK WE'LL MOVE
INTO A HYBRID OF SOME
RETAIL, SOME
WAREHOUSING, SOME
TRUCKING.
>> Reporter: THE
NATIONAL RETAIL
FEDERATION SAYS ONE IN
FOUR JOBS IS CONNECTED
TO THE RETAIL
INDUSTRY.
AND WHILE PRESIDENT
TRUMP HAS TALKED ABOUT
REVIVING THE COAL
INDUSTRY, WHICH
EMPLOYS 76,000 PEOPLE,
RETAILER JCPENNEY
EMPLOYS 114,000 ALONE.
BACK IN VIRGINIA, THE
STERN FAMILY IS HOPING
TO REINVENT THE FAMILY
BUSINESS.
>> THIS IS 43 YEARS OF
MY LIVELIHOOD.
>> Reporter: BUT HOW
AND WHERE ISN'T CLEAR.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC
NEWS, NORTH BETHESDA,
MARYLAND.
>>> UP NEXT, FOUR OF A
KIND, QUADRUPLETS AT
THE CENTER OF A
TUG-OF-WAR BETWEEN IVY
LEAGUE POWERHOUSES.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
IT COULD BE A BIG
SOURCE OF PRIDE HAVING
YOUR CHILD ACCEPTED
INTO AN IVY LEAGUE
SCHOOL, IMAGINE
MULTIPLYING THAT PRIDE
BY FOUR.
NBC'S REHEMA ELLIS HAS
THE STORY.
>> Reporter: THE WADE
BROTHERS HAVE ALWAYS
BEEN INACCEPTABLE,
NIGEL, ZACK, NICK AND
AARON BORN TWO MINUTES
APART, TWO MONTHS
PREMATURE.
THE QUADRUPLETS SHARED
EVERYTHING, A LOVE OF
LEARNING, SPORTS AND
NOW AN EXTRAORDINARY
DISTINCTION.
EACH ONE ACCEPTED TO
BOTH HARVARD AND YALE.
THE BIG NEWS CAME ON
THEIR CELL PHONES
DURING TRACK PRACTICE.
>> I REMEMBER I DIDN'T
EVEN READ THE WHOLE
THING AT FIRST.
I JUST SAW THE
CONGRATULATIONS AND MY
JAW DROPPED.
I WAS LIKE WHAT?
>> ONE BY ONE THEY
KEPT ROLLING IN SO IT
WAS AMAZING.
>> Reporter: BY THE
END, THEY HAD
ACCEPTANCE LETTERS
FROM 29 TOP COLLEGES.
WHAT WAS THE LOWEST
GRADE YOU EVER GOT IN
SCHOOL?
>> A B IN MATH.
IT WAS NOT A GOOD
TIME.
>> ONE GREAT THING
ABOUT HAVING BROTHERS
THAT ARE ALL
INTELLIGENT, YOU
COMPETE TO SEE WHO IS
BETTER.
>> Reporter: ALL THE
BOYS NEARLY STRAIGHT A
STUDENTS AT THEIR
PUBLIC HIGH SCHOOL.
THE SUCCESS, THE
RESULT OF PARENTS WITH
HIGH EXPECTATIONS.
>> WHAT I FEEL A DAD
DOES IS, HE'S THERE TO
HELP YOU OUT AND MAKE
SURE EVERYTHING IS
SQUARE AND REASSURE
YOU, NOT TO CODDLE YOU
AT ALL.
>> Reporter: YOU
DIDN'T CODDLE THE
BOYS.
>> NO.
>> Reporter: KIM, YOU
DIDN'T?
>> I MAY HAVE CODDLED
A LITTLE.
>> SHE'S SOFT.
>> Reporter: THE
QUESTIONS.
WHERE WILL THEY GO AND
HOW WILL THEY PAY FOR
IT?
>> I'M SEEING WHICH
SCHOOLS GIVE ME THE
MOST FINANCIAL AID AND
MAKE IT EASIER ON MY
PARENTS AND FAMILY.
>> Reporter: AND WHAT
WILL LIFE BE LIKE
WITHOUT EACH OTHER.
>> I WANT TO BE KNOWN
AS AARON WADE.
NOT JUST A WADE
BROTHERS.
THAT'S PART OF WHO I
AM BUT NOT ALL OF WHO
I AM.
>> Reporter: FOUR
OUTSTANDING BROTHERS
LOOKING FORWARD TO
STANDING OUT ON THEIR
OWN.
REHEMA ELLIS, NBC
NEWS, LIBERTY
TOWNSHIP, OHIO.
>> SOME PROUD PARENTS
TONIGHT WITH GOOD
REASON.
>>> THAT'S GOING TO DO
IT FOR US ON A FRIDAY
NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
LIVING OUT HERE.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, A BUCKLED
ROAD SHOWS THE LANDSLIDE
CONCERNS THAT FORCED FAMILIES
FROM THEIR HOMES, AND THERE'S
NOT MUCH TIME THE RECOVER.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD FRIDAY EVENING.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
I'M JENNEL WANG SITTING IN FOR
JESSICA AGUIRRE.
>> I'M RAJ MATHAI.
AS THE BAY AREA CLEANS UP AND
RESTORES POWER, ANOTHER STORM IS
HERE.
THIS IS HAPPENING AS MANY PEOPLE
AND BUSINESSES ARE RECOVERING
FROM WHAT HAPPENED LAST NIGHT.
THIS VIDEO SENT TO US BY ALEC
BERNARDO.
YOU CAN SEE A DOWNED TREE AT THE
KFC IN NEWARK.
NO ONE WAS HURT BUT THE
RESTAURANT IS RED TAGGED.
LIVE CAMERA NETWORK THE GOLDEN
GATE BRIDGE ON THE LEFT.
DUBLIN AND SAN JOSE.
NOT MUCH TRAFFIC ON THIS GETAWAY
FRIDAY.
A LOT OF PEOPLE TELECOMMUTING
BECAUSE OF THE FOUL WEATHER.
LIVE DOPPLER RADAR IS LIT UP IN
GREEN ESPECIALLY THIS THE NORTH
BAY.
EVERYONE IS GOING TO GET HIT A
BIT.
WE HAVE SEVERAL REPORTS ON THE
MICRO CLIMATE ALERT.
HI ROB.
>> SAN JOSE COMMUTE LOOKING
GOOD.
GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE A DIFFERENT
STORY AS WE HAVE GOT THE
WINDSHIELD WIPER COMMUTE GOING
ON THERE.
GUSTY WINDS ACROSS THE BRIDGE.
ON THE RADAR YOU CAN SEE THE
DOWNPOURS.
RIGHT NOW THE APPROACH TO THE
SAN MATEO BRIDGE DRY ON THIS
SIDE.
MID SPAN IN THE RAIN.
64 DEGREES.
RAIN PRESSING FROM WEST TO EAST
ACROSS THE BAY AREA.
THE OUTER FRINGE OF THIS STORM
IS