NEWS.
JOIN US FOR THOSE STORIES.
THE LOSS AND TALES OF INCREDIBLE
HEROISM COMING OUT OF LAS VEGAS.
>> BACK AT 6:30.
NIGHTLY NEWS IS NEXT.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT.
THE DEADLIEST MASS
SHOOTING IN
MODERN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
AT LEAST 59 DEAD, OVER
WOUNDED AS A SNIPER
OPENS FIRE
FROM A SMASHED-OUT
HOTEL WINDOW
WINDOW HIGH ABOVE A
COUNTRY MUSIC
FESTIVAL, UNLEASHING A
MASSACRE ON THE VEGAS
STRIP.
FIRST RESPONDERS ON A
FRANTIC MISSION TO
FIND THE GUNMAN.
SURVIVORS DESCRIBING
SCENES OF SHEER
TERROR.
>> BULLETS FLYING
EVERYWHERE.
EVERYBODY RUNNING.
IT WAS REALLY, REALLY
BAD.
>> TONIGHT A BAFFLING
MYSTERY.
WHY DID HE DO IT?
WHAT WE'VE LEARNED
ABOUT THE GUNMAN AND
HIS MASSIVE ARSENAL.
WE HAVE IT ALL COVERED
INCLUDING
EXTRAORDINARY ACTS OF
HEROISM IN A FIELD OF
HORROR.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> LAS VEGAS MASS
SHOOTING.
THIS IS NBC "NIGHTLY
NEWS" WITH LESTER HOLT
REPORTING TONIGHT FROM
LAS VEGAS.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THE HEARTS OF OUR
NATION ACHE TONIGHT
WITH A SICKENING
FAMILIARITY.
ANOTHER MASS MURDER,
ANOTHER TAKING OF
INNOCENT LIVES ON AN
UNIMAGINABLE SCALE.
LAST NIGHT'S ATTACK
HERE ALONG THE VEGAS
STRIP IS THE WORST
U.S. SHOOTING IN
MODERN HISTORY.
AS OF RIGHT NOW AT
LEAST 59 DEAD,
HUNDREDS INJURED
AS WE COME ON THE AIR
A BROKEN-OUT WINDOW ON
THE UPPER FLOOR OF THE
MANDALAY BAY HOTEL
BEHIND ME POINTS TO
WHERE HELL WAS
UNLEASHED.
A GUEST ROOM TURNED
SNIPER'S NEST FOR A
64-YEAR-OLD MAN ARMED
WITH MORE THAN A DOZEN
WEAPONS LAUNCHED HIS
WITHERING RAPID-FIRE
GUN ATTACK, TURNING AN
OPEN-AIR EVENING
CONCERT ON THE GROUNDS
JUST OVER MY SHOULDER
INTO AN URBAN KILLING
FIELD.
WE HAVE A TEAM
ASSEMBLED TO COVER ALL
ANGLES OF THIS
DEVELOPING STORY.
WE START WITH NBC'S
JOE FRYER.
>> Reporter: IN A
MATTER OF SECONDS, A
COUNTRY MUSIC FESTIVAL
TURNED TRAGIC AS A
STORM OF GUN FIRE
RAINING DOWN ON AN
INNOCENT CROWD.
>> HE WAS SHOOTING
EVERYBODY.
AND THERE WAS DEAD
PEOPLE EVERYWHERE.
AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
THERE WAS JUST -- IT
WAS JUST SHOOTING
RANDOMLY.
>> Reporter: IT
STARTED AT 10:08 P.M.
FIRST REPORTS OF SHOTS
FIRED AS SINGER JASON
ALDEAN PERFORMED.
INITIALLY THERE WAS
CONFUSION.
MANY WONDERING IF THE
SOUNDS WERE PART OF
THE SHOW.
>> IT'S FIREWORKS.
STOP.
IT'S FIREWORKS.
>> Reporter: BUT THEY
QUICKLY REALIZED WHAT
WAS HAPPENING.
>> WE HAVE AN ACTIVE
SHOOTER!
WE HAVE AN ACTIVE
SHOOTER INSIDE THE
FAIRGROUNDS!
>> Reporter: A GUNMAN
PERCHED ON THE 32nd
FLOOR OF THE MANDALAY
BAY RESORT HAD OPENED
FIRE ON 22,000 CONCERT
GOERS.
>> WE GOT ABOUT 40 TO
50 PEOPLE WERE PINNED
AGAINST THIS WALL.
>> Reporter: ALL OF
THEM SCRAMBLING TO
FIND SHELTER WHEREVER
THEY COULD.
>> AND THEN ONE AFTER
THE OTHER.
WE WERE LAYING DOWN ON
THE FLOOR.
I DIDN'T KNOW TO GET
UP, TO RUN, JUST TO
STAY, TO DUCK.
>> Reporter: AT 11:20,
1 HOUR AND 12 MINUTES
AFTER THE SHOOTING
BEGAN, THE S.W.A.T.
TEAM BUSTED INTO THE
GUNMAN'S HOTEL ROOM.
>> ALL UNITS ON THE
32nd FLOOR, S.W.A.T.
IS THERE.
MOVE BACK.
>> BREACH, BREACH,
BREACH.
>> Reporter: INSIDE
THEY FOUND 64-YEAR-OLD
STEPHEN PADDOCK THERE.
AUTHORITIES SAY HE
KILLED HIMSELF.
THEY LOOKED FOR
MARILOU DANLEY BUT SHE
WAS OUT OF THE
COUNTRY.
SHE IS NOT A SUSPECT.
>> RIGHT NOW WE
BELIEVE HE'S THE SOLE
AGGRESSOR AT THIS
POINT AND THE SCENE IS
STATIC.
>> Reporter: LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS
BELIEVE PADDOCK FIRED
OUT OF TWO ADJOINING
ROOMS USING A DEVICE
SIMILAR TO A HAMMER TO
SMASH THE WINDOWS.
AUTHORITIES SAY THEY
FOUND MORE THAN A
DOZEN WEAPONS INSIDE
THOSE ROOMS.
AS THE CHAOS UNFOLDED
OUR TEAM WAS ACTUALLY
STAYING IN THE
MANDALAY BAY TOWER
UNDER LOCKDOWN.
>> THERE ARE FLASHING
RED AND BLUE LIGHTS
EVERYWHERE AS THIS
AREA HAS BEEN FLOODED
BY POLICE AND
EMERGENCY RESPONDERS.
>> Reporter: WE WERE
SIX FLOORS ABOVE THE
GUNMAN WHO WAS ON THE
32nd FLOOR OF THE
HOTEL FIRING ACROSS
LAS VEGAS BOULEVARD
TOWARD THE CONCERT.
THE STAGE 400 YARDS
FROM THE HOTEL WITH
THE CROWD GATHERED IN
FRONT.
MANY THEN FLEEING TO
THE FESTIVAL'S MAIN
ENTRANCE.
>> IT WAS VERY SCARY
AT THE TIME.
AND I GOT MY WIFE UP.
AS I GOT HER UP, TWO
GUYS CAME RUNNING BY
THAT WERE CARRYING A
GIRL OR SOMEBODY THAT
WAS ALL BLOODY, AND IT
LOOKED LIKE THEY'D
BEEN SHOT.
>> Reporter: IN THE
END, A MASSIVE LOSS OF
LIFE AND HUNDREDS
INJURED IN THE WORST
MASS SHOOTING IN
MODERN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
DURING THAT LOCKDOWN,
OUR TEAM WAS TOLD TO
STAY IN THE HOTEL ROOM
FOR TEN HOURS.
IN THAT TIME LOOKING
THROUGH THE PEEPHOLE,
WE COULD SEE POLICE IN
THE HALLWAY CHECKING
ON GUESTS TO MAKE SURE
THEY WERE OKAY.
>> JOE, THANK YOU.
MEANTIME, POLICE AND
FEDERAL AGENTS ARE
DIGGING INTO THE
GUNMAN'S RECENT PAST
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT SET HIM OFF, WHAT
COULD POSSIBLY HAVE
LED HIM TO CARRY OUT
SUCH AN ATROCITY.
THE MORE DETAILS WE
LEARN ABOUT STEPHEN
PADDOCK, THE DEEPER
THIS MYSTERY GETS.
NBC NEWS JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS HAS THE
LATEST.
>> THIS WE UNDERSTAND
IS THE HOUSE THAT WAS
OWNED BY PADDOCK.
>> Reporter: LESS THAN
AN HOUR AFTER THE
AFTER THE SHOOTING
STOPPED --
>> THEY DO HAVE A
LARGE CREW OUT HERE.
>> Reporter: POLICE
AND FEDERAL AGENTS
DESCENDED ON THE HOME
OF STEPHEN PADDOCK IN
MESQUITE, NEVADA.
A SEARCH TURNED UP 19
MORE GUNS, AMMUNITION
AND EXPLOSIVES BUT NO
CLUES ABOUT WHAT DROVE
HIM TO COMMIT MASS
MURDER.
HE LIVED THERE WITH
HIS GIRLFRIEND MARILOU
DANLEY.
>> WE THE MESQUITE
POLICE DEPARTMENT HAVE
NOT HAD ANY CONTACT
WITH THESE PEOPLE IN
THE PAST.
WE HAVEN'T HAD ANY LAW
ENFORCEMENT CONTACTS,
NO ARRESTS OR NOTHING.
>> Reporter: A YOUNGER
BROTHER ERIC PADDOCK
SAYS THE FAMILY NEVER
SAW IT COMES.
>> JUST LIKE AN
ASTEROID FELL OUT OF
THE SKY.
THERE'S NO -- THERE
WAS NOTHING THAT WOULD
SAY HE WOULD DO THIS
KIND OF THING.
THERE'S NO
AFFILIATIONS.
THERE'S NO CHURCH,
THERE'S NO RELIGION,
THERE'S NO POLITICS,
THERE'S NO ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS
PADDOCK RECENTLY
TEXTED TO ASK HOW HIS
90-YEAR-OLD MOTHER WAS
DOING AFTER HURRICANE
IRMA AND TEXTED AGAIN
ABOUT ATTENDING A
FAMILY WEDDING.
THEIR FATHER, BENJAMIN
HOSKINS PADDOCK, WAS
ONCE ON THE FBI'S TEN
MOST WANTED LIST AFTER
ESCAPING FROM PRISON
IN 1968 WHILE SERVING
TIME FOR BANK ROBBERY.
THE FBI DESCRIBED THE
FATHER AS PSYCHOPATHIC
WITH SUICIDAL
TENDENCIES.
BUT THE SON, STEPHEN
PADDOCK, HAD NO
BRUSHES WITH THE LAW.
STATE AND FEDERAL
OFFICIALS SAY.
FIVE YEARS AGO HE SUED
ANOTHER LAS VEGAS
HOTEL AFTER HE SLIPPED
AND FELL, AN
OBSTRUCTION ON THE
FLOOR, HE SAID, THE
CASE WAS LATER
DISMISSED.
HE WAS A RETIRED
ACCOUNTANT AFTER
LIVING FOR A TIME IN
TEXAS AND FLORIDA, A
MULTIMILLIONAIRE REAL
ESTATE DEVELOPER, HIS
BROTHER SAYS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY IN
THE PAST FEW WEEKS HE
GAMBLED HEAVILY AT LAS
VEGAS HOTELS AND
CASINOS, PLACING TENS
OF THOUSANDS OF
DOLLARS IN BETS.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS AND
GUN STORE OWNERS SAY
HE HAS LEGALLY
PURCHASED RIFLES AND
HANDGUNS OVER THE PAST
SEVERAL MONTHS IN
NEVADA.
MORE THAN A DOZEN
ASSAULT-TYPE RIFLES
LIKE THIS WERE FOUND
IN HIS HOTEL ROOM,
FEDERAL OFFICIALS SAY,
ALONG WITH SOME SNIPER
RIFLES WITH SCOPES AND
TRIPODS.
POLICE SAY HE CHECKED
INTO THE MANDALAY BAY
HOTEL LAST THURSDAY
AND BROUGHT IN ALL THE
GUNS AND AMMUNITION
HIMSELF ALONG WITH HIS
LUGGAGE, KEEPING IT
HIDDEN FROM THE
HOUSEKEEPING STAFF.
BUT POLICE SAY THEY
DON'T KNOW WHY HE
TARGETED A COUNTRY
MUSIC CONCERT.
THEY FOUND NO NOTES,
NO EMAILS, NO SOCIAL
MEDIA POSTINGS OR HOW
LONG AGO HE DEVELOPED
THIS PLAN, BUT THEY
SAY THEY DO NOT
BELIEVE HE HAD ANY
HELP.
LESTER?
>> PETE WILLIAMS,
THANK YOU.
>>> IT IS HARD TO
WATCH THAT SMARTPHONE
VIDEO OF THE ATTACK
WITHOUT IMAGINING
YOURSELF IN SUCH A
SITUATION.
WHAT WOULD I DO?
HOW WOULD I REACT?
THOSE VIDEOS MADE US
ALL WITNESSES TO THE
SHOOTING.
ONLY THOSE WHO LIVED
THROUGH IT CAN SPEAK
TO THE HARD CHOICE OF
SURVIVAL IN A PLACE
WHERE IT APPEARED
THERE WERE NO GOOD
CHOICES.
THE IMAGES ARE HARD TO
SHAKE.
A NIGHT OUT TURNING
INTO A NIGHTMARE.
SPLIT SECOND
DECISIONS.
DO YOU RUN OR DO YOU
TAKE COVER?
MIKE CROFT WAS TEN
FEET FROM THE STAGE
WHEN THE SHOTS BEGAN.
>> I KNEW THEY CAME
FROM THE HOTEL.
I'M LIKE WE'RE
SCREAMING AT PEOPLE TO
GET DOWN ON THE GROUND
SO YOU'RE NOT A
TARGET.
>> Reporter: HIS
FRIEND ROB McINTOSH
HAD BEEN SHOT.
YOUR INSTINCT WAS GET
DOWN, NOT RUN.
>> YES.
OH, YEAH, MY BUDDY WAS
HIT.
I'M NOT LEAVING HIM.
>> Reporter: WHERE WAS
HE HIT?
>> HE GOT HIT THREE
TIMES IN THE CHEST.
>> Reporter: DID HE
REMAIN CONSCIOUS?
>> YES, THE WHOLE
TIME.
HE HAD HIS FINGER IN
THE BULLET HOLE.
LEAVE YOUR FINGER IN.
WE GOT SHIRTS OFF AND
COME PRESSED IT.
>> Reporter: A THAT
MOMENT BACKSTAGE MORE
CRITICAL DECISIONS.
BUZZ BRAINARD WORKING
WITH SIRIUS/XM THERE
WITH HIS 19-YEAR-OLD
SON HANK.
>> JUST EVERYBODY I
SAW DOVE UNDERNEATH
THE TOUR BUSES.
MY SON WAS THERE.
I HAD HIM DOWN AND
I WAS ON TOP OF HIM.
WE'RE ON THE GROUND
UNDERNEATH.
BULLETS WERE HITTING
THE DIRT, SO YOU COULD
FEEL THE DIRT --
>> Reporter: YOU'RE
FEELING THEN
CONCUSSION OF THE
BULLETS.
>> HITTING YOUR FACE,
THE DIRT IS.
>> Reporter: BRAINER
BELIEVING THE ONLY WAY
TO GET OUT WAS TO RUN
ACROSS THE STAGE THAT
JASON ALDEAN JUST
FLED.
>> I GRABBED MY SON BY
THE HAND.
HE'S 19 YEARS OLD, BUT
HE WAS MY LITTLE BOY
THERE.
>> Reporter: YEAH,
YEAH.
>> AND WE SPRINTED
ACROSS THE STAGE.
BY THE TIME WE MERGED
WITH THE CROWD THAT
WAS HERE, SO THEN IT
JUST -- IT BECAME
CHAOS.
>> Reporter: A BIT OF
A STAMPEDE.
>> IT WAS EXACTLY A
STAMPEDE.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
I MEAN, THERE WAS
REALLY NOWHERE TO
HIDE.
>> Reporter:
MEANWHILE, MIKE CROCK
HAD BEEN TRYING TO GET
HIS FRIEND HELP.
>> WE ACTUALLY LOADED
FOUR WOUNDED PEOPLE UP
IN THE BACK OF A
PICKUP TRUCK AND TRIED
TO GET TO THE
HOSPITAL.
FINALLY WE RAN INTO AN
AMBULANCE.
AND SO YOU KNOW, THEY
STARTED TRIAGING AND
WE GOT MY BUDDY IN THE
AMBULANCE.
AND ONE OF THE YOUNG
MEN THAT WAS IN THE
BACK OF THE TRUCK AS I
WAS CARRYING HIM, HE
PASSED AWAY.
SO THAT YOUNG MAN,
SOMEBODY'S SON, YOU
KNOW, PASSED AWAY
RIGHT THERE.
IT WAS NOT BY HIMSELF.
HE WAS ALWAYS WITH
SOMEBODY.
>> Reporter: BUT LATE
TODAY, THE MOMENT MIKE
HAD BEEN WAITING FOR.
>> LET ME TELL YOU,
YOU'RE ONE OF THE
LUCKY ONES.
>> Reporter: REUNITED
IN THE HOSPITAL WITH A
FRIEND HE HAD HELPED
SAVE.
>> YOU DID GOOD.
THANKS FOR STAYING
WITH ME.
>> Reporter: ONE
GLIMMER OF HOPE
TONIGHT.
SO MANY DESPERATE FOR
MORE.
MIKE CROCK'S FRIEND
ROB IS FACING MORE
SURGERY, BUT WE'RE
GLAD TO REPORT HE IS
EXPECTED TO RECOVER.
AND MIKE TOLD US HE'S
PLANNING TO DONATE
BLOOD FOR THE INJURED.
>>> NOW TO THOSE WHO
DIDN'T MAKE IT OUT.
THE COUNTRY MUSIC
FESTIVAL THAT CAME
UNDER ATTACK HERE HAD
BROUGHT IN TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF FANS FROM
FAR AND WIDE.
AMONG THOSE KILLED, A
NEWLYWED PROTECTING
HIS WIFE.
A SPECIAL EDUCATION
TEACHER.
A SINGLE MOM.
POLICE OFFICERS.
AND SO MANY MORE.
NBC'S STEPHANIE GOSK
HAS MORE ON THE
VICTIMS.
>> Reporter: AS
BULLETS STARTED
RAINING DOWN ON
SUNDAY, SONNY'S
INSTINCT WAS TO
PROTECT HIS WIFE OF
JUST OVER A YEAR,
HEATHER.
HE GRABBED HER AND
STARTED RUNNING WHEN
HE WAS SHOT IN THE
BACK.
HEATHER SAYS HE SAVED
MY LIFE AND LOST HIS.
AT THIS POINT I CAN
BARELY BREATHE.
MELTON WAS A
REGISTERED NURSE IN
TENNESSEE.
HIS WIFE IS A SURGEON.
THEY MET AT THE
HOSPITAL AND FELL IN
LOVE.
>> HE WAS A VERY KIND,
LOVING PERSON THAT
EVERYBODY LIKED A LOT.
>> HE WAS SHOT IN THE
CHEST.
>> Reporter: BRYCE
JORDAN LINED UP TO
DONATE BLOOD JUST
HOURS AFTER LEARNING
HIS COUSIN QUINTON
ROBBINS WAS KILLED.
ROBBINS ATTENDED THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA
LAS VEGAS.
IN HIS FREE TIME HE
COACHED HIS LITTLE
BROTHER'S FLAG
FOOTBALL TEAM.
>> I LOVED QUINTON.
HE WAS A VERY POPULAR
KID AROUND SCHOOL AND
AROUND TOWN.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST
TWO MANHATTAN BEACH,
CALIFORNIA, RESIDENTS
DIED IN THE MASSACRE,
INCLUDING RACHEL
PARKER, A LONG TIME
RECORDS TECHNICIAN FOR
THE POLICE DEPARTMENT.
AND SPECIAL EDUCATION
TEACHER SANDY CASEY.
HER PARTNER
CHRISTOPHER SAID SHE
LIVED LIFE TO THE
FULLEST AND MADE ME
THE HAPPIEST MAN IN
THE WORLD.
SECRETARY LISA ROMERO
AND OFFICE MANAGER
SUSAN SMITH ALSO AMONG
THE VICTIMS.
28-YEAR-OLD SINGLE
MOTHER JESSICA
KLEMCHUCK WAS VISITING
LAS VEGAS WITH HER
FIANCE BRENT URLAH.
YOU ARE HEAVEN SENT.
YOU ARE MY ONE AND
ONLY SHE WROTE TO HIM
LAST WEEK.
SHE LEAVES BEHIND
CHILDREN.
LAS VEGAS OFFICER
CHARLESTON HARTFORD.
>> ONE OF MY OFFICERS
WAS OFF DUTY ATTENDING
THE CONCERT AND LOST
HIS LIFE.
>> Reporter: ONE
WITNESS SAID OFF-DUTY
OFFICERS IN THE CROWD
WERE INJURED WHEN THEY
ACTED AS HUMAN
SHIELDS.
>> THEY LAID OVER TOP
OF US EVERY TIME A
ROUND WAS FIRED.
>> Reporter: MECHANIC
JORDAN McKILDON WAS A
BIG FAN OF LAS VEGAS.
HE CROSSED PATHS WITH
HEATHER GOOZE.
I'M WITH A YOUNG MAN
WHO DIED IN MY ARMS,
SHE WROTE ON FACEBOOK.
TONIGHT AS THE DEATH
TOLL CLIMBS, SO MANY
PEOPLE STILL SEARCHING
FOR LOVED ONES AND
ANSWERS.
FAMILIES ARE BEING
DIRECTED HERE TO THIS
CONVENTION CENTER.
WITH SO MANY
CASUALTIES, THE
IDENTIFICATION PROCESS
IS COMPLICATED.
PEOPLE MAY HAVE TO
WAIT DAYS BEFORE
KNOWING FOR SURE WHAT
HAPPENED TO THEIR
LOVED ONES.
>> SUCH A TRAGIC LOSS,
STEPHANIE GOSK, THANK
YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> THE EMERGENCY
RESPONSE IN THE CITY
WAS OVERWHELMING.
VICTIMS POURING INTO
HOSPITALS ANY WAY THEY
COULD FOR HOURS.
SOME CLINGING TO LIFE,
OTHERS WALKING
WOUNDED.
OUR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MIGUEL
ALMAGUER HAS MORE ON
THE MEN AND WOMEN ON
THE FRONT LINES IN THE
RUSH TO SAVE LIVES.
>> Reporter: AS CHAOS
TURNED TO CARNAGE,
THOUSANDS RAN FOR
EXITS WHILE THOSE IN
UNIFORM POURED IN TO
HELP.
>> WE'RE GETTING SHOT
AT.
WE'RE GETTING SHOT AT.
>> Reporter: FIRST
RESPONDERS RISKING
THEIR OWN LIVES TO
SAVE OTHERS.
>> WE'RE TAKING
GUNFIRE.
IT'S GOING RIGHT OVER
OUR HEADS.
>> Reporter: WEARING
KEVLAR HELMETS AND
VESTS, THEY TENDED TO
THE WOUNDED ANY WAY
THEY COULD.
>> WE'RE MAKING
TOURNIQUETS OUT OF
BLANKETS, BUT I'M
RUNNING OUT OF
BLANKETS HERE.
>> Reporter: THE
SERIOUSLY INJURED WERE
EVERYWHERE, CARRIED ON
STRETCHERS AND
WHEELBARROWS.
THOSE THAT COULD HELP
DID.
>> RIGHT NOW, WE NEED
YOUR TRUCK.
WE JUST NEED TO GET
PEOPLE OVER TO THE
HOSPITAL, OKAY?
>> THERE WERE TRUCKS
THAT HAD EIGHT PEOPLE
IN THE BACK OF THEM.
>> Reporter: TRAUMA
SUPERVISOR TONI MULLEN
HAS NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT
BEFORE.
>> WE PUT GURNEYS
OUTSIDE.
WE HAD WHEELCHAIRS
OUTSIDE WAITING FOR
THE PEOPLE TO BE
BROUGHT IN.
>> Reporter: FOR HOURS
AMBULANCES FERRIED IN
THOSE CLINGING TO
LIFE.
OVERWHELMING FIVE
HOSPITALS.
>> UMC IS AT CAPACITY
FOR VICTIMS UNLESS
IT'S LIFE THREATENING.
>> Reporter: ALL
EMERGENCY PERSONNEL
CALLED IN TO HELP.
TODAY HUNDREDS WAITED
FOR HOURS TO DONATE
MUCH-NEEDED BLOOD TO
HELP VICTIMS LIKE NICK
RABON, SHOT IN THE
CHEST.
HIS BROTHER A
PARAMEDIC, SAVED HIS
LIFE, THEN THOSE OF
STRANGERS.
>> JUST COMBINED
EFFORT OF BYSTANDERS
JUST HELPING PEOPLE.
IT WAS ONE OF THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL CRAZIEST
THINGS I'VE EVER SEEN
INSIDE OF A TRAGEDY.
>> Reporter: THE WORST
OF TIMES BRINGING OUT
THE BEST INSIDE.
SO MANY SAVED AMONG SO
MUCH LOSS.
AT THE TWO LARGEST
TRAUMA CENTERS IN LAS
VEGAS, INCLUDING THIS
ONE, AT LEAST A DOZEN
REMAIN IN CRITICAL
CONDITION.
50 MORE FACE SERIOUS
SURGERIES AND WHILE SO
MANY LIVES WERE SAVED,
IT'S IMPORTANT TO
REMEMBER TONIGHT MANY
ARE STILL FIGHTING FOR
THEIR LIVES.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT, MIGUEL
ALMAGUER, PART OF OUR
TEAM ON THE GROUND
HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
THANK YOU.
IN HONOR OF THE
VICTIMS PRESIDENT
TRUMP LED A MOMENT OF
SILENCE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE THIS AFTERNOON.
HE ALSO CONDEMNED THIS
ATTACK AS, QUOTE, AN
ACT OF PURE EVIL AND
ORDERED FLAGS TO FLY
AT HALF-STAFF.
THE PRESIDENT SAID
HE'LL VISIT LAS VEGAS
ON WEDNESDAY AFTER HIS
TRIP TO
HURRICANE-RAVAGED
PUERTO RICO TOMORROW.
>>> THERE'S MUCH MORE
STILL AHEAD AS WE
CONTINUE TONIGHT FROM
LAS VEGAS INCLUDING
THE SHOOTER'S GUNS.
INSIDE THE ARSENAL HE
USED TO CARRY OUT HIS
RAMPAGE.
POLICE SAY SOME MAY
HAVE BEEN FULLY
AUTOMATIC.
HOW DID HE GET AHOLD
OF THEM?
STAY WITH US.
>>> TONIGHT LAW
ENFORCEMENT SOURCES
TELL NBC NEWS THE
GUNMAN HERE IN LAS
VEGAS MAY HAVE BEEN
USING SEMIAUTOMATIC
WEAPONS CONVERTED TO
FIRE TO FULL AUTOMATIC
MODE.
SEMIAUTOMATIC WEAPONS
ARE LEGAL IN THE U.S.,
BUT FOR THREE DECADES
NEW SALES OF AUTOMATIC
WEAPONS HAVE BEEN
ILLEGAL.
THE QUESTION IS HOW
MAY THE SHOOTER HAVE
GOTTEN HIS HANDS ON
WHAT WERE ESSENTIALLY
MILITARY GRADE MACHINE
GUNS?
HERE'S NBC'S TOM
COSTELLO.
>> GET DOWN.
GET DOWN.
>> Reporter: VETERAN
COPS COULD TELL FROM
THE SOUND OF THE
GUNFIRE THAT FULLY
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS WERE
LIKELY INVOLVED.
AMONG THE ARMORY OF
GUNS, AMMUNITION,
TRIPODS AND SCOPES
RECOVERED FROM THE
HOTEL ROOM WERE 0.223
CALIBER AND 0.308
CALIBER RIFLES
POSSIBLY ILLEGALLY
CONVERTED INTO
AUTOMATIC MACHINE-GUNS
USED BY THE MILITARY,
ABLE TO STRIKE A
TARGET FROM LONG
DISTANCES.
>> IT GOES DOWN THE
BARREL WITH HIGH
VELOCITY.
THAT'S WHY IT'S SO
DEADLY.
IT WILL GO THROUGH A
POLICEMAN'S VEST,
THROUGH HIM, OUT THE
BACK AND INTO THE NEXT
PERSON.
>> Reporter: FEDERAL
LAW HAS OUTLAWED THE
SALE OF NEW MACHINE
GUNS, SEMIAUTOMATIC
WEAPONS ARE LEGAL IN
MOST IF NOT ALL
STATES.
SOME GUN ENTHUSIASTS
AND CRIMINALS USE $50
KITS AVAILABLE ONLINE
TO CONVERT THEM INTO
AUTOMATIC GUNS.
YOUTUBE CLIPS SHOW HOW
IT'S DONE.
>> A FULLY AUTOMATIC
CAPABILITY BY JUST
REPLACING THE STOCK.
>> Reporter: AND
POLICE SAY THE NUMBER
OF FULLY CONVERTED
MI
AUTOMATED GUNS HAS
RISEN SHARPLY.
FIRING OFF HUNDREDS OF
ROUNDS PER MINUTE.
>> MY VIEW IS THEY
HAVE NO PLACE IN OUR
SOCIETY.
THEY ARE WEAPONS OF
LAW.
>> Reporter: IN NERVE
>> Reporter: IN
NEVADA, THERE'S NO
LIMIT ON HOW MUCH
AMMUNITION YOU CAN BUY
AND SHOOTING ONE
DOESN'T REQUIRE MUCH
SKILL.
>> HE'S JUST EMPTYING
THE WHOLE MAGAZINE
INTO THE CROWD.
MASS MURDER ON A
VULGAR SCALE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
AT LEAST TWO NEVADA
GUN DEALERSHIPS SAY
THE SUSPECT LEGALLY
PURCHASED WEAPONS
THERE, BUT WHAT'S NOT
CLEAR IS HOW HE GOT
HIS HANDS ON SO MANY
POWERFUL WEAPONS OF
WAR.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC
NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> UP NEXT, MORE ON
THIS MASSACRE AND THE
LONG LINE OF HAS
SHOOTINGS IN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
, we could afford
a real babysitter instead
of your brother.
Hey.
Oh. That's my robe.
Is it?
You could save seven hundred
eighty two dollars
when Liberty stands with you.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
[radi♪ alarm]
♪
Julie is living with metastatic
breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women with hormone receptor-
positive HER2- metastatic breast
cancer as the first
hormonal based therapy.
♪
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
And IBRANCE plus letrozole
shrunk tumors in over half of
these patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE can
develop low white blood cell
counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if you have
fever, chills,
or other signs of infection
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts...
...infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver
blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Julie calls it her "new" normal.
Because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one-prescribed,
FDA-approved oral combination
treatment for HR+/HER2- MBC.
[pHi Anne.g]
So those financial regulations
being talked about?
They could affect your accounts,
so let's get together and talk,
and make sure
everything's clear.
Yeah, that would be great.
Being proactive...
It's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
A heart attack doesn't
or how healthy you look.
No matter who you are,
a heart attack can
happen without warning.
A Bayer Aspirin regimen can help
prevent another heart attack.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Bayer Aspirin.
when I was too busy with the
kids to get a repair estimate.
I just snapped a photo
and got an estimate in 24 hours.
My insurance company
definitely doesn't have that...
You can leave worry behind when
Liberty Stands With You™
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
Woman: So, Greg,
it's a lot to take in.
Woman 2:
And I know that's hard to hear,
but the doctors
caught it early.
Hi, Blake!
My dad has cancer.
Woman:
And I know how hard
that is to hear.
But you're in
the right place.
Man:
And Dr. Pascal and her team,
they know what to do.
They know what to do.
The doctors know what to do.
So here's the plan.
First off, we're going
to give you all...
(Voice fading away)
>>> WE'RE BACK FROM
LAS VEGAS, NOW THE
SITE OF THE WORST MASS
SHOOTING IN MODERN
AMERICAN HISTORY.
IN THIS COUNTRY WE
HAVE WITNESSED EVENTS
LIKE THESE FAR TOO
OFTEN, BUT IT ALL
SEEMS THAT THE WORST
OF TYPES OFTEN BRING
OUT THE BEST IN
HUMANITY.
HERE'S NBC'S CYNTHIA
McFADDEN.
>> Reporter: IT'S
BECOME PAINFULLY
COMMON.
>> IT'S HAPPENED
AGAIN.
A MASS SHOOTING AT AN
AMERICAN SCHOOL IN
SUBURBAN DENVER.
>> WHAT UNFOLDED JUST
A FEW STEPS FROM HERE
LAST NIGHT IS ALMOST
TOO MUCH TO BEAR.
>> OUR COLLECTIVE
SENSE OF SECURITY WAS
SHATTERED AGAIN TODAY
BY TERROR.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER
MASS SHOOTING IN
AMERICA.
AT 10:08 P.M. IN LAS
VEGAS A GRIM NEW
RECORD IS ABOUT TO BE
SET.
THE MOST DEADLY MASS
SHOOTING EVER.
AMERICA ITSELF HAS A
GRIM DISTINCTION, WITH
5% OF THE WORLD'S
POPULATION, IT ENDURES
MORE THAN 30% OF THE
MASS SHOOTINGS.
THE SLAUGHTER IN LAS
VEGAS NOW ADDED TO A
TRAGIC TIMELINE.
50 YEARS AGO 16 DEAD
IN TEXAS.
13 AT COLUMBINE.
32 DIE AT VIRGINIA
TECH.
AT SANDY HOOK
ELEMENTARY, 26 DEAD.
IN ORLANDO, 49.
BUT THERE IS ANOTHER
LIST, TOO.
NOT OF THE MASSACRES,
BUT OF THE HEROES.
THE PEOPLE WHO HELPED.
THE SANDY HOOK TEACHER
KAITLYNN, WHO SAVED
15 OPPORTUNITIES --
STUDENTS.
AND THE DOCTOR WHO
WORKED HOURS STRAIGHT
SAVING THE PULSE
NIGHTCLUB VICTIMS.
HE POSTED THIS PHOTO
OF HIS SHOES STAINED
WITH THE BLOOD OF 46
VICTIMS.
AND IN OREGON,
30-YEAR-OLD CHRIS
MINTZ, A U.S. ARMY
VET, WHO WAS SHOT FIVE
TIMES AFTER DIRECTLY
CONFRONTING A HEAVILY
ARMED GUNMAN WHO HAD
ALREADY KILLED NINE
PEOPLE.
IT'S TOO EARLY TO KNOW
ALL THE NAMES OF THOSE
WHO HELPED OTHERS LAST
NIGHT, BUT IN THE
COMING DAYS AND WEEKS,
WE WILL.
AND WHEN WE DO,
PERHAPS A NEW TIMELINE
IS IN ORDER.
A TIMELINE OF THE
HEROES.
CYNTHIA McFADDEN, NBC
NEWS.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH
MORE FROM LAS VEGAS IN
JUST A MOMENT.
[Burker] At Farmers,
we've seen almost everything
so we know how to cover almost
anything.
Even a "Red-Hot Mascot."
[MASCOT] Hey-ooo!
Whoop, whoop!
[CROWD 1] Hey, you're on fire!
[MASCOT] You bet I am!
[CROWD 2] Dude, you're on fire!
[MASCOT] Oh, yeah!
[CROWD 3] No, you're on fire!
Look behind you.
[MASCOT] I'm cool. I'm cool.
[BURKE] That's one way to fire
up the crowd.
But we covered it.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
Yep, and my teeth are yellow. I
mean I knew they weren't
perfect, but, ugh.
Oh well, all hope is lost!
Oh thanks! Clearly my whitening
toothpaste is not cutting it.
Time for Whitestrips.
Crest Glamorous White
Whitestrips are the only
ADA-accepted whitening strips
proven to be safe and effective.
They work below the enamel
surface to whiten 25x better
than a leading
whitening toothpaste.
Hey, nice smile!
Thanks! I crushed
the Tissue Test!
Yeah you did!
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
♪ I'm...
I'm so in love with you. ♪
♪ Whatever you want to do...
♪ ...is alright with me.
♪ Ooo baby let's...
♪ ...let's stay together...
Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
Our first concentrated pill
that rushes powerful relief.
A small new size that's fast,
cause it's liquid.
Woohoo!
You'll ask, what pain?
New Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
now's the time to get your ducks
in a row.ng 65...
[Quack!]
Medicare only covers about 80%
of your Part B medical expenses.
The rest is up to you.
So think about an AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like any standardized Medicare
Supplement insurance plans,
they help cover some of what
Medicare doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide and learn more.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
FROM LAS VEGAS.
FOR MOST OF YOU, OUR
SPECIAL COVERAGE WILL
CONTINUE ON THIS NBC
NEWS STATION.
THAT'S IT FOR THE
FIRST HALF HOUR OF
NIGHTLY NEWS, I'M
LESTER HOLT, THANK YOU
FOR WATCHING, MORE
NEWS IN JUST A MOMENT.
>>> LAS VEGAS MASS
SHOOTING.
THIS IS NBC "NIGHTLY
NEWS" WITH LESTER
HOLT.
REPORTING TONIGHT FROM
LAS VEGAS.
>>> GOOD EVENING,
WE'RE BACK IN LAS
VEGAS WITH MORE OF OUR
CONTINUING COVERAGE OF
THE DEADLY RAMPAGE
HERE.
NOW THE WORST MASS
SHOOTING IN MODERN
AMERICAN HISTORY.
AT LEAST 59 PEOPLE
WERE KILLED, MORE THAN
500 HAVE BEEN INJURED.
ALL AFTER A GUNMAN
OPENED FIRE FROM THE
32nd FLOOR OF THE
MANDALAY BAY HOTEL AND
CASINO ON TO A COUNTRY
MUSIC FESTIVAL BELOW
WHERE MORE THAN 20,000
HAD GATHERED FOR WHAT
THEY THOUGHT WOULD BE
A NIGHT OF FUN ALONG
THE FAMED VEGAS STRIP.
BY THE TIME POLICE HAD