THANKS FOR WATCHING.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH LESTER
HOLT.
MORE LOCAL NEWS AT 6:00.
HOPE YOU CAN JOIN US THEN.
>>> ON THIS SATURDAY
NIGHT,
BREAKING POINT.
CONFUSION, CHAOS AND
FEAR IN PUERTO RICO,
AS A MAJOR DAM MAY BE
CLOSE TO BURSTING.
THOUSANDS TOLD SO
EVACUATE BEFORE WHAT
COULD BE AN EPIC
FLOOD.
>>> DESPERATE HOURS,
FOUR DAYS AFTER THE
DEVASTATING
EARTHQUAKE.
THE FRANTIC SEARCH IN
MEXICO CITY FOR THE
MISSING, WITH TIME
RUNNING OUT.
A POWERFUL AFTERSHOCK
JOLTS SOUTHERN MEXICO.
>>> THE PRESIDENT IN A
NEW WAR OF WORDS WITH
PRO ATHLETES AFTER
BLASTING THOSE WHO
KNEELED DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM.
WHAT LeBRON JAMES HAD
TO SAY ABOUT THE
PRESIDENT.
>>> JOBS WITH A
FUTURE.
TENS OF THOUSANDS OF
THEM PAYING WELL, EVEN
WITHOUT A COLLEGE
DEGREE.
WHERE ARE THEY?
AND HOW DO YOU GET
THEM?
>>> WHY SO MANY ARE
ONCE AGAIN TRYING TO
STRIKE IT RICH IN THE
HILLS OF CALIFORNIA.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING,
RIGHT NOW, MILLIONS OF
U.S. CITIZENS ARE
CLINGING TO HOPE AS
THEIR ISLAND HOMES ARE
COPING WITH THE DEADLY
EFFECTS OF HURRICANE
MARIA.
IN PUERTO RICO,
COMMUNICATIONS ARE
VIRTUALLY NONEXISTENT.
AS 3 MILLION PEOPLE
STRUGGLE WITH THE
BASICS OF SURVIVAL.
NO POWER, FOOD AND
WATER SHORTAGES THAT
THREATEN LIVES.
IN THE VIRGIN ISLANDS.
THE MILITARY THREW A
LIFELINE.
AIRLIFTING AN AIR
TRAFFIC CONTROL TOWER
TO START THE PROCESS
OF RECOVERY.
GABE GUTIERREZ BEGINS
OUR COVERAGE TONIGHT
FROM PUERTO RICO.
>> Reporter: TAKE A
LOOK AT THE POWER OF
ALL THIS WATER.
MARIA DUMPED MORE THAN
15 INCHES OF RAIN ON
THIS AREA.
A DESPERATE SCRAMBLE
BEGAN TO EVACUATE.
TONIGHT THE ARMY CORPS
OF ENGINEERS IS
ASSESSING WHETHER THIS
DAM WILL HOLD UP.
THIS WOMAN WAS TOLD TO
LEAVE IMMEDIATELY.
BUT THERE'S A
CRIPPLING CONFUSION OF
INFORMATION MUCH THE
GOVERNMENT UNABLE TO
REACH HALF OF THE
ISLAND'S
MUNICIPALITIES.
SAYING THE EVACUATION
ZONE AFFECTED UP TO
70,000 PEOPLE.
THE ACTUAL NUMBER WAS
MUCH LOWER, JUST
HUNDREDS IN CERTAIN
COMMUNITIES NEAR THE
DAM.
>> THIS IS WHAT WE DO
ALL DAY.
>> Reporter: FOR MANY
FAMILIES, THEIR ONLY
CONNECTION TO THE
OUTSIDE WORLD IS ONE
SPOTTY A.M. RADIO
STATION.
DAVID CASTRO TOLD US
HE AND HIS PARENTS
EVACUATED LAST NIGHT.
>> MY MOTHER WAS
TERRIFIED.
I WAS FRUSTRATED,
WE'RE GOING BACK AND
FORTH, WE HAD NOWHERE
TO GO.
>> Reporter: BUT THEY
SOON RETURNED WHEN
THEY HEARD NOTHING
ELSE FROM OFFICIALS.
THE UNCERTAINTY IS
CRUSHING.
SO IS THE SEEMINGLY
ENDLESS WAIT FOR FUEL.
>> THE LINES ARE NOT
ONLY HERE, IT'S
EVERYWHERE.
>> ROBERT MARTINEZ IS
DESPERATE TO CALL HIS
DAUGHTER WHO LIVES
NEAR PHILADELPHIA.
THEY HADN'T SPOKEN
SINCE THE STORM.
>> IT'S FRUSTRATING TO
COMMUNICATE WITH OUR
FAMILIES.
BACK HOME, THEY CAN'T
HEAR FROM US, THEY
DON'T KNOW WHAT'S
GOING ON.
WE OFFERED HIM OUR
SATELLITE PHONE.
YOUR MOM AND I ARE
OKAY.
THE FOLKS IN THE AREA
ARE OKAY.
WE ARE WAITING TO HEAR
FROM OTHERS.
>> Reporter: CLOSER TO
SAN JUAN, PEOPLE
CLUSTER HOPING,
PRAYING FOR ONE MEASLY
BAR OF CELL SERVICE.
NEVER HAS THIS ISLAND
FELT SO DISCONNECTED.
NEVER HAS IT FELT SO
ALONE.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, ISABELLA, PUERTO
RICO.
>>> I'M HANS NICHOLS
ON BOARD A MILITARY
PLANE FLYING RELIEF TO
THE VIRGIN ISLANDS.
THE CREW HAS BEEN ON
HIGH ALERT.
>> WE HAVE A TIGHT
STRING.
WHEN WE GET THE CALL,
WE HAVE THREE HOURS TO
GET OFF.
>> Reporter: ST.
THOMAS WAS DEVASTATED
BY HURRICANE IRMA, AND
HIT AGAIN BY MARIA.
IN THE COCKPIT, THE
FOCUS IS ON THE
MISSION.
>> GET IN, OFFLOAD.
>> ON THE GROUND,
MASTERS ARE AT WORK.
SPEED A PREMIUM.
>> WE'RE DOING
EVERYTHING WE CAN, AS
FAST AS WE CAN, AS
FAST AS WE'RE ALLOWED.
>> WE'VE LANDED HERE
IN SAINT THOMAS WHERE
THE AIRFIELD IS MOSTLY
CLEAR OF DEBRIS,
THEY'RE BRINGING IN AN
AIR TRAFFIC CONTROL
MOBIL COMMAND TOWER.
THE IDEA IS TO USE
THIS AIRFIELD AS A
STAGING GROUND FOR THE
BROADER RELIEF EFFORT.
THIS PLANE IS GOING TO
TAKE OFF NOW, HEAD
OVER TO TEXAS, PICK UP
PALLETS OF WATER AND
COME BACK.
HANS NICHOLS, NBC
NEWS, ST. THOMAS, THE
VIRGIN ISLAND.
>>> A STRONG
AFTERSHOCK SENT WAVES
THROUGH MEXICO TODAY.
THE SHAKING WAS FELT
HUNDREDS OF MILES AWAY
IN MEXICO CITY, WHERE
THE SEARCH FOR
SURVIVORS CONTINUES,
FOUR DAYS AFTER
HUNDREDS WERE KILLED.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER
REMAINS ON THE GROUND
FOR US.
>> Reporter: EMERGENCY
SIRENS REMIND RESCUE
TEAMS THEY'RE ON SHAKY
GROUND.
A POWERFUL SHALLOW 6.2
AFTERSHOCK, FORCING
FIRST RESPONDERS TO
TEMPORARILY STOP THEIR
DESPERATE SEARCHES IN
MEXICO CITY.
A JARRING REMINDER OF
TUESDAY'S TREMOR,
KILLED MORE THAN 300.
>> ALL OF A SUDDEN,
THE FLOORS STARTED
PANCAKING.
BOOM, BOOM, BOOM.
>> Reporter: WESLEY
BOXY AND HIS WIFE
ELIZABETH MADE IT TO
THE ROOF OF THEIR
APARTMENT DURING THE
QUAKE.
HERE IS WHAT IT LOOKED
LIKE BEFORE THE
TREMOR, THIS IS WHAT'S
LEFT NOW.
>> I WAS SHAKING A LOT
MORE VIOLENTLY THAN
I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> ELIZABETH WAS
BURIED THIS MORNING.
STORIES OF HEART BREAK
AND TALES OF
INCREDIBLE SURVIVAL
CONTINUE TO PLAY OUT
HERE.
NOW, FOUR DAYS LATER,
BEING PULLED FROM THE
RUBBLE ALIVE WOULD BE
A MIRACLE.
THE WORK HERE IS
BACKBREAKING, THEY'RE
USING PICKS, SHOVELS
AND IN SOME CASES,
THEIR HANDS.
TONIGHT, L.A. COUNTY'S
ELITE FIRE AND RESCUE
TEAM IS DEPLOYED TO
FIND THE MISSING.
>> WHEN CONCRETE AND
REBAR COLLAPSE AND
CRUMBLE, IT'S LIKE A
SPIDER'S WEB, NOTHING
IS EASY.
>> Reporter: THE TEAM
JUST WORKING YARDS
FROM WHERE THE MENDOZA
FAMILY ARE CAMPING.
DESPERATE FOR
INFORMATION ABOUT HER
COUSIN WHO WAS ON THE
FOURTH FLOOR OF THIS
EMPLOYMENT CENTER WHEN
IT CRUMBLED.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO DO.
IT'S TOUGH FOR
EVERYBODY.
NOT ONLY PHYSICALLY,
BUT MENTALLY,
EMOTIONALLY.
>> Reporter: THE
DESPERATE CLINGING TO
HOPE, AS EVERY DAY
PRECIOUS TIME SLIPS
AWAY MANY.
THE DAMAGE FROM
TODAY'S 6.2 QUAKE
AFTERSHOCK WAS FELT
SOME 300 MILES AWAY,
IT WAS MINIMAL
CONSIDERING ITS SIZE.
IT THIS COUNTRY HAS
BEEN SHAKEN, A
DISASTER CAN HAPPEN AT
ANY MOMENT.
>>> KIM JONG-UN CALLED
THE PRESIDENT A
MENTALLY DERANGED
PERSON.
THIS FOLLOWS THE
PRESIDENT'S THREAT TO
TOTALLY DESTROY NORTH
KOREA IF PROVOKED.
WE GET MORE FROM KELLY
O'DONNELL.
>> Reporter: IN NORTH
KOREA'S CAPITAL, A
CITIZENS RALLY AGAINST
THE UNITED STATES.
A MASSIVE
CHOREOGRAPHED MARCH.
NEAR NORTH KOREA, U.S.
AIR FORCE B-1 BOMBERS
AND FIGHTER ESCORTS
LIKE THESE, FLEW
FURTHER NORTH OVER
INTERNATIONAL WATERS
THAN AT ANY TIME IN
ALMOST 20 YEARS.
>> AND WE CAN'T HAVE
MAD MEN OUT THERE
SHOOTING ROCKETS ALL
OVER THE PLACE.
>> Reporter: COMPETING
RHETORIC CONTINUED
TOO.
IN ALABAMA FRIDAY
NIGHT, THE PRESIDENT
SAID HE CONTAINED KIM
JONG-UN'S NUCLEAR
THREATS.
>> LITTLE ROCKET MAN.
WE'RE GOING TO DO IT.
BECAUSE WE REALLY HAVE
NO CHOICE.
>> Reporter: TODAY AT
THE UNITED NATIONS,
NORTH KOREAN'S FOREIGN
MINISTER LASHED OUT,
CALLING PRESIDENT
TRUMP MENTALLY
DERANGED, CLAIMING THE
PRESIDENT'S INSULTS
MAKE A ROCKET ATTACK
ON THE U.S. MAINLAND
MORE INEVITABLE.
ESCALATING WORDS,
EXPERTS CALL
DANGEROUS.
>> THE MORE HE
BELITTLES KIM JONG-UN
ON A WORLD STAGE, THE
MORE KIM JONG-UN HAS
TO RESPOND, TO SHOW
THAT HE WON'T BE
DISRESPECTED AND HE
WON'T BE
UNDERESTIMATED.
AND HE WON'T BE
INTIMIDATED.
>> Reporter: STILL,
ANOTHER MILITARY
DISPLAY, THIS TIME IN
IRAN, WHERE THE
REVOLUTIONARY GUARD
UNVEILED A NEW
BALLISTIC MISSILE,
CAPABLE OF REACHING
ISRAEL.
>> THIS LATEST TEST
SENDS A STRONG SIGNAL
FROM PRESIDENT TRUMP
STRAIGHT FROM THE
NORTH KOREAN PLAYBOOK.
LESS THAN A MONTH
BEFORE THE NEW IRAN
NUCLEAR DEAL HAS TO BE
CERTIFIED AGAIN.
A RISKY MOVE THAT
COULD BACKFIRE.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT RESPONDED TO
IRAN'S TEST ON
TWITTER, SAYING NOT
MUCH OF AN AGREEMENT
THAT WE HAVE.
THE PRESIDENT HAS
UNTIL MID OCTOBER TO
TELL CONGRESS IF HE
BELIEVES IRAN IS IN
COMPLIANCE WITH THE
NUCLEAR DEAL.
IF NOT, NEW SANCTIONS
COULD BE IMPOSED.
HE SAID HE'S MADE UP
HIS MIND BUT HAS NOT
YET DISCLOSED HIS
DECISION.
>> KELLY O'DONNELL,
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> SOME BIG NAMES IN
SPORTS ARE FEUDING
TONIGHT WITH THE
PRESIDENT WHO SAID NFL
TEAM OWNERS SHOULD
FIRE PLAYERS WHO
REFUSE TO STAND FOR
THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
HIS LANGUAGE WAS MUCH
MORE EXPLICIT THAN
THAT.
THE HARSH EXCHANGES
DID NOT STOP WITH
FOOTBALL.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT NOW PICKING
A FIGHT WITH
PROFESSIONAL ATHLETES.
>> WOULDN'T YOU LOVE
TO SEE ONE OF THESE
NFL OWNERS WHEN
SOMEONE DISRESPECTS
OUR FLAG, TO SAY, GET
THAT SON OF A BITCH
OFF THE FIELD RIGHT
NOW.
OUT, HE'S FIRED.
HE'S FIRED!
>> Reporter: TAKING
AIM AT PLAYERS LIKE
COLIN KAEPERNICK, WHO
PROTESTED THE
TREATMENT OF BLACKS BY
POLICE BY TAKING A
KNEE DURING THE
NATIONAL ANTHEM LAST
YEAR.
ROGER GOODELL
TWEETING, DIVISIVE
COMMENTS LIKE THESE
DEMONSTRATE A LACK OF
RESPECT FOR THE NFL,
OUR GREAT GAME AND ALL
OUR PLAYERS.
KAEPERNICK'S MOM WITH
THIS RESPONSE.
THE GOLDEN STATE
WARRIORS STAR PLAYER
STEPH CURRY AND HIS
TEAMMATES WERE ALREADY
CONSIDERING NOT GOING
TO THE WHITE HOUSE TO
CELEBRATE THEIR NBA
TITLE.
>> THE PRESIDENT, THE
THINGS THAT HE HAS
SAID AND THE THINGS HE
HASN'T SAID IN THE
RIGHT TIMES, THAT WE
WON'T STAND FOR IT.
>> Reporter: THIS
MORNING THE PRESIDENT
RESPONDED.
GOING TO THE WHITE
HOUSE IS CONSIDERED A
GREAT HONOR FOR THE
CHAMPIONSHIP TEAM.
STEPHAN CURRY IS
HESITATING, THEREFORE,
THE INVITATION IS
WITHDRAWN.
>> IT'S JUST KIND OF
BENEATH THE LEADER OF
A COUNTRY TO GO THAT
ROUTE.
IT'S NOT WHAT LEADERS
DO.
>> Reporter: LeBRON
JAMES WEIGHED IN
CALLING THE PRESIDENT
A BUM.
STEPH CURRY SAID HE
ALREADY AIN'T GOING,
SO, THEREFORE, NO
INVITE.
THE BACK AND FORTH
WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
IS UNDER FIRE FOR HIS
HANDLING OF RACIAL
TENSIONS.
IN THE LATEST POLL,
25% OF AMERICANS
APPROVE OF HOW MR.
TRUMP IS HANDLING RACE
RELATIONS.
THE PRESIDENT ALSO
CRITICIZED THE NFL FOR
GIVING PENALTIES FOR
HARD HITS.
>> THEY'RE RUINING THE
GAME.
>> YOU HAVE MOTHERS,
FATHERS ALL OVER THE
COUNTRY SAYING, WE
DON'T WANT OUR KIDS TO
PLAY FOOTBALL.
AND DONALD TRUMP WANTS
TO GO BACK INTO THE
TIME WHEN IT WAS THE
ROMAN GLADIATORS.
>> Reporter: DONALD
TRUMP USING RALLIES TO
RANT AGAINST OPPONENTS
IS NOTHING NEW.
PROFESSIONAL SPORTS,
NOW THE LATEST
POLITICAL FOOTBALL.
KRISTEN DAHLGREN, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
HAVE SIGNED A PETITION
CALLING ON LONDON TO
REVERSE ITS DECISION
TO SHUT DOWN UBER IN
THE CITY.
THE MAYOR OF LONDON
DEFENDED THE MOVE
TODAY AND SAID THE
ANGER SHOULD BE
DIRECTED AT UBER
ITSELF.
LUCY KAFANOV HAS
DETAILS.
>> Reporter: SHE'S ONE
OF 40,000 LONDON UBER
DRIVERS WHOSE FUTURE
IS NOW IN FLUX.
HOW IMPORTANT IS UBER
TO YOUR LIVELIHOOD?
>> EXTREMELY
IMPORTANT.
>> Reporter: THE
CITY'S DECISION NOT TO
RENEW THE COMPANY'S
OPERATING LICENSE
MEANS THE SINGLE
MOTHER OF TWO COULD BE
OUT OF A JOB SOON.
>> I WAS STUNNED, I
COULDN'T BELIEVE --
I'M A SINGLE MOM, I
HAVE CHILDREN, AND
IT'S NOT JUST
AFFECTING THOSE THAT
JUST GET UP AND GO TO
WORK.
>> Reporter: THE CITY
SAID UBER IS NOT FIT
AND PROPER TO HOLD A
LICENSE, CITING THE
COMPANY'S APPROACH TO
REPORTING CRIMINAL
OFFENSES, INCLUDING
ALLEGATIONS OF RAPE,
WHILE RAISING CONCERNS
ABOUT DRIVER
BACKGROUND CHECKS.
>> IT'S ANTI-SAFETY
AND SECURITY, AND WHAT
IT SHOULD HAVE BEEN
DOING IS ABIDING BY
THE RULES AND PLAYING
BY THE RULES THEY
HAVEN'T BEEN.
>> UBER DENIES THE
ALLEGATIONS VOWING TO
FIGHT BACK.
>> LONDON IS UBER'S
LARGEST EUROPEAN
MARKET.
UNTIL YESTERDAY, IT'S
MOST NOTABLE SUCCESS
STORY OUTSIDE THE U.S.
>> THE COMPANY'S
ARRIVAL HERE WAS
BITTERLY OPPOSED BY
DRIVER'S OF LONDON'S
ICONIC BLACK CABS.
THEY SAY UBER IS
UNDERREGULATED AND
WILL PUT THEM OUT OF
BUSINESS.
>> UBER'S TROUBLES RUN
DEEP.
AND NOT ONLY IN THE
U.K.
>> UBER HAS ABANDONED
SEVERAL CITIES
ALREADY.
THE NATIONAL
GOVERNMENTS ARE
ALREADY TAKING NOTICE
I THINK.
I THINK IT'S TIME UBER
ALSO TOOK NOTICE.
>> UBER WILL BE
ALLOWED TO OPERATE AS
IT APPEALS THE
DECISION, THE RAPID
ACCELERATION IN LONDON
HAS BEEN THRUST INTO
REVERSE.
LUCY KAFANOV, NBC
NEWS, LONDON.
>>> HELP WANTED, WHERE
THE JOB IS AND JOBS
THAT PAY WELL, EVEN IF
YOU DON'T HAVE A
COLLEGE DEGREE.
>>> ALSO, THE GOLDEN
OPPORTUNITY THAT HAS
SO MANY PEOPLE HEADING
TO THE REMOTE HILLS OF
CALIFORNIA.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH A
LOOK AT JOBS OF THE
FUTURE, WHAT SOME CALL
NEW COLLAR JOBS OR
MIDDLE SKILLS JOBS
THAT DON'T REQUIRE
FOUR YEARS OF COLLEGE,
BUT DO REQUIRE
ADDITIONAL TRAINING IN
COMPUTER OR TECH.
A SHORTAGE OF
CANDIDATES IS EXPECTED
TO GROW AS BABY
BOOMERS RETIRE AND E
COMMERCE EXPANDS.
THE AIRLINE INDUSTRY
IS AMONG THOSE WHERE
HELP IS WANTED.
WE GET MORE FROM ALI
VELSHI.
>> Reporter: JOE
McDERMOTT ISN'T JUST
LOOKING FOR PILOTS
WITH THE RIGHT STUFF.
HE'S LOOKING FOR A FEW
GOOD AIRPLANE
MECHANICS.
YOUR MECHANICS ARE
SORT OF TECH WORKERS?
>> THEY'RE TECH
WORKERS.
>> Reporter: AS
AIRPLANES HAVE BECOME
MORE COMPUTERIZED, THE
JOB OF MECHANICS IS
SHIFTING FROM OIL PANS
TO SILICON CHIPS.
BEING A MECHANIC THAT
WORKS ON AIRPLANES IS
NOT DISSIMILAR TO THE
WAY IT'S BEEN OVER
PAST DECADES, THERE
ARE BIG CHANGES,
INCLUDING IN THE
ELECTRONICS AND
TECHNOLOGY THAT GO
INTO THE AIRPLANES.
TO BE AN AIRCRAFT
MECHANIC, YOU HAVE TO
BE MUCH MORE
TECHNICALLY MINDED
THAN YOU WERE.
THE GAP IN TECHNICAL
SKILLS EXTENDS ACROSS
INDUSTRIES.
AND COMPANIES LIKE
TOYOTA, BOEING,
GENERAL MOTORS AND DOW
CHEMICALS ARE ALL
STARTING TO BRIDGE THE
GAP.
DELTA PARTNERED WITH A
COMMUNITY COLLEGE IN
LANSING, MICHIGAN,
CREATING A CURRICULUM
TO ENSURE THEY GET TOP
FLIGHT MECHANICS IN
THEIR PIPELINE.
>> IF WE DON'T DO
SOMETHING DIFFERENTLY,
TO BE ABLE TO PRODUCE
THOSE MECHANICS OF THE
FUTURE, THEN WE'RE
GOING TO BE STRUGGLING
TO BE ABLE TO SUCCEED
>> Reporter: WHEN
THESE STUDENTS IN
DELTA'S LANSING
PROGRAM GRADUATE IN
TWO YEARS, AT A COST
OF ABOUT $23,000, THEY
ARE NEARLY GUARANTEED
A JOB AS AN AIRLINE
MECHANIC.
MOST OF THEM AT
DELTA'S REGIONAL
PARTNERS, STARTING
SALARY?
$50,000 A YEAR.
>> OUR STUDENTS ARE
NOW LOOKING AT
MULTIPLE JOB OFFERS
EVEN BEFORE THEY
GRADUATE.
>> Reporter: JOBS
STUDENTS HOPE WILL ONE
DAY LEAD TO THE MAJOR
CARRIERS.
>> IT'S KIND OF LIKE
THE MAJOR LEAGUES, I
GUESS, THAT'S WHERE
EVERYONE WANTS TO BE.
>> I'M EXCITED.
I REALLY AM.
>> Reporter: GETTING
THE TRAINING THEY NEED
FOR A FUTURE THAT
SOARS.
>>> WE ARE BACK IN A
MOMENT WITH THE NEW
GOLD RUSH GOING ON IN
THE HILLS OF
CALIFORNIA.
TRZ
>>> IT WAS THE FIRST
TEST OF THE SEMESTER
IN AN ACCOUNTING CLASS
AT A COLLEGE IN
MARYLAND.
AS ALWAYS, THE
PROFESSOR SAID THE
STUDENTS COULD BRING
ONE 3x5 CARD WITH
NOTES TO CLASS.
THIS IS WHAT ONE
STUDENT BROUGHT.
A 3x5 FOOT CARD.
SINCE THE PROFESSOR
NEVER SPECIFIED
INCHES, HE ALLOWED IT.
HE TWEETED WELL PLAYED
AND LESSON LEARNED FOR
ME.
>>> IN CALIFORNIA THE
COMBINATION OF
WILDFIRES AND RECORD
SNOW MELT HAS LED TO
AN UNEXPECTED
WINDFALL.
STEVE PATTERSON
TONIGHT ON HOW THE
GOLDEN STATE IS ONCE
AGAIN LIVING UP TO ITS
NAME.
>> Reporter: SEARING
FLAMES, SURGING
STREAMS.
FLOOD AND FIRE.
WREAKING HAVOC IN
NORTHERN CALIFORNIA IN
RECENT MONTHS AND
YEARS.
BUT NOW UNEARTHING A
NEW ERA.
>> BOY, IS THAT A LOT
OF GOLD.
>> Reporter: OF PAY
DIRT.
THIS IS THE MOTHER
LODE.
120 MILE STRETCH THAT
GAVE THE GOLDEN STATE
ITS NICKNAME.
DURING THE ORIGINAL
GOLD RUSH, NEARLY $90
MILLION WORTH OF GOLD
WAS EXTRACTED HERE IN
THE MID 1800s.
THAT'S MORE THAN 2
BILLION IN TODAY'S
DOLLARS.
>> THAT'S A BIG PIECE.
>> Reporter: NOW MORE
THAN 100 YEARS LATER,
A NEW RUSH.
FLOODWATERS SWEEPING
DEBRIS AND
UNDISCOVERED GOLD INTO
CREEKS AND VALLEYS.
>> WE CALL THAT FLOOD
GOLD.
>> Reporter: EIGHT
YEARS AGO, SHANNON
QUIT HIS CORPORATE JOB
TO BECOME A FULL TIME
GOLD MINER.
>> IT'S ELATION, YOUR
HEART WORK IS PAYING
OFF.
YOU GO, GOOD GOLLY, I
MADE $5,000 IN TWO
MINUTES.
>> Reporter: SOUNDS
EASY.
BUT YOU HAVE TO GO WAY
OFF THE BEATEN PATH TO
GET ANYWHERE NEAR THE
GOOD STUFF.
IN OUR JOURNEY INTO
THE WILDERNESS, WE
ARRIVE AT ONE OF HIS
FAVORITE MINING SPOTS.
>> THERE'S ACTUALLY
QUITE A BIT OF GOLD IN
HERE.
LOOK AT ALL OF THAT.
>> THIS IS PROBABLY
THE BEST YEAR I'VE HAD
IN MINING PERIOD.
>> BUSINESS IS REALLY
GOOD.
>> Reporter: IT'S ALSO
GIVING A BOOST TO
TOURISM IN LOCAL BOONE
TOWNS.
WITH WINTER RAINS JUST
AROUND THE CORNER,
THERE'S NO SIGN OF IT
ENDING.
BUT THERE'S A RUSH
GREATER THAN GOLD.
>> IT'S ABOUT THE
FREEDOM OF DOING WHAT
YOU WANT TO DO, AND
DOING WHAT YOU LIKE.
IT'S REALLY KIND OF
LIVING THE DREAM.
>> A LIFE RICH IN ADD
ADVENTURE, NO MATTER
WHAT PANS OUT.
NBC NEWS, GOLD
COUNTRY, CALIFORNIA.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
FROM HOOPS SO SCOOPS.
WHAT DROVE THIS PRO
BASKETBALL STAR FROM
THE COURT TO THE ICE
CREAM COUNTER.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
THE WORLD OF
PROFESSIONAL SPORTS
HAS ITS OBVIOUS
REWARDS FOR THOSE WHO
MAKE IT BIG.
IT CAN ALSO TAKE A BIG
TOLL ON ATHLETES,
WHICH IS WHY ONE
BASKETBALL STAR
DECIDED TO TAKE A
BREAK AND TRY
SOMETHING A BIT SOFTER
AND SWEETER.
KATIE BECK HAS THE
STORY.
>> Reporter: AT THE
TOP OF HER GAME,
PROFESSIONAL
BASKETBALL PLAYER
ANGEL McCOUGHTRY TRIES
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
>> WHO WANTS TO WALK
AWAY FROM SOMETHING
THEY LOVE.
BUT I KNOW IF I WANT
THE LONGEVITY IN MY
CAREER, THIS IS
SOMETHING I HAVE TO DO
NOW.
>> Reporter: IN 2016,
SHE WAS ONE OF THE TOP
SCORERS IN THE WNBA.
A STAR ON THE ATLANTA
DREAM WHO WON TWO
OLYMPIC GOLDS WITH
TEAM USA.
>> I HAD TENDINITIS IN
MY KNEES.
I WOKE UP WOBBLING
LIKE A PENGUIN.
I HAD PLANTAR FASCITIS
IN MY FEET.
>> SHE OPTED TO TAKE A
SEASON OFF.
LISTENING TO HER BODY,
REPAIRING IT.
IN THE MEANTIME, SHE
DECIDED TO SHOOT FOR
ANOTHER GOAL.
THIS DREAM WAS PERHAPS
A LONGSHOT.
>> HEY, I WONDER IF I
COULD OPEN MY OWN ICE
CREAM SHOP.
>> YOU DIDN'T HAVE ANY
BUSINESS EXPERIENCE
BEFORE YOU DID THIS?
>> NO BUSINESS
EXPERIENCE.
I JUST KNOW HOW TO RUN
UP AND DOWN A
BASKETBALL COURT.
>> SHE SAID IT WAS HER
SWEET TOOTH THAT LED
HER HERE AT HER SHOP
IN ATLANTA, A CASE OF
HOMEMADE FLAVORS, MANY
SHE MAKES HERSELF.
>> IT'S LIKE EATING A
BLUEBERRY CHEESECAKE.
>> THAT'S EXACTLY WHAT
IT IS.
>> WINNER.
>> Reporter: YOUNG
LOCALS BEHIND THE
COUNTER.
>> TOAST TO SOME ICE
CREAM.
>> Reporter: YOUNGER
ONES PLAYING GAMES AND
TAKING SPOONFULS ON
HER STOOP.
AFTER A SWEET SUMMER,
HER STORE WILL GO ON
AND SO WILL SHE, BACK
TO THE COURT.
>> I WORKED TOO HARD
NOT TO BE ABLE TO HAVE
A SHOT.
>> Reporter: SPEAKING
OF TAKING SHOTS, HER
MESSAGE FOR YOUNG
GIRLS.
>> FIND YOUR PASSION
IN LIFE.
IT CAN TAKE YOU PLACES
YOU'VE NEVER DREAMED.
>> LIFE CAN BE EVEN
SWEETER WHEN YOU FIND
MORE THAN ONE.
KATIE BECK, NBC NEWS,
ATLANTA.
>>> AND THAT'S NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS FOR THIS
SATURDAY.
TOMORROW ON NIGHTLY
NEWS WITH KATE SNOW,
REMNANTS OF AN ANCIENT
WORLD DISCOVERED RIGHT
OFF THE COAST OF
ALABAMA.
I'M JOSE DIAZ.
THANK YOU FOR THE
PRIVILEGE OF YOUR
TIME, AND GOOD NIGHT.
FREE SPEECH WEEK, CALLED OFF AT
U-C BERKELEY.
BUT THAT )S NOT STONG
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 6.
FREE SPEECH WEEK CALLED OFF AT
UC BERKELEY.
THAT'S NOT STOPPING A CONSER
CONSERVATIVE SPEAK R FROM GOING
ANYWAY.
>> GOOD EVENING EVERYONE.
THANK YOU FOR JOINING US.
FREE SPEECH WEEK FEATURING A
LINE UP OF CONSERVATIVE SPEAKERS
CANCELLED A DAY BEFORE IT WAS
SUPPOSED TO START.
A CONTROVERSIAL SPEAKER SAYS
HE'LL SHOW UP ANYWAY.
PROTESTORS WILL BE THERE FOR
HIM.
WE HAVE COVERAGE FOR YOU.
THE DEVELOPMENTS HAVE PEOPLE'S
HEADS SPINNING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
A LOT OF BACK AND FORTH ON THIS.
THE UNIVERSITY DID PUT OUT A
STATEMENT TODAY THEY RECEIVED
INFORMATION THAT THE EVENT WAS
CANCELLED.
THE UNIVERSITY SAID THEY DID
WORK HARD TO FACILITY THIS
INCLUDING PUTTING IN PLACE PLANS
TO SPEND A SUBSTANTIAL AMOUNT OF
MONEY ON SECURITY.
SO THEY SAY THAT SHOULD SPEAKERS
SHOW UP TOMORROW, THEY'RE
PREPARED.
>> Reporter: BERKELEY ON SUNDAY.
WHERE HE PLANS TO COME WITH A
NUMBER OF SPEAKS AFTER IT WAS
ANNOUNCED THE GROUP CANCELLED
FREE SPEECH WEEK.
HE ANNOUNCED HE WOULD COME
ANYWAY.
AND