I'M ADDING TO MY ALLERGY
MEDICINE.
>> AN EXTRA DOSE.
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT,
CROSSING THE LINE.
LATE WORD OF A MAJOR MOVE BY THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION.
THE U.S. SET TO INTERVENE IN THE
CRISIS IN SYRIA.
>>> STATE OF EMERGENCY.
AS A HISTORIC FIRE TORCHES
COLORADO, HUNDREDS OF HOMES ARE
GONE.
TENS OF THOUSANDS ARE
EVACUATING.
>>> ALSO, A MASSIVE STORM MOVING
EAST.
TORNADOES ON THE GROUND AND A
WILD NIGHT AHEAD.
>>> WARNING SIGNS.
DOCTORS SEE A BIG RISE IN AN
UNUSUAL FORM OF DEMENTIA, LOVED
ONES NOTICING CHANGES IN YOUNGER
PATIENTS, WELL BEFORE SIGNS OF
MEMORY LOSS.
WHAT DOCTORS SAY YOU SHOULD BE
LOOKING FOR.
>>> AND MAKING A DIFFERENCE.
BY OFFERING A FREE RIDE TO EVERY
STUDENT IN TOWN.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>> FROM NBC NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS
IS "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH BRIAN
WILLIAMS.
>>> GOOD EVENING, I'M LESTER
HOLT IN TONIGHT FOR BRIAN.
THE WHITE HOUSE ANNOUNCED LATE
THIS AFTERNOON THAT SYRIA'S
GOVERNMENT HAS CROSSED THE RED
LINE BY USING NERVE GAS AND
OTHER CHEMICAL WEAPONS AGAINST
THE OPPOSITION IN ITS ONGOING
CIVIL WAR, WITH FRESH
INTELLIGENCE IN HAND, IT
SAYS CONCLUDES SYRIA HAS USED
WEAPONS MULTIPLE TIMES IN THE
PAST YEAR, THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION SAID IT WOULD
BEGIN INCREASING MILITARY
ASSISTANCE TO THE SYRIAN
OPPOSITION.
BUT WHAT KIND OF SUPPORT IS
UNCLEAR AS IS JUST HOW DEEPLY
INVOLVED IN THE SYRIAN CRISIS
THIS U.S. IS PREPARED TO GET.
OUR WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENT
CHUCK TODD HAS MORE FOR US ON
THIS.
CHUCK?
>> GOOD EVENING, LESTER.
AFTER MONTHS OF INTERNAL
DELIBERATIONS, THE WHITE HOUSE
LATE TODAY ANNOUNCED ITS FIRST
SIGNIFICANT EFFORT TO TRY TO
INTERVENE IN THE SYRIAN CIVIL
WAR.
THE DECISION AFTER THE WHITE
HOUSE CONFIRMED ASSAD HAS BEEN
USING CHEMICAL WEAPONS AND AMONG
GROWING PUBLIC PRESSURE TO DO
MORE, FROM JOHN McCAIN ON THE
RIGHT TO BILL CLINTON ON THE
LEFT.
POUR MONTHS PRESIDENT OBAMA HAS
SAID BASHAR AL ASSAD'S USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS AGAINST HIS OWN
PEOPLE WOULD BE A RED LINE AND
WOULD LEAD TO A CHANGE OF
POLICY.
TODAY CONFIRMING THAT THE RED
LINE HAS INDEED BEEN CROSSED.
A NEW INTELLIGENCE ASSESSMENT
SHARED WITH CONGRESS AND KEY
U.S. ALLIES AROUND THE WORLD.
ASSAD HAS USED CHEMICAL WEAPONS,
NAMELY, SARIN GAS, ON A SMALL
SCALE, KILLING AS MANY AS 150
SYRIANS.
TODAY'S ASSESSMENT, A
CONFIRMATION OF A PRELIMINARY
INTELLIGENCE REPORT THAT THE
PRESIDENT SPOKE ABOUT LAST
APRIL.
>> WHAT WE HAVE RIGHT NOW IS AN
INTELLIGENCE ASSESSMENT.
AND AS I SAID, KNOWING THAT
POTENTIALLY CHEMICAL WEAPONS
HAVE BEEN USED, INSIDE OF SYRIA,
DOESN'T TELL US WHEN THEY WERE
USED, HOW THEY WERE USED,
OBTAINING CONFIRMATION AND
STRONG EVIDENCE, ALL OF THOSE
THINGS WE HAVE TO MAKE SURE WE
WORK ON WITH THE INTERNATIONAL
COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: SINCE THEN, THE
WHITE HOUSE DISCLOSED TODAY THAT
THEY HAVE BEEN QUIETLY RAMPING
UP SUPPORT FOR THE SYRIAN
OPPOSITION, SPECIFICALLY, A
GROUP CALLED THE SUPREME
MILITARY COUNCIL.
THE ASSISTANCE INCLUDES SOME
MILITARY SUPPORT AND THE WHITE
HOUSE PROMISED MORE DIRECT
MILITARY SUPPORT ON THE WAY, BUT
AIDES WOULD NOT DISCLOSE THE
SPECIFICS OF THE ARMS THE U.S.
IS SENDING.
THE WHITE HOUSE ALSO SAID
HEZBOLLAH'S INCREASED ROLE IN
HELPING ASSAD ADDED TO THE
PRESIDENT'S SENSE OF URGENCY TO
DO MORE.
REPUBLICAN SENATOR JOHN McCAIN,
WHO HAS BEEN A VOCAL CRITIC OF
MR. OBAMA'S SYRIAN POLICY RACED
TO THE SENATE FLOOR JUST BEFORE
THE WHITE HOUSE MADE ITS
ANNOUNCEMENT.
>> THE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES HAS BETTER UNDERSTAND
THAT JUST SUPPLYING WEAPONS,
HE'S NOT GOING TO CHANGE THE
EQUATION ON THE GROUND OR THE
BALANCE OF POWER.
>> Reporter: AS FOR ADDITIONAL
ASSISTANCE, WHITE HOUSE AIDES
SAY THOSE DECISIONS WILL BE MADE
AFTER CONSULTING CONGRESS.
AND THE PRESIDENT HEADS TO
NORTHERN IRELAND NEXT MONTH WITH
A MEETING WITH G-8.
ONE ADDITIONAL STEP COULD
INCLUDE A NO-FLY ZONE, SOMETHING
THE WHITE HOUSE WOULDN'T CONFIRM
TODAY.
>> CHUCK TODD, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO A FAST-MOVING AND
DANGEROUS SITUATION IN THE STATE
OF COLORADO.
HUNDREDS OF HOMES ARE NOW GONE
AS A WILDFIRE SPREADS OUT OF
CONTROL.
THE MOST HOMES DESTROYED BY A
SINGLE FIRE IN THE STATE'S
HISTORY.
TENS OF THOUSANDS EVACUATED AND
TONIGHT, OFFICIALS IN COLORADO
SPRINGS HAVE ORDERED A MANDATORY
EVACUATION FOR PART OF THE CITY.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER IS ON THE
FIRE LINES AGAIN TONIGHT.
GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
NOT JUST MASSIVE, THIS FIRE IS
VERY DESTRUCTIVE.
IT HAS TORCHED SOME 15,000
ACRES.
MORE EVACUATIONS ORDERED AS WIND
SPEEDS KICK UP AND THE BLAZE
GROWS.
THE BLACK FOREST FIRE, THE MOST
DESTRUCTIVE IN COLORADO HISTORY.
DEVOURING 360 HOMES AND
COUNTING.
>> GIVE ME SOME WATER!
>> THIS IS WHAT THE FIRE FIGHT
LOOKS LIKE TO A MILITARY GROUND
TEAM.
13,000 PROPERTIES ARE
THREATENED.
39,000 PEOPLE FORCED TO FLEE.
ROBERT SCHMID AMONG THEM.
>> WE WERE THE TYPICAL HOUSE
POOR.
WE BOUGHT THIS, THIS IS OUR
DREAM HOME IN THE FOREST AND
IT'S GONE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
NEIGHBORHOODS IN COLORADO
SPRINGS ARE BEING EVACUATED
BECAUSE OF SHIFTING WINDS.
THE MILITARY HAS JOINED THE
FIGHT ON THE GROUND AND IN THE
AIR.
HOT EMBERS ARE BEING CARRIED
THROUGH THE SKY FOR MILES,
IGNITING ROOFTOPS.
THE AIR ATTACK IN FIREFIGHTS
LIKE THIS ONE IS CRITICAL.
BUT FOR THIS HOME IT'S GOING TO
BE TOO LATE.
BUT AMID THE DESTRUCTION, CREWS
HAVE SAVED HUNDREDS OF HOMES.
>> I FEEL LIKE I'VE BEEN GIVEN A
MIRACLE.
I SAW THE VIDEO THAT WAS ON TV,
AND I'M LOOKING TOWARDS MY HOUSE
AND I SEE AN INFERNO.
>> Reporter: STILL, THIS FIRE IS
MORE DESTRUCTIVE THAN LAST
YEAR'S WALDO CANYON FIRE,
WHICH LEVELED 347 HOMES AND
CLAIMED 2 LIVES.
WITH FOUR MAJOR FIRES IN THE
STATE, THE GOVERNOR HAS DECLARED
A DISASTER.
$10 MILLION HAVE BEEN AUTHORIZED
TO HELP, DESPERATELY NEEDED
MONEY THAT COMES AS THE U.S.
FOREST SERVICE FACES CUTBACKS.
500 FEWER FIREFIGHTERS AND 50
FEWER ENGINES AVAILABLE.
>> THE FOREST SERVICE IS GOING
TO DO MORE WITH LESS.
WE'RE GOING TO MEET THE
CHALLENGE WITH LESS
FIREFIGHTERS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT IN COLORADO
SPRINGS, IT'S ALL AVAILABLE
HANDS ON DECK.
THIS MOVING MONSTER, A HISTORIC
FIRE THAT'S NOT DONE YET.
AND LESTER, LATE TONIGHT
BREAKING NEWS.
THE SHERIFF'S DEPARTMENT SAYS
THERE HAVE BEEN TWO FATALITIES
NOW CONNECTED TO THIS FIRE.
OFFICIALS TELL ME THAT THEY HAVE
DISCOVERED TWO BODIES INSIDE THE
BURN ZONE.
NO ADDITIONAL INFORMATION JUST
YET.
IT'S GOING TO BE A LONG NIGHT
FOR FIREFIGHTERS ON THE FRONT
LINE.
>> MIGUEL, THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> NOW TO THE MASSIVE WEATHER
SYSTEM THAT SPAWNED NEARLY 20
TORNADOES OVER THE PAST 24
HOURS, NOW MOVING TO THE EAST,
CREATING A DANGEROUS SITUATION
TONIGHT IN BIG METROPOLITAN
AREAS.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO IS FOLLOWING
IT ALL FROM WASHINGTON, WHERE
IT'S BEEN A WILD DAY.
TOM, GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: LESTER, WE'VE HAD
TORNADO WARNINGS IN D.C.,
MARYLAND AND VIRGINIA THROUGHOUT
THE DAY.
WE HAVE A REPORT OF A 4-YEAR-OLD
BEING HIT AND KILLED BY A
FALLING TREE IN VIRGINIA, A
WOMAN IN MARYLAND WHO WAS HIT BY
LIGHTNING TODAY, AND THERE HAS
BEEN AN AWFUL LOT OF DAMAGE.
THROUGHOUT THE DAY, THE OHIO
VALLEY AND MIDATLANTIC HAVE BEEN
IN THE TARGET ZONE AS SEVERAL
LINES OF POWERFUL STORMS WITH
HIGH WINDS TOOK AIM AT THE
REGION, TOSSING CARS AND TEARING
APT BUILDINGS.
THIS AFTERNOON, DARK CLOUDS AND
HEAVY RAIN ROLLED INTO
WASHINGTON.
THIS IS TRAVELING OUT OF THE
WEST, DIRECTLY TOWARD MONTGOMERY
COUNTY AND TOWARD WASHINGTON,
D.C.
BRINGING WATERSPOUT AND TORNADO
WARNINGS.
>> I MEAN, IT IS THERE.
GET INSIDE IMMEDIATELY IF YOU'RE
OUT AND AROUND THAT AREA.
>> Reporter: THESE STORMS FIRST
BEGAN POPPING UP LAST NIGHT,
BRINGING DAMAGES WINDS AND HEAVY
RAIN.
IN WORTH COUNTY, IOWA, A
TERRIFYING 45 MINUTES AS
FIREFIGHTERS WORKED TO RESCUE A
CHILD AND TWO ADULTS FROM A
SUBMERGED SUV.
WITHOUT WARNING, THE CHILD'S
SAFETY LINE SUDDENLY DIPPED
BELOW THE SURFACE OF THE WATER.
>> THE VEHICLE WENT OFF THE ROAD
INTO A -- A FLOODED DITCH.
SEVERAL DIFFERENT FIRE
DEPARTMENTS WORKED TOGETHER AND
WERE ABLE TO RESCUE.
>> Reporter: RESCUERS SAY ALL
THREE SHOULD BE OKAY.
ALREADY MORE THAN A DOZEN
REPORTS OF TORNADOES AND PLENTY
OF LIGHTNING.
THE WILLIS TOWER IN CHICAGO TOOK
A DIRECT HIT LAST NIGHT.
EARLIER TODAY, AS THE STORMS
MOVED THROUGH PENNSYLVANIA AND
NEW JERSEY, MORE THAN 1,000
RECORDED LIGHTNING STRIKES,
EVERY 15 MINUTES.
THIS MORNING, IN MARYLAND,
POWERFUL STORMS BEGAN PULLING
DOWN TREES.
IN OHIO, HAIL BATTERED CARS AND
IN PENNSYLVANIA, HEAVY RAIN AT
THE U.S. OPEN DELAYED PLAY.
THROUGHOUT THE DAY, AIRPORTS
FROM D.C. TO NEW YORK, CANCELED
OR DELAYED THEIR TAKEOFFS AND
LANDINGS AS THE STRONG LINE OF
SUMMER THUNDERSTORMS TOOK THEIR
TOLL.
THE LATEST NUMBERS WE HAVE,
ABOUT 664,000 PEOPLE WITHOUT
POWER.
THAT'S IN VIRGINIA AND MARYLAND
FOR THE MOST PART.
ALSO ON THE DELMARVA PENINSULA.
ALL EYES ARE GOING TO BE ON
THESE SKIES TONIGHT TO SEE WHAT
HAPPENS WITH THE WIND AND THE
RAIN.
LESTER?
>> THE THREAT INCLUDES A BIG
PART OF THE COUNTRY, INCLUDING
MAJOR POPULATION CENTERS,
METEOROLOGIST CHRIS WARREN
IS TRACKING THE STORM FROM
WEATHER CHANNEL HEADQUARTERS.
HI, CHRIS.
>> GOOD EVENING TO YOU, LESTER.
THESE STORMS ARE STILL STRONG
AND STILL DANGEROUS AS WE'RE
TRACKING THEM RIGHT NOW.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK WHERE CLOUDS
AND RAIN ARE RIGHT NOW.
IT'S A LINE OF STORMS THAT WE'RE
LOOKING AT HERE, AND THIS IS
OVER THE PAST FEW HOURS HERE
THIS AFTERNOON AND THE EVENING.
STILL A CHANCE FOR DAMAGING
WINDS, WHICH COULD LEAD TO DOWN
TREES AND POWER LINES.
ALSO LARGE HAIL, AND POSSIBLY A
FEW TORNADOES.
NOW WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A LOOK
AND SHOW YOU WHAT THE RADAR IS
GOING TO LOOK LIKE TONIGHT.
SO THIS IS THE FUTURE RADAR.
AND AS WE GO THROUGH TIME HERE
DURING THE OVERNIGHT HOURS,
YOU'RE GOING TO SEE THINGS
REALLY CLEAR OUT.
WE'RE GOING TO WATCH THESE
STORMS MOVE OUT BY TONIGHT, AND
THEN TOMORROW MUCH MORE ON THE
WAY OF IMPROVEMENT.
THE NORTHEAST A FEW SHOWERS
EXPECTED.
AND LESTER, IN COLORADO, AFTER A
WEEK OF RECORD TEMPERATURES WITH
HIGHS IN THE 90s, STILL NO
SIGNIFICANT RELIEF FOR
FIREFIGHTERS IN SIGHT.
>> CHRIS WARREN, THANK YOU.
>>> AN IMPORTANT DECISION FROM
THE SUPREME COURT TODAY THAT IS
LOOK LIKELY TO INFLUENCE THE
EMERGING FIELD OF GENETIC
MEDICINE AND MAKE SOME MEDICAL
TESTS CHEAPER.
THE ISSUE IS WHETHER PARTS OF
THE HUMAN BODY, INDIVIDUAL GENES
COULD BE OWNED BY A PATENTED
COMPANY.
PETE WILLIAMS HAS MORE ON THIS
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THE COURT'S
DECISION INVOLVES THE MEDICAL
TESTS THAT ACTRESS ANGELINA
JOLIE TOOK BEFORE DECIDING
UNDERGO A DOUBLE MASTECTOMY LAST
MONTH.
>> I FEEL GREAT.
I FEEL WONDERFUL, AND I'M VERY,
VERY GRATEFUL FOR ALL THE
SUPPORT.
IT'S BEEN AWESOME.
>> Reporter: THE TEST DETECTS
MUTATIONS IN TWO GENES THAT CAN
PREDICT HIGHER RATES OF BREAST
AND OVARIAN CANCERS.
ONLY ONE COMPANY PERFORMS IT,
MYRIAD GENETICS OF UTAH.
AFTER DISCOVERING WHICH OF THE
BODY'S TWO GENES CAN SIGNAL A
CANCER RISK, IT WAS GIVEN A
PATENT ON THE ACTUAL GENES.
ELIZABETH OF MASSACHUSETTS WAS
AMONG THOSE SUING, CLAIMING
MYRIAD'S MONOPOLY MADE THE TEST
TOO EXPENSIVE.
>> MY GENETIC COUNSELOR AT THE
TIME TOLD ME THAT MY HEALTH
INSURANCE WOULD NOT COVER THE
GENETIC TESTING.
>> Reporter: TODAY A UNANIMOUS
SUPREME COURT SAID MYRIAD WAS
NOT ELIGIBLE FOR A PATENT
BECAUSE IT DID NOT CREATE
ANYTHING.
A HUMAN GENE, THE COURT SAID, IS
A PRODUCT OF NATURE AND CANNOT
BE PATENTED.
IN RESPONSE, MYRIAD SAYS ENOUGH
OF ITS OTHER PATENTS SURVIVED TO
PROTECT ITS TESTS FROM
COMPETITION, BUT THE DECISION
FREES UP GENES FOR MORE RESEARCH
AND FOR OTHER COMPANIES TO TRY
OFFERING A CANCER SCREENING TEST
OF ITS OWN.
>> A GOOD DAY FOR PATIENT
ADVOCATES AND INDIVIDUAL
PATIENTS THAT ARE LOOKING FOR
ACCESS TO CHEAPER AND
ALTERNATIVE TESTS.
WHEN YOU DON'T HAVE A MONOPOLY
ON THE GENE, YOU CAN'T STOP
COMPETITORS FROM COMING IN.
>> Reporter: MYRIAD'S
CHALLENGERS SAY THE RULE COG
ALSO CREATE MORE COMPETITION IN
TESTS FOR NEUROMUSCULAR AND
HEART DISEASES, AND COULD
STIMULATE MORE RESEARCH TO FIND
OTHER HUMAN GENES LINKED TO
SPECIFIC DISEASES.
STILL TO COME RULING ABOUTS ON
SAME-SEX MARRIAGE, THE FUTURE OF
AFFIRMATIVE ACTION, AND THE
VOTING RIGHTS ACT.
THE NEXT DAY FOR DECISIONS IS
THIS COMING MONDAY.
PETE WILLIAMS AT THE SUPREME
COURT.
>>> NEW DEMANDS FROM CONGRESS
TODAY FOR AN EXPLANATION OF
BROAD GOVERNMENT SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAMS ARE NECESSARY.
A WEEK AFTER THE EXISTENCE OF
THE PROGRAMS WAS LEAKED, GENERAL
KEITH ALEXANDER, THE HEAD OF THE
NSA SAID THE GOVERNMENT WOULD
RELEASE MORE INFORMATION ABOUT
THEM, AND ALSO NEW DETAILS ABOUT
SPECIFIC TERRORIST PLOTS.
FOR HIS PART, FBI DIRECTOR
ROBERT MUELLER SAYS THE LEAKS BY
A FORMER GOVERNMENT CONTRACTOR
HAVE CAUSED SIGNIFICANT HARM TO
THE SAFETY OF AMERICANS, AND HE
SAID TERRORISTS WILL ADJUST
THEIR TACTICS.
>>> AT LEAST ONE PERSON HAS BEEN
KILLED AND DOZENS MORE HURT,
SOME OF THEM CRITICALLY, AFTER A
MASSIVE EXPLOSION AT A CHEMICAL
PLANT IN LOUISIANA.
AN EMPLOYEE CAUGHT THE MOMENT OF
IMPACT ON CAMERA AS WORKERS RAN
FOR THEIR LIVES.
THE FIRE BURNED FOR HOURS.
IT'S NOW OUT, AND OFFICIALS SAY
EVERYONE HAS BEEN ACCOUNTED FOR.
EARLY TESTS DID NOT INDICATE
DANGEROUS LEVELS OF CHEMICALS IN
THE AIR.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT, A BIG
SPIKE IN A DIFFERENT FORM OF
DEMENTIA THAN WE'RE USED TO
SEEING.
MEMORY LOSS ISN'T THE FIRST RED
FLAG.
UNUSUAL WARNING SIGNS DOCTORS
ARE SEEING NOW IN YOUNGER
PATIENTS.
>>> AND, LATER, WHICH AIRLINES
ARE BEST AT GETTING YOU THERE ON
TIME AND WHICH ARE STRUGGLING TO
KEEP UP.
THE NEW NUMBERS ARE OUT.
WE'LL TELL THEM TO YOU.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH HEALTH NEWS
AND A DISEASE THAT IS
INCREASINGLY BEING RECOGNIZED.
IT'S A DETERIORATION OF THE
BRAIN THAT IS DIFFERENT FROM
ALZHEIMER'S AND CAUSES DIFFERENT
PROBLEMS.
BUT AS NBC'S CHIEF SCIENCE
CORRESPONDENT ROBERT BAZELL
REPORTS, IT STILL CAUSES
PEOPLE'S LIVES TO SLIP AWAY.
>> Reporter: TWO YEARS AGO,
62-YEAR-OLD BARBARA WHITMARCH
WAS A HIGHLY REGARDED SCIENTIST
AT THE NATIONAL INSTITUTES OF
HEALTH.
SHE AND HUSBAND JOHN MARRIED 30
YEARS, HAD RAISED SIX CHILDREN.
>> WHAT DID YOU HAVE FOR
BREAKFAST?
>> Reporter: THEN JOHN BEGAN TO
NOTICE CHANGES.
>> HER ABILITY TO FEEL EMPATHY,
HER PERSONALITY JUST DISAPPEARED
OVER A PERIOD OF TIME.
THAT'S THE HARDEST PART OF THIS
DISEASE.
I WOULD ASK HER, IS ANYTHING
WRONG?
SHE WOULD SAY NO, I LOVE YOU,
EVERYTHING IS FINE.
BUT SHE WASN'T THERE.
AND SHE SAID IT IN THAT FLAT
WAY.
>> Reporter: JOHN, ALSO A
SCIENTIST, WAS WORRIED AND ASKED
HER TO SEE A PSYCHIATRIST.
ULTIMATELY, SHE WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH FRONT TEMP ROLL DEMENTIA,
OR FTD, A DISEASE THAT STRIKES A
DIFFERENT PART OF THE BRAIN THAN
ALZHEIMER'S.
>> THERE'S A HUGE LOSS OF
TISSUE.
>> Reporter: IT DOESN'T START
WITH MEMORY PROBLEMS, BUT WITH
PERSONALITY CHANGES.
>> IT'S A TRAGIC PROBLEM,
BECAUSE OFTEN THE FIRST
MANIFESTATIONS OF THE DISEASE
ARE BAD JUDGMENTS, A DISRUPTION
OF FAMILY INFRASTRUCTURE
HAPPENS.
>> Reporter: NOW BARBARA LIVES
IN A LOCKED NURSING HOME.
SHE MOVES COMPULSIVELY AND
CONSTANTLY.
>> DO YOU KNOW HOW OLD I'LL BE?
ROAR SHE SELDOM RECOGNIZES JOHN
OR THEIR CHILDREN AND RARELY
SPEAKS.
UNTIL RECENTLY DOCTORS THOUGHT
FTD WAS RARE, BUT THAT VIEW IS
CHANGING.
>> WE'RE STARTING TO REALIZE
THAT FRONTAL DEMENTIA IS MORE
COMMON IN PEOPLE THAN PEOPLE
WITH ALZHEIMER'S DISEASE UNDER
THE AGE OF 60.
>> Reporter: BEFORE HER ILLNESS,
BARBARA WATCHED HER WEIGHT
CLOSELY.
SHE HAS GAINED 30 POUNDS IN A
YEAR.
>> FOOD IS PROBABLY CENTRAL TO
HER THINKING, HER BEHAVIOR, HER
WALKING.
SHE FORAGES, IF YOU WILL.
>> Reporter: THERE IS NO
TREATMENT FOR FTD.
VICTIMS' BRAINS CONTINUE
DETERIORATING AND THEY DIE
WITHIN YEARS.
NOT ONLY IS FTD FAR MORE COMMON
THAN MOST PEOPLE REALIZE,
STUDYING IT COULD PROVIDE CLUES
TO OTHER IMPORTANT CONDITIONS,
INCLUDING LOU GEHRIG'S DISEASE
AND HUNTINGDON'S DISEASE.
>> GIVE ME A KISS, SOMETHING.
>> Reporter: AND JUST AS
IMPORTANT, THEY SAY, MORE
AWARENESS OF THE DISEASE COULD
SPARE FAMILIES OF VICTIMS THE
PAIN OF BELIEVING THEIR LOVED
ONES NO LONGER CARE.
ROBERT BAZELL, NBC NEWS,
SACRAMENTO.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
A BIG CHANGE TO SOMETHING THAT
HAS BEEN AN AMERICAN TRADITION
FOR CENTURIES.
For our families...
our neighbors...
and our communities...
America's beverage companies
have created...
a wide range of new choices.
Developing smaller portion sizes
and more..
low and no-calorie
beverages...
adding clear calorie labels so
you know...
exactly what you're choosing...
and in schools, replacing
full-calorie soft drinks...
with lower-calorie options.
With more choices and fewer
calories...
America's Beverage Companies are
delivering.
>>> THE CENSUS IS TELLING US A
LOT ABOUT WHO WE ARE AS A PEOPLE
AND THE RAPIDLY CHANGING MAKEUP
OF OUR POPULATION.
WE LEARNED TODAY THAT LAST YEAR,
MORE NON-HISPANIC WHITE
AMERICANS DIED THAN WERE BORN.
THAT GROUP IS STILL THE NATION'S
LARGEST, BUT IT HAS BEEN
SHRINKING FOR YEARS.
AND FOR THE FIRST TIME, MINORITY
GROUPS NOW ACCOUNT FOR ABOUT
HALF OF AMERICAN CHILDREN UNDER
THE AGE OF 5.
IN 2012, THE HISPANIC POPULATION
GREW THE MOST IN SHEER NUMBERS.
BUT THE ASIAN POPULATION FOR THE
FIRST TIME IS NOW THE FASTEST
GROWING POPULATION IN THE
COUNTRY.
>>> THE LATEST REPORT CARD ON
HOW AIRLINES ARE DOING IS OUT.
IT'S FOR APRIL AND OVERALL, IT
SHOWS BELOW-AVERAGE PERFORMANCE.
FIRST, THE GOOD NEWS.
THE BEST PERFORMERS WERE
HAWAIIAN AIRLINES, ALASKA
AIRLINES, AND DELTA, WITH
ON-TIME ARRIVALS ABOVE 85%.
THE WORST PERFORMERS WERE
AMERICAN EAGLE, WHICH WAS ON
TIME JUST UNDER 67% OF THE TIME,
FOLLOWED BY FRONTIER AND
EXPRESSJET.
AND AMONG AIRPORTS, PASSENGERS
WERE MOST LIKELY TO BE DELAYED
FLYING INTO NEWARK.
>>> NOW HEAR THIS.
THE U.S. NAVY RETROFITTING THE
WAY IT COMMUNICATES FROM A
SYSTEM THAT HAS BEEN AROUND FROM
THE OLD TELETYPE DAYS TO E-MAIL.
AS PART OF THE CHANGE, THE
SERVICE SAID IN A MEMO THAT IT'S
NOT NECESSARY ANYMORE TO LIMIT
NAVY MESSAGES ENTIRELY TO UPPER
CASE, AND THAT ALL NAVY COMMANDS
ARE AUTHORIZED TO USE STANDARD
MIXED-CASE CHARACTERS.
THAT'S UPPER AND LOWER CASE.
BUT TRADITION IS HARD TO CHANGE,
AND AS YOU CAN SEE, THE
ANNOUNCEMENT ITSELF WAS IN ALL
CAPS.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
OUR "MAKING A DIFFERENCE"
REPORT.
ONE CITY'S HISTORIC PROMISE KEPT
TO EVERY KID IN TOWN.
>>> MAKING A DIFFERENCE, BROUGHT
TO YOU BY ALKA SELZER FRUIT
CHEWS.
FOR FAST HEARTBURN RELIEF.
>>> AS STUDENTS AND PARENTS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY WORRY ABOUT
PAYING FOR COLLEGE, IT'S WORTH
LOOKING AT THE EXPERIENCE OF
LOOKING AT ONE CITY WHERE
EVERYONE WHO GRADUATES FROM HIGH
SCHOOL GETS A SCHOLARSHIP.
IT'S ABOUT MONEY, YES, BUT ALSO
ABOUT DREAMS, AND IT'S TONIGHT'S
"MAKING A DIFFERENCE" REPORT.
FROM JOHN YANG IN MICHIGAN.
>> Reporter: SHANNON WIE
GRADUATED FROM KALAMAZOO'S ROY
NORRIS HIGH SCHOOL WITH 75% OF
HER TUITION AT MICHIGAN STATE
UNIVERSITY PAID.
>> JADE KAYLA HUBBARD.
>> Reporter: 95% OF HER TUITION
AT UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN PAID.
SINCE 2005, EVERY STUDENT WHO
SPENDS FOUR YEARS IN A KALAMAZOO
PUBLIC HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES
WITH AT LEAST 65% OF THEIR
TUITION AT ANY PUBLIC COLLEGE IN
MICHIGAN PAID.
>> THAT IS AWESOME.
THAT IS THE GREATEST.
>> Reporter: FUNDED BY ANONYMOUS
DONORS, THE KALAMAZOO PROMISE IS
ONE OF THE MOST GENEROUS
SCHOLARSHIP PROGRAMS IN AMERICA.
FULL RIDES FOR GRADUATING
SENIORS WHO START AS
KINDERGARTNERS.
LESS IF THEY START LATER.
>> APART FROM USING ENGLISH AS A
MOTIVATION TO WRITE --
>> Reporter: JADE HUBBARD, WHO
WANTS TO STUDY SCIENCE OR
TECHNOLOGY, WILL BE THE FIRST IN
HER FAMILY TO GO DO COLLEGE.
>> IT AFFECTED MY GRADES, HOW I
ACTED, BECAUSE I KNEW I WOULD
HAVE A FUTURE.
>> Reporter: SO FAR THE PROGRAM
HAS PAID $44 MILLION IN TUITION
FOR 2800 STUDENTS.
AND THE MONEY WILL NEVER END.
DONORS DESIGNED IT TO LAST
FOREVER.
>> SO YOU STILL WANT TO BE A
DOCTOR?
>> Reporter: MICHAEL RICE IS
SUPERINTENDENT OF KALAMAZOO
SCHOOLS.
>> WHAT WE'VE LEARNED IS THE
PROMISE DOESN'T COME FREE, THAT
KIDS HAVE TO EARN IT.
THEY HAVE TO EARN IT EVERY DAY.
>> WHERE ARE THEY GOING?
>> Reporter: STUDENTS SEEM TO BE
STEPPING UP.
ENROLLMENT IN ADVANCED PLACEMENT
CLASSES, READING AND MATH TEST
SCORES AND GRADUATION RATES, ALL
ON THE RISE, AND THEY'RE
STARTING EARLY.
THESE THIRD GRADERS HAVE BIG
DREAMS.
>> I WANT TO BE A VETERINARIAN.
>> I WANT TO BE AN INVENTOR.
>> I WANT TO BE A POLICE
OFFICER.
>> YOUNG ZACH JULIAN HAD DREAMS
TOO.
THIS FALL HE'LL STUDY
ENGINEERING AT WAYNE STATE
UNIVERSITY, HIS TUITION FULLY
PAID.
>> I JUST NEED TO DO WELL.
I CAN'T LET THE PEOPLE DOWN.
>> Reporter: EVEN THOUGH YOU
DON'T KNOW WHO THEY ARE?
>> I DON'T KNOW WHO THEY ARE.
I JUST CAN'T LET THEM DOWN.
>> Reporter: ZACHARY'S DONORS
PROVIDING THE MONEY AND THE
MOTIVATIONS TO MAKE DREAMS COME
TRUE.
JOHN YANG, KALAMAZOO, MICHIGAN.
>> THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR
THURSDAY NIGHT, THANK YOU FOR
BEING WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
SANTA CLARA COUNTY WANTS ITS
MONEY BACK FROM ITS EMPLOYEES.
IT IS DEMANDING THE TOP PAID
ATTORNEYS IN THE D.A.'S OFFICE
WHO GOT HUNDREDS OF HOURS OF
FREE TIME OFF.
THEY WANT THAT PAY BACK.
IT COMES AFTER OUR INVESTIGATIVE
UNIT EXPOSED THE D.A. JEFF ROSEN
HANDING OUT THE UNAUTHORIZED
DAYS OFF.
THE INVESTIGATIVE REPORT HE
BROKE THAT STORY AND JOINS US
NOW WITH THE NEW DETAILS.
>> THEY SENT THIS LETTER TO THE
ASSOCIATION CALLING WHAT THE
D.A. DID A SECRET ACTION AND THE
TIMEOFF AN INAPPROPRIATE
GIVEAWAY.
NOW HIS OFFICE IS DEMANDING
ATTORNEYS PAY UP OR POSSIBLY
FACE AN INVESTIGATION.
THE MESSAGE IS CHEER.
PAY IT BACK.
>> IT IS IMPORTANT FOR US TO
CORRECT THIS PROBLEM.
>> FOR A YEAR AND A HALF, TO
HAVE PAID ATTORNEYS WERE
SECRETLY GIVEN FREE TIME OFF.
NOW THE COUNTY IS DEMANDING IT
BE RETURNED.
>> CERTAINLY IT WASN'T THE
INTENT OF THE CONTRACT.
SO I DON'T THINK IT WAS A VERY
WISE STEP TO TAKE.
>> IT COMES TWO MONTHS AFTER WE
EXPOSE D.A. JEFF ROSEN DEMAND
TIME SHEETS BE ALTERED, CHANGING
HUNDREDS OF VACATION AND SICK
TIME HOURS.
THEY BANKED TO IT USE OR CASH
OUT LATER.
ROSEN TOLD US IN APRIL IT WAS TO
MAKE UP FOR A 5% BONUS.
>> I DIRECTED THIS TO HAPPEN.
I WANTED THIS TO HAPPEN.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT I WANTED TO
HA