>> THANK YOU.
LESTER HOLT JOINS US NOW FROM
SOUTH KOREA.
THANKS FOR TUNING IN.
>> SEE YOU BACK HERE AT 6:00.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> TONIGHT, CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
CHILDREN GASPING FOR
AIR, ASSAD BLAMED FOR
A GRISLY MASSACRE ON
HIS OWN PEOPLE.
ONE OF THE DEADLIEST
OF ITS KIND IN SYRIA'S
SIX YEARS CIVIL WAR.
>>> RUSSIAN
INVESTIGATION
DIVERSIONS, FIRST THE
WIRETAP CLAIM WITHOUT
EVIDENCE, NOW THE
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
ACCUSES OBAMA'S
NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISOR OF DIRTY
TRICKS.
SUSAN RICE FIRES BACK
ONLY TO NBC NEWS.
>>> ADVERTISERS REVOLT
ON BILL O'REILLY.
AT LEAST A DOZEN
COMPANIES PULL THEIR
ADS FOLLOWING
COMPLAINTS OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT.
>>> INTERNET PRIVACY
RULES ROLLED BACK,
INTERNET PROVIDERS
ALLOWED TO SELL YOUR
BROWSING HISTORY
WITHOUT YOUR
PERMISSION.
TONIGHT, HOW TO SHIELD
YOUR INFORMATION.
>>> FRONT LINES HERE
IN SOUTH KOREA WITH
THE AMERICANS THAT
COULD BE CALLED INTO
ACTION.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>> Announcer: THIS IS
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
WITH LESTER HOLT,
REPORTING TONIGHT FROM
SOUTH KOREA.
>>> GOOD EVENING TO
OUR VIEWERS IN THE
WEST.
WE ARE ONCE AGAIN IN
THE AIRBASE IN SOUTH
KOREA.
WHERE WE
LEARNED MOMENTS AGO
FROM SOUTH KOREAN
OFFICIALS, THEY HAVE
FILED A MISSILE INTO
THE's SEA, ALSO KNOWN
AS THE SEA OF JAPAN.
AS WE TOLD YOU THOSE
LAUNCHES ARE
IDENTIFIED AND TRACKED
AND IDENTIFIED ON THIS
BASE.
THIS MOVE HIGHLIGHTS
HOW TENSE THINGS ARE
IN THIS REGION AND WHY
AMERICANS REMAIN IN A
HIGH STATE OF
READINESS.
WE SPENT TIME WITH
SOME TODAY AND MORE ON
THEIR TRAINING IN JUST
A MOMENT.
>>> AND ANOTHER
TROUBLE SPOT OVERSEAS,
SYRIA, THE WORLD
REACTING WITH HORROR
AND REVULSION TO THE
APPARENT POISON GAS
ATTACK THAT KILLED
DOZENS OF CIVILIANS
AND SICKENED DOZENS
MORE, MANY SMALL
CHILDREN.
THE WHITE HOUSE
TONIGHT POINTING THE
FINGER OF BLAME TO
SYRIAN PRESIDENT
ASSAD, ALSO CALLING
OUT THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION,
SUGGESTING IF IT STOOD
UP TO ASSAD DURING ITS
WATCH, THIS MIGHT NOT
HAVE HAPPENED.
NOW, IS PRESIDENT
TRUMP WILLING TO STEP
IN?
A WORD OF CAUTION.
THERE ARE UPSETTING
IMAGES IN THIS REPORT.
RICHARD ENGEL HAS THE
LATEST.
>> Reporter: THESE
DISTURBING IMAGES
TAKEN JUST AFTER THE
EXPLOSION.
WITNESSES SAY IT WAS A
CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACK.
IN THE VIDEO IT
APPEARS TO BEAR ALL
THE HALLMARKS.
THIS BOY, USING ALL
HIS STRENGTH JUST TO
BREATHE.
FIRST RESPONDERS
DOUSED THE VICTIMS
WITH WATER AND
STRIPPED OFF THEIR
CLOTHES TO WASH OFF
WHAT THEY SAID WAS A
CHEMICAL WEAPON.
MEDICS AND VOLUNTEERS
IN THIS REBEL
CONTROLLED PART OF
SYRIA RUSHED THE
INJURED TO LOCAL
CLINICS, THEY CLAIM
SYRIAN PRESIDENT
BASHAR AL ASSAD'S
REGIME FIRED WITH A
CHEMICAL NERVE AGENT
BANNED, SARIN.
>> NO ONE IS DOING
ANYTHING TO STOP THESE
DEATH ATTACKS.
>> Reporter: OTHER
VICTIMS WERE TAKEN TO
A MAKESHIFT CLINIC
BUILT IN A CAVE TO
PROTECT IT.
THERE, A FATHER KISSED
HIS DAUGHTER GOOD-BYE.
NEARBY, THIS ACTIVIST
WAS RECORDING WHAT HE
WAS SEEING, SAYING
WARPLANES WERE STILL
OVERHEAD, THEN --
HOSPITALS ARE OFTEN
TARGETED IN THIS WAR
THAT RESPECTS NO
CONVENTIONS.
AMAZINGLY, THE
ACTIVIST SURVIVED.
IN 2013, THE U.S.
THREATENED WAR WHEN
MORE THAN 1,000 PEOPLE
WERE KILLED IN ANOTHER
ALLEGED CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
PRESIDENT OBAMA HAD
WARNED THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS WOULD
CROSS A RED LINE.
BUT WHEN RUSSIA
BROKERED A DEAL, A
U.S. MILITARY RESPONSE
NEVER CAME.
IN A STATEMENT ON
TODAY'S ATTACK,
PRESIDENT TRUMP SAID
THESE HEINOUS ACTIONS
BY THE BASHAR AL ASSAD
REGIME ARE A
CONSEQUENCE OF THE
PAST ADMINISTRATION'S
WEAKNESS.
A U.S. INTELLIGENCE
OFFICIAL TELLS NBC
NEWS TONIGHT WHILE
DETAILS ARE STILL
COMING IN IT APPEARS
THIS WAS ACTUALLY A
CHEMICAL ATTACK.
THE SYRIAN ARMY DENIES
IT USED CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
LESTER.
>> RICHARD ENGEL
TONIGHT, THANK YOU.
>>> TURNING BACK HOME
TO THE DRAMA OVER THE
RUSSIAN INVESTIGATION
AND WHAT CRITICS ARE
CALLING REPEATED
ATTEMPTS BY PRESIDENT
TRUMP AND THE WHITE
HOUSE TO DEFLECT
ATTENTION AWAY FROM
IT.
THEIR LATEST TARGET,
FORMER NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISOR,
SUSAN RICE.
RICE IS FIRING BACK
EXCLUSIVELY TO NNS
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL.
>> Reporter: FOR MORE
THAN A MONTH IT'S BEEN
THE TWEET THAT LOOMED
OVER THE PRESIDENT
WITHOUT ANY EVIDENCE
MR. TRUMP TWEETING
TERRIBLE.
JUST FOUND OUT OBAMA
HAD MY WIRED TAPPED IN
TRUMP TOWER, A CHARGE
IMMEDIATELY SHOT DOWN
BY REPUBLICANS.
HAVE YOU SEEN ANY
EVIDENCE TRUMP TOWER
WAS WIRETAPPED?
>> SEEN NO EVIDENCE
WHATSOEVER.
>> NO SUCH WIRETAP
EXISTED.
>> Reporter: EVEN A
RARE REBUKE FROM THE
FBI DIRECTOR.
>> I HAVE NO
INFORMATION THAT
SUPPORTS THOSE TWEETS.
>> Reporter: JAMES
COMEY DROPPING A
BOMBSHELL THEY ARE
INVESTIGATING WHETHER
THERE WAS HACKING AND
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
CHAIRMAN, DEVIN NUNES
CLAIMING HE HAS SEEN
INTEL TRUMP TRANSITION
OFFICIALS WERE SWEPT
UP IN LEGAL
SURVEILLANCE LEADING
THE PRESIDENT TO SAY
HE FELT VINDICATED.
>> I SOMEWHAT DO, I
MUST TELL YOU, I
SOMEWHAT DO.
>> Reporter: NUNES
WALKS BACK HIS CHARGE
AND THE "NEW YORK
TIMES" REPORTS THE
INFORMATION HE USED
CAME FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE.
TONIGHT, A NEW FOCUS,
WHITE HOUSE GOING
AFTER OBAMA NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISOR SUSAN
RICE FOR REQUESTING
THE NAMES OF TRUMP
OFFICIALS ACCIDENTALLY
COLLECTED BY
SURVEILLANCE BE
REVEALED OR UNMASKED.
RICE RESPONDING TO US
EXCLUSIVELY TONIGHT.
>> WE ONLY DO IT TO
PROTECT THE AMERICAN
PEOPLE TO DO OUR JOBS
IN THE NATIONAL
SECURITY ROOM.
>> Reporter: NOW,
SHE'S UNDER FIRE FROM
REPUBLICAN CRITICS.
>> I BELIEVE SUSAN
RICE ABUSED THIS
SYSTEM AND SHE DID IT
FOR POLITICAL
PURPOSES.
SHE NEEDS TO BE
BROUGHT IN AND
QUESTIONED UNDER OATH.
>> DID YOU SEEK THE
NAMES OF PEOPLE
INVOLVED TO UNMASK THE
INVOLVED IN THE TRUMP
TRANSITION, TRUMP
CAMPAIGN IN ORDER TO
SPY ON THEM?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
ABSOLUTELY NOT, FOR
ANY POLITICAL
PURPOSES, TO SPY,
EXPOSE, ANYTHING, BUT
LET ME --
>> DID YOU LEAK THE
NAME OF MIKE FLYNN?
>> I LEAKED NOTHING TO
NOBODY AND NEVER HAVE
AND NEVER WOULD.
>> Reporter: FORMER
INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS
SAY ALL THIS TAKES
CRITICAL FOCUS AWAY
FROM THE RUSSIA
INVESTIGATION.
>> I THINK IT IS A
DISTRACTION TO GO DOWN
ALL OF THESE OTHER
ALLEYS.
IT WON'T IN THE END
LEAD TO AN ANSWER TO
THE PRIMARY QUESTION.
>> TONIGHT, MEMBERS OF
THE HOUSE CAUTION THE
WITNESS COMMITTEE SAY
RICE IS LIKELY TO BE
CALLED AS A WITNESS IN
A WIDELY HIGHLY
POLITICIZED
INVESTIGATION.
LESTER.
>> ANDREA MITCHELL.
>>> TONIGHT, AFTER
BEING LEFT FOR DEAD IN
CONGRESS, THE WHITE
HOUSE IS TRYING TO
REVIVE PLAN TO REPEAL
AND REPLACE OBAMACARE.
IT COMES AFTER
PRESIDENT TRUMP
PONDERED LEAVING
OBAMACARE TO, IN HIS
WORDS, TO EXPLODE, HIS
ADMINISTRATION IS
TRYING AGAIN TO REACH
A DEAL.
HOW FAR ARE THEY
WILLING TO GO TO WIN
OVER HOLDOUT
REPUBLICANS.
HALLIE JACKSON HAS
DETAILS.
>> Reporter: VICE
PRESIDENT PENCE TODAY,
RALLYING REPUBLICANS
TO RESURRECT A
HEALTHCARE DEAL, A NEW
FRAMEWORK RISING FROM
THE ASHES LESS THAN
TWO WEEKS AFTER THE
ORIGINAL CRASHED AND
BURNED.
>> THE PRESIDENT AND I
REMAIN CONFIDENT
WORKING WITH THE
CONGRESS WE WILL
REPEAL AND REPLACE
OBAMACARE.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S
THE STRATEGY NOW?
OFFER TO LET STATES
ASK PERMISSION FROM
THE GOVERNMENT TO
ALLOW INSURERS TO
CHARGE SICK PEOPLE
MORE MONEY, TO KEEP
COSTS LOWER FOR
HEALTHIER PEOPLE.
NO ONE COULD BE DENIED
INSURANCE OUTRIGHT BUT
IT MAY EFFECTIVELY GUT
THE PROMISE FOR
PROTECTION OF PEOPLE
WITH PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS.
>> I THINK IT'S A HAIL
MARY PASS TO BRING
THIS LEGISLATION BACK
AND WILL BE A MORE
RADICAL PROPOSAL THAN
THE FIRST ONE.
>> Reporter: IT'S A
NOD TO THE POLITICAL
PRESSURE REPUBLICANS
FACE TO DO SOMETHING
ON HEALTHCARE AND
OLIVE BRANCH TO THE
HOLDOUTS IN THE
CONSERVATIVE FREEDOM
CAUCUS LED BY
CONGRESSMAN MARK
MEADOWS.
>> I CAN TELL YOU
NEGOTIATIONS ARE GOING
ON AT AN EXTREMELY
FAST CLIP.
IS THERE A VOTE
SCHEDULED?
NO.
IS THERE EVEN A
CONSENSUS A VOTE
SHOULD BE SCHEDULED?
NO.
>> I DON'T WANT TO PUT
AN ARTIFICIAL
DEADLINE.
WE'RE NOT AT THAT
STAGE.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT AT THE
BUILDER'S UNION.
>> IT WAS ABOUT TIME
WE HAD A BUILDER IN
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: STICKING
TO HIS CONSTRUCTION
COMFORT ZONE INSTEAD.
>> HELLO, IVANKA.
>> Reporter: AS HIS
DAUGHTER KEEPS HER
FOCUS ON WOMEN IN THE
WORK FORCE ON EQUAL
PAYDAY.
>> MY FATHER WANTS TO
CREATE 25 MILLION JOBS
IN THIS COUNTRY AND
WOMEN NEED TO
PARTICIPATE FOR THAT
TO BE FULLY REALIZED.
>> Reporter: THE VICE
PRESIDENT TONIGHT WILL
BE BACK ON THE HILL
AGAIN FOR MORE
HEALTHCARE TALKS.
SPEAKER PAUL RYAN
WON'T BE THERE A SIGN
A SIGN HOUSE LEADERS
MAY BE LETTING THEM
WORK IT OUT ON THEIR
OWN.
NOBODY WANTS TO GET
OUT OVER THEIR SKIS BY
PROMISING A PLAN OR
TIMELINE THAT'S NOT
REALISTIC.
LESTER.
>> HALLIE JACKSON AT
THE WHITE HOUSE
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
THE BACKLASH THIS
EVENING IS GROWING
AGAINST FOX NEWS STAR,
BILL O'REILLY.
A SLEW OF ADVERTISES
INCLUDING VERY BIG
NAMES TODAY SAY
THEY'RE PULLING THEIR
ADS FROM "THE O'REILLY
FACTOR" AFTER MORE
COMPLAINTS OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT HAVE COME
TO LIGHT.
ANNE THOMPSON WITH THE
NEW FALLOUT.
>> Reporter: BILL
O'REILLY IS RARELY AT
A LOSS FOR WORDS.
>> HI.
I'M BILL O'REILLY.
THANKS FOR WATCHING US
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: SO FAR HE
SAID NOTHING ON HIS
SHOW ABOUT THE GROWING
CONTROVERSY OF OFF
SCREEN ALLEGATIONS OF
SEXUAL HARASSMENT.
BUT TONIGHT IS
ADVERTISERS ARE
SPEAKING WITH THEIR
WALLETS, BMW,
MITSUBISHI MOTORS AND
DRUG MAKER GLAXO
SMITHKLINE ARE PULLING
THEIR ADS FROM "THE
O'REILLY FACTOR".
ALLSTATE SAYING IN A
STATEMENT INCLUSIVITY
AND SUPPORT FOR WOMEN
ARE IMPORTANT AllState
VALUES.
WE HAVE SUSPENDED OUR
ADVERTISING.
THEY FOUND FOX NEWS OR
O'REILLY PAID FIVE
WOMEN $13 MILLION TO
SETTLE HARASSMENT AND
INAPPROPRIATE BEHAVIOR
CLAIMS AGAINST THE
STAR ANCHOR.
>> YOU'RE SEEING
COMPANIES SPEAK ABOUT
THEIR VALUES AND THEIR
CONVICTIONS.
IF THEY'RE NOT ALIGNED
WITH FOX NEWS THEY'RE
SUPPORTING WITH THEIR
DOLLARS THEY WILL TAKE
THOSE DOLLARS AWAY.
>> Reporter: LATE
TODAY, FOX NEWS SAID
IN A STATEMENT WE
VALUE OUR PARTNERS AND
ARE WORKING WITH THEM
TO ADDRESS THEIR
CURRENT CONCERNS.
EARLIER THIS WEEK IN A
STATEMENT, O'REILLY
SAID HIS FAME MADE HIM
VULNERABLE TO LAWSUITS
AND HE ACTED QUICKLY
TO PUT TO REST ANY
CONTROVERSIES TO SPARE
HIS CHILDREN.
HIS SHOW IS THE NUMBER
ONE PROGRAM ON CABLE
NEWS, PULLING IN MORE
THAN $100 MILLION A
YEAR IN AD REVENUE.
MORE THAN 350 BRANDS
ADVERTISED ON THE SHOW
IN THE FIRST THREE
MONTHS OF THIS YEAR.
TODAY, COMPANIES WAIT
TO CHANGE THEIR PLANS
TO SEE WHAT IF ANY
CHANGES FOX AND
O'REILLY MAKE.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC
NEWS NEW YORK.
>>> AS WE SAID AT THE
TOP OF THE BROADCAST,
BREAKING NEWS IN SOUTH
KOREA, WORD NORTH
KOREA FIRED AND
UNIDENTIFIED
PROJECTILE INTO THE
SEA.
A NEW PROVOCATION
COMING A SHORT TIME
AFTER THE WHITE HOUSE
SAID THE CLOCK HAS NOW
RUN OUT AND ALL
OPTIONS ARE ON THE
TABLE.
ALL OF IT FOLLOWS MORE
TOUGH TALK FROM NORTH
KOREA CALLING JOINT
U.S.
SOUTH KOREAN MILITARY
EXERCISES A DRESS
REHEARSAL FOR
INVASION.
WE TAGGED ALONG FOR
SOME OF THOSE
EXERCISES AND FOUND
AMERICAN AND SOUTH
KOREAN OFFICERS
CONFIDENT AS THEY
PLANNED TO COUNTER ONE
OF THE MORE PERSISTENT
THREATS THIS REGION
FACES.
>> Reporter: THE WAR
BEING WAGED IN THIS
CORNER OF SOUTH KOREA
TODAY WON'T DRAW A
DROP OF BLOOD.
AMERICANS AND SOUTH
KOREAN TROOPS ENGAGE
IN MOCK URBAN COMBAT
LESS THAN 15 MILES
FROM THE DMZ, AND
RUNNING THROUGH THE
PLAYBOOK OF A
POTENTIAL WAR THAT HAS
HAUNTED THIS PENINSULA
FAR TOO LONG.
>> WE THINK WE COULD
SEE EVERYTHING FROM
CONVENTIONAL TOTAL WAR
HERE AND ALSO
EXPERIENCE CIVILIAN
OPERATIONS AFTER
VICTORY, WHETHER
ATTACK IN URBAN STRONG
POINT.
>> Reporter: AS IF ON
CUE, THE COLONEL WAS
INTERRUPTED BY A
RESCUE CHOPPER
SWOOPING IN TO PLUCK
MOCK CASUALTIES FROM A
ROOFTOP.
THE AMERICANS AND
SOUTH KOREANS ARE
TAKING PART IN AN
ANNUAL JOINT EXERCISE
KIM JONG-UN HAS LONG
DECRIED AS A
PROVOCATION BUT WHAT
WAS SEEN ON THIS SIDE
AS A DETERRENT.
STILL, THE STATUS QUO
THAT HAS GINGERLY
MAINTAINED PEACE IS
THREATENED AS KIM JONG
UN RUSHES TOWARDS A
NUCLEAR WEAPON
CAPABILITY.
IT RAISES THE QUESTION
WHAT ABOUT SEOUL AND
IT'S SUSPECTED NORTH
KOREA WOULD REIGN DOWN
THOUSANDS OF ARTILLERY
ROUNDS ON THIS
SPRAWLING METROPOLIS,
BUT WON'T GO
UNPUNISHED.
>> THIS IS A ROBUST
RESPONSE NOT ONLY
AMERICAN BUT SOUTH
KOREAN TROOPS WORKING
HAND-IN-HAND.
>> Reporter: THE U.S.
WAR PLAN IS TO QUICKLY
OVERWHELM AND KNOCK
OUT THE NORTH'S
ARTILLERY THREAT.
MOBILE RADAR UNITS
LIKE THIS WILL TRACK
THE INCOMING ROUNDS
FROM THEIR SOURCE EVEN
BEFORE THEY LAND.
YOU CAN'T SHOOT WHAT
YOU CAN'T SEE?
>> EXACTLY.
>> Reporter: THIS
ALLOWS YOU TO SEE
WHAT'S COMING DOWN AND
COMING AT YOU?
>> YES, SIR.
>> Reporter: THE EYES
OF A SOPHISTICATED
RESPONSE.
>> YOU CAN TRACK THE
50 INCOMING ROUNDS
SIMULTANEOUSLY?
>> YES, SIR.
>> REPORTER:  THAT'S A
LOT.
>> YES, SIR.
>> Reporter: THEY
PASSED A CREW OF
MOBILE ROCKET SYSTEM
IS THE FANGS OF THE
RESPONSE WHO QUICKLY
AIM AND FIRE RIGHT
BACK AT THE SOURCE.
>> THIS IS A VERY
IMPORTANT DRILL FOR US
TO GO OVER AND
REHEARSE AS MANY TIMES
IN DIFFERENT SCENARIOS
AS POSSIBLE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS
WHAT IT WOULD LOOK
LIKE IN ACTION FOR
REAL.
THE FACT THAT TROOPS
TRAIN WITHIN A FEW
MILES WHERE THEY WOULD
FIGHT IS NOT LOST ON
THEM.
>> Reporter: HOW HAS
IT CHANGED THE
SOLDIERS?
>> THEY'VE DRIVEN OUT
THERE, DONE
COMMUNICATIONS CHECKS
FROM THERE AND MADE
SURE THEY HAVE ALL THE
VISIBILITY THEY NEED
AND GIVES US A SENSE
OF PURPOSE.
>> Reporter: LIKE THE
AIRMEN AT THE AIR BASE
AMERICAN SOLDIERS IN
SOUTH KOREA ARE HOPING
THEIR PREPARATION AND
READINESS WILL GIVE
NORTH KOREA PAUSE.
>>> STILL HEAD, YOUR
INTERNET BROWSING
HISTORY, UP FOR SALE,
THE REPEAL THAT MAKES
IT LEGAL WITHOUT YOUR
PERMISSION AND WHAT TO
DO IF YOU FEAR FOR
YOUR PRIVACY.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP
HAS SIGNED A NEW LAW
THAT ROLLS BACK
INTERNET PRIVACY RULES
PASSED IN THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION.
NO LONGER WILL
INTERNET PROVIDERS BE
REQUIRED TO GET YOUR
PERMISSION BEFORE
SELLING YOUR INTERNET
BROWSING HISTORY TO
MARKETERS.
WILL YOUR INTERNET
SURFING REALLY BE FAIR
GAME?
>> Reporter: THE LAST
TIME YOU SHOPPED
ONLINE FOR A PAIR OF
SHOES, DID THE ADS
FOLLOW YOU FOR DAYS OR
EVEN WEEKS?
YOUR INTERNET PROVIDER
KNOWS FAR MORE ABOUT
YOUR BROWSING HABITS
THAN GOOGLE, FACEBOOK
OR AMAZON.
NOW, THAT PROVIDER CAN
LEGALLY SELL THAT
INFORMATION WITHOUT
YOUR PERMISSION.
PRIVACY ADVOCATES ARE
SO OUTRAGED, ADAM
McELHANEY HAS RAISED
OVER $200,000 ON A GO
FUND ME PAGE FOR
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
WHO PASSED THE LAW.
>> IT SENDS A SIGNAL
PEOPLE ARE VERY UPSET
THEIR DATA IS NOT
THEIRS ANYMORE.
>> Reporter: IT'S
UNLIKELY INTERNET
COMPANIES WOULD SELL
PERSONAL BROWSING
HISTORIES BECAUSE
THEY'RE STILL REQUIRED
TO PROTECT CUSTOMER
PRIVACY PRESUMABLY
NAMES, ADDRESSES AND
SOCIAL SECURITY
NUMBERS.
ONLY ANONYMOUS
BROWSING INFORMATION
COULD BE SOLD BUT
PRIVACY EXPERTS WARN
THAT MAY NOT BE
ENOUGH.
>> SOMEBODY WITH A
SOPHISTICATED
ALGORITHM PROGRAM
COULD FIND OUT WHO YOU
ARE BY THE BREADS
CRUMBS ON THE
INTERNET.
>> Reporter: THEY SAY
THEY'RE COMMITTED TO
PROTECTING CUSTOMER
PRIVACY BECAUSE WE
VALUE YOUR TRUST.
IF YOU'RE STILL
CONCERNED, SECURITY
EXPERTS SUGGEST LIMIT
YOUR WEB BROWSING TO
HTTPS SITES.
THE "S" STANDS FOR
SECURE.
CALL YOUR INTERNET
PROVIDER AND OPT OUT
OF TARGETED MARKETING.
IF YOU'RE REALLY
CONCERNED, PAY FOR A
VPN, VIRTUAL PRIVATE
NETWORK THAT PUTS YOUR
WEB SURFING IN A
BUBBLE, BUT VPNs CAN
ALSO DISABLE SOME
SITES LIKE VIDEO
STREAMING.
THE BOTTOM LINE, FOR
THE MOST PART, PEOPLE
HAVE TO TRUST THE
INTERNET PROVIDERS ARE
KEEPING THEIR INTERNET
PROMISES.
>>> BACK IN A MOMENT
WITH AN INTERNET MEGA
MERGER.
COULD IT MEAN HAVING
TO CHANGE YOUR E-MAIL
ADDRESS?
>>> TWO BIG STORIES IN
THE BUSINESS WORLD
TELL YOU ABOUT.
VERIZON HAS DECIDED TO
COMBINE AOL AND YAHOO!
UNDER ONE NEW COMPANY
CALLED OATH.
IF YOU HAVE AN AOL OR
YAHOO! E-MAIL ACCOUNT
THEY'RE NOT EXPECTED
TO CHANGE.
>>> PAYLESS SHOE
SOURCE HAS FILED FOR
BANKRUPTCY PROTECTION
DECIDING TO CLOSE 400
STORES AS IT STRUGGLES
TO COMPETE WITH ONLINE
STORES.
>>> CELEBRATIONS
TONIGHT IN THE
CAROLINAS.
THE NORTH CAROLINA TAR
HEELS WON THEIR SIXTH
NCAA CHAMPIONSHIP A
THRILLER OVER GONZAGA,
A DAY AFTER SOUTH
CAROLINA WON THE
WOMEN'S CHAMPIONSHIP
OVER MISSISSIPPI
STATE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
NORTH KOREA'S HIGHEST
DEFECTOR IN DECADES
LIVING LIFE ALWAYS
LOOKING OVER HIS
SHOULDER.
NE. NAT=PL ..NBCAY EA SPOSTOEWL=
>>> FINALLY, LAST
NIGHT WE INTRODUCED
YOU TO A HIGH RANKING
NORTH KOREAN DEFECTOR,
WHO COULD POTENTIALLY
SHARE THE DEADLY FATE
THAT HAS WE FALLEN
OTHERS WHO DEFIED KIM
JONG-UN.
THAE YONG HO IS THE
DEPUTY AMBASSADOR TO
THE UK WHEN HE
DEFECTED WITH HIS
YOUNG WIFE AND SONS.
WE MET ON THE CROWDED
STREETS OF SEOUL
FLANKED BY SECURITY
AGENCIES WHOSE
IDENTITIES WE AGREED
TO MASK AND TALKED
ABOUT THE AIRPORT
ASSASSINATION OF KIM
JONG-UN'S HALF-BROTHER
AND EXPECTATION HE
COULD BE NEXT.
>> WE'RE OUT IN PUBLIC
RIGHT NOW.
ARE YOU AFRAID FOR
YOUR SAFETY AT THIS
MOMENT?
>> AT THIS MOMENT I
DON'T THINK SO
BECAUSE, YOU KNOW,
THERE ARE, YOU KNOW,
MANY SECURITY INCH THE
OFFICERS AROUND ME.
BUT ANYTHING CAN
HAPPEN, YOU KNOW.
YOU SEE, EVEN THE
HALF-BROTHER OF NORTH
KOREAN BELIEVE KIM
JONG-NAM WAS
ASSASSINATED.
A PUBLIC PLACE LIKE
THE AIRPORT.
>> HOW DID YOU REACT
TO THAT?
>> AT THE TIME I HEARD
THE STORY I WAS NOT
SURPRISED AT ALL.
>> DO YOU THINK KIM
JONG-UN ORDERED HIS
DEATH?
>> DEFINITELY, YES.
>> DO YOU THINK HE
WANTS YOUR DEATH?
>> YES.
>> YOU THINK HE WANTS
TO KILL YOU?
>> YES.
KIM JONG-UN IS A MAN
WITH THE CHARACTER
THAT ANYTHING NO
MATTER WHETHER IT IS A
COUNTRY OR HUMAN
BEING, YOU KNOW,
SHOULD BE ELIMINATED
IF A COUNTRY OR HUMAN
BEING POSE A KIND OF
THREAT TO HIM.
>> IN THE UNITED
STATES, WE WOULD SAY
YOU'RE A MARKED MAN.
>> I'M SURE I'M
ALREADY A MARKED MAN.
>> A SHORT WHILE
LATER, AWAY FROM THE
CROWDS, THAE TALKED
ABOUT THE HORRIBLE
PRICE OF HIS BETRAYAL.
>> YOUR DECISION WOULD
ALSO IMPACT PEOPLE YOU
LOVE.
YOU HAVE A BROTHER AND
A SISTER STILL IN
NORTH KOREA.
WHAT IS YOUR
EXPECTATION AS TO WHAT
HAS HAPPENED TO THEM?
>> I CANNOT DEFINITELY
SAY TO WHICH PLACE MY
FAMILY MEMBERS WERE
SENT, BUT ONE THING I
AM SURE IS THAT THEY
MAY HAVE BEEN SENT TO
EITHER TO REMOTE AREAS
OR LABOR CAMPS OR TO
SOME, WORST SCENARIO,
THEY WERE SENT TO
POLITICAL PRISON
CAMPS.
ALL THEIR HOUSES BY
NOW WERE CONFISCATED
BY THE REGIME.
>> IS THAT HARD FOR
YOU TO LIVE WITH?
>> OH, YES, YOU KNOW.
SO FAR I CANNOT GET
RID OF THIS KIND OF
NIGHTMARE EVERY NIGHT.
>> THAE HAS CALLED IN
HIS WORDS FOR THE
ELIMINATION OF KIM
JONG-UN AND HOLDS OUT
HOPE SOME DAY BEING
REUNITED WITH HIS
FAMILY STILL INSIDE OF
NORTH KOREA.
>>> THAT WILL DO IT
FOR US ON THIS TUESDAY
NIGHT FROM THE AIR
BASE IN SOUTH KOREA.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
I'LL SEE YOU BACK IN
THE U.S. TOMORROW
NIGHT.
FOR ALL OF US, THANKS
FOR WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.GUNRE  WI COTRYWHATNSTIT
>>> [ BLEEP ].
>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, GUNFIRE IN
WINE COUNTRY, WHAT INVESTIGATORS
SAY LED TO THIS DEADLY SHOOTOUT.
THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS RIGHT
NOW.
GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I'M JESSICA AKBEERY.
>> I'M RAJ MATHAI.
WE'VE BEEN COVERING THIS.
A CAR RIDDLED WITH BULLETS, A
SCHOOL ON LOCKDOWN AND
INVESTIGATORS LINING THE STREETS
NEAR WEST PARK ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
RIGHT OFF HIGHWAY 29.
SEVERAL OFFICERS WERE INVOLVED
IN THIS SHOOTING.
NBC BAY AREA'S RICK BOON IS IN
NAPA WITH A CELL PHONE AND THE
NEW DETAILS.
>> Reporter: YEAH, I JUST TALKED
TO NEIGHBORS, AND THEY TELL ME
THAT AS THEY HEARD THOSE SHOTS
YOU JUST PLAYED THERE, THEY
DUCKED FOR COVER.
THAT'S WHAT A LOT OF PEOPLE ON
THIS TRESTREET, WHEN THEY HEARD
THOSE BULLETS.
THIS ALL BEGAN JUST BEFORE 2
CHE2:00 P.M.
OFFICERS FIRED SEVERAL SHOTS AT
A REEK AFT
A VEHICLE AFTER THE CAR FIRST
FIRED AT POLICE.
NEIGHBORS CALLED POLICE AFTER
HEARING SHOTS NEAR A HOME.
POLICE RESPONDED.
THAT'S WHEN THE ALTERCATION
HAPPENED.
IT PLAYED OUT DIRECTLY ACROSS
THE STREET FROM WEST PARK
ELEMENTARY.
THE SCHOOL WAS PLACED ON HO
LOCKDOWN, PARENTS SHOWED UP,
WORRIED, BUT COULDN'T GET
THROUGH BAUGH THE STREETS ARE
SHUT