NIGHTLY NEWS IS NEXT.
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT,
WITHOUT WARNING.
WHAT CAUSED A MAJOR BRIDGE TO
SUDDENLY COLLAPSE SENDING CARS
AND PEOPLE PLUNGING INTO THE
RIVER BELOW?
TONIGHT, NEW DETAILS ON THE
INVESTIGATION AND THE SPOTLIGHT
IT'S SHINING ON OUR NATION'S
AGING INFRASTRUCTURE.
>>> A CALL TO ACTION FROM
PRESIDENT OBAMA TO THE
MILITARY'S NEXT GENERATION.
TONIGHT HIS WARNING ABOUT AN
ALARMING RISE IN SEXUAL
ASSAULTS.
>>> BACKLASH AFTER CONTROVERSIAL
COMMENTS BY ONE OF THE WORLD'S
WEALTHIEST MEN.
WHAT HE SAID ABOUT WORKING MOMS
ON WALL STREET THAT TONIGHT HAS
IGNITED A FIRESTORM.
>>> AND THE HEROES WHO RISKED
THEIR LIVES IN OKLAHOMA.
THE TEACHERSIPAL AT
THE SCHOOL HARDEST HIT AND THE
EMOTIONAL REUNION FOR THE
PARENTS AND THE DAY CARE WORKERS
WHO SAVED THEIR CHILDREN.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M ANN CURRY IN FOR BRIAN
TONIGHT.
AS A DRAMATIC BRIDGE COLLAPSE
SENT CARS PLUNGING INTO A RIVER
IS COMPLICATING TRAVEL FOR SOME
OF US HEADED INTO THE LONG
MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND.
THE NTSB IS INVESTIGATING BUT IT
ALREADY APPEARS A FACTOR THAT
MAY HAVE TO BE CONSIDERED ALSO
AFFECTS ONE IN NINE BRIDGES
ACROSS OUR NATION.
FOR DETAILS ON WHAT HAPPENED WE
GO TO THE PACIFIC NORTHWEST
WHERE AYMAN MOHYELDIN JOINS US
FROM MOUNT VERNON, WASHINGTON.
AYMAN, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING, ANN.
THE SKAGIT RIVER BRIDGE SITS ON
WASHINGTON'S BUSIEST CORRIDOR,
THE I-5.
MORE THAN 70,000 CARS CROSS THIS
BRIDGE EVERY DAY.
OFFICIALS ARE SCRAMBLING TO KEEP
TRAFFIC FLOWING SMOOTHLY AS THEY
TRY TO DETERMINE WHAT HAPPENED
HERE.
IT HAPPENED WITHOUT WARNING.
>> THERE WAS A LOUD BOOM, A BIG
PUFF OF DUST.
>> Reporter: THE NORTH END OF
THE SKAGIT RIVER BRIDGE
COLLAPSED JUST AFTER RUSH HOUR
LAST NIGHT, SENDING TWO VEHICLES
ON A 25-FOOT PLUNGE.
>> THE BRIDGE OVER I-5 JUST
COLLAPSED.
WE HAVE VEHICLES IN THE WATER.
>> Reporter: ALL THREE PEOPLE IN
THE CARS SURVIVED INCLUDING DAN
SLY.
>> THERE WAS NO HOPE.
THAT'S WHAT I WAS THINKING.
>> Reporter: FEDERAL AND STATE
INSPECTORS SAY A TRUCK WITH AN
OVERSIZED LOAD IS TO BLAME.
>> A VERY HEAVY VEHICLE CRASHED
INTO NOT JUST ONE BUT PROBABLY
MULTIPLE GIRDERS ON THE BRIDGE
AND IT FAILED.
>> Reporter: THE BRIDGE WAS
BUILT IN 1955.
INSPECTED JUST LAST NOVEMBER IT
WAS LISTED AS FUNCTIONALLY
OBSOLETE BY THE FEDERAL HIGHWAY
ADMINISTRATION WHICH MEANS THE
DESIGN IS OUTDATED BUT
STRUCTURALLY SOUND.
>> THE PROBLEM WITH THE BRIDGE
IS IT WAS A FRACTURE CRITICAL
DESIGN WHICH MEANS IF SOMETHING
GOES WRONG WITH THE KEY
STRUCTURAL ELEMENT YOU MAY HAVE
A CATASTROPHIC RESULT.
>> Reporter: EXPERTS SAY BRIDGES
ACROSS THE COUNTRY ARE
VULNERABLE.
IN 2007 DOZENS OF CARS PLUNGED
60 FEET INTO THE MISSISSIPPI
WHEN A BRIDGE IN MINNESOTA
COLLAPSED, KILLING 13 PEOPLE.
AND 14 DIED IN 2002 WHEN A
500-FOOT SPAN OF THE I-40 BRIDGE
COLLAPSED IN EASTERN OKLAHOMA.
ACCORDING TO THE AMERICAN
SOCIETY OF CIVIL ENGINEERS, ONE
IN NINE OF THE NATION'S BRIDGES
ARE RATED AS STRUCTURALLY
DEFICIENT REQUIRING REPAIR OR
REPLACEMENT.
MORE THAN 200 MILLION TRIPS ARE
TAKEN DAILY ACROSS DEFICIENT
BRIDGES.
>> THERE ARE MORE STRUCTURALLY
DEFICIENT BRIDGES IN OUR CITIES
THAN THERE ARE McDONALD'S
FRANCHISES NATIONWIDE.
>> Reporter: THE STATE OF
WASHINGTON WILL RECEIVE $1
MILLION FROM THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT TO HELP REBUILD THE
SKAGIT RIVER BRIDGE.
THE GOVERNOR SAYS IT WILL COST
$15 MILLION.
>> AS FAR AS TIME TO RESTORE THE
I-5 CORRIDOR, MAYBE IT'S WEEKS.
IF NOT, THERE ARE CERTAINLY
MONTHS INVOLVED.
>> Reporter: THE DRIVER OF THE
OVERSIZED TRUCK TESTED NEGATIVE
FOR DRUGS AND ALCOHOL.
HIS WIFE SAID HE WAS HORRIFIED
AS HE WATCHED THE BRIDGE
COLLAPSE IN HIS REAR-VIEW MIRROR
BUT WAS RELIEVED THERE WAS NO
LOSS OF LIFE.
ANN?
>> AYMAN MOHYELDIN TONIGHT,
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> PRESIDENT OBAMA TOOK ON THE
GROWING PROBLEM OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT AND ABUSE IN THE ARMED
SERVICES TODAY.
HE USED A VERY HIGH PROFILE
APPEARANCE TO DO IT.
HIS SPEECH AT THE GRADUATING
CLASS OF THE U.S. NAVAL ACADEMY.
HE WAS TRYING TO SEND A MESSAGE
TO A NEW GENERATION OF LEADERS
AS THE PENTAGON STRUGGLES WITH
HOW TO FIX THIS DISTURBING
PROBLEM.
NBC WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENT
KRISTEN WELKER NOW JOINS US WITH
DETAILS ON THIS STORY.
GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
>> Reporter: ANN, GOOD EVENING
TO YOU.
PRESIDENT OBAMA TOLD THE
GRADUATES THE CULTURE OF SEXUAL
ASSAULT IN THE MILITARY HAS TO
END.
HE SAID IT'S MORE THAN A MATTER
OF CONDUCT.
IT'S A MATTER OF NATIONAL
SECURITY.
AGAINST A RAINY SKY PRESIDENT
OBAMA USED TODAY'S GRADUATION
SPEECH AT THE U.S. NAVAL ACADEMY
TO CALL FOR HIGHER STANDARDS OF
CONDUCT IN THE MILITARY.
>> WE NEED YOUR HONOR.
WE NEED YOUR COURAGE.
>> Reporter: HE URGED THE FUTURE
MILITARY LEADERS MORE THAN A
THOUSAND GRADUATES TO END SEXUAL
ASSAULT IN THE ARMED FORCES.
>> THOSE WHO COMMIT SEXUAL
ASSAULT NOT ONLY ARE COMMITTING
A CRIME.
THEY THREATEN THE TRUST AND
DISCIPLINE THAT MAKES OUR
MILITARY STRONG.
THAT'S WHY WE HAVE TO BE
DETERMINED TO STOP THESE CRIMES.
>> Reporter: THE STERN WORDS
CAME ALMOST THREE WEEKS AFTER A
REPORT BY THE DEFENSE DEPARTMENT
REVEALED UNREPORTED SEXUAL
ASSAULTS IN THE MILITARY ROSE
37% IN 2012 TO AN ESTIMATED
26,000 CASES.
THE MILITARY HAS ALSO FACED A
RECENT SPATE OF SEX ASSAULT
SCANDALS INCLUDING THE
REVELATION THIS WEEK THAT AN
ARMY SERGEANT AT WEST POINT HAD
BEEN ACCUSED OF VIDEOTAPING
FEMALE CADETS WHEN THEY WERE IN
THE BATHROOM OR SHOWER,
PROMPTING A VOW FROM DEFENSE
SECRETARY CHUCK HAGEL TO CRACK
DOWN.
>> WE'LL DO EVERYTHING WE NEED
TO DO TO FIX IT.
>> Reporter: TODAY, MR. OBAMA
SAID THE MILITARY CULTURE ALSO
NEEDS TO CHANGE AND CITED A LACK
OF TRUST IN GOVERNMENT
INSTITUTIONS.
A NOT SO SUBTLE REFERENCE TO THE
CONTROVERSY AT THE IRS, JUSTICE
AND STATE DEPARTMENT THAT HAVE
ROILED WASHINGTON AND HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
>> IT ONLY TAKES THE MISCONDUCT
OF A FEW TO FURTHER ERODE THE
PEOPLE'S TRUST IN THEIR
GOVERNMENT.
>> Reporter: VETERANS ADVOCATES
SAY THE MESSAGE COMES FROM THE
TOP BUT FUNDAMENTAL CHANGE HAS
TO COME FROM THE NEXT GENERATION
OF OFFICERS.
>> STARTING WITH THE PRESIDENT
GOING DOWN THROUGH THE OFFICER
CORE IS NEEDED.
THIS SHOULD BE UNACCEPTABLE IN
SOCIETY.
IT SHOULD BE UNTHINKABLE IN A
STRUCTURE LIKE THE MILITARY.
>> Reporter: NOW DEFENSE
SECRETARY CHUCK HAGEL WILL
DELIVER A SIMILAR MESSAGE WHEN
HE ADDRESSES GRADUATES AT WEST
POINT, THE NATION'S OLDEST
MILITARY ACADEMY TOMORROW.
ABOUT A THOUSAND CADETS ARE
EXPECTED TO GRADUATE.
ANN?
>> KRISTEN, THANK YOU TONIGHT.
>>> AN UPDATE ON THE CONTROVERSY
OVER THE IRS TARGETING
CONSERVATIVE GROUPS FOR EXTRA
SCRUTINY.
LOIS LERNER, THE WOMAN IN CHARGE
OF THE OFFICE AT THE CENTER OF
THE SCANDAL WAS ASKED TO RESIGN
BUT HAS REFUSED.
SHE WAS PLACED ON ADMINISTRATIVE
LEAVE WITH PAY YESTERDAY AFTER
PLEADING THE 5th DURING A
CONGRESSIONAL HEARING ON THE
ISSUE.
>>> THE MEMORIAL DAY TRAVEL RUSH
IS UNDER WAY TONIGHT.
31 MILLION AMERICANS ARE
EXPECTED TO TRAVEL BY CAR.
A MILLION MORE ON TRAINS AND
BUSES.
ABOUT 2 MILLION WILL FLY TO
THEIR HOLIDAY DESTINATIONS.
IN A LOT OF PLACES THE WEATHER
IS NOT COOPERATING WITH THE
UNOFFICIAL START OF SUMMER.
WEATHER CHANNEL METEOROLOGIST
CHRIS WARREN JOINS US WITH MORE
ON THIS STORY.
CHRIS, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING, ANN.
THIS WEEKEND THERE IS GOING TO
BE SOME SEVERE WEATHER AND SOME
SNOW.
LET'S START OFF WITH A LOOK AT
WHERE THERE WILL BE SEVERE
WEATHER.
THE THREAT TONIGHT FOR THE
SEVERE WEATHER WILL BE IN THE
TEXAS PANHANDLE ALL THE WAY UP
TO PARTS OF WESTERN NEBRASKA.
WITH THIS, THERE WILL BE A
CHANCE FOR DAMAGING WINDS, LARGE
HAIL AND A LOW CHANCE OF A
TORNADO.
NOW, LOOKING AHEAD TO SATURDAY,
TO TOMORROW, THERE IS A CHANCE
FOR MOUNTAIN SNOW IN PARTS OF
NORTHERN NEW YORK AND NORTHERN
NEW ENGLAND.
THIS IS UNUSUAL LATE SPRING SNOW
POSSIBLE ABOVE ABOUT 1,000 FEET.
THERE COULD BE SOME POWER
OUTAGES WITH THE SNOW FALLING ON
THE LEAVES, POSSIBLY BRINGING
DOWN POWER LINES.
CHANCE FOR SEVERE WEATHER THERE
IN THE NORTHERN PLAINS.
ALSO LOOKING AT THE THREAT FOR
SEVERE WEATHER PUSHING OFF A
LITTLE BIT FARTHER TO THE PLAINS
BUT NOT MOVING VERY FAST ON
SUNDAY.
STILL A CHANCE FOR MOUNTAIN SNOW
IN THE GREEN AND ADIRONDACK
MOUNTAINS IN THE HIGHER
ELEVATIONS.
ON MONDAY, MEMORIAL DAY, IT WILL
BE WARMER IN THE NORTHEAST.
ANN, THAT LOOKS LIKE THE BEST
DAY TO BE OUTSIDE IN THE
NORTHEAST.
>> ALL RIGHT.
GOOD INFORMATION, CHRIS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> TURNING NOW TO MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, AT THE END OF A TRYING
WEEK.
FIVE DAYS AFTER A MASSIVE
TORNADO HIT THAT COMMUNITY,
POLICE HAVE REMOVED THE LAST
CHECKPOINTS CLOSING OFF THE
AFFECTED AREAS.
RESIDENTS ARE PICKING UP THE
PIECES AND NBC'S KATE SNOW HAS A
MOVING INTERVIEW WITH SOME OF
THE TEACHERS AT PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WHERE SEVEN
CHILDREN WERE KILLED.
GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
TWO MORE CHILDREN WERE LAID TO
REST TODAY, 3rd GRADERS AT PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY.
THEIR PRINCIPAL WAS ON HAND FOR
THOSE MEMORIALS.
TONIGHT SHE AND OTHERS ARE
SPEAKING OUT FOR THE FIRST TIME
ABOUT THE LOSS AND WHAT THEY DID
TO TRY TO PROTECT HUNDREDS OF
OTHERS WHEN THE TORNADO HIT.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN BACK HERE?
>> NO.
THIS IS MY FIRST TIME.
>> Reporter: PRINCIPAL AMY
SIMPSON AND HER TEACHERS HAD
ONLY 16 MINUTES FROM THE TIME
THE TORNADO TOUCHED DOWN IN
OKLAHOMA TO THE MOMENT THEY WERE
HIT.
>> THEY COME RIGHT OUT OF THEIR
DOORS AND LINE UP AGAINST HERE.
>> Reporter: THE KIDS WERE
CROUCHED DOWN ALONG HALLWAY
WALLS SINGING THE ABCs.
SECONDS BEFORE IMPACT SIMPSON
GOT ON THE INTERCOM AND SAID
SIMPLY, IT'S HERE.
>> FIRST IT'S JUST A RATTLING
LIKE SOMEONE WALKING ON THE
ROOF.
THEN YOU FEEL THINGS FALL INTO
YOUR HAIR.
JUST LITTLE THINGS, YOU KNOW.
THEN ALL OF THE SUDDEN -- BIGGER
THINGS.
THAT'S WHEN I STARTED TO YELL.
>> Reporter: WHAT DID YOU YELL?
>> JUST IN GOD'S NAME, GO AWAY.
GO AWAY.
>> Reporter: SO YOU CAME OUT OF
YOUR OFFICE AND YOU WENT THIS
WAY.
>> CLIMBED OVER.
>> Reporter: WHEN IT WAS OVER
SHE WALKED AROUND THE CORNER TO
WHERE LINDA PATTERSON'S PRE-K
CLASS WAS MOMENTS BEFORE.
WHAT ARE YOU HEARING?
>> I HEAR THE CHILD UNDER ME
SAYING I'M NOT BREATHING, I
CAN'T BREATHE.
I HAD WEIGHT ON HER.
>> Reporter: WHAT BLEW ON TOP OF
YOU?
>> A WALL.
SOME TWO BY FOURS, A CAR.
>> Reporter: A CAR?
>> A CAR WAS THERE ON TOP OF ALL
OF THIS DEBRIS.
>> Reporter: THE LOWER HALF OF
LINDA'S BODY WAS PINNED UNDER
THE CAR.
SHE USED HER ARMS TO PULL OUT
CHILDREN AROUND HER.
>> Reporter: YOU SAVED THEIR
LIVES.
>> NO.
>> YES, SHE DID.
>> I DID WHAT -- THAT'S WHAT I
NEEDED TO DO.
THAT'S WHERE I NEEDED TO BE.
>> Reporter: PLAZA TOWERS WAS
BUILT IN 1966 AND HAD NO
BASEMENT OR REINFORCED SHELTER.
>> WE ARE PROBABLY THE FASTEST
GROWING DISTRICT, THE THIRD
LARGEST DISTRICT.
AS WE BUILD AND BUILD, THE MONEY
HAS GONE FOR CLASSROOM SPACE.
>> Reporter: NOT FOR SHELTERS.
>> NOT FOR SHELTERS.
>> Reporter: PIERCE SAYS THERE
ARE FRESH DISCUSSIONS HAPPENING
NOW ABOUT ALL OF THIS, WHETHER
THEY SHOULD BUILD SHELTERS IN
EVERY SCHOOL IN OKLAHOMA.
IT'S A SUBJECT THAT MAY WELL
COME UP ON SUNDAY WHEN PRESIDENT
OBAMA VISITS HERE.
ALSO SUNDAY A MEMORIAL SERVICE
FOR THE PUBLIC TO RECOGNIZE
THOSE WHO WERE LOST THIS WEEK.
ANN?
>> AN IMPORTANT MOMENT FOR
MOORE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH, KATE.
THERE WILL BE MORE FROM KATE
SNOW AND HER CONVERSATION WITH
THE PRINCIPAL AND TEACHERS AT
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY ON "ROCK
CENTER" TONIGHT AT 10:00/9:00
CENTRAL.
>>> OVERSEAS TODAY WE HEARD FOR
THE FIRST TIME FROM THE FAMILY
OF THAT BRITISH SOLDIER KILLED
IN AN ACT OF TERRORISM ON A
LONDON STREET.
IN AN EMOTIONAL NEWS CONFERENCE
LEE RIGBY'S ANGUISHED FAMILY
MEMBERS INCLUDING HIS WIDOW
DESCRIBED HIM AS A DEVOTED SON
AND FATHER.
THE TWO MURDER SUSPECTS SHOT
AFTER RUSHING AT POLICE REMAIN
HOSPITALIZED.
TWO WOMEN WHO WERE ARRESTED ON
SUSPICION TO COMMIT MURDER HAVE
BEEN RELEASED WITHOUT CHARGE.
>>> AND ANOTHER SCARE IN BRITAIN
TODAY ABOARD A FLIGHT FROM
LAHORE, PAKISTAN, TO THE UK.
PILOTS PUT OUT AN EMERGENCY
SIGNAL AND THE PLANE WAS
ESCORTED BY BRITISH FIGHTER JETS
BEFORE MAKING AN EMERGENCY
LANDING.
OFFICIALS SAY TWO PASSENGERS
ALLEGEDLY THREATENED TO BLOW UP
THE PLANE AFTER AN ARGUMENT WITH
THE CREW.
BUT THAT INCIDENT DOES NOT
APPEAR TO BE TERROR-RELATED.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT ON "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS" AS IT CONTINUES ON
THIS FRIDAY, THE FIRESTORM
IGNITED BY ONE OF THE WEALTHIEST
MEN IN THE WORLD.
WHAT HE SAID THAT UPSET A LOT OF
WORKING MOMS.
AND WHAT HE'S SAYING NOW
TONIGHT.
>>> LATER, A NEW WORLD RECORD
AND A FRESH START AT ONE OF THE
MOST POPULAR SUMMER DESTINATIONS
IN AMERICA.
>>> WE ARE BACK WITH THE
CONTROVERSIAL COMMENTS MADE BY
ONE OF THE WEALTHIEST MEN IN THE
WORLD WHO IS ALSO A HIGH PROFILE
PHILANTHROPIST.
THERE IS NO DOUBT PAUL TUDOR
JONES IS AMONG THE MOST SAVVY OF
INVESTORS BUT WHAT HE SAID ABOUT
CERTAIN WORKING MOMS ON WALL
STREET HAS ELICITED A BACKLASH.
WE GET OUR REPORT NOW FROM NBC'S
ANDREA MITCHELL.
>> Reporter: IT'S THE SOUND BITE
REVERBERATING FROM COLLEGE
CAMPUSES TO WALL STREET.
PAUL TUDOR JONES, A SELF-MADE
HEDGE FUND BILLIONAIRE AND
PHILANTHROPIST SAID WOMEN AREN'T
EQUIPPED FOR THE ELITE CROWD OF
MACRO TRADERS IF THEY ARE
MOTHERS BECAUSE, IN HIS WORDS, A
CHILD IS A FOCUS KILLER, CITING
TWO WOMEN HE WORKED WITH IN THE
'70s.
>> THEY BOTH HAD CHILDREN.
AS SOON AS THAT BABY'S LIPS
TOUCHED THAT GIRL'S BOSOM,
FORGET IT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
EVERY SINGLE INVESTMENT IDEA.
EVERY DESIRE TO UNDERSTAND,
EVERY DESIRE TO UNDERSTAND
WHAT'S GOING TO MAKE THIS GO UP
OR DOWN IS GOING TO BE
OVERWHELMED BY THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL EXPERIENCE WHICH A MAN
WILL NEVER SHARE.
>> Reporter: IT WAS THE TALK OF
CABLE NEWS FROM "MORNING JOE" TO
CNBC.
>> EXCEPT THIS HAPPENS TO BE
ABOUT HAVING BABIES FOR WOMEN.
>> GIVE ME A BREAK.
FATHERS LOVE THEIR CHILDREN,
WORRY ABOUT THEIR CHILDREN,
THINK ABOUT THEIR CHILDREN JUST
AS MUCH AS MOTHERS.
>> Reporter: TUDOR HELPED THE
ROBIN HOOD FOUNDATION RAISE A
RECORD-BREAKING $80 MILLION TO
FIGHT POVERTY LAST WEEK
APOLOGIZED TODAY SAYING HE'S
TALKING ABOUT MACRO TRADERS.
FEWER THAN 1,000 GLOBAL TRADERS
IN HIGHLY SPECIALIZED FINANCIAL
INSTRUMENTS WHO ARE ON CALL 24/7
AND REQUIRE A HIGH DEGREE OF
SKILL, FOCUS, AND REPETITION.
THAT DIDN'T CUT IT WITH CRITICS.
>> HE TALKED ABOUT THE MOTHER
BOND EXPERIENCE MEN CANNOT FEEL.
MADE ME WONDER IF HE DOESN'T
KNOW WHAT IT FEELS LIKE HOW DOES
HE KNOW IT KNOCKS WOMEN OFF
THEIR GAME?
>> Reporter: MORE WOMEN ARE
GRADUATING FROM BUSINESS SCHOOLS
BUT FEW ARE HIGH STAKES TRADERS.
PART OF THE CONVERSATION ABOUT
THE GLASS CEILING ON WALL
STREET.
WOMEN ARE ONLY 4% OF THE CEOs IN
THE TOP 500 COMPANIES.
IS IT BECAUSE OF MOTHERHOOD?
MARISSA MAYER TOOK OVER AT
YAHOO! AND BECAME A NEW MOTHER
TELLING SAVANNAH GUTHRIE --
>> Reporter: OVERALL I HAVE BEEN
HAVING A TERRIFIC TIME BEING
BOTH A CEO AND A MOTHER.
>> Reporter: IT'S NOT LIKE WOMEN
AREN'T DEBATING WORK LIFE
BALANCE.
>> DON'T LEAN BACK.
LEAN IN.
>> Reporter: HEDGE FUNDS RUN BY
WOMEN OUTPERFORM THOSE RUN BY
MEN.
ANDREA MITCHELL, NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
THE BEST LIST OF THE BEST SAND
UNDER THE SUN AS WE HEAD INTO
THE UNOFFICIAL START OF SUMMER.
>>> TODAY PRESIDENT OBAMA SIGNED
A BILL AWARDING THE
CONGRESSIONAL GOLD MEDAL TO THE
FOUR LITTLE GIRLS KILLED IN THE
BOMBING OF A BIRMINGHAM,
ALABAMA, CHURCH IN 1963.
FAMILY MEMBERS OF ADDIE MAE
COLLINS, DENISE McNAIR, CAROL
ROBERTSON AND CYNTHIA WESLEY
LOOKED ON AS THE FOUR WERE GIVEN
THE HIGHEST CIVILIAN HONOR THIS
COUNTRY CAN BESTOW.
THEIR DEATHS AT THE HANDS OF
WHITE SUPREMACISTS HELPED PROPEL
THE CIVIL RIGHTS MOVEMENT.
>>> THIS MORNING IN SEASIDE
HEIGHTS, NEW JERSEY, SEVEN
MONTHS AFTER HURRICANE SANDY
CAUSED BILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN
DAMAGE, NEW JERSEY GOVERNOR
CHRIS CHRISTIE CUT A WORLD
RECORD SETTING FIVE AND A HALF
MILE-LONG RIBBON TO OFFICIALLY
RE-OPEN THE JERSEY SHORE.
HE SAID 80% OF THE SHORE HAS
BEEN RESTORED WHICH IS IMPORTANT
FOR THE $38 BILLION A YEAR
TOURISM INDUSTRY THERE.
>>> ANOTHER BEACH THAT TOOK A
POUNDING WHEN HURRICANE SANDY
CAME ASHORE WAS THE MAIN BEACH
IN EAST HAMPTON ON NEW YORK'S
LONG ISLAND WHICH TODAY TOPPED
01:08:40:A LIST OF THE BEST.
SOME OTHER SUMMER FAVORITES WERE
CAPE FLORIDA STATE PARK, CAPE
HATTERAS ON THE OUTER BANKS OF
NORTH CAROLINA AND COAST GUARD
BEACH ON CAPE COD.
WE PUT THE FULL LIST ON THE
WEBSITE AT NBCNIGHTLYNEWS.COM.
>>> IT WON'T HAPPEN IN TIME FOR
THE MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND, BUT
THE U.S. PARKS SERVICE ANNOUNCED
TODAY THAT FURLOUGHS OF PARK
POLICE OFFICERS WILL BE COMING
TO AN END.
THE PARK POLICE WERE THE ONLY
FEDERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCY
FORCED TO TAKE DAYS OFF WITHOUT
PAY UNDER THE BUDGET CUTS KNOWN
AS THE SEQUESTER.
THE AGENCY FOUND COST SAVINGS
ELSEWHERE AND THE FURLOUGHS WILL
END ON JUNE 1.
>>> A LOT OF STAR GAZERS WILL BE
STAYING UP LATE THIS WEEKEND.
THREE OF THE BRIGHTEST LIGHTS IN
THE SKY ARE SET TO PUT ON A RARE
SHOW.
VENUS, JUPITER AND MERCURY WILL
APPEAR AS A BRIGHT TRIANGLE OF
LIGHT IN THE WESTERN SKY.
THE BEST NIGHT TO CATCH IT IS ON
SUNDAY ABOUT 30 MINUTES AFTER
SUNSET.
IT WON'T HAPPEN AGAIN UNTIL
2015.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK AN
EMOTIONAL REUNION FOR GRATEFUL
PARENTS IN OKLAHOMA.
AND THE DAY CARE WORKERS WHO
SERVED AS HUMAN SHIELDS TO
PROTECT THE CHILDREN IN THEIR
CARE.
>>> EVEN AMID THE RUBBLE OF THE
DEVASTATING TORNADO IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, GRATITUDE CAN BE
FOUND.
A YOUNG MOTHER WE TOLD YOU ABOUT
ON TUESDAY HAS REACHED OUT TO
THANK THE DAY CARE WORKERS WHOSE
ACTIONS SAVED THE LIVES OF HER
CHILDREN.
AT 3 YEARS OLD GRAYSON IS
ALREADY A SURVIVOR.
WHAT'S IT LIKE TO BE IN A
TORNADO, GRAYSON?
>> IT'S LOUD.
>> Reporter: LOUD?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: WE FIRST MET
GRAYSON AND HIS 6-WEEK-OLD
BROTHER BRADEN IN THE HOSPITAL
THE DAY AFTER THE TORNADO HIT.
SEEING WHAT'S LEFT OF THEIR DAY
CARE CENTER IT'S HARD TO BELIEVE
ANYONE MADE IT OUT ALIVE.
>> IT'S A MIRACLE.
IT IS A MIRACLE.
ALL THOSE KIDS, MY BOYS GOT OUT.
>> Reporter: THEIR MOTHER JANICE
SAID IT IS THANKS TO THEIR
HEROIC TEACHERS.
>> WHAT DID THE TEACHERS DO?
>> PUT COTS OVER THE HEADS.
>> Reporter: THEY PUT COTS OVER
THE CHILDREN AND LAID ON TOP TO
SHIELD THEM WITH THEIR OWN
BODIES AS THE TORNADO HIT.
WHAT DID THE KIDS DO?
>> SCARED.
>> Reporter: THEY WERE SCARED.
AM AMAZINGLY, GRAYSON SUFFERED
ONLY ONLY MINOR HEAD INJURIES.
WHERE DOES IT HURT?
>> ON MY EAR.
>> Reporter: WHICH EAR HURTS A
LOT?
>> THIS ONE.
>> Reporter: WHAT DO YOU SAY TO
THE TEACHERS?
>> THANK YOU.
>> Reporter: FOR COVERING YOUR
CHILD.
>> RISKING YOUR LIFE TO PROTECT
MY BOYS.
>> Reporter: YESTERDAY SHE GOT
THE CHANCE.
>> GRAYSON.
OH, BABY.
>> Reporter: JANNA, THE BOYS AND
THEIR DAD KEN VISITED ABBY
LARSON WHO RAN THE DAY CARE
CENTER.
>> DID YOU MISS US?
>> MM-HMM.
>> YEAH.
HE WANTS TO GET BACK.
>> HE WAS EXCITED.
>> GO!
>> Reporter: GRAYSON AND HIS
FRIENDS HAVE BEEN MISSING DAY
CARE.
>> IT'S BROKEN.
WE'LL GET IT FIXED.
>> Reporter: ABBY SAYS SHE'LL
REE BUILD THE DAY CARE CENTER
AND TAKES COMFORT IN SEEING A
GRAYSON.
JUST DAYS AFTER WE LAST SAW HIM,
HIS CUTS ARE HEALING.
JANNA SPOKE TO THE TEACHERS WHO
SAVED HER BOYS.
>> I'M THANKFUL AND BLESSED TO
HAVE ALL OF Y'ALL TO TAKE CARE
OF THE KIDS.
>> Reporter: THANKFUL THEY STILL
HAVE WHAT IS MOST PRECIOUS.
>> I WANT TO HUG EVERYBODY SINCE
Y'ALL SAVED MY BOYS' LIVES.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
THANK YOU.
>> AFTER A WEEK OF SO MUCH
SADNESS, SOMETHING TO BE HAPPY
ABOUT.
THAT IS OUR BROADCAST FOR THIS
FRIDAY EVENING.
I'M ANN CURRY IN FOR BRIAN
WILLIAMS.
FOR ALL OF US HERE AT NBC NEWS,
THANK YOU AND GOOD NIGHT.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
>>> GOOD FRIDAY EVENING,
EVERYONE.
I'M JANELLE WANG.
>> AND I'M JESSICA AGUIRRE.
>>> A BASKETBALL PLAYER IS
GETTING ATTENTION FOR AN
ACCUSATION OF MURDER.
THE ONCE BUDDING ATHLETE IS NOW
IN JAIL CHARGED WITH KILLING AN
EMERGING RAP STAR.
MARY AN FAVO JOINS US LIVE WITH
DETAILS AND REACTION FROM
WHITE'S FATHER, MARY ANN.
>> WELL, THE MURDER HE'S ACCUSED
OF HAPPENED NEARLY A YEAR AGO,
IN JUNE OF LAST YEAR.
HE IS ACCUSED OF MURDERING A
RAPPER.
AND HE IS WELL KNOWN IN THE BAY
AREA SPORTS WORLD.
HE PLAYED AT TWO DIFFERENT
UNIVERSITIES HERE, INCLUDING
SANTA CLARA UNIVERSITY.
IT WAS THIS AMAZING SHOT FROM
BEYOND HALF COURT THAT BROUGHT
SAN FRANCISCO STATE BASKETBALL
PLAYER DESENSE WHITE NATIONWIDE
ATTENTION.
NOW THE BASKETBALL STAR IS
GETTING ATTENTION FOR SOMETHING
THAT HAPPENED OFF THE COURT.
WHITE IS ACCUSED OF MURDERING A
MAN IN GEORGE.
U.S. MARSHALS ARRESTED HIM APRIL
24 IN PACIFICA.
>> MR. WHITE WAS ARRESTED IN OUR
COUNTY, AND WE FILED IN THE
DISTRICT ATTORNEY'S OFFICE A
FUGITIVE PROCEEDING AGAINST HIM
IN COURT.
THAT'S EXTRADITION PROCEEDINGS.
>> WHITE WAS TRANSFERRED BACK TO
SAN FRANCISCO IN MAY FACING
EXTRADITION.
HE IS ACCUSED OF MURDERING A
RAPPER IN A PARKING GARAGE NEAR
ATLANTA.
AT LEAST FOUR O