BA BUENA RIGHT OFF THE FREEWAY.
WE WILL DON'T TO UPDATE THE
STORY ON OUR 6:30.
THE STATE OF
EMERGENCY HERE IN HARD-HIT
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
MILES OF DEVASTATION AFTER A
OUS TORNADO DECIMATED
EVERYTHING IN ITS PATH.
>> IT'S ABOUT A MILE RIGHT AT
OUR TAIL.
>> A CATASTROPHIC RAMPAGE FOR 17
MILES ON THE GROUND.
RIGHT NOW RESCUE TEAMS ARE STILL
SEARCHING FOR MISSING PEOPLE.
AT LEAST 24 ARE CONFIRMED DEAD.
HUNDREDS MORE ARE INJURED.
AND MANY OF THEM CHILDREN WHO
WERE PULLED FROM AN ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL THAT TOOK A DIRECT HIT.
TONIGHT THE MOMENT OF IMPACT
HERE.
THE VICTIMS AND THE SURVIVORS.
FRIENDS AND NEIGHBORS NOW
OVERWHELMED BY TRAGEDY, AND THE
SEVERE WEATHER KEEPS ON COMING.
WE HAVE AN ACTIVE AND DANGEROUS
SITUATION IN SEVEN SEPARATE
STATES FOR TENS OF MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS.
OUR TEAM IS HERE AND ON THE
GROUND, AND OUR SPECIAL COVERAGE
BEGINS NOW.
>> Announcer: "DEVASTATION IN
OKLAHOMA."
THIS IS "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
BRIAN WILLIAMS REPORTING TONIGHT
FROM MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
>>> WELL, GOOD EVENING FROM WHAT
HAS TO BE THE SADDEST PLACE ON
EARTH, THE MOST TORN-UP PLACE ON
EARTH, AND THAT'S THE CITY OF
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
WE'RE SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA CITY,
AND TODAY WE HAD OUR SUSPICIONS
AND WORST FEARS REALIZED.
WE LEARNED TODAY OFFICIALLY WHAT
TORE THROUGH HERE YESTERDAY
AFTERNOON WAS, IN FACT, AN EF-5
TORNADO.
WE GOT THIS VIDEO IN TODAY OF
THE INCEPTION OF THE TORNADO.
ITS VERY BEGINNING AS IT STARTED
TO MARCH ALONG ITS PATH.
THAT MEANS -- THAT CATEGORY MEAN
THESE WINDS HIT BETWEEN 200, 210
MILES AN HOUR.
THE BASE OF THIS STORM NOW
CONFIRMED TO BE AT ITS WIDEST
POINT, 1.3 MILES WIDE ON THE
GROUND.
THE PATH WAS 17 MILES LONG, 17
MILES OF REAL ESTATE.
IT WAS ON THE GROUND FOR 40
MINUTES.
AND A WORD ABOUT THE DEATH TOLL
HAVING FLUCTUATED UP AND DOWN
OVERNIGHT AND INTO TODAY.
IT STANDS RIGHT NOW CONFIRMED AT
24.
AND SADLY, THAT NUMBER INCLUDES
AT LEAST 9 CHILDREN.
237 PEOPLE ARE LISTED AS
INJURED.
THE INSURANCE CLAIMS LIKELY
TOPPING $1 BILLION, BUT LUCKILY
THERE WILL BE TIME TO DISCUSS
ALL OF THAT.
AND EVEN AS WE STAND HERE
TONIGHT AMID ALL THIS, SEVERE
WEATHER IS STILL IN THE NEWS
THIS EVENING.
WE HAVE A COMBINATION OF WATCHES
AND WARNINGS OVER SEVEN SEPARATE
STATES TONIGHT, THOUGH WE'RE
HAPPY TO REPORT IT LOOKS LIKE
THE DALLAS/FT. WORTH METROPLEX
WILL AVOID THE WORST OF THE
SEVERE WEATHER.
FIRST OFF, TO START OUR
COVERAGE, A VERY BASIC
QUESTION, WHAT HAPPENED HERE TO
CAUSE ALL THIS?
LESTER HOLT, PART OF OUR TEAM
HERE WITH US TO START OFF OUR
COVERAGE.
LESTER, LET'S BEGIN WITH THIS
DEATH TOLL.
A LOT OF AMERICANS WENT TO BED
LAST NIGHT HEARING A NUMBER 51,
SOME OF THEM 91.
A LOT OF US WOKE UP THIS MORNING
TO SEE IT DOWNGRADED TO 24.
WE TALK ABOUT THE FOG OF WAR IN
SITUATIONS LIKE THIS.
IS THAT WHAT HAPPENED?
>> IT LOOKS LIKE A WAR ZONE AND
IT WAS, IN FACT, A FOG OF WAR.
THE CHAOS AND CONFUSION OF THOSE
EARLY HOURS OF A HECTIC SEARCH
AND RESCUE OPERATION.
MEANTIME, TODAY THE FIRST VICTIM
IDENTITIES WERE RELEASED, THAT
OF A LITTLE 9-YEAR-OLD GIRL
KILLED IN HER SCHOOL.
TODAY NEW IMAGES OF THE STORM AS
IT BARRELED INTO MOORE,
REINFORCING WHAT EVERYONE HERE
IS SAYING --
>> THE WHOLE ROOF JUST CAME OFF.
>> Reporter: THIS ONE WAS BEYOND
ANYTHING THEY CAN REMEMBER.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> Reporter: SURVIVORS EMERGED
FROM SHELTER INTO AN ALIEN WORLD
OF UTTER DESTRUCTION.
>> THE LORD GIVETH, AND THE LORD
TAKETH AWAY.
>> Reporter: AIDED BY CADAVER
DOGS, TODAY'S SEARCHERS WENT
DOOR TO DOOR.
THE TWISTER IS RESPONSIBLE FOR
AT LEAST 24 DEATHS INCLUDING 9
CHILDREN.
7 OF THEM WERE STILL INSIDE
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
AMONG THEM 9-YEAR-OLD JANAE
HORNSBY.
THESE SISTERS TOOK THEIR OWN
CHILDREN FROM THE SCHOOL JUST
MINUTES BEFORE THE TORNADO HIT.
>> WE HAD TURNED ON THE RADIO IN
THE CAR, AND THEY SAID SOMETHING
ABOUT A CHILD.
I CAN'T EVEN REMEMBER HER NAME.
THAT SHE'S ALIVE.
SHE'S AT A HOSPITAL IN NORMAN.
AND I TOLD MY DAUGHTER, MIA, IS
THAT YOUR FRIEND?
SHE STARTED CRYING.
MOM, THAT'S MY FRIEND.
BUT SHE'S ALIVE?
SHE'S ALIVE.
>> Reporter: IN 40 PETRIFYING
MINUTES THE LANDSCAPE OF THIS
SUBURBAN TOWN WAS CHANGED
FOREVER.
>> I HAVE BLOOD IN MY HAIR FROM
MY FRIEND.
SHE WAS ON TOP OF ME.
SHE WAS BLEEDING BECAUSE SHE GOT
HIT PRETTY HARD.
>> Reporter: AT THIS 7-ELEVEN,
FOUR BODIES WERE RECOVERED TODAY
INCLUDING A 3-MONTH-OLD BABY.
THE MOORE MEDICAL CENTER, WHERE
PATIENTS WERE EVACUATED, NOW
LOOKS LIKE THIS.
ENTRANCES BLOCKED WITH CRUMBLED
CARS TOSSED DURING THE STORM.
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD ONCE DOTTED
WITH TREES, SWIMMING POOLS AND
CUL-DE-SACS NOW COMPLETELY
OBLITERATED, UNRECOGNIZABLE.
THE TWISTER'S DEVASTATING PATH
17 MILES LONG.
>> THE STREETS ARE JUST GONE.
THE SIGNS ARE JUST GONE.
SO WE'VE BEEN WORKING VERY HARD
TO IDENTIFY VARIOUS AREAS OF
NEED.
>> THERE IT IS.
IT'S A MILE RIGHT THERE.
>> Reporter: JOHN WELCH, PILOT
REPORTER FOR KFOR TV'S CHOPPER 4
WATCHED THE HORROR UNFOLD.
>> LOOK AT THAT.
IT'S JUST LIKE A LAWN MOWER WENT
RIGHT THROUGH.
>> Reporter: TODAY WE SURVEYED
THE DAMAGE.
>> THIS WAS THE HEART OF THE
SEARCH YESTERDAY.
>> Reporter: ITS PATH WAS EERILY
REMINISCENT OF THAT TAKEN BY A
RECORD-SETTING TORNADO THAT HIT
HERE 14 YEARS AGO.
THAT TWISTER HAD SPEEDS OF MORE
THAN 300 MILES PER HOUR, DAMAGED
MORE THAN 8,000 HOMES AND KILLED
AT LEAST 36.
THAT 1999 TORNADO TOOK DON
BESSINGER'S FENCE.
THIS ONE TOOK HIS HOME.
HE RODE OUT THE ASSAULT IN A
NEIGHBOR'S STORM SHELTER.
WHAT WAS IT LIKE WHEN YOU WERE
IN THERE?
COULD YOU HEAR IT?
>> IT WAS LOUD.
EVERYTHING WAS BANGING AGAINST
THE DOORS AND
IT WAS THE HOUSES BREAKING APART
HITTING THE DOOR.
WE THOUGHT THE DOOR WAS GOING TO
FLY OFF, AND THE MASSIVE DEBRIS
HIT.
SO WE MADE IT TO THE CORNER OF
THE STORM SHELTER BECAUSE WE
THOUGHT THE DOOR WAS GOING TO
LEAVE.
>> Reporter: TODAY HOMEOWNERS
TRICKLED BACK INTO DESTROYED
NEIGHBORHOODS STARTING WITH THE
SMALL PIECES, AS THEY CONFRONTED
THE BIG TASK OF PUTTING THEIR
LIVES BACK TOGETHER.
AND WE MENTION THAT FLUCTUATING
NUMBER OF CONFIRMED DEAD.
OFFICIALS SAY IT COULD CHANGE
AGAIN BECAUSE THERE ARE STILL
THOSE UNACCOUNTED FOR, BRIAN, AS
THE SEARCH GOES ON.
AND THEY POINT OUT
WE COULD SEE AS MANY AS 20,000
PEOPLE DISPLACED BY ALL THIS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
AND THERE'S SO MUCH OF THIS,
THIS IS GOING TO BE A LONG HAUL
THAT BEGINS WITH A GRID AND
HOUSE-BY-HOUSE SEARCHES, WHICH
HAVE NOT YET ALL BEEN COMPLETED.
LESTER HOLT STARTING OFF OUR
COVERAGE HERE TONIGHT.
LESTER, THANKS.
>>> IF YOU WERE WATCHING OUR
SPECIAL COVERAGE YESTERDAY IN
THE IMMEDIATE AFTERMATH OF THIS
TORNADO, THEN YOU KNOW IT TOOK
ONLY AN HOUR OR TWO FOR A KIND
OF SICK FEELING TO ARRIVE IN
THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
WHAT ABOUT THE ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL?
THERE WAS THAT DIRE FIRST REPORT
THAT UPWARDS OF 75 STUDENTS AND
FACULTY MIGHT BE TRAPPED, MIGHT
BE UNACCOUNTED FOR.
LUCKILY THOSE DIRE NUMBERS DID
NOT MATERIALIZE, BUT SADLY THERE
HAS WELL BEEN MORE THAN ENOUGH
BAD NEWS TO GO AROUND AT THAT
SCHOOL.
KATE SNOW HAS BEEN THERE FOR US
TODAY.
KATE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: BRIAN, GOOD EVENING
TO YOU.
THERE WERE TWO SCHOOLS THAT WERE
ACTUALLY IN THE DIRECT PATH OF
THIS TORNADO.
ONE OF THEM, LUCKILY, HAD NO
FATALITIES THAT WE KNOW OF SO
FAR.
BUT THE OTHER, AT LEAST SEVEN
FATALITIES THAT WE KNOW OF,
AND THIS WAS A WEEK THAT WAS
SUPPOSED TO BE FILLED WITH
CELEBRATION.
LAST WEEK AT SCHOOL,
GRADUATION.
TOMORROW WAS SUPERKIDS DAY AT
THE SCHOOL.
INSTEAD THEY'RE MOURNING THEIR
CLASSMATES.
INSIDE THE WALLS OF THE PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, 500
STUDENTS WERE COUNTING DOWN THE
DAYS IN THEIR FINAL WEEK OF
CLASS, BUT IN JUST A MATTER OF
MINUTES, THEIR CAMPUS WENT
FROM LOOKING LIKE THIS TO THIS.
CLASSROOMS COMPLETELY
OBLITERATED, AN AUDITORIUM CAVED
IN.
PARENTS OF OTHER STUDENTS TELL
NBC NEWS CHILDREN WERE IN THAT
AUDITORIUM.
>> WE'VE SEEN IT FROM THE AIR.
THIS IS IT RIGHT HERE BEHIND ME
AS I STEP OUT OF THE WAY, AND
LET JOE ZOOM IN.
THIS IS THE FRONT OF PLAZA
TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
THIS SCHOOL IS BASICALLY GONE.
>> Reporter: IN THE HOURS AFTER
THE TORNADO, DRAMATIC IMAGES,
YOUNG CHILDREN WERE RESCUED, AND
WITH DARKNESS, THE SEARCH FOR
SURVIVORS CONTINUED.
SOME CHILDREN HAD ESCAPED FROM
HARM.
THEIR PARENTS HAD PICKED THEM UP
JUST BEFORE THE SCHOOL WENT ON
LOCKDOWN MONDAY, BUT THE
MAJORITY STAYED INSIDE AS THEY
PRACTICED IN DRILLS MANY TIMES.
MATH TEACHER RHONDA CROSSWHITE
WAS HELPING HER SIXTH GRADERS
WITH AN END OF SCHOOL GAME WHEN
THE PRINCIPAL CAME OVER THE
LOUDSPEAKER AND TOLD THEM TO GO
TO THE HALLWAY.
DAMIAN KLINE IS A FOURTH GRADER.
>> SHE TOLD US ALL TO JUST GET
YOUR MATH BOOK OR YOUR BAG.
I ALREADY HAD MY BAG.
THEN WE WENT IN THE HALL.
>> Reporter: WHY DID SHE TELL
YOU TO GET A MATH BOOK OR A BAG?
>> SO WE COULD PUT IT OVER OUR
HEAD.
>> Reporter: A FIFTH GRADE
TEACHER SAW THE FUNNEL CLOUD
APPROACHING AND YELLED FOR
EVERYONE TO LEAVE THE HALLWAY
AND GET INTO CLOSETS OR
BATHROOMS.
>> HE SAID YOU'VE GOT TO GET
THEM IN THERE.
I SAID, OKAY, I'LL GET THEM IN.
I'LL STAY OUT HERE.
HE SAID, YOU'RE GETTING IN
THERE, TOO.
>> Reporter: SHE WAS IN A
BATHROOM STALL CROUCHED OVER
FOUR CHILDREN, AND SHE DID WHAT
TEACHERS DO.
>> I REMEMBER THE LITTLE BOY
SAYING I LOVE YOU, MISS
CROSSWHITE.
PLEASE DON'T LET ME DIE WITH
YOU.
WE ARE NOT DYING TODAY.
QUIT SAYING THAT.
AND I DID THE TEACHER THING THAT
WE'RE PROBABLY NOT SUPPOSED TO
DO, I PRAYED, AND I PRAYED OUT
LOUD.
>> WHAT DID YOU SAY?
>> I SAID, GOD PLEASE DON'T TAKE
THESE KIDS TODAY.
>> Reporter: THE CEILING CRASHED
DOWN ON THEM, BUT THE WALLS
STILL STOOD.
WHEN IT WAS QUIET AGAIN, SHE
SENT A SMALL BOY TO CLIMB UP THE
BATHROOM WALL AND LOOK OUT.
>> AND HE GOT UP THERE, AND HE
LOOKED DOWN AT ME, AND HE SAID,
THERE'S NOTHING LEFT.
>> Reporter: DAMIAN WAS IN THE
SAME BATHROOM CROUCHED UNDER A
SINK.
HOW LOUD WAS IT?
>> IT WAS PRETTY LOUD.
>> Reporter: WERE YOU SCARED?
>> MM-HMM.
THERE WAS A BUNCH OF PEOPLE
SCREAMING.
WE COULD HEAR THEM FROM THE
GIRLS RESTROOM.
>> Reporter: HIS MOM SPENT AN
ANXIOUS HOUR WONDERING IF HER
LITTLE BOY WAS STILL ALIVE, AND
NOW SHE WONDERS WHY THE SCHOOL
DIDN'T HAVE A BETTER SHELTER
PLAN.
>> WELL, I DEFINITELY THINK
EVERY SCHOOL IN
OKLAHOMA SHOULD HAVE AN
UNDERGROUND SHELTER.
IT SHOULDN'T TAKE A TORNADO THIS
SIZE AND THIS MANY KIDS HURT,
MISSING AND LOST THEIR LIVES TO
REALIZE THAT THEY NEED
UNDERGROUND SHELTERS.
>> Reporter: IT'S ACTUALLY
REMARKABLE HOW MANY CHILDREN DID
GET OUT OF THIS SCHOOL.
AND, BRIAN, MISS CROSSWHITE WAS
TELLING US THAT THEY HAD SORT OF
A FIREMEN'S BRIGADE GOING WITH
ADULTS HELPING SOME OF THE KIDS
OUT OF THE SCHOOL,
WALKING OVER A BOOKCASE, USING
IT AS STAIRS AND PASS THEM ALONG
FROM ONE ADULT TO THE NEXT TO
GET THEM TO SAFETY.
BUT WE'VE BEEN TOLD HOW HORRIBLE
THE SCENE WAS WITH CHILDREN
LYING EVERYWHERE, INJURED
CHILDREN, A LOT OF PARENTS COULD
BARELY TAKE IT.
>> TWO ISSUES EMERGED THERE, THE
BRAVERY OF THE TEACHERS AND,
SECOND, THIS ISSUE OF WHY THERE
WASN'T A SHELTER THERE.
AND WE'RE ACTUALLY GOING TO TAKE
THAT ON LATER IN THE BROADCAST.
KATE, THANKS FOR YOUR REPORTING
HERE TODAY ON THE GROUND.
>>> AGAIN, IF YOU WERE WITH US
WHEN THIS NEWS FIRST BROKE
YESTERDAY RIGHT ON THROUGH "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS" LAST NIGHT, YOU
HEARD OUR INTERVIEW, A VERY
EARLY TENTATIVE INTERVIEW
BY PHONE WITH THE MAYOR OF
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
WE ASKED HIM AT THE TIME A
QUESTION SO MANY PEOPLE HAVE,
WHERE DO YOU BEGIN?
WELL, WE'RE HAPPY TO WELCOME
MAYOR GLENN LEWIS HERE WITH US
TONIGHT.
MR. MAYOR, THANK YOU FOR MAKING
TIME.
LET'S USE THIS HOUSE AS AN
EXAMPLE.
I FOUND A PHOTOGRAPH OF TWO
YOUNG WOMEN ON THE FRONT YARD,
BUT I ALSO KNOW -- I'VE COVERED
A LOT OF THESE.
THIS COULD BE FROM 12 MILES
AWAY.
>> RIGHT.
>> THIS WOMAN IS SAID TO HAVE
SEVERAL YOUNG CHILDREN AT HOME.
THEY THINK SHE GOT OUT.
THEY'RE NOT SURE.
THIS IS ONE HOUSE IN YOUR TOWN.
WHERE DO YOU BEGIN?
>> PROBABLY AT THE VERY
BEGINNING WHERE IT STARTED RIGHT
BACK OVER HERE AT PLAZA TOWERS.
THAT'S KIND OF GROUND ZERO.
IT ACTUALLY STARTED ACROSS THE
STREET IN OKLAHOMA CITY.
BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY IS IN
OKLAHOMA CITY.
AND IT'S JUST AS DEVASTATED AS
PLAZA TOWERS.
THEY ACTUALLY HAD MORE OF A SAFE
ROOM.
PLAZA TOWERS IS ONE OF THE OLDER
SCHOOLS.
THE OLDER SCHOOLS DON'T HAVE
THEM.
ALL THE NEW SCHOOLS THAT ARE
BUILT HAVE SAFE ROOMS.
UNFORTUNATELY, THAT ONE DIDN'T.
>> WE SHOULD PROBABLY -- FOR
PEOPLE WHO DON'T KNOW
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, WE SHOULD
PROBABLY EMPHASIZE IN PLAIN
ENGLISH, NOT A WHOLE LOT OF
PEOPLE GETTING RICH HERE.
THIS IS A WORKING CLASS TOWN.
>> YES, SIR.
MOST OF THE PEOPLE HERE ARE
SCHOOLTEACHERS OR STATE
EMPLOYEES OR FEDERAL EMPLOYEES.
THEY WORK FOR THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT USUALLY AT
TINKERFIELD OR FAA.
>> THERE IS ALMOST A FAITH-BASED
FEMA HERE IN OKLAHOMA.
THERE'S ACTUAL FEMA HERE IN
OKLAHOMA.
THERE ARE PRIVATE DONORS, AND
I'VE BEEN ASSURED ALL DAY THAT
SO MANY PEOPLE WILL BE LINING UP
TO TAKE CARE OF THE GOOD PEOPLE
WHO HAVE BEEN HIT.
>> YES.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO COUNT ON THAT
TO REBUILD THIS CITY YET AGAIN
AFTER '99.
>> YES, SIR.
THAT IS FOR A FACT.
WE WILL REBUILD IT.
WE'VE ALREADY STARTED THE PLANS.
WE ACTUALLY STARTED THE PROCESS.
IF YOU LOOK OVER ACROSS THE
STREET AT THE HOSPITAL OVER
THERE, THEY'VE STARTED TO CLEAN
UP ALREADY.
WARREN PETERS ALREADY CLEANED UP
THEIR PARKING LOT.
THEY'RE WORKING ON IT.
THERE'S SO MANY TRUCKS THEY
CAN'T GET TO IT.
WE'VE STARTED THE PROCESS
ALREADY.
WE STARTED PUTTING UP STREET
SIGNS.
THAT'S THE FIRST THING YOU HAVE
TO DO.
PEOPLE SAY, WHY DO YOU DO STREET
SIGNS FIRST?
IT'S LIKE YOU TAKE
CARE OF THE PEOPLE THAT ARE
INJURED, THEN YOU START PUTTING
UP THE STREET SIGNS.
>> WHY?
>> WELL, YOU CAN'T FIND WHERE
YOU'RE AT.
IF YOU LIVED HERE FOR 30 YEARS,
YOU DON'T KNOW WHAT STREET IS.
>> IT DOESN'T LOOK LIKE HOME.
>> THE HOUSE DOESN'T LOOK THE
SAME EITHER.
>> I JUST WANTED TO JOIN
EVERYBODY WATCHING WISH YOU GOOD
LUCK.
THANK YOU FOR SPENDING TIME WITH
US TONIGHT.
MAYOR GLENN LEWIS HERE IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
>>> NOW, LET'S TALK ABOUT THE
WEATHER EVENT THAT CAUSED ALL
THIS.
WE'RE STANDING IN FRONT OF THE
WRECKAGE OF JUST ONE OF THESE
RESIDENTIAL HOMES.
WEATHER CHANNEL METEOROLOGIST
OUR OLD FRIEND JIM CANTORE IS
HERE WITH US.
JIM, YOU AND I WERE TALKING
BEFORE ABOUT A STATISTIC
THAT'S STARTING TO SURFACE TODAY
THAT THE SHEER ENERGY, THE
OUTPUT OF THIS STORM EQUALED THE
BOMB IGNITED IN HIROSHIMA.
>> WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT THAT
BLAST, CERTAINLY THAT IS AN
AMAZING ANALOGY.
I MEAN YOU JUST HAVE TONS OF
DEBRIS EVERYWHERE.
BRIAN, UNRECOGNIZABLE.
IT'S HARD TO IMAGINE ANYONE
COULD SURVIVE IN THIS.
>> NOW, SAFE ROOMS.
LET'S TALK ABOUT IT AND LET'S
TALK ABOUT WHAT THIS REGION
NEEDS TO DO.
>> THEY DO.
I MEAN, IF WE'RE GOING TO PUT
OUR KIDS IN A HALL AND TEACH
THEM HOW TO CROUCH AND HOLD
THEIR HANDS OVER THEIR HEAD, WE
HAVE TO HAVE A PLACE THAT'S NOT
GOING TO BE BLOWN APART.
WE HAVE TO HAVE BUILDINGS THAT
CAN SUSTAIN THE TYPE OF DAMAGE
THAT THEY'RE USED TO HERE,
OBVIOUSLY.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT
200-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS.
THAT'S THE FIRST THING AND
OBVIOUSLY A BIG THING THEY NEED
TO ADDRESS.
PEOPLE'S HOMES.
I WAS DOWN IN TUSCALOOSA, AS
WERE YOU, AND AFTER THE 27,
APRIL 2011 OUTBREAK, WE SAW THEM
BUILD BACK HOMES FOR $75,000
WITH SAFE ROOMS.
>> WITH SHELTERS.
>> WITH SAFE ROOMS IN THEM.
SO THIS IS NOT AN UNDOABLE
THING.
>> NOW, BRING US UP TO DATE.
WE MENTIONED SEVEN DIFFERENT
STATES HAVE WATCHES AND
WARNINGS.
TONIGHT AS WE STAND HERE
TALKING --
>> A WEEK AND A HALF AGO THE
ATMOSPHERE DECIDED
WE'RE GOING TO PULL A SWITCH,
AND ALL OF A SUDDEN
THE TORNADO DROUGHT IS OVER AND
YOU'VE SEEN THE RESULTS OF THAT.
WHAT WE'RE LOOKING AT TONIGHT IS
THUNDERSTORMS ALL THE WAY REALLY
FROM NEW YORK AND CONNECTICUT ON
DOWN THROUGH TENNESSEE.
SHREVEPORT IS CERTAINLY GOING TO
FACE SOME OF THESE THUNDERSTORMS
TONIGHT, AUSTIN, TEXAS, MEMPHIS
TENNESSEE, AS WELL.
TORNADO WATCHES.
>> JIM CANTORE, THANK YOU FOR
BEING PART OF THE COVERAGE.
>> ALWAYS, ALWAYS.
>> WE'LL TAKE A BREAK IN OUR
COVERAGE.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'RE GOING
TO TALK MORE ABOUT THIS BUILDING
CODE AND SHELTER ISSUE HERE IN
THIS DEVASTATED TOWN OF MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
>>> WELCOME BACK.
HERE IN THE STATE OF OKLAHOMA,
THE EXPRESSION "THIS HARD LAND"
COMES TO MIND, AND IT'S TRUE IN
MORE WAYS THAN ONE.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT IT, THE
NATIONAL CONFERENCE OF TORNADO
PREPARATION IS HELD IN OKLAHOMA
CITY, AND THEY DO THAT EVERY
YEAR FOR A REASON.
THIS WEATHER IS A SURPRISE TO NO
ONE, AND FOR THE MOST PART
THEY'RE READY FOR IT WHEN IT
COMES.
BUT NATIONWIDE, ESPECIALLY
PEOPLE ON BOTH COASTS ARE ASKING
WHY AREN'T THERE MORE SHELTERS,
CELLARS, BASEMENTS?
WHY AREN'T THERE MORE SAFE
HOUSES WITHIN HOUSES ACROSS THIS
REGION GIVEN THE WEATHER HERE?
OUR REPORT ON THAT TONIGHT FROM
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO.
>> Reporter: YET ANOTHER
DEVASTATING TORNADO, AND SO MANY
PEOPLE ARE ASKING, WHY AREN'T
THERE MORE BASEMENTS IN THE VERY
PLACE THEY NEED THEM MOST,
TORNADO ALLEY, AND WHY AREN'T
THERE MORE TORNADO SHELTERS?
MANY OF THOSE WHO MANAGED TO GET
UNDERGROUND SURVIVED.
>> IT RIPPED OPEN THE DOOR, AND
IT -- JUST GLASS AND DEBRIS
STARTED SLAMMING ON US.
WE THOUGHT WE WERE DEAD, TO BE
HONEST.
>> Reporter: BASEMENTS ARE NOT
COMMON IN OKLAHOMA BECAUSE THE
SOIL, HEAVY WITH CLAY AND WATER,
MAKES ANYTHING UNDERGROUND PRONE
TO FLOODING AND MOLD.
SO MOST HOMES ARE BUILT ON A
CONCRETE SLAB.
AND MOST HOMES CAN ONLY
WITHSTAND 90-MILE-PER-HOUR
WINDS, NOT 200.
>> WE JUST DON'T DESIGN HOMES ON
THE INTERIOR OF THIS COUNTRY TO
WITHSTAND THE WINDS THE SAME WAY
THEY WOULD DO ALONG THE COAST.
>> Reporter: BUT BUILDING A SAFE
ROOM FOR A SHELTER IS A
DIFFERENT MATTER.
A RESIDENTIAL
SAFE ROOM CAN BE INSTALLED IN
THE GROUND OR INSIDE THE HOME
ITSELF.
A REINFORCED BOX ALMOST LIKE A
BANK VAULT BUT BUILT TO FEMA
TORNADO STANDARDS, BUT THEY COST
8,000 TO $10,000 EACH.
OKLAHOMA HAS A LOTTERY TO DECIDE
WHO GETS STATE HELP TO PAY FOR
THEM.
LAST YEAR 500 HOMEOWNERS WERE
CHOSEN OUT OF 16,000 APPLICANTS.
SEPARATELY, THE CITY OF MOORE
WAS APPLYING FOR $2 MILLION IN
FEDERAL AID TO HELP BUILD SAFE
ROOMS IN 800 HOMES, BUT THE CITY
COMPLAINED THAT THE PROGRAM WAS
DELAYED BECAUSE FEMA STANDARDS
WERE, QUOTE, A CONSTANTLY
CHANGING TARGET.
FEMA SAYS IT'S LOOKING INTO WHAT
CAUSED THE DELAY.
SO WHY WEREN'T SCHOOLS BETTER
PREPARED?
>> I KNOW CERTAINLY YESTERDAY
RAISED A LOT OF QUESTIONS WITH
PEOPLE, WHY DON'T SCHOOLS
HAVE STORM SHELTERS?
>> Reporter: TODAY STATE
OFFICIALS SAID 100 SCHOOLS DO
HAVE SAFE ROOMS, BUT THEY'RE
EXPENSIVE.
LIVE
THE FEMA ESTIMATE, $1.4 MILLION
PER SCHOOL.
>> WHEN YOU HAVE A LIMITED
NUMBER OF FUNDS, YOU SET
PRIORITIES ON WHICH SCHOOLS YOU
DO WANT TO ASK FOR.
NOT A MATTER THEY WOULD BE LEFT
OUT FOR ANY REASON.
IT WAS A MATTER THEY HADN'T BEEN
BROUGHT FORWARD YET.
>> Reporter: THE TOWN OF MOORE
HAD NOT BUILT ANY COMMUNITY
TORNADO SHELTERS BECAUSE THE
TOWN SAID IT FACED ONLY A 1% TO
2% CHANCE OF A TORNADO EVER
HITTING ON ANY SPRING DAY.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC NEWS.
>>> A LOT OF TOUGH QUESTIONS
BEING ASKED HERE TODAY.
AND WE'LL BE BACK WITH MORE FROM
HERE RIGHT AFTER THIS.
For our families...
our neighbors...
and our communities...
America's beverage companies
have created...
a wide range of new choices.
Developing smaller portion sizes
and more..
low and no-calorie
beverages...
adding clear calorie labels so
you know...
exactly what you're choosing...
and in schools, replacing
full-calorie soft drinks...
with lower-calorie options.
With more choices and fewer
calories...
America's Beverage Companies are
delivering.
>>> BACK HERE IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, LET'S SPEND A MOMENT
TALKING ABOUT THE TRUE FIRST
RESPONDERS, THE RESCUE TEAMS,
THE NATIONAL GUARD.
REMEMBER, WHEN THEY WALK THROUGH
AREAS LIKE THIS, THEY'RE WALKING
THROUGH HOME.
THEIR STORY TONIGHT FROM NBC'S
GABE GUTIERREZ.
>> Reporter: ON A SOGGY,
MISERABLE AFTERNOON IN OKLAHOMA,
THE SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS HIT
HOME.
>> WORDS CAN'T DESCRIBE
EVERYTHING WE HAVE SEEN RIGHT
NOW.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE
OKLAHOMA NATIONAL GUARD, MORE
THAN 200 SOLDIERS AND AIRMEN
CALLED TO DUTY.
AROUND THE CLOCK FRANTIC SEARCH
AFTER THE MASSIVE TWISTER.
>> AS A FATHER OF TWO YOUNG
ELEMENTARY STUDENTS, IT HURTS
KNOWING THAT THERE ARE CHILDREN
LOST.
>> Reporter: SERGEANT MIKE BELL
IS AN ARMY RESERVIST.
HE GREW UP IN THIS STATE AND WAS
PART OF THE SEARCH AND RESCUE
TEAM 14 YEARS AGO DURING ANOTHER
HUGE TWISTER.
>> A THOUSAND TIMES WORSE.
IT'S LIKE A WAR ZONE.
>> Reporter: THE RESCUE AND
RECOVERY EFFORT IS NOT LIMITED
TO THOSE IN UNIFORM.
15-YEAR-OLD MORGAN SMITH RODE
OUT THE STORM IN AN UNDERGROUND
SHELTER.
WHEN SHE EMERGED, A NEIGHBOR WAS
TRAPPED IN THE DEBRIS ACROSS THE
STREET.
>> ME AND MY MOM RAN ACROSS THE
STREET AND CAME OVER HERE.
AND WE DUG HER OUT OF LIKE WHERE
THAT RED THING IS, SHE WAS DOWN
RIGHT BEHIND THAT.
>> Reporter: RESCUERS HAVE NOW
SCOURED THIS NEIGHBORHOOD AT
LEAST TWICE.
ON THIS PASS ALL THEY FIND IS
EMPTY HOMES.
SERGEANT MIKE BELL SAYS HE HAD
TO BE HERE.
THIS IS PERSONAL.
THIS IS HOME.
>> AS AN OKLAHOMAN, IT HURTS.
>> Reporter: HIS STAKE CHANGED
FOREVER.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC NEWS, MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
INFORMATION FOR ALL THOSE
LOOKING TO HELP THE FOLKS HERE.
>> A TEACHER SAVED MY LIFE.
>>> WE'VE TRIED TO MAKE THIS
EASY ON YOU BY ASSEMBLING A LIST
ON OUR WEBSITE OF ALL THE RELIEF
AGENCIES BECAUSE SO MANY OF OUR
VIEWERS HAVE ASKED US FOR HELP,
THEY WOULD LIKE TO HELP THE
FOLKS HERE.
AND A REMINDER FOR SOME OF YOU,
THIS WILL BE A SPECIAL HOUR-LONG
EDITION OF NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS."
WE'LL KEEP GOING FOR THE NEXT
HOUR.
IF YOUR STATION DOESN'T STAY
WITH US,
WE'LL BE STREAMING OUR COVERAGE
LIVE ON THAT VERY SAME WEBSITE.
WE'RE ALSO BACK ON THE AIR, A
PRIME TIME SPECIAL AT 8:00 P.M.,
7:00 CENTRAL TIME OF WHAT
HAPPENED HERE.
THAT'S THE FIRST HALF OF OUR
COVERAGE TONIGHT.
I'M BRIAN WILLIAMS IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
>>> DEVASTATION IN OKLAHOMA.
THIS IS NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
BRIAN WILLIAMS REPORTING TONIGHT
FROM MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
>> AND WELCOME BACK TO THOSE OF
YOU FOLLOWING US ON OUR LOCAL
NBC STATIONS TO WHAT IS OUR
SECOND HALF HOUR, SPECIAL
HOUR-LONG COVERAGE TONIGHT FROM
THIS DEVASTATED CITY OF MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA CITY
WHERE WE'VE HAD CONFIRMATION
TODAY THESE WERE SOME OF THE
STRONGEST WINDS ON EARTH.
AN EF-5 TORNADO.
THAT IS THE STRONGEST POSSIBLE
CATEGORY.
WE WOKE UP TO SOME GOOD NEWS.
THE WILDLY FLUCTUATING DEATH
TOLL, WHICH STOOD AT 51 WHEN SO
MANY AMERICANS WENT TO BED LAST
NIGHT, ROSE TO 91 OVERNIGHT IN