AND NBC NIGHTLY NEWS IS COMING
UP NEXT.
WE WILL SEE YOU AT 6:00.
>>> ON THIS SUNDAY
NIGHT, PALM SUNDAY
ATTACKS.
A STATE OF EMERGENCY
DECLARED IN EGYPT
AFTER DEADLY BOMBINGS
AT TWO CHURCHES, MORE
THAN 40 PEOPLE KILLED,
MANY OF THEM CHILDREN,
AS ISIS CLAIMS
RESPONSIBILITY.
>>> RISING TENSIONS.
THE NEW TOUGH TALK
ABOUT RUSSIA AND SYRIA
AS THE SECRETARY OF
STATE LEAVES ON A
MISSION TO MOSCOW AND
ANOTHER KEY WHITE
HOUSE OFFICIALS IS
FORCED OUT.
>>> WAKE-UP CALL FOR
AMERICAN CITIES AFTER
COMPUTER HACKERS
TRIGGERED MORE THAN
150 EMERGENCY SIRENS
IN DALLAS, EXPOSING
VULNERABILITY THERE
AND BEYOND.
>>> AND DRAMATIC
IMPROVEMENT.
THE SIMPLE TREATMENT
FOR PEOPLE WITH
PARKINSON'S THAT SLOWS
THE DISEASE AND
CHANGES LIVES.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN
NEW YORK, THIS IS "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
KATE SNOW.
>> GOOD EVENING.
AT THE BEGINNING OF
THE HOLIEST WEEK ON
THE CHRISTIAN
CALENDAR, CHURCHES
WERE PACKED ALL OVER
THE WORLD TODAY, AND
WHEN ISIS TARGETED
EGYPT'S CHRISTIAN
MINORITY WITH BOMBINGS
AT TWO CHURCHES IN
CITIES NORTH OF CAIRO,
THE LOSS OF LIFE AND
DEVASTATION WERE
EXTENSIVE.
A STATE OF EMERGENCY
HAS BEEN DECLARED AND
THE MILITARY DEPLOYED
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
THE ATTACKS COMES
POPE FRANCIS IS SET TO
VISIT EGYPT LATER THIS
MONTH, A TRIP THE
VATICAN SAYS WILL GO
ON AS PLANNED.
OUR MATT BRADLEY IS IN
CAIRO TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: A DAY OF
DEVOTION TURNED TO
HORROR.
A CROWDED PALM SUNDAY
MASS IN CAIRO, RIPPED
APART BY WHAT THEY
BELIEVE WAS A BOMB
PLACED UNDER A PEW.
HOURS LATER A SUICIDE
BOMBER SCENE AT ST.
MARK'S CHURCH IN
ALEXANDRIA.
SECURITY SHOWS A MAN
BLOWING HIMSELF UP
FEET AWAY FROM A
PLAYING CHILD, AFTER
POLICE STOPPED HIM
FROM ENTERING THE
CHURCH.
THAT OFFICER NOW HAIL
AS A HERO.
THE TWIN BOMBINGS HAVE
LEFT AT LEAST 43 DEAD,
MORE THAN 100 INJURED
AND THE MIDDLE EAST
LARGEST CHRISTIAN
COMMUNITY IN SHOCK.
MANY OF THE DEAD ARE
CHILDREN.
"THE SITUATION IS
PAINFUL" A RELATIVE OF
ONE OF THE VICTIMS
SAID.
"WHY WEREN'T PROPER
MEASURES TAKEN TO
PROTECT THE PEOPLE?"
ISIS QUICKLY CLAIMED
RESPONSIBILITY FOR
BOTH ATTACKS,
FULFILLING A PLEDGE
MADE IN FEBRUARY TO
TARGET EGYPTIAN
CHRISTIANS.
ISIS ATTACKS
CHRISTIANS WITH
HORRIFYING REGULARITY.
EGYPTIAN PRESIDENT AL
SISI MET WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP LAST
WEEK.
THE TWO LEADERS
PLEDGED TO FIGHT ISIS
TERROR TOGETHER.
>> I WANT TO SAY TO
YOU, MR. PRESIDENT,
THAT YOU HAVE A GREAT
FRIEND AND ALLY IN THE
UNITED STATES AND IN
ME.
>> Reporter: MR. TRUMP
TWEETING AFTER TODAY'S
ATTACKS HE HAS "GREAT
CONFIDENCE" IN THE
EGYPTIAN LEADER, BUT
EXPERTS ARE NOT
CONFIDENT IN WHAT SO
FAR APPEARS TO BE
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
UNCLEAR MIDDLE EAST
POLICY.
>> ISIS AND ITS
AFFILIATES ATTACKS
AGAINST THE
TWO CHURCHES REALLY
SHOW THE INABILITY OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP TO
UNDERSTAND THE
COMPLEXITY AND THE
GRAVITY OF THE CRISIS
IN THE MIDDLE EAST.
>> Reporter: A
VULNERABLE MINORITY
FOR WHOM ISIS REMAINS
THE TOP CONCERN.
IN THE AFTERMATH OF
THESE TRULY TERRIBLE
ATTACKS, MANY EGYPTIAN
CHRISTIANS ARE TURNING
THEIR ANGER ON THE
GOVERNMENT.
THERE WERE PROTESTS IN
ALEXANDRIA TODAY
DEMANDING BETTER
SECURITY, AND IN
ADDITION TO ANNOUNCING
A THREE-MONTH STATE OF
EMERGENCY, PRESIDENT
SISI HAS FIRED A TOP
MINISTRY OF INTERIOR
OFFICIAL.
KATE?
>> MATT BRADLEY IN
CAIRO TONIGHT, MATT,
THANK YOU.
>>> IN THIS COUNTRY
THE MANHUNT
INTENSIFIED FOR A
HEAVILY ARMED SUSPECT
AUTHORITIES SAY STOLE
MORE THAN A DOZEN
HIGH-POWERED GUNS IN
WISCONSIN AND SENT
PRESIDENT TRUMP AN
ANTI-GOVERNMENT
MANIFESTO.
NBC'S BLAKE McCOY HAS
THE NEW DETAILS.
>> Reporter: THE
DESPERATE HUNT FOR
JOSEPH JAKABOWSKI
STRETCHING INTO A
FIFTH DAY, A MAN
AUTHORITIES FEAR MAY
BE PLANNING TO ATTACK
SCHOOLS, CHURCHES OR
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS.
TODAY 50 MILES FROM
WHERE HE WAS LAST SEEN
ON SURVEILLANCE
CAMERAS, SECURITY
STEPPED UP AT
CHURCHES.
>> WE ENHANCED OUR
ENTRY AREA BY HAVING
USHERS AND DEACONS AT
THE DOORS.
THE DOORS WERE ALL
LOCKED.
THE LOCAL POLICE
DEPARTMENT WERE
FANTASTIC.
>> Reporter: SERVICE
AT THIS CHURCH IN SUN
PRAIRIE WERE KHAN
CERTIFIED AFTER
REPORTS OF A MAN ASKS
SUSPICIOUS QUESTIONS
EARLIER IN THE WEEK.
>> WE DON'T KNOW IF
THE GUY WAS THE SAME
PERSON, WE CAN'T ASK
THAT QUESTION BUT
WE'RE DOING WHAT WE
CAN TO MAKE SURE
EVERYBODY IS PREPARED.
>> Reporter: FOOD
ANOTHER POSSIBLE
SIGHTING REPORTED IN
DARLINGTON, WISCONSIN,
ABOUT 65 MILES FROM
JANESVILLE.
>> WE DON'T KNOW IF
HE'S IN JANES ADVISE,
WISCONSIN OR SOMEWHERE
ELSE IN THE NATION.
>> Reporter: 400 TIPS
HAVE POURED IN BUT SO
FAR AS HE ALLUDE
ELUDED MORE THAN 150
LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICERS SEARCHING FOR
HIM.
>> YOU ARE HEARING ON
THE NEWS IT HAPPENED
OVER HERE, OVER THERE.
IT IS LIKE, WOW, IN
JANESVILLE?
>> Reporter: POLICE
SAY HE HAS A BULLET
PROOF VEST, A HELMET
AND ARSENAL OF WEAPONS
STOLEN FROM THIS GUN
STORE.
>> WE KNOW THERE WERE
LONG GUNS STOLEN, WE
KNOW HANDGUNS WERE
STOLEN.
>> Reporter: THE
BIGGEST CLUE
AUTHORITIES ARE
WORKING ON, THIS
CELLPHONE VIDEO TAKEN
AS HE MAILED A
161-PAGE MANIFESTO
ADDRESSED TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
>> REVOLUTION.
IT'S TIME FOR CHANGE.
>> Reporter: POLICE
HAVE NOW INTERVIEWED
THE MAN WHO TOOK THE
VIDEO AND SAY HE IS
COOPERATING.
>> TODAY IS THE DAY.
SO REMEMBER THIS FACE.
>> GAME TIME.
>> HE DOESN'T CARE IF
YOU KNOW HIM.
THIS IS THE END GAME
FOR HIM.
THERE'S NO ESCAPE
PLAN.
THE ONLY PLAN IS THE
ATTACK PLAN.
>> Reporter: KIDS IN
JANESVILLE ARE ON
SPRING BREAK THIS WEEK
SO SCHOOLS WERE GOING
TO BE CLOSED TOMORROW.
POLICE ARE STEPPING UP
PATROLS AT OTHER
POTENTIAL TARGETS AND
WARN THIS MAN COULD BE
ANYWHERE.
KATE?
>> VERY SCARY.
BLAKE McCOY, THANK
YOU.
>>> SECRETARY OF STATE
REX TILLERSON ARRIVED
IN EUROPE TONIGHT FOR
CRUCIAL AND HIGHLY
ANTICIPATED MEETINGS
WITH THE RUSSIANS.
THE TWO NATIONS HAVE
TRADED CONDEMNATIONS
AND WARNINGS SINCE THE
U.S. FIRED CRUISE
MISSILES AT SYRIA LAST
WEEK.
TENSIONS COMPLICATING
THE RELATIONSHIP
BETWEEN MOSCOW AND
WASHINGTON.
NBC'S KELLY O'DONNELL
HAS MORE ON WHAT'S AT
STAKE.
>> Reporter: UNDER THE
RADAR, NO MORE.
REX TILLERSON, THE
MEDIA WARY --
>> NO COMMENT.
>> Reporter: --
LOW-KEY SECRETARY OF
STATE IS EMERGING
WEEKS AFTER TAKING
OFFICE.
TODAY HIS FIRST SUNDAY
SHOW INTERVIEWS.
>> I HOPE THAT RUSSIA
IS THINKING CAREFULLY
ABOUT ITS CONTINUED
ALLIANCE WITH BASHAR
AL ASSAD.
>> Reporter: A STERN
MESSAGE TILLERSON IS
EXPECTED TO TAKE TO
RUSSIA WHERE HE WILL
MEET WITH THE FOREIGN
MINISTER THIS WEEK.
WITH HIS OWN
ESTABLISHED TIES TO
VLADIMIR PUTIN FROM
HIS FORMER OIL
EXECUTIVE DAYS, A
PUTIN MEETING MAY ALSO
BE POSSIBLE.
>> HOW HE REACTS TO
SECRETARY TILLERSON,
THE KINDS OF SIGNALS
HE SAYS IN TERMS OF
THE FUTURE, THAT'S
WHAT WE NEED TO BE
WATCHING.
>> Reporter: TENSE
RELATIONS.
DAMAGED BY RUSSIA'S
PROTECTION OF SYRIA'S
ASSAD REGIME AND
CLOUDED BY PUTIN'S
INTERFERENCE IN THE
2016 ELECTION, WITH
ONGOING INVESTIGATIONS
BY CONGRESS AND THE
FBI.
IN MOSCOW, NBC'S BILL
NEELEY.
>> Reporter: HERE IN
MOSCOW, THE KREMLIN
WANTS CLARITY FROM REX
TILLERSON.
WHAT IS AMERICA'S
STRATEGY IN SYRIA?
WHAT ABOUT ASSAD?
DOES PRESIDENT TRUMP
WANT BETTER RELATIONS
WITH PUTIN OR MORE
MISSILE STRIKES?
AGREEMENT, UNLIKELY.
>> Reporter: TODAY
U.N. AM BASSOR NIKKI
HALEY BLASTED RUSSIA
OVER SYRIA'S CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
>> THEIR INITIAL
REACTION WAS, ASSAD
DIDN'T DO IT, THE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT
DIDN'T DO IT.
>> Reporter: IN 2013
PUTIN PROMISED THAT
RUSSIA'S INFLUENCE
WOULD STOP ASSAD'S USE
OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
>> RUSSIA HAS FAILED
IN THAT COMMITMENT,
AND THE RESULT OF
THEIR FAILURE HAS LED
TO THE KILLING OF MORE
CHILDREN AND
INNOCENTS.
>> Reporter: THE
TILLERSON MISSION TO
MOSCOW COMES AS THE
WHITE HOUSE NATIONAL
SECURITY TEAM IS
RESHAPED.
NEW TONIGHT, K.T.
McFARLAND CHOSEN BY
OUSTED ADVISER MICHAEL
FLYNN, IS OUT, OFFERED
AN AMBASSADORSHIP.
FOLLOWING REMOVAL OF
POLITICAL STRATEGIST
STEVE BANNON FROM THE
NATIONAL SECURITY
COUNCIL BY NEW
ADVISER H.R.
McMASTER.
>> STEVE BANNON
PROVIDES THE PRESIDENT
WITH ADVICE ON A BROAD
RANGE OF ISSUES AND
WILL CONTINUE TO DO
SO.
>> Reporter: AS
NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER, McMASTER SAYS
RUSSIA SHOULD BE
COMPELLED TO EXPLAIN
HOW IT COULD NOT HAVE
KNOWN IN ADVANCE ABOUT
THE CHEMICAL ATTACK IN
SYRIA WHEN SOME OF ITS
OWN PERSONNEL ARE
STATIONED AT THE VERY
BASE FROM WHICH THAT
ATTACK WAS LAUNCHED.
A TOUGH ISSUE FOR
SECRETARY TILLERSON IN
RUSSIA THIS WEEK.
KATE?
>> KELLY O'DONNELL
DOWN IN FLORIDA.
KELLY, THANK YOU.
>>> THE U.S. IS ALSO
ENGAGING IN A POWERFUL
SHOW OF FORCE TONIGHT
AIMED AT NORTH KOREA.
A U.S. NAVY STRIKE
GROUP IS HEADED TOWARD
THE KOREAN PENINSULA
AFTER DAYS OF GROWING
TENSIONS.
NBC'S JANIS MACKEY
FRAYER IS IN SEOUL,
SOUTH KOREA, JANICE?
>> Reporter: KATE,
TENSION HERE IS
NOTHING NEW.
THE U.S. STRIKE ON
SYRIA IS WIDELY SEEN
AS A MESSAGE TO
KIM JONG-UN THAT THE
U.S. IS WILLING TO
STRIKE NORTH KOREA
ALSO.
THEY HAVE ORDERED THE
"USS CARL VINSON" TO
HEAD TO THE KOREAN
PENINSULA BECAUSE OF
RECENT PROVOCATIONS.
THIS AMERICAN SHOW OF
FORCE IS MET WITH A
DEFIANT VOW FROM THE
NORTH TO BOLSTER ITS
OWN DEFENSES, SAYING
THE STRIKE ON SYRIA IS
JUSTIFICATION FOR THE
REGIME'S NEEDS FOR A
NUCLEAR ARSENAL.
THE CONCERN OF A U.S.
STRIKE ON NORTH KOREA
COUNTERATTACK, THE
NORTH HAS MISSILES
POINTED AT SEOUL AND
THERE ARE 28,000 U.S.
MILITARY PERSONNEL
STATIONED IN SOUTH
KOREA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
BEEN PRESSING CHINA'S
LEADER TO REIN IN THE
NORTH.
THE TWO MET
FACE-TO-FACE FOR THE
FIRST TIME LAST WEEK,
JUST 48 HOURS AFTER
NORTH KOREA'S LATEST
MISSILE TEST.
THESE ARE CAUTIOUS
TIMES, WITH THE U.S.
WEIGHING OPTIONS,
NORTH KOREA MARKING
KEY ANNIVERSARIES THIS
MONTH, AND SPECULATION
KIM JONG-UN MAY BE
PREPARING FOR A SIXTH
NUCLEAR TEST.
KATE?
>> JANIS, THANK YOU.
>>> NEW DETAILS ABOUT
THE SUSPECT IN THE
DEADLY TRUCK ATTACK IN
STOCKHOLM, SWEDEN, TWO
DAYS AGO.
OFFICIALS SAY THE
SUSPECT FROM
UZBEKISTAN WAS ORDERED
TO LEAVE SWEDEN IN
DECEMBER AFTER HE WAS
DENIED PERMANENT
RESIDENCY.
POLICE ALSO SAID A
SECOND SUSPECT IN THE
ATTACK HAS BEEN
ARRESTED.
FOUR PEOPLE WERE
KILLED.
>>> THERE'S A SHOWDOWN
COMING TOMORROW IN
ALABAMA, WHERE THE
GOVERNOR FACES A
HEARING IN THE
LEGISLATURE ON WHETHER
HE SHOULD BE
IMPEACHED.
HE IS ACCUSED OF
MISUSING HIS OFFICE,
AND AS NBC'S SARAH
DOLLOPP REPORTS, IT
STEMS FROM A
PERSONAL RELATIONSHIP.
>> Reporter: WHAT
BEGAN AS AN ALLEGED
AFFAIR BETWEEN
ALABAMA'S GOVERNOR AND
AN AIDE IS AT THE
CENTER OF AN EFFORT TO
IMPEACH HIM.
HEARINGS SET TO BEGIN.
AGAINST TWO-TERM
MEMBER ROBERT BENTLEY.
A SEX SCANDAL ENGULFED
HIS ADMINISTRATION
LAST YEAR WHEN GRAPHIC
RECORDINGS OF PHONE
CONVERSATIONS BETWEEN
THE GOVERNOR AND TOP
AIDE REBECCA MASON
CAME TO LIGHT.
>> WHEN I STAND BEHIND
YOU AND I PUT MY ARMS
AROUND YOU --
>> Reporter: WHILE THE
GOVERNOR DENIES HAVING
A PHYSICAL AFFAIR WITH
THE WOMAN, HE
APOLOGIZED TO HIS
CONSTITUENTS ON
FRIDAY, VOWING TO
REMAIN IN OFFICE.
>> I DO NOT PLAN TO
RESIGN.
I HAVE DONE NOTHING
ILLEGAL.
>> Reporter: TWO
SEPARATE
INVESTIGATIONS BY A
LEGISLATIVE COMMITTEE
AND STATE ETHICS
OFFICIALS FOUND
PROBABLE CAUSE THAT
BENTLEY VIOLATED
ETHICS AND CAMPAIGN
LAW BY USING STATE LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICERS
AND OTHER RESOURCES TO
TRY TO KEEP THE
RECORDINGS FROM GOING
PUBLIC.
>> BUT SEEING THIS
EMBARRASSMENT TO OUR
STATE RIGHT NOW --
>> Reporter: IF HE IS
FOUND GUILTY, BENTLEY
WOULD BE ONLY THE
NINTH GOVERNOR IN U.S.
HISTORY TO BE REMOVED
FROM OFFICE.
HIS FATE NOW IN THE
HANDS OF THE ALABAMA
LEGISLATURE.
SARAH DOLLOF, NBC
NEWS.
>>> CITIES AND TOWNS
THROUGHOUT THE UNITED
STATES ARE WAITING TO
SEE WHAT BECOMES OF
THE PRESIDENT'S PLAN
TO REBUILD THE
COUNTRY'S
INFRASTRUCTURE.
THE NEED WAS
HIGHLIGHTED
DRAMATICALLY OVER THE
LAST COUPLE OF WEEKS
BY DERAILMENTS AT PENN
STATION HERE IN NEW
YORK CITY.
WE GET MORE FROM NBC'S
MORGAN RADFORD.
>> Reporter: TWO
DERAILMENTS IN JUST 11
DAYS.
>> WE WILL BE
DIRECTING YOU THE
SAFEST WAY TO EVACUATE
THE TRAIN.
>> Reporter: TRAIN
SERVICE COMING TO A
HALT IN NEW YORK,
LEAVING HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF COMMUTERS
STRANDED.
>> I'M STANDING ON THE
TRAIN, I'M PAYING SO
MUCH MONEY.
IT IS NOT WORTH IT TO
ME.
>> Reporter: EXPERTS
SAY THE DERAILMENTS
PROVE OUR NATION'S
RAILWAY SYSTEM IS
SIMPLY TOO OLD.
>> I THINK IT SHOULD
SERVE AS A WAKE-UP
CALL.
IT'S A REALIZATION OF
HOW FRAGILE THE ENTIRE
SYSTEM IS.
>> Reporter: TAKE
NEW YORK'S PENN
STATION.
MORE THAN 10 MILLION
RIDERS PASS THROUGH
EACH YEAR.
THAT'S MORE THAN 1,300
TRAINS PER DAY, DOUBLE
THE NUMBER FROM THE
'70s.
>> IT IS NOTHING SHORT
OF CATASTROPHIC.
>> Reporter: JOHN IS
THE CURRENT HEAD OF
THE GATEWAY PROJECT, A
$24 BILLION PROPOSAL
DESIGNED TO DOUBLE THE
CAPACITY OF TRAINS
ALONG THE NORTHEAST
CORRIDOR, INCLUDING
PENN STATION.
>> THIS IS THE MOST
URGENT INFRASTRUCTURE
PROJECT IN AMERICA.
IT CAN'T GO FORWARD
WITHOUT FEDERAL
COMMITMENT, IT CAN'T.
THIS IS COMPLETELY IN
JEOPARDY.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP PROMISED A
TRILLION DOLLAR
INFRASTRUCTURE PLAN,
BUT WHEN HE REVEALED
HIS BUDGET IN MARCH,
IT SHOWED A $2.4
BILLION CUT FROM THE
TRANSPORTATION BUDGET.
TOP DEMOCRATS SAY OUR
FUTURE DEPENDS ON NEW
IMPROVEMENTS.
>> IT IS VITAL TO OUR
NORTHEAST ECONOMY AND
IT MAKES A WORLD OF
SENSE.
>> Reporter: THE
REALITY OF IT IS, THIS
IS ALSO BIGGER THAN
GIST NEW YORK.
>> THIS IS A NATIONAL
ISSUE AND WHETHER IT'S
THE LOCKS AND DAMS IN
THE MIDWEST OR IT'S
AGING BRIDGES AND
TUNNELS, HIGHWAY
SYSTEMS, AIRPORTS, WE
ARE WAY BEHIND AS A
COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: A COUNTRY
MOVING FORWARD ONE
STEP AND ONE RIDE AT A
TIME.
>> ON WEDNESDAY
PRESIDENT TRUMP TOLD
THE "NEW YORK TIMES"
HE PLANNED TO PRESENT
A TRILLION-DOLLAR
INFRASTRUCTURE PLAN TO
CONGRESS, BUT WOULDN'T
SPECIFY WHETHER
PROPOSALS LIKE THE
GATEWAY PROJECT WOULD,
IN FACT, BE INCLUDED,
KATE.
>> MORGAN, THANK YOU
SO MUCH.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, THE COMPUTER
HACKING ATTACK THAT
WOKE UP A MAJOR
AMERICAN CITY IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE NIGHT,
SOUNDING ALARMS ABOUT
INFRASTRUCTURE
SECURITY AROUND THE
COUNTRY.
>>> FOR A LOT OF US
CONCERNS ABOUT
COMPUTER HACKING ARE
FOCUSED ON THE
PERSONAL STUFF, STOLEN
IDENTITIES OR P.I.N.
NUMBERS OR SOMEONE
LOOKING AT YOUR
EMAILS WITHOUT
PERMISSION, BUT
TONIGHT THE 7MILLION
RESIDENTS OF DALLAS
HAVE PROOF THAT A HACK
ATTACK CAN MEAN
CITY-SIZE TROUBLE, AS
STEVE PATTERSON
REPORTS WHAT HAPPENED
THERE IS RAISING THE
ALARM FOR A LOT OF
AMERICAN CITIES AND
TOWNS.
[ SIRENS ]
>> Reporter: IT
SOUNDED LIKE AN AIR
RAID OVER DALLAS.
>> THAT IS NOT A
DRILL.
>> Reporter: ON FRIDAY
NIGHT, ALL 156 OF THE
CITY'S EMERGENCY
SIRENS SCREAMING IN
UNISON INTO THE EARLY
HOURS OF SATURDAY
MORNING.
>> THEY SAY ALARMS ARE
COMING FROM ALL OVER
DALLAS.
>> Reporter: THE
CAUSE, NOT A STORM BUT
A CYBERATTACK,
CREATING FEAR AND
CONFUSION, CLOGGING
911 FOR HOURS.
MORE THAN 4,000 CALLS.
THE CULPRIT UNKNOWN.
>> THIS IS LIKE
FINDING, YOU KNOW, A
NEEDLE IN A HAYSTACK.
>> Reporter: THE
INCIDENT COMES AFTER
YEARS OF WARNINGS FROM
THE CYBER SECURITY
COMMUNITY ABOUT THE
DANGER HACKING CAN
CAUSE TO VITAL
INFRASTRUCTURE.
HOMELAND SECURITY
STATISTICS PINPOINT
NEARLY 300 ATTACKS
REPORTED ON CRITICAL
SYSTEMS IN 2015 ALONE.
>> CERTAINLY THOSE
PARTS OF OUR
INFRASTRUCTURE THAT IS
READILY ACCESSIBLE IS
VULNERABLE TO THESE
ATTACKS.
>> Reporter: TEXAS IS
ONE OF THE FIVE MOST
HACKED STATES
ACCORDING TO THE TECH
FIRM DIGITAL GUARDIAN.
SECOND ONLY TO
CALIFORNIA, WHERE IN
SAN FRANCISCO AN
ATTACK TOOK LIGHT RAIL
TICKET MACHINES OFF
LINE DURING ONE OF THE
BUSIEST SHOPPING
WEEKENDS LAST YEAR.
>> WE HAVE REACHED A
POINT WHERE CYBER
CRIME IS NOW
PERVASIVE.
THESE KINDS OF ATTACKS
ARE HAPPENING ALL THE
TIME.
>> Reporter: SOUNDING
THE ALARMS FROM THE
CYBER SECURITY
COMMUNITY FOR AMERICAN
CITIES.
STEVE PATTERSON, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
THE BENEFITS OF
CYCLING.
HOW FOR SOME IT IS
TURNING BACK THE CLOCK
ON A DEBILITATING
DISEASE.
>>> EVERYONE KNOWS
EXERCISE IS GOOD FOR
US, BUT CYCLING IS
GETTING SOME NEW
ATTENTION NOW.
TURNS OUT IT CAN HELP
RELIEVE THE SYMPTOMS
OF PARKINSON'S, A
CHRONIC AND
PROGRESSIVE DISEASE
THAT GETS WORSE AS
PEOPLE AGE.
OUR MEDICAL
CORRESPONDENT DR. JOHN
TORRES ON A SIMPLE AND
SURPRISING DISCOVERY.
>> Reporter: YOU WOULD
NEVER GUESS THAT JUDD
STOVER HAS SUFFERED
FROM PARKINSON'S
DISEASE FOR THE LAST
SEVEN YEARS, BECAUSE
HE DOESN'T HAVE
TREMORS.
HE DOESN'T HAVE MUSCLE
STIFFNESS, AND HIS
FEET DON'T SHUFFLE
WHEN HE WALKS.
ONE BIG REASON HE'S SO
ACTIVE AND SYMPTOM
FREE?
HE SAID YES TO A
SURPRISING NEW
THERAPY.
>> SLOW IT DOWN EVEN
MORE AND BETTER BY
DOING THIS STUFF,
WHERE DO I SIGN UP?
>> Reporter: WHAT DID
HE SIGN UP FOR?
A CLINICAL TRIAL USING
A SIMPLE TREATMENT.
>> HOW YOU FEELING?
>> FEELING GOOD.
>> Reporter: CYCLING.
RESEARCHERS AT THE
CLEVELAND CLINIC ARE
FINDING CYCLING IS
HELPING PATIENTS STOP
THE SYMPTOMS OF
PARKINSONS AND CAN
EVEN DO SOMETHING THAT
MEDICINE CAN'T -- SLOW
DOWN THE PROGRESSION
OF THE DISEASE ITSELF.
NEUROSCIENTIST JAY
ALBERTS MADE A
STUNNING DISCOVERY.
CYCLING CAN INCREASE
CERTAIN PROTEINS IN
THE BRAIN THAT HELP
MOVEMENT AND COGNITIVE
FUNCTION.
AND SO THESE CHANGES
ARE SIMILAR TO WHAT
HAPPENS WHEN THEY'RE
ON MEDICATION?
>> EXACTLY RIGHT.
WHEN YOU HAVE
MEDICATION YOU HAVE
INCREASED ACTIVATION
IN THIS AREA.
YOU HAVE A SIMILAR
INCREASE IN ACTIVATION
FOLLOWING EXERCISE.
SO EXERCISE IS, IN
FACT, MEDICINE.
>> Reporter: TO
ACTIVATE THOSE CHANGES
IN THE BRAIN, PATIENTS
HAVE TO DO FORCED
EXERCISE, WHICH MEANS
THEY'RE WORKING HARDER
THAN THEY'RE USED TO
DOING, BUT IT'S THAT
HARD WORK THAT GIVES
THEM THE BENEFITS.
SO GET THOSE BENEFITS,
WHAT'S THE FORMULA?
CYCLING THREE TIMES A
WEEK FOR 45 MINUTES AT
80 TO 09 RPMs.
>> I DON'T CARE WHAT
CONDITION YOU'RE IN.
THAT'S PRETTY
STRENUOUS.
>> Reporter: THAT
FORMULA HAS WORKED SO
WELL, ALBERTS HAS
TAKEN THE RESEARCH OUT
OF THE LAB, AND INTO
THE GYM.
>> THE PROGRAM
RETURNED ME TO NORMAL
OR VERY CLOSE TO
NORMAL.
>> Reporter: AT 60
DIFFERENT YMCAs ACROSS
THE COUNTRY, NOW
OFFERING CLASSES
CALLED PEDALING FOR
PARKINSON'S.
>> IT IS JUST LIKE
TURNING ON A LIGHT
BULB.
THAT WAS THE
DIFFERENCE BETWEEN
PEDALING AND NOT
PEDALING.
>> EACH PEDAL STROKE A
STEP TOWARD LIVING A
BETTER LIFE WITH
PARKINSON'S DISEASE.
>> THAT'S MY GOAL,
BETTER EVERY DAY.
>> Reporter: DR. JOHN
TORRES, NBC NEWS,
CLEVELAND.
>> JUST FASCINATING.
>>> UP NEXT, A PIECE
OF WORLD WAR II
HISTORY GETS NEW LIFE,
THANKS TO A VETERAN
WHO KNOWS IT WELL.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, A
RELIC OF WORLD WAR II
IS ABOUT TO PLY THE
WATERS ONCE AGAIN,
THIS TIME IN
FRIENDLIER TERRITORY.
IT'S ALL ABOUT A LABOR
OF LOVE FOR A MAN WHO
CAME OF AGE SERVING
ABOARD IT AND NEVER
FORGOT THE EXPERIENCE.
THE STORY FROM NBC'S
KERRY SANDERS IN NEW
ORLEANS.
>> Reporter: AT 92
YEARS OLD, IT'S
NATURAL TO LOOK BACK
AT HISTORY.
>> THE INVASION FLEET
IS MOVING TOWARDS
FRANCE.
>> Reporter:
ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
WERE PART OF IT AS JIM
NIERSON WAS.
>> WELCOME ABOARD,
SIR.
GREAT TO HAVE YOU PACK
BACK.
>> Reporter: THAT'S
JIM IN WORLD WAR II, A
MEMBER OF THE CREW ON
PT BOAT 305, AND JIM
TODAY.
>> YOU DON'T SEE ANY
ENEMY SHIPS OUT THERE,
DO YOU?
>> NO.
>> Reporter: ON THE
VERY BOAT WHERE THIS
18-YEAR-OLD BOY
QUICKLY BECAME A MAN.
>> WE ALL KNOW THAT
WAR IS HELL, BUT YOU
DON'T THINK ABOUT IT
BEING HELL.
YOU JUST DO YOUR JOB.
>> Reporter: IT'S A
MARVEL THIS PT BOAT
JIM WAS ON IS NOW ONCE
AGAIN OPERATIONAL.
DECOMMISSIONED AS WAR
SURPLUS, SHE WAS USED
AS A TOUR BOAT IN NEW
YORK CITY, AN OYSTER
BOAT IN THE CHESAPEAKE
BAY, UNTIL VOLUNTEERS
AT THE WORLD WAR II
MUSEUM IN NEW ORLEANS
BEGAN A TEN-YEAR
PASSION PROJECT.
REFASHIONING HER
MAHOGANY HULL, EASY
COMPARED TO FINDING
ORIGINAL PARTS.
>> WE GOT PIECES FROM
ALL OVER THE UNITED
STATES AND ALL OVER
THE WORLD.
THE RADAR DOME CAME
FROM A COLLECTOR IN
AUSTRALIA.
THE ENGINES CAME FROM
A FARMER IN INDIANA
WHO USED THEM IN
TRACTOR PULLS.
WE FOUND THE SIGHT FOR
THE TORPEDOS ON EBAY.
>> Reporter: ON EBAY?
>> ON EBAY, CAME OUT
OF PENNSYLVANIA.
THE ONLY ONE WE'VE
SEEN IN TEN YEARS.
>> MAN YOUR GUNS!
>> Reporter:
EVERYTHING IS AS IT
WAS DURING WORLD WAR
II, EXCEPT THE MACHINE
GUNS ARE NOT REAL AND
THERE IS NO
AMMUNITION.
IN NEW ORLEANS, THE
MAIDEN VOYAGE FOR
PAYING CUSTOMERS SET
FOR LATER THIS MONTH.
TICKETS EXPENSIVE,
$350, BUT RIDES ARE
ALREADY SOLD OUT FOR
WEEKS.
ARE AND SO MANY OTHER
PEOPLE, THANKFULLY,
CHANGED THE COURSE OF
HISTORY.
>> UH, PROBABLY HAD A
LITTLE BIT TO DO WITH
IT.
>> Reporter: JUST LIKE
THE GREATEST
GENERATION, YOU'RE
MODEST.
PT 305 AND CREW SANK
ENEMY SHIPS IN THE
MEDITERRANEAN.
NOW SHE'S A LIVING
LINK TO THE RAPIDLY
DISAPPEARING GREATEST
GENERATION.
KERRY SANDERS, NBC
NEWS ON LAKE
PONTCHARTRAIN, NEW
ORLEANS.
>> GREAT ADDITION DOWN
IN NEW ORLEANS.
>>> THAT IS "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS" FOR THIS
SUNDAY NIGHT.
LESTER HOLT WILL BE IN
TOMORROW.
I'M KATE SNOW
REPORTING FROM
NEW YORK.
I WILL SEE YOU
TOMORROW ON MSNBC.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, HAVE A GREAT
NIGHT.
RIT N ATIX.SECHI FOA MSINSANOSE
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, SEARCHING
FOR A MISSING SAN JOSE STATE
STUDENT.
TONIGHT A POTENTIAL BREAK
THROUGH IN THE CASE.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
GOOD EVENING AND THANK YOU FOR
JOINING US TONIGHT.
I'M PEGGY BUNKER.
>> AND I'M TERRY McSWEENEY,
WE'RE FOLLOWING A DEVELOPING
STORY.
A 23-YEAR-OLD KEVIN RED RICO MAY
HAVE BEEN SPOT THIS EVENING.
HE'S BEEN MISSING SINCE
WEDNESDAY.
HIS CAR FOUND IN BENECIA.
>> AND CHUCK COPPOLA JOINING US
NOW WITH THE LATEST.
AND THERE IS NEW NEWS ABOUT THE
SEARCH THIS AFTERNOON.
>> Reporter: VERY LATE NEWS THIS
AFTERNOON.
RIGHT NOW I'M STANDING ALONGSIDE
THE HIGHWAY 680 BRIDGE OVER THE
CARQUINEZ STRAIGHT AND A GROUP