I DON'T SEE SMOKE AND I DON'T
SMELL SMOKE.
>> ONE MORE THING.
HOW DID THEY COME AT THE HOUSE?
ARE MOST OF THE VEHICLES IN THE
DRIVEWAY OR DID THEY COME AT IT
THROUGH A BACK WAY?
>> THIS WHOLE AREA IS FIVE
STREETS IN THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
THEY WENT DOWN EVERY SIDE
STREET.
THERE ARE FLASHING LIGHTS AT
EVERY END AND OFFICERS WITH
RIFLES BY THEIR SIDES AT EVERY
SINGLE END.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THERE IS A PARADE OF TRAFFIC
HAPPENING NOW.
A BUNCH OF LIGHTS FLASHING GOING
UP MY STREET TOWARD FRANKLIN.
THERE ARE FIVE CARS HEADED UP.
>> OKAY.
YEAH.
WE JUST SAW KIND OF A SECOND
WAVE OF SUVs, POLICE CARS
ARRIVE.
THAT WOULD BE CONSISTENT.
IT'S GETTING TOUGHER BECAUSE THE
CAMERA LENS IS OVERWHELMED BY
THE STROBES.
IT'S HARD FOR US TO SEE, PICK
OUT INDIVIDUAL MOVEMENT EXCEPT
THAT VEHICLES KEEP COMING AND
GOING.
I'M NOT SURPRISED TO HEAR OF
MORE OF THEM COMING DOWN WHERE
YOU ARE.
I COULD BE CONVINCED THAT WE
HAVE SEEN MORE ACTIVITY.
A LIGHT TRUCK JUST ARRIVED IN
THE FOREGROUND THERE ON THE
RIGHT.
THOSE ARE ERECTABLE SPOTLIGHTS
THEY CAN PUT UP.
ONCE THE SCENE IS COLD, LET'S
SAY THE SUSPECT WAS TAKEN OUT OF
THERE.
THEY WOULD STILL WANT TO GET AT
THE START OF THE INVESTIGATION
TONIGHT, SEE WHAT THEY ARE
DEALING WITH.
EVEN THOUGH, AS KERRY AND I AND
PETE WILLIAMS AND I HAVE BEEN
THEORIZING IT'S LIKELY, KNOWING
HOW THESE GUYS WORK, THEY WILL
NOT USE LIGHT FOR THE TAKEDOWN
ITSELF.
YOU SEE AN FBI AGENT GETTING OUT
OF THE LATEST CAR TO ARRIVE.
THIS FLASH-BANG TECHNOLOGY, IF
THAT EXPLAINS POPS PEOPLE HEARD
OTHER THAN GUNFIRE, THEY ARE A
BRIEFLY DEVASTATING WEAPON THAT
CAN JUST TAKE HOLD OF YOUR
SENSES AND LEAVE THE SUSPECT
BLINDED AND DEAFENED MOMENTARILY
WHILE PEOPLE MOVE IN.
CLOSED SPACE.
I HAVE SEEN THEM USED OUTDOORS
IN A COURTYARD, A WARTIME
BACKDROP IN AFGHANISTAN.
THEY ARE VERY EFFECTIVE.
JUST TOLD WE HAVE ANOTHER GUEST.
CLINT VAN ZANT, FBI VETERAN
PROFILER.
WHAT CAN YOU ADD, CLINT?
>> WELL, AS YOU KNOW MY
BACKGROUND IS AS A HOSTAGE
NEGOTIATOR.
HAVING BEEN IN SIMILAR
SITUATIONS LIKE THIS WORKING
WITH TACTICAL TEAMS, THIS IS A
HAND IN GLOVE OPERATION.
THE NEGOTIATOR IS ON THE SCENE.
HE OR SHE WILL BE WORKING HARD
TO EXTEND A HAND AND ALLOWS THIS
INDIVIDUAL TO COME OUT.
WITH THE POTENTIAL EXPLOSIVE
DEVICE OF SOMETHING INSIDE THE
BEST CASE SCENARIO WOULD BE FOR
THE NEGOTIATOR TO GET THE
SUBJECT TO COME OVER THE SIDE OF
THE BOAT, CROP TO THE GROUND SO
THAT THE TACTICAL TEAM.
ANYTHING LIKE THAT.
THEN THEY CAN CLOSE, MAKE THE
ARREST AND THEN ADMINISTER FIRST
AID.
IT'S GOING TO HAVE TO WORK LIKE
THAT.
THEY ARE NOT GOING TO ENDANGER A
POLICE OFFICER OR AGENT IN THE
ARREST AND HAVE THIS GUY TRY TO
BLOW HIMSELF UP AT THE LAST
SECOND.
>> WE HAVE BEEN CIRCUMSPECT
BECAUSE THERE'S BEEN SO MUCH
REPORTED WRONG OVER THE PAST
COUPLE OF DAYS ABOUT PASSING
THINGS ALONG.
THIS DOES MAKE SENSE THOUGH.
BOSTON GLOBE IS TWEETING OUT
THAT ONE OF THE PHOTOGRAPHERS IS
IN CLOSE ENOUGH TO BE ABLE TO
HEAR COPS SAY, YOU KNOW, THE
CLASSIC MOVIE LINE "COME OUT ON
YOUR OWN TERMS, COME OUT WITH
YOUR HANDS UP."
IT WOULD INDICATE -- THE
SURPRISE HERE -- IT WOULD
INDICATE THE SUSPECT IS ALIVE,
ABLE TO COMMUNICATE AND ABLE TO
MOVE.
CLINT, AFTER TWO VOLLEYS OF
GUNFIRE AND WELL OUTNUMBERED
IT'S SURPRISING TO A LOT OF US.
>> HE WAS PROBABLY WOUNDED LAST
NIGHT IN THE EXCHANGE OF GUNFIRE
IN WHICH HIS BROTHER WAS KILLED.
HE WAS PROBABLY SHOT AT THAT
TIME.
THAT ACCOUNTS FOR THE BLOOD THAT
MAY HAVE BEEN SEEN AT THE SCENE
WHEN HE GOT ON TO THE BOAT OR
SUBSEQUENT TO THAT.
AS WE HEARD THE VOLLEY OF
GUNFIRE IT SOUNDED LIKE AT LEAST
ONE IF NOT TWO 30-ROUND
MAGAZINES FROM THE TACTICAL
OFFICER'S WEAPON.
IF THEY SHOT RIGHT AT THE BOAT
IT WOULD HAVE BEEN TURNED THE
BOAT INTO SWISS CHEESE.
REALIZE LAW ENFORCEMENT, I'M
SURE AS A GROUP HAS AN
UNDERSTANDING THAT THEY WOULD
LIKE TO DO EVERYTHING THEY CAN
LIKE IN ANY OTHER SITUATION.
THEY WOULD LIKE TO GIVE THIS
INDIVIDUAL EVERY OPPORTUNITY TO
SURRENDER.
WE NEED TO TALK TO HIM.
HE HAS INFORMATION WE NEED.
BUT THERE ARE RULES OF
ENGAGEMENT THAT WILL SUGGEST IF
YOUR LIFE IS IN DANGER, THE LIFE
OF SOMEBODY ELSE DO WHAT YOU
HAVE TO DO.
TRY TO TAKE HIM ALIVE.
DON'T PUT YOUR LIFE ON THE LINE
TO DO IT.
>> BOSTON P.D. CAR COMING OUT.
VEHICLES COMING AND GOING.
WE HAVE SEEN THIS ALL NIGHT
LONG.
HERE ARE FOLKS TOLD A HALF HOUR
BEFORE THE GUNSHOTS IT'S OKAY TO
COME OUT.
FOLK IN WATERTOWN WHO WERE
FOLLOWING INSTRUCTIONS ALL DAY
AND ALL DAY WE HAVE BEEN SEEING
THE KIDS LOOKING AT THE
GROWN-UPS IN THEIR LIVES AND THE
GROWN-UPS WERE TOLD DON'T COME
TO THE DOOR UNLESS YOU ARE
CERTAIN IT'S LAW ENFORCEMENT.
WE SAW HOUSE-TO-HOUSE SEARCHES
TAKING PLACE WITH LAW
ENFORCEMENT IN MILITARY DRESS.
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS DRAWN.
CAME TO THE HOUSE.
EMPTIED THE HOUSE OF OCCUPANTS
AND WENT IN TO SEARCH IT.
THIS IS SOME OF THE DOOR-TO-DOOR
SEARCHES.
THIS PARTICULAR HOUSE WE ARE
SHOWING THE RESIDENTS WERE ASKED
TO COME OUT FIRST BEFORE THEY
WENT IN.
TYPICAL TO WANT TO CLEAR IT
BEFORE YOU SEARCH.
AGAIN, THIS IS -- THIS WAS THE
STANCE OF LAW ENFORCEMENT ALL
DAY.
THOSE WEAPONS ARE THE SAME
ISSUED TO THE ARMED FORCES
OVERSEAS.
THAT'S A BASIC M-4
SEMI-AUTOMATIC LONG BARRELLED
WEAPON.
THEY WERE NOT FOOLING AROUND.
THEY HAD AN EXTREMELY DANGEROUS
SUSPECT PINNED DOWN.
SEVERAL PEOPLE NOTICED A BLACK
VEHICLE WHICH PEOPLE ASSUME TO
BE A HEARSE IN THE FOREGROUND.
WE DON'T KNOW IF THAT'S TRUE.
VARIOUS SIZES AND SHAPES OF
VEHICLES.
SOME OF WHICH FOLKS HAVE NEVER
SEEN BEFORE BECAUSE THEY ARE FOR
SPECIALIZED TASKS.
LESTER HOLT, ANYTHING FROM WHERE
YOU ARE.
>> Reporter: YOU'RE TALKING
ABOUT THE FEAR AND THE CHILDREN
OF PEOPLE WHO HEARD EXPLOSIONS
AND SHOTS LAST NIGHT.
ANY OF US WHO HEARD SHOTS FIRED
IN ANGER KNOW WHAT A HORRIBLE
SOUND THAT IS.
IT TAKES A WHILE TO LEARN WHEN
IT'S COMING YOUR WAY.
YOU DON'T KNOW.
THAT'S WHAT A LOT OF PEOPLE
HEARD LAST NIGHT WITH EXPLOSIONS
AND SHOTS.
I WANT TO POINT OUT WE HAVE BEEN
WATCHING POLICE OFFICERS WORK SO
WELL TOGETHER.
DIFFERENT AGENCIES.
WE KNOW THAT TYPICALLY THEIR
ARRIVAL IS BETWEEN AGENCIES.
THEY ARE UNITED IN PURPOSE.
KEEP IN MIND THIS COMMUNITY WAS
ATTACKED.
THE GREATER BOSTON AREA ATTACKED
AND THE BOMBINGS ON MONDAY.
THEN ONE OF THEIR OWN, A POLICE
OFFICER AT M.I.T., MURDERED,
AMBUSHED YESTERDAY.
ANOTHER POLICE OFFICER, TRANSIT
OFFICER WAS SERIOUS LY WOUNDED T
THE BEGINNING OF THE CHASE.
THERE IS SUCH A SENSE OF PURPOSE
AND DEDICATION WE ARE SEEING
FROM LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCIES
THAT ALL CONVERGED IN WATERTOWN.
FBI HAS TAKEN THE LEAD BUT THEY
HAVE ALL FOUND A ROLE.
S.W.A.T. TEAMS TOOK VARIOUS
ROLES AS THEY WENT THROUGH
NEIGHBORHOODS AND POKED THROUGH
BACKYARDS LOOKING FOR THE VERY
KIND OF THING THEY FOUND HERE
TONIGHT.
BY THE WAY, THE BOAT SEEMED TO
HAVE A SHRINK WRAP.
WE ARE TOLD IT HAD A TEAR IN IT.
THAT WAS THE SUSPICIOUS POINT --
THE TEAR AND THE BLOOD STAINS
SUGGESTING THAT SOMEONE HAD BEEN
IN THERE OR WAS IN THERE WHICH,
AS IT TURNS OUT WAS THE CASE.
THAT WAS THE KIND OF WORK THEY
WERE DOING TODAY, LOOKING FOR
TELLTALE SIGNS THAT SOMEONE
MIGHT BE HIDING OUT.
BRIAN, BACK TO YOU.
>> WHDH H, OUR STATION IS
BREAKING NEWS THAT THEY ARE
HEARING FROM THE SCENE.
LET'S LISTEN IN.
>> YOU SAID A SUCCESSFUL
RECOVERY WHICH WE WOULD SAY THEY
HAVE THIS 19-YEAR-OLD BOMBING
SUSPECT E IN CUSTODY AND HE'S
ALIVE.
>> WELL, I DON'T KNOW ABOUT THAT
ASSUMPTION.
I THINK YOU HAVE THE GUY
RECOVERED WITH NO INJURY.
I'M GOING TO SEE --
>> IS HE ALIVE?
>> NO TELLING.
>> DAN, YOU'RE WATCHING FROM
THERE.
COOPER IS TALKING TO HIS
SOURCES.
HE MAY BE ABLE TO ADD.
STEVE, WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
>> HE'S ALIVE.
IN CUSTODY AND ALIVE.
THEY HAVE ASKED FOR A MEDIC TO
THE SCENE.
>> SUSPECT NUMBER TWO ALIVE.
>> HE'S ALIVE.
>> IN CUSTODY.
HE'S IN CUSTODY.
THEY ARE ASKING FOR A MEDIC TO
THE SCENE WHICH MEANS THEY ARE
GOING TO BE TRYING TO TREAT HIM.
SPECIFICS, I DON'T KNOW WHAT
THAT MEANS.
HE IS IN CUSTODY.
>> EXCELLENT.
>> THAT'S THE BEST NEWS.
8:42 ON FRIDAY NIGHT.
>> IS IT OVER?
IS IT ALL OVER?
>> IT'S ALL OVER.
>> IT'S OVER.
>> THEY HAVE AN AMBULANCE ON THE
SCENE.
>> AMBULANCE ON THE SCENE.
>> THEY THINK THE GUY IS IN GOOD
ENOUGH SHAPE?
WE SEE THE AMBULANCE PULLING IN
RIGHT NOW.
>> OUTSTANDING.
>> WE'LL FOLLOW THAT.
GREAT NEWS, STEVE.
>> YOU WONDER HOW -- STEVE, DO
WE HAVE ANY IDEA --
>> AMBULANCE CAN NOW GO TO THE
SCENE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT CONDITION
HE'S IN.
IS THAT CORRECT?
OKAY, THANKS.
YEAH, JUST TO RECAP.
FROM THE SCENE ACCORDING TO MY
SOURCE THE SUSPECT IS IN
CUSTODY.
HE IS ALIVE.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT CONDITION
HE'S IN.
THEY HAVE CALLED FOR A MEDIC TO
THE SCENE.
IT'S A HOT SCENE.
THEY ARE STILL OFFICIALLY
SECURING THE SCENE.
THAT WOULD GO ALONG WITH WHAT
DAN WAS SAYING WITH THE LIGHT
APPLAUSE HE MAY HAVE HEARD FROM
HIS VANTAGE POINT.
>> IT'S BEEN A HORRIFYING NIGHT
IN BOSTON, THE WORLD HAS BEEN
WATCHING WHAT'S HAPPENING.
THIS CHAIN OF EVENTS.
REALLY ABOUT THE BEST POSSIBLE
OUTCOME TONIGHT.
THE SECOND SUSPECT WANTED IN THE
MARATHON BOMBING NOW ALIVE,
CAPTURED, IN CUSTODY AND ABOUT
TO BE ATTENDED BY MEDICS THERE
IN WATERTOWN.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHAT HIS
CONDITION IS NOW.
DAN, YOU ARE JOINING US WITH
CONFIRMATION OF WHAT STEVE SAID.
>> STATE POLICE GAVE ME A STRONG
HEAD SHAKE.
AN OFFICER SAYING, YES, HE'S
ALIVE.
THEY ARE BRINGING HIM UP IN THIS
DIRECTION.
THEY APPEAR TO BE AT EASE.
THEY ARE PROBABLY GOING UP BIRCH
OR FRANKLIN AREA NOW.
EVERYBODY IS STANDING DOWN,
SATISFIED.
A FEW OF THE OFFICERS TAKING
PICTURES TO COMMEMORATE THE
MOMENT OF THIS SUCCESSFUL END.
INCREDIBLE TO THINK WHEN THIS
CITY WAS SHUT DOWN BECAUSE OF
THE CONCERN, THE DANGER, THE
WORRY ABOUT HOW IT WOULD END.
IT ENDED WITH A WHIMPER, NOT A
BANG.
WE HAD BANGS AND IT COULD HAVE
ENDED WITH MORE.
THESE OFFICERS, WHATEVER THEY
DID, WERE ABLE TO BRING AT LEAST
THE END OF THIS TO A PEACEFUL
CONCLUSION.
>> THAT'S FANTASTIC, DAN.
OF COURSE, NOW AS YOU MENTIONED
THE MEDIC IS AT THE BOAT --
>> YOU HAVE BEEN LISTENING TO
THE COVERAGE OF OUR STATION WHDH
IN BOSTON AS THEY WERE TALKING
YOU SAW THE WATERTOWN EMS
AMBULANCE THAT WAS PARKED THERE
FOR SO LONG TAKE A RIGHT AND GO
DOWN TO THE NEIGHBORHOOD.
YOU HEAR THESE MULTIPLE REPORTS.
SUSPECT HAS BEEN APPREHENDED.
THERE IS A CHANGE IN MOOD,
STANCE AND DEMEANOR THERE.
THE SHOT WE HAVE BEEN LOOKING
AT --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> NOW WE ARE HEARING -- LISTEN
TO THAT.
OUR REPORTS ARE RICOCHETTING
AROUND AND PEOPLE VIA BROADCAST
OR SOCIAL MEDIA OR TELEVISION
CREWS, PEOPLE ON THE SIDEWALK IN
NEWTOWN ARE REACTING WITH
CHEERS.
PETE WILLIAMS?
>> WE HAVE CONFIRMED HERE,
BRIAN, AS WELL THAT THE SUSPECT
IS IN CUSTODY.
WE DON'T KNOW PRECISELY HIS
CONDITION.
NOW THE QUESTION IS, OF COURSE,
WHAT HAPPENS NOW.
HE'LL BE IN FEDERAL CUSTODY HERE
BECAUSE THIS ENTIRE
INVESTIGATION SINCE THE BOMBING
HAS BEEN UNDER THE FBI'S
JURISDICTION BECAUSE OF A
FEDERAL LAW, A TERRORISM ATTACK
IS UNDER THE JURISDICTION OF THE
FBI.
THEY WILL TAKE HIM NOW.
IF HE'S GRAVELY WOUNDED OR NEEDS
MEDICAL ATTENTION HE WILL BE
TAKEN TO A HOSPITAL WHERE HE
WILL BE GIVEN MEDICAL ATTENTION.
IF YOU THINK ABOUT THE SCENARIO
INVOLVING UMAR ABDEL MUTALLAB,
THE SO-CALLED CHRISTMAS DAY
BOMBER, SIMILAR SITUATION.
HE WAS BADLY HURT, TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL, GIVEN TREATMENT.
THEN THE FBI PROCEEDED TO
QUESTION HIM AT LENGTH.
THAT WAS A CONTROVERSIAL THING
AT THE TIME.
PEOPLE THOUGHT HE SHOULD HAVE
BEEN NOT GIVEN A MIRANDA
WARNING.
IT TURNED OUT HE WAS QUESTIONED
FOR A TIME AND THEN GIVEN HIS
MIRANDA WARNING AND THE POLICE
SAID HE KEPT TALKING.
THEY USED IT AS A TEXTBOOK
EXAMPLE.
THIS WILL REMAIN A CONTROVERSIAL
DECISION.
IT IS THE STATED POLICY OF THE
OBAMA ADMINISTRATION TO TAKE
ANYONE LIKE THIS WHO CREATES A
CRIME IN THE UNITED STATES AND
TREAT THEM IN THE REGULAR
CIVILIAN JUSTICE SYSTEM.
THEY WILL TAKE HIM AWAY.
WHEN THE APPROPRIATE TIME COMES,
BEGIN TO QUESTION HIM.
>> PETE, I GOT AN E-MAIL USING A
TERM OF ART IN LAW ENFORCEMENT.
SOMEBODY SAID, REMEMBER, THIS IS
A FEDERAL SHOW.
>> MEANING THE FBI IS IN CHARGE.
WE HAVE ALREADY HEARD SOME
MEMBERS OF THE SENATE SAY THIS
PERSON SHOULD BE DECLARED AN
ENEMY COMBATANT, NOT GIVEN
MIRANDA WARNING AND SHOULD BE
SUBJECT TO A MILITARY-STYLE
INTERROGATION.
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION WILL
NEVER GO FOR THAT.
THEY BELIEVE SUSPECTS WHO COMMIT
CRIMES HERE SHOULD BE TREATED IN
THE CRIMINAL JUSTICE SYSTEM.
THAT'S WHAT THEY WILL INTEND TO
DO.
>> MICHAEL LEITER WHO WAS, AMONG
OTHER THINGS, IN THE ROOM THE
NIGHT OF THE BIN LADEN RAID WHEN
IT WAS PLANNED AND ORDERS
CARRIED OUT FROM THE SITUATION
ROOM.
FORMER HEAD OF COUNTER TERRORISM
FOR THIS COUNTRY, MICHAEL, WALK
US THROUGH WHAT IS LIKELY TO
HAPPEN NOW.
WHAT'S THE FIRST SET OF OFFICIAL
EYEBALLS THAT WILL SIT DOWN
ACROSS FROM OR RIDE WITH THIS
SUSPECT.
ESPECIALLY FOR THOSE OF US WHO
WOULD SIMPLY LIKE TO KNOW WHAT
IT TAKES FOR A 19-YEAR-OLD TO BE
CONVINCED THAT PUTTING A BOMB
DOWN NEXT TO LITTLE KIDS IS A
GOOD IDEA.
>> BRIAN, AS PETE MENTIONED
DURING THE CHRISTMAS DAY BOMBER
IN 2009, WE HADN'T FULLY
ESTABLISHED A PROTOCOL AND
DISCUSSION ABOUT HOW A TERROR
SUSPECT WOULD BE INTERROGATED.
WE WORKED THROUGH THE PROBLEM
MORE.
THERE WILL HAVE ALREADY BEEN
PRETHIS ARREST A VERY EXTENSIVE
DISCUSSION BETWEEN THE FBI AND
THE REST OF THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY ABOUT HOW SUCH AN
INTERROGATION WILL OCCUR AND
WHAT THE KEY ISSUES ARE.
THE FBI IS IN CHARGE AS THE LAW
ENFORCEMENT ENTITY FOR THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT IN CHARGE OF
THE INVESTIGATION.
BUT THEY WILL HAVE ALREADY HAVE
WORKED WITH ORGANIZATIONS LIKE
CENTRAL INTELLIGENCE AGENCY AND
THE LIKE TO FIGURE OUT WHAT
SORTS OF QUESTIONS NEED TO BE
ASKED ABOUT FOREIGN CONTACTS AND
THE LIKE.
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN HERE IS THEY
WILL TAKE HIM INTO CUSTODY.
THERE IS, OF COURSE, THE
POSSIBILITY THAT THEY WILL
MIRANDAIZE HIM RIGHT AWAY.
THEY WILL LIKELY USE WHAT'S
KNOWN AS THE PUBLIC SAFETY
EXCEPTION.
THAT GIVES THEM LEGAL AUTHORITY
TO QUESTION HIM INITIALLY ABOUT
THINGS WHICH POSE AN IMMEDIATE
THREAT TO PUBLIC SAFETY.
THEY CAN ASK, ARE THERE MORE
IMPROVISED EXPLOSIVE DEVICES
ANYWHERE?
THAT CAN TAKE SOME TIME.
THEY CAN GET ALL OF THAT
INFORMATION FROM HIM BEFORE THEY
ACTUALLY MIRANDAIZE HIM.
ONCE THEY MIRANDAIZE HIM, THEY
WILL GO THROUGH ALL OF THE
THINGS THEY NEED TO KNOW.
THAT WILL BE DONE BY FBI AGENTS
BUT, AGAIN, SUPPORTED BY THE
REST OF THE NATIONAL SECURITY
COMMUNITY.
IN MY VIEW, THEY WILL WANT TO
KNOW, AGAIN, ANY WEAPONS OUT
THERE.
MOTIVATION, ANY OTHER
ASSOCIATES, ARE THERE FURTHER
DANGERS.
THESE ARE THE KEY ISSUES THEY
WILL PURSUE.
THEN THEY WILL START MOVING OUT
TOWARDS MOTIVATION, MORE DISTANT
NETWORKS, THINGS LIKE THAT.
>> MICHAEL, ALREADY THIS THING
IS REICH SPIDER CRACKS WHEN A
ROCK HITS THE WINDSHIELD.
THIS HAS GONE IN ALL DIRECTIONS
ALREADY TODAY.
WE HAVE LEARNED FROM WHDH IN NEW
BEDFORD, MASS, THREE PEOPLE HAVE
BEEN TAKEN INTO CUSTODY.
ALL EXPECTED TO BE ROOMMATES
PRESENTLY OR AT ONE TIME WITH
SUSPECT TWO.
THIS KIND OF THING WILL HA.
THEY HAVE BEEN IN THIS KID'S
COMPUTER FOR A COUPLE OF HOURS.
THEY HAVE GOTTEN ALL RETRIEVABLE
EVIDENCE FROM THE HOUSE HE SARED
WITH HIS BROTHER FOR HOWEVER
LONG.
PETE WILLIAMS, YOU HAVE
SOMETHING NEW?
>> WELL, YES.
SEVERAL LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIALS CONFIRMED HE'S ALIVE,
IN CUSTODY.
UNBELIEVABLE, AS ONE SAID WHO'S
BEEN FOLLOWING THIS.
THE NEXT QUESTION IS WHAT SORT
OF CONDITION IS HE IN.
IS HE GRAVELY WOUNDED, WALKING?
WE DON'T KNOW.
WE ARE TRYING TO FIND OUT NOW.
>> A BIG NIGHT IN WATERTOWN,
MASS.
I WILL TELL YOU, WHAT A 24 HOURS
THOSE PEOPLE HAVE ENDURED.
THESE ARE JUST CITIZENS OF A
TOWN IN EASTERN MASS.
THIS WAS VISITED UPON THEM AFTER
THEY WITNESSED THE HORRIBLE
BOMBING AT THE FINISH LINE OF
THE BOSTON MARATHON.
THERE IS YOUR SUSPECT, IN
CUSTODY AND ALIVE.
WE BELIEVE HE SURVIVED ONE OR
MORE BULLET WOUNDS LAST NIGHT IN
A HAIL OF GUNFIRE.
LESTER HOLT IS AT STREET LEVEL,
AS WE HAVE SEEN.
ACROSS FROM THE TOWN DINER IN
THIS TOWN THAT CAN NOW START TO
BREATHE AND LIVE A LITTLE BIT.
LESTER?
>> WE HEARD 30 SECONDS OF
SUSTAINED APPLAUSE FROM THE
CROWD WHEN WORD GOT OUT THAT HE
WAS IN CUSTODY.
THESE FOLKS HAVE LIVED THROUGH
HELL WITH THE SHOTS AND
EXPLOSIONS.
I'M WITH RITA WHO LIVES IN THE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
WHAT'S YOUR REACTION TO THE FACT
THAT THEY HAVE HIM IN CUSTODY.
>> I'M RELIEVED.
FEEL LIKE I HAVE BEEN WATCHING A
BAD MOVIE I COULDN'T TURN OFF.
I'LL BE ABLE TO SLEEP TONIGHT.
>> THE HELICOPTER CAME OVER AND
YOU SAID, I WILL BE GLAD WHEN
THAT'S OVER.
>> I WILL BE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO
BE IN A WAR ZONE.
LISTENING TO THEM MADE IT FEEL
LIKE THAT'S WHAT IT'S LIKE.
VERY UNSETTLING.
>> Reporter: GRATEFUL FOR YOU
AND THE COMMUNITY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR TALKING
TO US.
BIG RELIEF, BRIAN, FOR FOLKS
THAT WERE POTENTIALLY GOING TO
FACE ANOTHER NIGHT OF
UNCERTAINTY THAT THIS PERSON
COULD BE OUT THERE, A PERSON
WHO'S SHOWN WILLINGNESS TO DO
GREAT HARM.
FOLKS HAVE BEEN OUT ALL DAY.
THEY WILL REST WELL TONIGHT HERE
IN WATERTOWN.
>> LESTER, THANKS.
IF MICHAEL LEITER CAN STILL HEAR
US IN WASHINGTON -- ARE YOU WITH
US?
>> I AM, BRIAN.
>> I HAVE BEEN SAYING ALL DAY AS
LONG AS WE KEEP THE BALANCE MORE
GOOD GUYS THAN BAD WE'LL BE ALL
RIGHT.
THE OTHER LESSON IS ABOUT LAW
ENFORCEMENT, TRAILS PEOPLE LEAVE
BEHIND.
THE LEAPS AND BOUNDS TECHNOLOGY
HAS TAKEN.
WE HAVE SAID MANY TIMES IN THE
PAST COUPLE OF DAYS.
FOLLOWING OKLAHOMA CITY WE WERE
IN ROUGH SHAPE IN TERMS OF THE
ABILITY TO INVESTIGATE THIS TYPE
OF THING.
NOW THE SWEEP OF TECHNOLOGY.
IT'S HARD TO GET AWAY WITH
SOMETHING BAD IN THIS COUNTRY.
>> IT IS.
THIS IS A SILVER LINING ON A
DARK CLOUD GOING BACK TO 1996
WITH OKLAHOMA CITY, 1998 WITH
KENYA AND TANZANIA, THE FIRST
WORLD TRADE CENTER BOMBING
THROUGH 9/11.
WHAT THE LAST 12 YEARS HAVE
GIVEN US IS INCREDIBLE HUMAN
CAPITAL.
INCREDIBLE TALENT WITHIN
ORGANIZATIONS LIKE THE FBI AND
CIA.
INCREDIBLE COORDINATION BETWEEN
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT AND STATE
AND LOCAL GOVERNMENTS.
WHAT WE HAVE SEEN TODAY WOULDN'T
HAVE HAPPENED IN 2000.
AND THE TECHNOLOGY TO PULL IT
TOGETHER.
FIVE YEARS AGO IT COULD HAVE
OCCURRED AND WE MIGHT NOT HAVE
HAD NEARLY THE DIGITAL RECORD
THAT WAS DEVELOPED IN THIS CASE.
ONE CAN ONLY IMAGINE HAD THERE
NOT BEEN THE VIDEO AND
PHOTOGRAPHIC EVIDENCE OF THE
PERPETRATORS.
>> THANK YOU.
WE ARE TOLD THE SUSPECT
SUFFERING FROM AT LEAST ONE
GUNSHOT WOUND AND BLOOD LOSS.
NOT KNOWN IF THEY ARE FRESH
WOUNDS FROM TONIGHT'S EXCHANGE
OF FIRE.
HE'S BEING TAKEN TO MOUNT AUBURN
HOSPITAL IN CAMBRIDGE.
THE SAME HOSPITAL WHERE TRANSIT
POLICE OFFICER IS RECOVERING
FROM A GUNSHOT WOUND BY EITHER
THIS KID OR HIS OLDER BROTHER
LAST NIGHT.
THIS IS A TIME TO READ A SAD
STATEMENT FROM THE FAMILY OF
SEAN COLLIER, THE POLICE OFFICER
KILLED LAST NIGHT ON THE M.I.T.
CAMPUS.
FAMILY HAS RELEASED AN OFFICIAL
PHOTOGRAPH ALONG WITH THESE
WORDS.
WE ARE HEART BROKEN BY THE LOSS
OF OUR WONDERFUL AND CARING SON
AND BROTHER, SEAN COLLIER.
OUR ONLY SOLACE IS THAT SEAN
DIED BRAVELY DOING WHAT HE
COMMITTED HIS LIFE TO DO --
SERVING AND PROTECTING OTHERS.
WE ARE THANKFUL FOR THE SUPPORT
AND CONDOLENCES OFFERED BY SO
MANY PEOPLE.
WE ARE KBROOGRIEVING THIS LOSS
ASK THAT THE MEDIA RESPECT OUR
PRIVACY AT THIS TIME.
AND SO WE WILL.
YOU SEE THE M. P I.T. MARKINGS
ON HIS LAPELS.
CAMPUS POLICE OFFICER.
DID NOT EVEN HAVE A CHANCE TO DO
HIS JOB.
THE ACCOUNTS ARE HE WAS, SADLY
BASICALLY EXECUTED BY ONE OR
BOTH OF THESE SUSPECTS.
OLDER BROTHER AND YOUNGER.
YOUNGER BROTHER STILL ALIVE
BEING TRANSPORTED TO A HOSPITAL.
WHAT'S GOING TO START HAPPENING
THERE IN WATERTOWN, AND YOU CAN
TELL THIS ALREADY, YOU SAW ONE
TACTICAL OFFICER COME OUT TOWARD
THE WAITING CROWD.
IT WILL BE A KIND OF GAUNTLET.
PEOPLE ARE SO ANXIOUS TO EXPRESS
THEIR THANKS.
YOU WILL HEAR EVERY ENTERING AND
EXITING VEHICLE APPLAUDED NOW
AND HERE IS MY PREDICTION COMING
TRUE.
THIS IS GOING TO HAPPEN ALL
NIGHT LONG.
THESE ARE THE PEOPLE WHO
LIBERATED THEIR TOWN IN EFFECT.
GONE THROUGH 24 HOURS OF HELL IN
WATERTOWN, MASS.
HEY, LESTER.
>> YOU'RE SEEING THE AMBULANCE
JUST WENT BY THE CROWD.
THEY BELIEVE THERE IS A BIG
APPLAUSE FROM THE CROWD AS IT
PARTED AND THE AMBULANCE WENT
BY.
WHETHER THE SUSPECT IS TRULY IN
THERE IS NOT CLEAR.
WE BELIEVE HE MIGHT HAVE BEEN.
THAT'S QUITE A REACTION FROM THE
CROWD.
THESE FOLKS HAVE HAD A REALLY
TOUGH NIGHT LAST NIGHT.
FACING ANOTHER TOUGH NIGHT.
THEY HAVE BEEN STANDING HERE
WITH US LISTENING TO THE BEST
THEY CAN.
THEY HEARD HE WAS IN CUSTODY AND
FOLKS ARE OBVIOUSLY JOYOUS.
VERY GOOD REASON.
WE ARE ALL HAPPY THERE WAS NO
FURTHER BLOODSHED HERE.
AND THAT THIS IS OVER.
>> YOU'RE GOING TO BE ON THE
HAPPIEST CORNER IN THE
COMMONWEALTH OF MASSACHUSETTS.
ESPECIALLY WHEN ALL THE
VEHICLES, FIRST RESPONDERS, LAW
ENFORCEMENT START COMING OUT.
LESTER HOLT, THANK YOU.
8:59:30 IN THE EAST COAST.
LISTEN TO THAT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WE'LL GIVE THIS A FEW SECONDS.
COMING UP AT 9:00 WE'LL UPDATE
EVERYBODY ON WHAT HAS
TRANSPIRED.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> 9:00 IN WATERTOWN,
MASSACHUSETTS, AND ELSEWHERE
ALONG THE EAST COAST.
6:00 P.M. IN LOS ANGELES.
DZHOKHAR TSARNAEV, SAID TO BE A
19-YEAR-OLD STUDENT AT U-MASS,
HAS BEEN APPREHENDED.
HE IS SUFFERING FROM BLOOD LOSS.
AT LEAST ONE BULLET WOUND.
NOT ASCERTAINED YET IF IT WAS
SUFFERED TONIGHT OR IN LAST
NIGHT'S EXCHANGE OF GUN FIRE.
AFTER THE ALL-CLEAR WAS GIVEN
AFTER A DAY-LONG LOCK DOWN,
PEOPLE OF WATERTOWN IN THE
BOSTON METROPOLITAN AREA WERE
TOLD BY PUBLIC OFFICIALS IT WAS
FLOODED WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT,
THE REGION WAS.
IT WAS REALLY, WE WERE GIVEN
INDICATIONS, A MATTER OF TIME.
CONFIDENCE WAS HIGH THEY WERE
GOING TO FIND THIS GUY.
AS YOU SEE, WATERTOWN FIRE
DEPARTMENT ENGINE ONE COME OUT
OF THERE.
AND 30 MINUTES AFTER THEIR
ANNOUNCEMENT THAT PEOPLE CAN
COME OUT AGAIN AFTER THIS
DAY-LONG LOCK DOWN THE EXCHANGE
OF GUNFIRE.
WE HEARD FROM OUR OWN FOLKS ON
THE GROUND.
OUR CAMERA CREWS.
PEOPLE LIKE LESTER HOLT, KERRY
SANDERS THAT GUNFIRE HAD TAKEN
PLACE.
THIS WILL WHIP UP THE CROWD.
THE FIRE ENGINE HITTING THE
SIREN ON THE WAY OUT.
THIS WILL BEGIN THE SLOW PARADE
OF FIRE AND POLICE OUT OF THE
SCENE.
APPARENTLY THE SUSPECT WAS HOLED
UP UNDER A TARP IN A TRAILERED
BOAT IN THE BACKYARD OF A
PRIVATE HOUSE.
TWO OR THREE-STORY FRAME HOUSE.
AND ALL THIS TIME WE HAVE BEEN
WAITING FOR THIS TO RESOLVE.
S.W.A.T. TEAMS WERE ASSEMBLED.
AND HE'S BEING TRANSPORTED TO
THE SAME HOSPITAL WHERE AN MTA
COP IS RECOVERING FROM GUNSHOTS
SUSTAINED LAST NIGHT.
AS THIS SLOW PARADE OF VEHICLES
NOW EXITS, KERRY SANDERS, WHAT A
WILD -- WHAT, 20 HOURS, 18 HOURS
IT'S BEEN IN THAT TOWN.
>> I'VE GOT TO SAY I'M LOST.
IT'S BEEN -- I GUESS I STARTED
WORKING THURSDAY AT 5:00 A.M.
AND HAVE BEEN WORKING STRAIGHT
THROUGH.
IT'S HARD TO KEEP CLEAR
EVERYTHING THAT'S BEEN GOING ON.
WAYNE METRANO IS A RESIDENT
HERE.
THERE ARE MEMBERS OF THE
COMMUNITY WE HEAR CHEERING, HIGH
FIVING, BIG SMILES.
HOW DO YOU FEEL NOW KNOWING THAT
THIS IS OVER, THAT HE'S IN
CUSTODY AND HE'S ALIVE?
>> IT'S BEEN A BUSY 18