>> THANKS, JEFF.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
WE'LL BE BACK AT 6:00.
WE'LL SEE YOU THEN.
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT
SHOWDOWN OVER THE BAN ON GAYS IN
THE BOY SCOUTS.
TONIGHT, LATE WORD ON THE VOTE
AT AN ORGANIZATION THAT'S
INCLUDED MORE THAN 100 MILLION
AMERICAN KIDS.
>>> SHOCK WAVES IN AN ACT OF
TERRORISM.
NEW ARRESTS IN LONDON AS WE
LEARN MORE ABOUT THE YOUNG
BRITISH SOLDIER VICIOUSLY
ATTACKED AND HEAR ABOUT THE
BRAVE WOMAN WHO STARED DOWN THE
MAN WITH THE KNIFE.
>>> DRONE WAR.
THE PRESIDENT LAYS OUT NEW
ATTACKS OVERSEAS.
DURING AN IMPASSIONED DEFENSE OF
HIS POLICY AND A NEW PUSH TO
CLOSE GUANTANAMO.
>>> NOWHERE FAST.
AS WE HEAD INTO A LONG HOLIDAY
WEEKEND, WILD WEATHER IS
SNARLING TRAFFIC ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
>>> AND LIFELINE.
THE NEW MOM WHO WENT INTO LABOR
AS THE TORNADO CLOSED IN IS
REUNITED WITH THE NURSES WHO
STAYED WITH HER AS THE HOSPITAL
WAS RIPPED APART AROUND THEM.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M ANN CURRY, IN TONIGHT FOR
BRIAN.
THERE WAS A MAJOR TURNING POINT
LATE TODAY IN THE AMERICAN
INSTITUTION THAT'S BEEN AROUND
FOR MORE THAN 100 YEARS AND A
PART OF THE LIVES OF MORE THAN
100 MILLION AMERICAN CHILDREN.
AFTER MONTHS OF CONSIDERATION,
ABOUT AN INITIATIVE THAT DIVIDED
ITS RANKS DURING A PASSIONATE
DEBATE, TONIGHT THE BOY SCOUTS
OF AMERICA HAS VOTED TO ALLOW
OPENLY GAY MEMBERS.
NBC'S PETE WILLIAMS BROKE THE
NEWS BACK IN JANUARY THAT THE
SCOUTS WERE CONSIDERING THIS
CHANGE, AND HE STARTS US OFF
TONIGHT WITH THE LATE
DEVELOPMENTS FROM OUR WASHINGTON
NEWSROOM.
PETE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: ANN, GOOD EVENING.
THIS IS A BIG CHANGE FOR AN
ORGANIZATION THAT HAS FOUGHT FOR
DECADES TO PRESERVE THE STRICT
BAN ON ADMITTING GAY SCOUTS AND
SCOUTING OFFICIALS SAY TONIGHT
IT PASSED HANDILY WITH 60% OF
THE VOTE OF ITS NATIONAL
COUNCIL.
SO, THIS MEANS THE LONG-STANDING
POLICY WILL BE LIFTED THAT HAD
BANNED GAY SCOUTS, BUT IT
REMAINS IN EFFECT FOR BANNING
GAY SCOUT LEADERS.
THE VOTE ENDS A WRENCHING
PROCESS THAT STARTED FOUR MONTHS
AGO WHEN BOY SCOUT LEADERS
REVEALED THEY WERE CONSIDERING A
CHANGE.
>> THIS ISSUE IS A DEFINING
ISSUE IN OUR COUNTRY AND OUR
STATE AND OUR SOCIETY.
>> Reporter: THE DECISION CAME
TODAY AT THIS CONFERENCE CENTER
NEAR DALLAS, A MEETING OF
SCOUTING'S 1,400-MEMBER NATIONAL
COUNCIL, AFTER THE BOY SCOUTS
PROPOSED IN JANUARY TO LET LOCAL
TROOPS DECIDE THE ISSUE FOR
THEMSELVES, GENERATING A STORM
OF PETITIONS FROM SOME PARENTS
WHO THOUGHT THAT WENT TOO FAR
AND OTHERS NOT FAR ENOUGH.
TODAY THEY VOTED TO END THE BAN
ON GAY SCOUTS BUT CONTINUED THE
BAN ON GAY ADULTS AS SCOUT
LEADERS.
>> THIS IS A CHALLENGING COMPLEX
AREA.
IT'S A DIFFICULT DECISION FOR A
LOT OF PEOPLE, BUT WE'RE MOVING
FORWARD TOGETHER, AND WITHIN OUR
MOVEMENT, EVERYONE AGREES ONE
THING -- NO MATTER HOW YOU FEEL
ABOUT THIS ISSUE, KIDS ARE
BETTER OFF IN SCOUTING.
>> Reporter: CHURCH GROUPS
SPONSOR 70% OF ALL LOCAL SCOUT
UNITS, AND MANY FOUGHT TO KEEP
THE BAN.
>> AND FOCUSING ON BUILDING
STRONG, YOUNG MEN AND NOT
GETTING AN ORGANIZATION TURNED
INTO A SEXUAL AGENDA ITEM OF A
SPECIAL INTEREST ORGANIZATION.
>> Reporter: BUT THE MORMON
CHURCH, IT SPONSORS ONE-QUARTER
OF THE NATION'S SCOUTING UNITS,
SIGNALED IT WOULD NOT OPPOSE THE
ADMISSION OF GAY SCOUTS.
A SURVEY CONDUCTED FOR THE BOY
SCOUTS FOUND THAT 48% OF PARENTS
OF CURRENT SCOUTS SUPPORT THE
BAN, DOWN FROM 57% THREE YEARS
AGO.
BUT A MAJORITY OF BOY SCOUTS
THEMSELVES, 56%, OPPOSE THE BAN
ON ADMITTING GAY SCOUTS.
42% OPPOSING IT STRONGLY.
CHUCK AND RHONDA MONTERA OF
DENVER ARE AMONG PARENTS IN
FAVOR OF A CHANGE.
THEY HAVE TWO SONS IN THE CUB
SCOUTS.
>> WHEN WE LOOK 50 YEARS IN THE
FUTURE, IT WILL BE LIKE CIVIL
RIGHTS, AND IT'S LIKE, WHAT TOOK
US SO LONG?
>> Reporter: THE SCOUTS SAY THE
NEW POLICY TAKES EFFECT JANUARY
1st OF 2014, WHICH SCOUTING
OFFICIALS SAY WILL GIVE LOCAL
UNITS THE TIME TO ADJUST.
NOW, AS FOR CONSIDERING A CHANGE
IN THE BAN ON GAY SCOUT LEADERS,
THE ORGANIZATION SAYS THIS WAS A
LENGTHY PROCESS AND IT HAS NO
PLANS FOR FURTHER REVIEW.
ANN?
>> ALL RIGHT, PETE WILLIAMS
TONIGHT.
THANKS SO MUCH, PETE.
>>> THERE IS ALSO WORD TONIGHT
OF NEW ARRESTS AFTER THAT
VICIOUS ACT OF TERRORISM ON THE
STREETS OF LONDON.
AGAIN, FAIR WARNING, THESE
IMAGES ARE DIFFICULT TO TAKE.
A BRITISH SOLDIER WAS ATTACKED
AND KILLED IN THE STREETS AS WE
NOW KNOW, HE WAS A YOUNG HUSBAND
AND FATHER.
WE'RE ALSO HEARING FROM THE
BRAVE WOMAN WHO STARED DOWN THE
MAN WITH THE KNIFE.
WE GET THE LATEST NOW FROM
NBC'S MICHELLE KOSINSKI IN
LONDON.
>> Reporter: MOTHERS AND
CHILDREN ON THEIR WAY TO SCHOOL
THIS MORNING CARRIED FLOWERS, A
DAY-LONG PROCESSION, TRIBUTES
AND RAW EMOTION.
THE VICTIM, VICIOUSLY HACKED TO
DEATH ON THE STREET, HAS NOW
BEEN IDENTIFIED.
25-YEAR-OLD BRITISH SOLDIER LEE
RIGBY SERVED IN AFGHANISTAN, THE
FATHER OF A 2-YEAR-OLD SON.
IN A STATEMENT, HIS FAMILY SAID
"LEE WAS LOVELY.
HE WOULD DO ANYTHING FOR
ANYBODY.
ALL HE WANTED TO DO FROM WHEN HE
WAS A LITTLE BOY WAS BE IN THE
ARMY."
AND THAT IS WHY, ONE OF THE TWO
SUSPECTS TOLD ONLOOKERS, THEY
TARGETED HIM.
>> WE MUST FIGHT THEM AS THEY
FIGHT US, AN EYE FOR AN EYE, A
TOOTH FOR A TOOTH.
>> Reporter: THIS SUSPECT HAS
BEEN IDENTIFIED AND WAS BORN IN
BRITAIN OF NIGERIAN DISSENT.
REPORTEDLY A DEVOUT MUSLIM, HERE
HE IS IN A DEMONSTRATION OUTSIDE
OF A LONDON POLICE STATION IN
2007.
TODAY IT EMERGED THAT BOTH
SUSPECTS WERE KNOWN TO BRITISH
SECURITY SERVICES PRIOR TO NOW,
BUT SOURCES SAY THERE WAS NO
INDICATION THEY WERE PLANNING
ANY ATTACK.
TERROR ANALYSTS SAY LONE
WOLF-STYLE OPERATIONS ARE
BECOMING THE NEW FACE OF AL
QAEDA-INSPIRED ATTACKS.
>> NO LONGER THE LARGE-SCALE,
SOPHISTICATED PLOTS FROM
OVERSEAS, BUT INSTEAD, VERY
UNSOPHISTICATED AND SIMPLE
ATTACKS, WHICH CAN STILL VERY
MUCH AFFECT THE PSYCHE OF CITIES
LIKE BOSTON AND LONDON.
>> Reporter: POLICE RAIDED SIX
HOMES AROUND LONDON TODAY AS
PART OF THIS INVESTIGATION AND
MADE TWO MORE ARRESTS ON
SUSPICION OF CONSPIRACY TO
MURDER.
ONE EXTRAORDINARY CITIZEN WHO
WAS UNAFRAID, SEEN HERE TRYING
TO TALK DOWN ONE OF THE
SUSPECTS, IS INGRID LOYO
KENNETH.
>> JUST KEEPING HIM CALM.
I'D HAVE TO THINK THAT IF YOU
HAD SOMETHING TO SAY, IGNORING
HIM WOULD JUST MAKE HIM MORE
UPSET.
>> Reporter: OTHER WOMEN GUARDED
THE BODY OF THE YOUNG SOLDIER
WHO SURVIVED WAR AND HAS FALLEN
TO TERROR AT HOME.
MICHELLE KOSINSKI, NBC NEWS,
LONDON.
>>> NOW TO THE MAJOR ADDRESS BY
PRESIDENT OBAMA ON
COUNTERTERRORISM AND OUR USE OF
FORCE OVERSEAS.
THE PRESIDENT TODAY ISSUED NEW
GUIDELINES FOR DRONE STRIKES
AGAINST SUSPECTED TERRORISTS
WHILE MAKING AN IMPASSIONED
DEFENSE OF HIS POLICIES.
OUR WHITE HOUSE CORRESPONDENT
PETER ALEXANDER JOINS US FROM
THE NORTH LAWN.
PETER, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: ANN, GOOD EVENING
TO YOU.
TODAY THE PRESIDENT REFINED HIS
IDEA THAT THE SO-CALLED WAR ON
TERROR LAUNCHED BY THE BUSH
ADMINISTRATION IS NO LONGER
RELEVANT, INSTEAD PRESENTING A
MUCH MORE NARROW DEFINITION OF
AMERICAN COUNTERTERRORISM.
DECLARING AMERICA AT A
CROSSROADS, PRESIDENT OBAMA
TODAY REFRAMED THE FIGHT AGAINST
TERRORISM AND THE EVOLVING
THREAT NOW FACING THE U.S.
>> WE MUST DEFINE OUR EFFORT NOT
AS A BOUNDLESS, GLOBAL WAR ON
TERROR, BUT RATHER AS A SERIES
OF PERSISTENT, TARGETED EFFORTS
TO DISMANTLE SPECIFIC NETWORKS
OF VIOLENT EXTREMISTS THAT
THREATEN AMERICA.
OUR NATION IS STILL THREATENED
BY TERRORISTS.
FROM BENGHAZI TO BOSTON, WE HAVE
BEEN TRAGICALLY REMINDED OF THAT
TRUTH.
>> Reporter: IN HIS MOST
THOROUGH DEFENSE OF AMERICA'S
SECRET WAR, THE PRESIDENT LAID
OUT CLEAR AND NARROW GUIDELINES
FOR DRONE STRIKES, ARGUING THEY
ARE LEGAL AND CAREFULLY
CONSIDERED.
>> BEFORE ANY STRIKE IS TAKEN
THERE MUST BE NEAR CERTAINTY
THAT NO CIVILIANS WILL BE KILLED
OR INJURED, THE HIGHEST STANDARD
WE CAN SET.
>> Reporter: BUT THERE'S A CHECK
ON THE PRESIDENT'S POWER BY
CONGRESS.
>> IT'S BRIEFED ON EVERY STRIKE
THAT AMERICA TAKES.
EVERY STRIKE.
>> Reporter: AND THAT THEY WORK.
>> SIMPLY PUT, THESE STRIKES
HAVE SAVED LIVES.
>> Reporter: TO MAKE HIS
POLICIES MORE TRANSPARENT, THE
PRESIDENT IS TRANSFERRING MORE
CONTROL OF THE DRONE PROGRAM
HE ALSO RENEWED HIS PLEDGE TO
SHUT DOWN GUANTANAMO BAY,
ANNOUNCING AN END ON THE BAN TO
SEND DETAINEES TO YEMEN, CALLING
ON SOME INMATES TO BE MOVED TO
U.S. PRISONS AND TRIED IN
CIVILIAN COURTS.
THE MOVE WOULD SAVE THE U.S.
NEARLY $1 MILLION A YEAR FOR
EACH OF THE 166 INMATES, 103 OF
THEM NOW STAGING AN EXTENDED
HUNGER STRIKE.
>> I THINK THE PRESIDENT, AFTER
MONTHS OF BEING UNCOMFORTABLE
WITH WHERE HE WAS IN THE
NATIONAL DEBATE, WANTEDED TO
TAKE CONTROL OF THE NARRATIVE
AND THEN CONSOLIDATE THESE
ISSUES OVER GUANTANAMO AND
DRONES AND PUT HIMSELF WHERE HE
WANTS TO BE.
>> I KNOW THE POLITICS ARE HARD,
BUT HISTORY WILL CAST A HARSH
JUDGMENT ON THIS ASPECT OF OUR
FIGHT AGAINST TERRORISM AND
THOSE OF US WHO FAIL TO END IT.
>> Reporter: THAT JUDGMENT
VOICED BY AN ANTIWAR ACTIVIST,
WHO REPEATEDLY DISRUPTED THE
PRESIDENT.
>> WHY WAS HE KILLED?
>> Reporter: AT ONE POINT
RENDERING THE COMMANDER IN CHIEF
SPEECHLESS FOR 30 SECONDS.
>> THE VOICE OF THAT WOMAN IS
WORTH PAYING ATTENTION TO.
THESE ARE TOUGH ISSUES, AND THE
SUGGESTION THAT WE CAN GLOSS
OVER THEM IS WRONG.
>> Reporter: ALSO TODAY ON THE
TOPIC OF NATIONAL SECURITY
LEAKS, THE PRESIDENT SAID THAT
HE'S ASKED ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC
HOLDER TO CONDUCT A 45-DAY
REVIEW, ANN, OF THE JUSTICE
DEPARTMENT'S GUIDELINES FOR
INVESTIGATIONS THAT INVOLVE
JOURNALISTS.
ANN?
>> ALL RIGHT, PETER ALEXANDER
TONIGHT.
PETER, THANK YOU.
>>> IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA, DARKENED
SKIES AGAIN TODAY AS THE FIRST
FUNERALS WERE HELD FOR THE 24
VICTIMS OF MONDAY'S TORNADO, 10
OF THEM CHILDREN.
FOR THE SURVIVORS, THIS IS ALSO
A DAY TO RECONNECT AND START
MOVING FORWARD AGAIN.
NBC'S JANET SHAMLIAN JOINS US
NOW FROM MOORE.
HEY, JANET, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: ANN, GOOD EVENING
TO YOU.
IT'S JUST WHAT THEY DIDN'T NEED
HERE, THUNDERSTORMS AND
FLOODING, PUTTING THIS COMMUNITY
ON EDGE AND SHUTTING DOWN
CLEANUP EFFORTS FOR SEVERAL
HOURS.
AND IT CAME ON A DAY WHEN
STUDENTS AND PARENTS WERE TAKING
THEIR FIRST STEPS TOWARDS
SOMETHING RESEMBLING NORMAL.
THE CHILDREN OF MOORE, OKLAHOMA,
HEADED BACK TO SCHOOL TODAY,
DAYS AFTER THE TORNADO RIPPED
THROUGH TWO OF THEIR BUILDINGS,
KILLING SEVEN OF THEIR
CLASSMATES.
>> HOW ARE YOU, SWEETHEART?
>> WE TALK TO EACH OTHER AND WE
JUST GOT TO SAY HI TO EACH OTHER
AGAIN.
>> Reporter: STUDENTS FROM THE
TWO DEVASTATED SCHOOLS WERE SENT
TO OTHER SCHOOLS FOR THE FINAL
ASSEMBLY, A CHANCE FOR CLOSURE,
TO SEE FRIENDS, TO SAY GOOD-BYE.
>> THIS WILL BRING A LITTLE MORE
IMPACT TO WHAT HAPPENED, BECAUSE
YOU'RE NOT GOING TO SEE SOME OF
YOUR FRIENDS, THOUGH.
>> WE DIDN'T GET TO SAY GOOD-BYE
TO OUR CLASSES, AND IT WAS
REALLY GOOD TO SEE THEM AND TO
BE ABLE TO LOVE ON THEM.
>> Reporter: IT WAS ALSO AN
OPPORTUNITY TO RECONNECT, AND IN
SOME CASES, EXPRESS THANKS TO
TEACHERS FOR GUARDING WHAT EVERY
PARENT CHERISHES MOST.
>> I'M NEVER GOING TO HAVE
ANYTHING, YOU KNOW, ANY WORDS
TO, YOU KNOW, TO REPAY HER FOR
WHAT SHE DID.
YOU KNOW, SHE THREW HERSELF ON
MY DAUGHTER TO PROTECT HER.
>> Reporter: THE GATHERINGS CAME
AS MOORE BURIED THE FIRST OF ITS
24 VICTIMS.
9-YEAR-OLD ANTONIO CANNED ALERO
WAS LAID TO REST.
SHE'S AMONG THE SEVEN CHILDREN
WHO DIED WHEN THE TORNADO
FLATTENED PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY.
EXPERTS COUNSELING CHILDREN HERE
SAY THE SURVIVING STUDENTS ARE
VICTIMS, TOO, LIKELY TRAUMATIZED
BY WHAT THEY SAW MONDAY, WHO
THEY DIDN'T SEE TODAY.
>> PARENTS JUST NEED TO SPEAK
HONESTLY WITH THEIR CHILDREN BUT
TO ALSO REASSURE THEM THAT THERE
ARE PEOPLE WORKING THAT THEY
DON'T EVEN SEE TO MAKE SURE THAT
THEY'RE SAFE.
>> Reporter: THUNDERSTORMS AND
FLOODING IN THE REGION MADE
CLEANUP ALMOST IMPOSSIBLE EARLY
TODAY, BUT UTILITY CREWS AND
TRASH HAULERS WERE ABLE TO GET
OUT LATE THIS AFTERNOON.
FOR A COMMUNITY THAT SUFFERED A
LIFETIME OF HEARTACHE, IN ONLY
DAYS, ONE CHILD'S WORDS MAY SUM
UP MOORE'S RESILIENT SPIRIT.
>> IT MAKES ME REAL GLAD BECAUSE
SOME OF MY HOUSE GOT RIPPED
DOWN, AND IT MAKES ME GLAD TO
SEE MY FRIENDS AND THAT THEY'RE
ALIVE AND THAT I'M ALIVE AND
THAT I'M OKAY.
SO, THAT'S ALL.
>> Reporter: AND LATE TODAY,
OFFICIALS HAVE DRASTICALLY
REVISED DOWNWARD THE NUMBER OF
HOMES DAMAGED HERE.
IT IS 1,200, NOT 13,000.
A BIT OF GOOD NEWS.
ANN, BACK TO YOU.
>> IT IS.
JANET SHAMLIAN, THANK YOU SO
MUCH TONIGHT.
>>> WELL, BAD WEATHER IS MAKING
NEWS ELSEWHERE TONIGHT AS WELL,
A LOT OF UNSETTLED WEATHER IN
THE NORTHEAST IN PARTICULAR
COULD MEAN A VERY HECTIC HOLIDAY
TRAVEL WEEKEND AHEAD.
WEATHER CHANNEL METEOROLOGIST
CHRIS WARREN NOW JOINS US.
HEY, CHRIS.
GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
>> ANN, GOOD EVENING.
SEVERE WEATHER HAS ALREADY
THROWN A REAL WRENCH INTO
TRAVEL, AND WE HAVE SEEN SOME
LONG DELAYS HEADING INTO THE
NORTHEAST AT THE AIRPORT, NEWARK
AND LaGUARDIA, BOTH HAVING FULL
ON GROUND STOPS.
LET'S TAKE A LOOK RIGHT NOW AT
WHERE THAT THREAT DOES CONTINUE
FOR SEVERE WEATHER TONIGHT IN
THE NORTHEAST.
IT'S GOING TO BE HEAVY RAIN,
FLASH FLOODING WITH THE THREAT,
ALSO DAMAGING WINDS YOU'LL HAVE
TO WATCH OUT FOR.
IN TEXAS AND THE SOUTHERN
PLAINS, TORNADOES A POSSIBILITY,
ALSO LARGE HAIL THAT COULD BE
BIGGER THAN BASEBALLS.
NOW, FOR TRAVEL, IF YOU'RE
PLANNING TO HEAD OUT OF TOWN
TOMORROW ALONG WITH ABOUT 35
MILLION MEMORIAL DAY HOLIDAY
TRAVELERS THIS WEEKEND, LOOK FOR
SOME COOL AND RAINY WEATHER IN
THE NORTHEAST.
IF YOU'RE HEADING TO THE ROADS,
LIKE 31 MILLION, IN FACT, MORE
THAN 31 MILLION PEOPLE WILL BE,
YOU HAVE TO WATCH OUT FOR THAT
RAIN IN THE NORTHEAST.
ALSO, IN THE MIDDLE PART OF THE
COUNTRY, THE CHANCE FOR MORE
STORMS.
ANN?
>> ALL RIGHT, CHRIS.
THANK YOU SO MUCH FOR YOUR
REPORTING TONIGHT.
>>> AND ONE MORE NOTE ABOUT THE
WEATHER.
THE PEOPLE AT NOAA WHO TRACK
HURRICANES FOR A LIVING SAID
TODAY THEY EXPECT ANOTHER BUSY
SEASON IN THE ATLANTIC.
13 TO 20 NAMED STORMS, 7 TO 11
HURRICANES, 3 TO 6 OF THOSE
HURRICANES ARE EXPECTED TO BE
MAJOR.
LAST YEAR WAS THE THIRD BUSIEST
SEASON ON RECORD WITH 19 NAMED
STORMS, ONE OF WHICH, OF COURSE,
WAS HURRICANE SANDY, WHICH
CAUSED $50 BILLION IN DAMAGE.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT, ON THE
REBOUND.
AS MILLIONS OF FAMILIES PLAN
THEIR VACATIONS, WHAT THEY'LL BE
SEEING A LOT MORE OF ON THE
ROADS THIS SUMMER.
>>> AND LATER, AN AMAZING
ACCOMPLISHMENT AT 30,000 FEET AT
AN AGE WHEN A LOT OF PEOPLE
WOULD RATHER BE ON A NICE, FLAT
GOLF COURSE.
>>> MEMORIAL DAY WEEKEND MEANS A
LOT OF PEOPLE HITTING THE ROAD,
AND IT'S LIKELY YOU'RE GOING TO
BE SEEING A LOT MORE RVs OUT
THERE.
THEY'RE MAKING A BIG COMEBACK
AFTER A BIG SLUMP DURING THE
RECESSION, AND THAT IS GOOD NEWS
FOR THE PEOPLE OF ECKHART
COUNTY, INDIANA, WHERE MANY OF
THEM ARE MADE.
NBC'S JOHN YANG HAS OUR REPORT.
>> Reporter: FOR PAUL ASH AND
HIS FAMILY, GOING ON VACATION
MEANS LOADING UP THEIR 30-FOOT
RV AND HEADING OUT ON THE OPEN
ROAD.
>> IT DOES ALLOW YOU TO VACATION
IN THE STYLE THAT YOU WANT AT A
PRICE YOU CAN AFFORD.
>> Reporter: MORE AND MORE
PEOPLE AGREE.
AT DEALERSHIPS LIKE THIS ONE
OUTSIDE OF LOS ANGELES, BUSINESS
IS BOOMING, A WELCOME CHANGE
FROM JUST A FEW YEARS AGO.
>> IT'S SOMETHING I'VE BEEN
THINKING ABOUT FOR FOUR OR FIVE
YEARS AND FINALLY DECIDED NOW
PERHAPS MIGHT BE THE TIME.
>> Reporter: FROM 2006 TO 2009
RV SALES PLUNGED 58% AS THE
RECESSION DEEPENED AND BANKS
STOPPED LENDING.
AS THE ECONOMY BOUNCES BACK, SO
HAVE SALES, SHOOTING UP 72%.
GOOD NEWS FOR KEYSTONE RV IN
ELKHART COUNTY, INDIANA.
THIS COUNTY'S UNEMPLOYMENT RATE
WAS ONCE THE HIGHEST IN THE
NATION, ABOVE 20% FOUR YEARS
AGO.
NOW IT'S LESS THAN HALF THAT.
IN 2009 WHEN THE RECESSION WAS
AT ITS WORST KEYSTONE CUT BACK
TO JUST 1,900 EMPLOYEES.
NOW, JUST FOUR YEARS LATER, THEY
EMPLOY 3,200 PEOPLE, A RECORD
FOR THE COMPANY, AND THEY'RE
STILL HIRING.
MORE JOBS AT HIGHER WAGES.
>> I THINK YOU'LL SEE THAT
THROUGHOUT THE COUNTY.
EVERYONE'S FORCED TO DO THAT
BECAUSE THE LABOR POOL'S GETTING
A LITTLE BIT TIGHTER.
>> Reporter: MATTHEW MILLER IS A
RECENT HIRE DRAWN BY BETTER PAY.
AS A HIGH SCHOOL STUDENT, HE SAW
HIS FATHER GET LAID OFF FROM AN
RV PLANT.
NOW HE'S A HUSBAND AND FATHER
HIMSELF.
>> IT'S VERY COMFORTING KNOWING
THAT I CAN WORK IN A PLACE LIKE
THIS, NOT HAVE TO NECESSARILY BE
WORRIED ABOUT MY JOB, AND KNOW
THAT I'M GOING TO BE ABLE TO
PROVIDE FOR MY FAMILY.
>> Reporter: AS ACCELERATING RV
SALES SET A ONCE STRUGGLING
MIDWESTERN COUNTY ON THE ROAD TO
RECOVERY.
JOHN YANG, NBC NEWS, GOSCHAN,
INDIANA.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
A PHOTO SESSION BEFORE THE
SENIOR PROM THAT'S GETTING A LOT
OF ATTENTION TONIGHT.
>>> WE'VE GOT A GORGEOUS VIEW
TODAY OF A VOLCANO ERUPTING IN
ALASKA AND A PICTURE TAKEN FROM
THE INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION.
THE VOLCANO IN THE ALEUTIAN
ISLANDS BEGAN SPEWING OUT ASH ON
MAY 13th.
THIS PHOTO WAS TAKEN ON MAY
18th.
THE PLUME OF ASHES RISES ALMOST
FOUR MILES UP INTO THE
ATMOSPHERE AND STRETCHES ACROSS
HUNDREDS OF MILES.
>>> AND AN 80-YEAR-OLD JAPANESE
CLIMBER MADE IT TO THE TOP OF
THE WORLD TODAY.
YUICHIRO MIURA BROKE THE RECORD
FOR THE OLDEST PERSON TO CLIMB
MT. EVEREST.
WHEN HE REACHED THE SUMMIT.
HE HAS CLIMBED EVEREST TWICE
BEFORE.
HE SET THE RECORD FOR THE OLDEST
PERSON TO CLIMB THE SUMMIT TEN
YEARS AGO.
BEFORE ANOTHER CLIMBER TOOK THE
CROWN FOUR YEARS LATER.
HE POSTED ON HIS FACEBOOK PAGE
TODAY, "THIS IS THE BEST FEELING
IN THE WORLD."
>>> PREPARATIONS FOR MEMORIAL
DAY ARE UNDER WAY AT ARLINGTON
CEMETERY.
THE 3rd U.S. INFANTRY REGIMEN,
WHICH IS THE ARMY'S OFFICIAL
CEREMONIAL UNIT, PLACED FLAGS ON
GRAVE SITES OF EACH SERVICE
MEMBER BURIED AT ARLINGTON.
267,000 IN ALL IN THE ANNUAL
TRADITION KNOWN AS FLAGS IN.
>>> THE YEAR WAS 1979, THE HAIR
WAS BIG, THE CLOTHES WERE
POLYESTER, AND THAT IS THE
FUTURE PRESIDENT OF THE UNITED
STATES BEFORE HIS SENIOR PROM.
TWO PREVIOUSLY UNPUBLISHED
PHOTOGRAPHS WERE GIVEN TO "TIME"
MAGAZINE BY THE GIRL IN THE
MIDDLE, KELLY ALLMAN, WHO WAS
ESCORTED BY BARACK OBAMA'S BEST
FRIEND AT PONOHO SCHOOL IN
HAWAII.
SHE ALSO INCLUDED A NOTE TO
YOUNG BARRY AS HE WAS KNOWN BACK
THEN, WROTE IN HER YEARBOOK, HE
OBSERVED THAT SHE WAS "EXTREMELY
SWEET AND FOXY."
OBAMA'S DATE WAS MEGAN HUGHES, A
SENIOR AT A NEARBY ALL-GIRLS
SCHOOL.
>>> UP NEXT, A INCREDIBLE
SURVIVAL STORY WE HAVEN'T HEARD
ABOUT UNTIL NOW.
A MOTHER IN LABOR AS THE TORNADO
CLOSED IN.
>>> IN THE THREE DAYS SINCE THAT
DEVASTATING TORNADO IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, WE HAVE SEEN SO MUCH
DESTRUCTION, LOSS OF LIFE AND
MISERY.
BUT TONIGHT, WE'RE GOING TO
LEAVE YOU WITH THE STORY OF SOME
PEOPLE WHO HAVE COME TOGETHER TO
HELP, WHETHER IT'S CLEANING UP,
COOKING A MEAL OR EVEN HELPING
WITH A VERY SPECIAL DELIVERY.
NBC'S RON MOTT HAS OUR REPORT.
>> Reporter: SHAYLA TAYLOR
EMBRACED HER NEWBORN SON AGAIN,
A TREASURED MOMENT AFTER GOING
INTO LABOR DURING AN EF-5
TORNADO.
>> IT JUST TOOK THE WALL OFF.
AND THE FIRST THING I DID, OF
COURSE, WAS ASK IF ALL THE
NURSES WERE STILL THERE AND IF
THEY WERE OKAY.
>> Reporter: THIS MORNING, SHE
REUNITED WITH NURSES WHO MOVED
HER TO ANOTHER HOSPITAL WHEN
THEIRS TOOK A DIRECT HIT.
>> MY NURSE GAVE ME A SHOT TO
SLOW DOWN THE CONTRACTIONS, YOU
KNOW, TO KIND OF KEEP ME FROM
GOING INTO TRANSITION.
AND ACTUALLY HAVING A BABY IN
THE MIDST OF A TORNADO.
>> Reporter: SHE LATER DELIVERED
8 POUNDS 3 OUNCE BRADEN
EMANUEL, NOW THE TALK OF THE
TOWN.
>> HE'S A MIRACLE, AND I LOVE
THE NAME THAT SHE HAS FOR HIM,
EMANUEL, GOD IS WITH US, BECAUSE
GOD DEFINITELY WAS WITH US.
>> Reporter: PERFECT STRANGERS
ARE WITH THE COMMUNITY, TOO,
COMING FROM NEAR AND FAR, SOME
TOTING BROOMS AND RAKES, OTHERS
CARRYING TRAYS OF STEAM PULLED
PORK, ALL IN THE SPIRIT, THEY
SAY, OF SIMPLY LOVING THY
NEIGHBOR.
>> IT'S OKLAHOMA.
IT'S JUST KIND OF THE WAY IT IS
HERE.
WE ALL RALLY TOGETHER WHEN
THERE'S A NEED.
>> Reporter: AND YOU'RE ABLE TO
MOBILIZE A TEAM QUICKLY.
HOW DOES THAT HAPPEN?
>> BEING BARBECUE COOKS DOING
COMPETITIONS WE LEARN HOW TO
COOK MOBILE.
>> Reporter: OPERATION BARBECUE
RELIEF IS ALSO HERE, FIRST
COOKED UP DURING JOPLIN,
MISSOURI'S BRUSH WITH A TORNADO
TWO YEARS AGO.
>> THEY NEED COMFORT.
BARBECUE IS COMFORT FOOD.
>> Reporter: WHILE THE GOING IS
TOUGH TODAY FOR MANY, HOPE AND
GRATITUDE ARE IN AMPLE SUPPLY.
>> THOSE WOMEN WERE, THEY WERE
GODSENDS.
THEY DID THEIR BEST TO TAKE CARE
OF ME.
>> Reporter: AND THE LITTLE GUY
ALREADY NICKNAMED TWISTER.
RON MOTT NBC NEWS, MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
>>> AND THAT IS OUR BROADCAST
FOR THIS THURSDAY EVENING.
I'M ANN CURRY IN TONIGHT FOR
BRIAN.
AND FOR ALL OF US HERE AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU AND GOODNIGHT.
>>> NBC BAY AREA NEWS, STARTS
NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING, I'M JESSICA
AGUIRRE, WE BEGIN WITH THE
DEADLY SHOOTING IN SANTA CRUZ OF
TWO POLICE OFFICERS, SHOT AT
POINT BLANK RANGE.
THEY WERE AMBUSHED.
THE GUNMAN WHO KILLED THEM WENT
ON TO GO ON A RAMPAGE THROUGH
THE STREETS, UNTIL HE WAS
KILLED.
MORE ON THE DETAILS.
>> Reporter: WELL, THE DEA SAID
TODAY NOT ONLY WAS THE SHOOTING
JUSTIFIED, IT WAS HEROIC.
TODAY, WE LEARNED HOW CLOSE
GOULET CAME TO SHOOTING PEOPLE
IN THE COMMUNITY.
NEARLY THREE MONTHS AFTER BUTCH
BAKER AND HIS CO-WORKER WERE
LAID TO REST, ON FEBRUARY 26th,
THE TWO OFFICERS WENT TO TALK TO
SEXUAL ASSAULT SUSPECT, JEREMY
GOULET AND TRIED TO COAX HIM OUT
OF HIS HOME.
IT SHOWED HE AGREED TO COME OUT.
>> BOTH OFFICERS WERE THERE AT
THE DOOR STEP WHEN GOULET EXITED
THE HOME.
AND WITHIN THREE SECONDS, HE
FIRED FIVE ROUNDS AT THE TWO
OFFICERS FROM HIS PERSONALLY
OWNED .45 CALIBER AUTOMATIC
PISTOL.
>> Reporter: THE INVESTIGATION
FOUND HE WENT TO S