HE A HERO OR A TRAITOR, TEXT OR
CALL.
WE'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT 6:00.
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT,
DAMAGE CONTROL.
AFTER THE EXPLOSIVE EXPOSURE OF
OUR NATION'S SPY PROGRAM.
TONIGHT, NEW DETAILS ABOUT THE
SOURCE OF FORMER CIA EMPLOYEE,
AND NEW QUESTIONS ABOUT HOW MANY
PEOPLE HAVE ACCESS TO OUR
NATION'S TOP SECRETS.
>>> THE CANCER RISK FOR MILLIONS
OF AMERICAN CHILDREN UNDERGOING
CT SCANS EACH YEAR.
DOCTORS ARE NOW SOUNDING THE
ALARM, RAISING QUESTIONS ABOUT
HOW OFTEN THEY ARE REALLY
NECESSARY.
>>> HIGH DRAMA AS THE GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN TRIAL GETS UNDER WAY
IN FLORIDA.
WHY LEGAL EXPERTS SAY WHAT'S
HAPPENING RIGHT NOW COULD HAVE
THE BIGGEST IMPACT OF ALL ON THE
OUTCOME.
>>> AND LIFE AS A BEATLE.
A NEVER BEFORE SEEN LOOK FROM
BEHIND THE SCENES FROM ONE OF
THE BEATLES BEHIND THE LENS.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>> FROM NBC WORLD HEADQUARTERS
IN NEW YORK, THIS IS "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS WITH BRIAN
WILLIAMS."
>>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
AN INTERNATIONAL MANHUNT FOR THE
29-YEAR-OLD MAN WHO SAYS HE'S
THE ONE WHO EXPOSED THE
GOVERNMENT SECRET SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAM.
WHAT HE TOLD "THE GUARDIAN"
NEWSPAPER IN A STORY PUBLISHED
LAST WEEK CAUSED A FIRESTORM OF
CONTROVERSY OVER PRIVACY AND
NATIONAL SECURITY.
EDWARD SNOWDEN HAS BEEN
IDENTIFIED AS A CONTRACTOR WHO
WORKED AT THE NATIONAL SECURITY
AGENCY, AND YESTERDAY FROM
HALFWAY ACROSS THE WORLD, HE
STEPPED FROM THE SHADOWS,
ADMITTING HE WAS THE LEAK.
AND TONIGHT, THE U.S. GOVERNMENT
IS HOT ON SNOWDEN'S TAIL AS IT
INVESTIGATES WHETHER OR NOT HE
BROKE THE LAW BY SHARING
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION.
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL IS WORKING
THE STORY FOR US TONIGHT FROM
WASHINGTON.
ANDREA?
>> Reporter: LESTER, GOOD
EVENING.
THEY HAVE LAUNCHED THE MANHUNT
FOR.
THE 29-YEAR-OLD NSA CONTRACTOR,
EDWARD SNOWDEN, HAS TURNED THE
MASSIVE NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY
INSIDE OUT.
FEDERAL AGENTS AT THE HOME TODAY
OF EDWARD SNOWDEN'S MOTHER IN
ELLICOTT CITY, MARYLAND, ONLY
MILES FROM THE NSA IN FT. MEADE.
>> ARE YOU GUYS WITH THE FBI?
>> Reporter: SNOWDEN'S MOTHER
POLITELY DUCKED REPORTERS.
>> PLEASE DO NOT GET IN MY WAY.
THANK YOU.
HAVE A GOOD DAY.
>> Reporter: FBI AGENTS SHOWED
UP AT HIS FATHER'S HOME NEAR
ALLENTOWN, PENNSYLVANIA.
>> MY NAME IS EDWARD SNOWDEN.
I WORK FOR BOOZ ALLEN HAMILTON
AS AN INFRASTRUCTURE FOR THE NSA
IN HAWAII.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO THE
GUARDIAN, THE 29-YEAR-OLD WAS A
HIGH SCHOOL DROPOUT.
HE ENLISTED IN THE ARMY, BUT WAS
DISCHARGED FIVE MONTHS LATER FOR
BREAKING BOTH LEGS IN A TRAINING
ACCIDENT.
WORKED FOR THE CIA UNDERCOVER IN
GENEVA AND SAYS HE BECAME
DISILLUSIONED.
SIGNED UP FOR A MILITARY
CONTRACTOR AT A BASE IN JAPAN.
HE JOINED BOOZ ALLEN HAM 8 ON
THE WORKING IN HAWAII.
AND A MONTH LATER HE COPIED TOP
SECRET DOCUMENTS AND THEN FLEW
TO HONG KONG TO MEET WITH GLENN
GREENWALD OF "THE GUARDIAN."
SNOWDEN SAYS HAVING BECOME
HARDENED ABOUT THE GOVERNMENT'S
SURVEILLANCE PROGRAMS.
HE TOLD "THE GUARDIAN" --
>> I'M JUST ANOTHER GUY THAT
SITS IN THE OFFICE DAY TO DAY
AND
WATCHES WHAT IS HAPPENING AND
THINK THIS IS NOT OUR PLACE TO
DECIDE.
THE PUBLIC NEEDS TO DECIDE
WHETHER THESE ARE RIGHT OR
WRONG.
>> THAT'S THE REASON WHY HE FELT
SO COMPELLED TO INFORM HIS
CITIZENS ABOUT THE CAPABILITIES
THIS MASSIVE SURVEILLANCE
PROGRAM PROVIDES.
>> Reporter: NO SIGN OF HIM AT
HIS HOME IN HAWAII, AND HE MAY
HAVE LEFT HONG KONG AS WELL.
>> HONG KONG DOES HAVE AN
EXTRADITION TREATY WITH THE U.S.
AND A RECORD OF CLOSE
COOPERATION, BUT EXTRADITION
COULD TAKE MONTHS, AND CHINA HAS
A VETO.
NO ACTION CAN BE TAKEN UNTIL
THERE IS A CHARGE.
PLUS SNOWDEN STILL HAS TO BE
FOUND.
>> Reporter: A BIG WORRY NOW FOR
THE U.S. WHAT DO THE CHINESE
KNOW?
>> OBVIOUSLY WE WOULD BE
CONCERNED IF SOME OF THE VERY
SENSITIVE INFORMATION HE HAS
WOULD FALL INTO THE HANDS OF A
FOREIGN INTELLIGENCE.
>> Reporter: CALLING THE TOP
SECRET LEAKS GUT-WRENCHING.
>> THE DAMAGE THAT THESE
REVELATIONS INCUR ARE HUGE.
>> Reporter: BRITAIN'S FOREIGN
SECRETARY CANCELED A TRIP TO
WASHINGTON TODAY TO DEFEND
COOPERATING WITH THE NSA.
>> THIS RELATIONSHIP HAS BEEN
AND REMAINS ESSENTIAL TO THE
SECURITY OF BOTH NATIONS.
>> Reporter: BUT TO A BAND OF
SUPPORTERS IN NEW YORK TODAY,
SNOWDEN IS COURAGEOUS.
JULIAN ASSANGE OF WIKILEAKS
CALLED HIM A HERO.
MICHAEL MOORE TWEETED HERO OF
THE YEAR.
MANY AGREE THE POWER OF THE NSA
COULD BE THEY'RE ROAD.
>> WE NEED TO MAKE AN INFORMED
JUDGMENT IF WE NEED MORE CIVIL
LIBERTIES PROTECTIONS IN THE
LAW.
>> Reporter: WHY HIRE SOMEONE
WITH SO LITTLE FOREIGN EDUCATION
TO HANDLE SUCH SENSITIVE
SECRETS?
INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS SAY THE
REAL WHIZ KIDS ARE KIDS, THE
GENERATION THAT LEARNED
COMPUTERS EVEN BEFORE THEY COULD
TALK.
LESTER?
>> ANDREA, THANKS.
SNOWDEN IS ONE OF THE MILLION
AMERICAN GRANTED INTELLIGENCE
CLEARANCES, CARRYING OUT MANY OF
THE GOVERNMENT'S INTELLIGENCE
FUNCTIONS.
BUT IT DOES RAISE QUESTIONS
WHETHER TOO MANY CONTRACTORS ARE
NOW IN ON THE GOVERNMENT'S
SECRETS.
TO GET THAT PART OF THE STORY
TONIGHT FROM NBC'S SENIOR
INVESTIGATIVE CORRESPONDENT LISA
MYERS.
>> Reporter: MOST US THINK
INTELLIGENCE INVOLVES SPIES FROM
THE CIA, EAVESDROPPING BY THE
SUPER SECRET NSA, AND
INFORMATION GATHERED BY THE
PENTAGON.
BUT THERE IS ALSO A HUGE SHADOW
INTELLIGENCE COMMUNITY OF
PRIVATE CONTRACTORS, SOME OF
THEM CORPORATIONS WITH FAMILIAR
NAMES.
AFTER 9/11, WHEN THE GOVERNMENT
FAILED TO CONNECT THE DOTS, THE
DEMAND FOR PRIVATE INTELLIGENCE
EXPLODED, LEADING TO WHAT A
FORMER OFFICIAL CALLED A HIRING
BINGE OF BATTALIONS OF YOUNG,
SMART NERDS.
>> WHAT ONCE STARTED AS A
PROCESS OF AUGMENTING AND
FIGHTING THE WAR ON TERRORISM
HAS NOW BECOME AN INDUSTRIAL
SYSTEM.
IT'S AN INDUSTRIAL SYSTEM THAT
WORKS ON A PROFIT MOTIVE.
>> Reporter: NEAR THE NSA HUGE
COMPLEX IN FT. MEADE, MARYLAND
THERE ARE NOW OFFICE BUILDINGS
FULL OF CONTRACTORS.
ACCORDING TO THE GOVERNMENT,
ALMOST FIVE MILLION INDIVIDUALS
NOW HOLD SECURITY CLEARANCES.
1.4 MILLION OF THEM TOP SECRET.
ONE-THIRD HELD BY PRIVATE
CONTRACTORS.
A CHECK OF THE JOB WEBSITE
MONSTER.COM TODAY SHOWED 796 JOB
OPENINGS REQUIRING TOP SECRET
CLEARANCES.
THE CURRENT DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE, JAMES CLAPPER,
WORKED FOR PRIVATE CONTRACTORS
BETWEEN GOVERNMENT JOBS AND
HIS PREDECESSOR MIKE McCONNELL
NOW WORKS FOR BOOZ ALLEN.
MANY CONTRACTORS HAVE
INTELLIGENCE OR MILITARY
EXPERIENCE, BUT OTHERS ARE
20-SOMETHING TECHNICIANS LIKE
EDWARD SNOWDEN.
>> THEY'RE NOT MOTIVATED
NECESSARILY BY PATRIOTISM.
THEY'RE NOT MOTIVATED
NECESSARILY BY A SCAR OF 9/11.
THIS IS A JOB.
>> Reporter: WHILE ACKNOWLEDGING
THE RISK, INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS
ARGUE THAT PRIVATE CONTRACTORS
NOW ARE CRITICAL, EVEN
INDISPENSABLE.
>> THE INTELLIGENCE AGENCIES
TELL ME THAT THEY SIMPLY COULD
NOT FUNCTION EFFECTIVELY WITHOUT
THE PERSONNEL, TECHNOLOGY, AND
EXPERTISE OF THESE PRIVATE
CONTRACTORS.
>> Reporter: A DELICATE BALANCE
WITH THE NATION'S SECURITY AT
STAKE.
LISA MYERS, NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO A STORY WE'RE
FOLLOWING CLOSELY OVERSEAS
TONIGHT.
CONTINUING CONCERN ABOUT THE
HEALTH OF FORMER SOUTH AFRICAN
PRESIDENT NELSON MANDELA,
WHO HAS BEEN HOSPITALIZED SINCE
SATURDAY WITH A LUNG INFECTION.
NBC'S KEIR SIMMONS IS IN
PRETORIA TONIGHT WITH THE
LATEST.
KEIR, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
THOSE CLOSE TO NELSON MANDELA
HAVE BEEN COMING TO THE HOSPITAL
HERE.
FOR THE FIRST TIME HIS DOCTORS
SAY HIS CONDITION IS SERIOUS,
AND SOUTH AFRICA'S PRESIDENT HAS
CALLED ON THE NATION TO PRAY FOR
MANDELA AND HIS FAMILY.
THIS AFTERNOON, WINNIE MANDELA
PAID A VISIT TO THE HOSPITAL IN
PRETORIA.
NELSON MANDELA'S FORMER WIFE AND
FELLOW ANTI-APARTHEID
CAMPAIGNER.
THEY WERE MARRIED THROUGHOUT HIS
27 YEARS IN PRISON.
TUBERCULOSIS WEAKENED HIS LUNGS.
DOCTORS TREATING THE FORMER
PRESIDENT DESCRIBE HIM AS IN
SERIOUS BUT STABLE CONDITION.
>> FORMER PRESIDENT NELSON
MANDELA REMAINS IN THE HOSPITAL,
AND HIS CONDITION IS UNCHANGED.
>> Reporter: THROUGHOUT THE DAY,
VISITORS HAVE COME AND GONE.
BUT REPORTS SUGGEST ONLY THOSE
CLOSEST TO HIM ARE ACTUALLY BY
HIS SIDE, INCLUDING CURRENT WIFE
GRACA MACHEL, SEEN HERE ON HIS
94th BIRTHDAY.
ACROSS SOUTH AFRICA THERE ARE
PRAYERS AS WELL AS FEARS.
>> WE LOVE HIM VERY MUCH.
HE NEEDS TO RECOVER.
>> IT IS TIME FOR HIM TO GO.
IT'S TIME TO GO.
>> Reporter: THE FORMER
PRESIDENT, WHO TURNS 95 NEXT
MONTH, HAS LONG BEEN IN FAILING
HEALTH.
MANY PEOPLE WERE SHOCKED BY HIS
FRAIL APPEARANCE IN THIS AWKWARD
PHOTO OP LAST APRIL.
THE FATHER OF HIS NATION, NOW
SURROUNDED BY FAMILY.
IN THE FIGHT OF HIS LIFE.
AND ANOTHER MEMBER OF NELSON
MANDELA'S FAMILY ON HER WAY TO
THE HOSPITAL HERE, HIS DAUGHTER
ZENANI, FLYING IN FROM
ARGENTINA, WHERE SHE IS SOUTH
AFRICAN'S AMBASSADOR.
MEANWHILE, WELL WISHES, HOPES
FOR HIS RECOVERY ARE POURING IN
FROM AROUND THE WORLD, LESTER.
>> ALL RIGHT, KEIR, THANK YOU.
>>> MEANTIME, ALSO OVERSEAS,
WE'RE MONITORING THE HEALTH OF
BRITAIN'S PRINCE PHILIP, THE
QUEEN'S HUSBAND, WHO SPENT HIS
92nd BIRTHDAY TODAY IN THE
HOSPITAL, RECOVERING FROM
EXPLORATORY ABDOMINAL SURGERY.
THE QUEEN STOPPED BY TO CHECK ON
HIM FOR ABOUT A HALF HOUR THIS
EVENING.
BUCKINGHAM PALACE SAYS THE
PRINCE IS IN GOOD SPIRITS.
HE WILL REMAIN IN THE HOSPITAL
AT LEAST THROUGH NEXT WEEK.
>>> IN A FLORIDA COURTROOM, JURY
SELECTION BEGAN IN THE TRIAL OF
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN, WHO IS CHARGED
WITH SECOND-DEGREE MURDER IN THE
SHOOTING DEATH OF AN UNARMED
TEENAGER LAST YEAR.
THE KILLING OF TRAYVON MARTIN
LED TO LARGE PROTESTS BEFORE THE
ARRESTS OF ZIMMERMAN, WHO SAYS
HE ACTED IN SELF-DEFENSE.
NBC'S RON MOTT IS COVERING THE
TRIAL FOR US.
HELLO, RON.
>> Reporter: HEY THERE, LESTER,
GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
FEBRUARY 26th LAST YEAR, GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN WAS A NEIGHBORHOOD
WATCH LEADER AT A CONDO COMPLEX
NEAR HERE.
TRAYVON MARTIN WAS STAYING
THERE, AND THEIR PATHS CROSSED
WITH DEADLY CONSEQUENCES.
>> I FELT HIS ARM GOING DOWN TO
MY SIDE AND I GRABBED MY FIREARM
AND SHOT HIM ONE TIME.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN 15 MONTHS
AFTER TELLING POLICE ABOUT HIS
SIDE OF THE STORY HE SHOT AND
KILLED UNARMED 17-YEAR-OLD
TRAYVON MARTIN, 29-YEAR-OLD
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN IS NOW ON TRIAL
FOR MURDER.
>> I CAN TELL YOU AS A FAMILY,
WE'RE VERY CONFIDENT IN THE
OUTCOME OF THE CASE, AND VERY
CONFIDENT THAT THE STATE WILL
NOT BE ABLE TO MEET ITS BURDEN.
>> Reporter: SIX PANELISTS SHOWN
FROM A POOL OF 500 TO SERVE ON
THE JURY.
A PROCESS THAT COULD TAKE WEEKS
AS ATTORNEYS WADE THROUGH STACKS
OF QUESTIONNAIRES.
>> THE DEFENSE WANTS WHITE
JURORS WHO LOVE THEIR GUNS,
MAYBE VICTIMS OF A CRIME.
AND THE DEFENSE WANTS THOSE WHO
DON'T WANT VIGILANTES WALKING
AROUND WITH GUNS IN THEIR
POCKETS.
>> Reporter: ZIMMERMAN HAS
PLEADED NOT GUILTY.
HIS ATTORNEY SAYS HE ACTED IN
SELF-DEFENSE AFTER BEING
ATTACKED BY MARTIN.
>> WE ARE --
>> TRAYVON!
>> Reporter: THE SIX-WEEK PERIOD
BETWEEN THE SHOOTING AND
ZIMMERMAN'S ARREST SPARKED
PROTESTS HERE AND AROUND THE
COUNTRY, WITH CRITICS CHARGING
RACE WAS A FACTOR IN THE CASE,
ARGUING POLICE WOULD HAVE BEEN
QUICKER TO MAKE AN ARREST HAD
THE VICTIM BEEN WHITE.
>> ALL OF THESE ISSUES SNOW
BALLED INTO A LARGER NARRATIVE
ABOUT RACE THAT I DON'T THINK
WAS REALLY PART OF THE STORY
WHEN TRAYVON MARTIN DIED.
>> Reporter: MARTIN KILLED LESS
THAN AN HOUR SEEN BUYING CANDY
AND ICED TEA FROM A CONVENIENCE
STORE.
THE ENCOUNTER BETWEEN MARTIN AND
ZIMMERMAN COULD BE HEARD ON A
911 CALL.
>> SO YOU THINK HE'S YELLING
HELP?
>> YES.
>> WHAT IS YOUR --
>> JUST -- THERE'S GUNSHOTS.
>> YOU JUST HEARD GUNSHOTS?
>> YES.
>> HOW MANY?
>> JUST ONE.
>> Reporter: TODAY, MARTIN'S
FAMILY ASKED FOR PEACE AND
JUSTICE.
>> WE ARE RELIEVED THAT THE
START OF THE TRIAL IS HERE WITH
THE JURY SELECTION, AS WE SEEK
JUSTICE FOR OUR SON TRAYVON,
AND WE ALSO SEEK A FAIR AND
IMPARTIAL TRIAL.
>> Reporter: ONCE THE JURY IS
SEATED, THE TRIAL IS EXPECTED TO
RUN ANYWHERE FROM THREE TO SIX
WEEKS.
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN'S ATTORNEY SAID
IT'S TOO SOON TO KNOW IF HE WILL
TAKE THE STAND IN HIS OWN
DEFENSE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
RON MOTT, THANK YOU.
WE WANT TO NOTE HERE THAT GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN HAS SUED NBCUNIVERSAL,
THE PARENT COMPANY OF THIS
NETWORK FOR DEFAMATION.
THE COMPANY HAS STRONGLY DENIED
HIS ALLEGATIONS.
THERE IS A LOT MORE TO TELL YOU
ABOUT AS WE CONTINUE TONIGHT.
DOCTORS SOUNDING THE ALARM ABOUT
CT SCANS AND CANCER RISKS FOR
MILLIONS OF AMERICAN KIDS.
>>> LATER, AN INSPIRING FATHER
AND SON BREAKING BARRIERS AND
HELPING A LOT OF FOLKS ACHIEVE
WHAT WAS ONCE THOUGHT TO BE
IMPOSSIBLE.
>>> OUR HEALTH NEWS TONIGHT
INVOLVES A NEW WARNING FOR
PARTICIPANTS ABOUT CHILDREN
UNDERGOING MULTIPLE CT SCANS TO
HELP DOCTORS DIAGNOSIS MEDICAL
ISSUES AND THE RISK DEVELOPING
CANCER LATER ON IN LIFE.
AS SUMMER RAPIDLY APPROACHES AND
KIDS ARE OUT OF SCHOOL, DOCTORS
WILL SEE THE USUAL INCREASE IN
INJURIES FROM KIDS PLAYING
OUTSIDE, AND OFTENTIMES THAT
MEANS A CT SCAN IS NECESSARY.
NOW DOCTORS ARE STARTING TO TAKE
A CLOSER LOOK AT HOW OFTEN KIDS
GET THEM, AND THE EFFECTS OF ALL
THAT RADIATION.
WE GET OUR REPORT TONIGHT FROM
CHIEF MEDICAL EDITOR DR. NANCY
SNYDERMAN.
>> Reporter: 5-YEAR-OLD DAJON
FRAZIER IS HAVING A CT SCAN
TODAY.
HIS MOTHER IS FOLLOWING UP ON A
COMPLEX EAR AND EYE CONDITION,
AND THIS SCAN IS THE BEST WAY TO
MAKE THE DIAGNOSIS.
>> ONLY THING MY CONCERN WAS
REALLY MORE SO THAN ANYTHING WAS
JUST TO MAKE SURE HE WAS ALL
RIGHT.
>> Reporter: WHILE CT SCANS ARE
INVALUABLE, THERE IS ALSO A
RISK.
UNNECESSARY EXPOSURE TO
RADIATION CAN BE DAMAGING TO
GROWING CHILDREN, AND REPEATED
OR HIGH DOSAGES MAY INCREASE THE
RISK OF CANCER LATER IN LIFE.
RESEARCHERS ANALYZED DATA IN
CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 15 WHO
HAD CT SCANS BETWEEN 1996 AND
2011.
THEY LOOKED AT THE FREQUENCY AND
THE LEVEL OF RADIATION DOSAGES,
AND ESTIMATED THAT OF THE FOUR
MILLION SCANS PERFORMED EACH
YEAR, MORE THAN 4800 CHILDREN
COULD DEVELOP FUTURE CANCERS.
>> THE LARGEST INCREASE FOR
ABDOMEN CTs, ESPECIALLY IN OLDER
CHILDREN, AND THIS IS WORRISOME
BECAUSE ABDOMEN CT HAS THE
GREATEST RADIATION EXPOSURE AND
THE GREATEST CANCER RISKS,
ESPECIALLY IN GIRLS.
>> Reporter: HOSPITALS ACROSS
THE COUNTRY ARE MAKING EFFORTS
TO REDUCE RADIATION EXPOSURE FOR
THEIR SMALLEST AND MOST
VULNERABLE PATIENTS.
DR. SHIREEN'S TEAM AT DOCTOR'S
MEDICAL CENTER IN WASHINGTON,
D.C. HAS BEEN ABLE TO REDUCE THE
NUMBER OF CT SCANS BY ABOUT 30%
IN THE PAST TWO YEARS BY
CAREFULLY EVALUATING A CHILD'S
RISK BASED ON INJURY, ILLNESS,
AND MEDICAL HISTORY.
>> WE LOOK AT THEIR MENTAL
STATUS.
ARE THEY AWAKE, ALERT, ABLE TO
TALK TO YOU?
DO THEY RECOGNIZE THEIR PARENTS?
AND THEN WE LOOK AT A SLEW OF
SIGNS AND SYMPTOMS.
>> THIS IS HIS EAR.
>> Reporter: DR. RAYMOND DEE,
CHIEF OF RADIOLOGY, MEETS WITH
PARENTS TO CAREFULLY RAISE THE
PROS AND CONS OF CT SCAN.
>> IT WILL ALLOW US TO AVOID
PROCEDURE?
OTHER PROCEDURES AS WELL?
THE RISK AND BENEFIT IS
SOMETHING THAT NEEDS TO BE
BALANCED.
>> Reporter: HOSPITALS THAT
DON'T HAVE LOW-DOSE CT SCANNERS
CAN RETROFIT THEM FOR $150,000
TO $200,000.
BUT THEY HAVE TO MAKE THAT
CAPITAL INVESTMENT.
AND IN THE MEANTIME, IF YOUR
CHILD OR GRANDCHILD NEEDS A CT
SCAN, ASK IF IT'S NECESSARY,
LESTER, HOW MANY SLICES THEY
REALLY HAVE TO IMAGE, AND
FRANKLY, IF THERE ARE OTHER
ALTERNATIVES THERE ARE ALWAYS
QUESTIONS.
>> GOOD QUESTIONS TO ASK.
ALL RIGHT, NANCY, THANKS VERY
MUCH.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
AN AMATEUR PHOTOGRAPHER WHO
CAPTURED BEATLEMANIA AS FEW
OTHERS COULD.
♪
>>> RINGO STARR, PHOTOGRAPHER IN
THE BEATLES' FIRST MOVIE "A HARD
DAY'S NIGHT."
IT TURNS OUT RINGO WAS QUITE A
PHOTOGRAPHER IN REAL LIFE AS
WELL, AND HE IS OUT WITH AN
EXHIBIT AND AN eBOOK ON iTUNES
THIS WEEK WITH NEVER BEFORE SEEN
SHOTS FROM HIS PERSONAL ARCHIVE,
BEHIND THE SCENES AT THE HEIGHT
OF BEATLE MANIA.
RINGO SPOKE TO KEIR SIMMONS
ABOUT WHAT IT FELT LIKE FOR THE
BEATLES TO CONQUER AMERICA IN
1964.
>> WHEN WE GOT TO AMERICA, IT
WAS LIKE TOO BIG, ALL OF THE
MUSIC WE LOVED CAME OUT OF
AMERICA.
♪ CLOSE YOUR EYES AND I'LL MISS
YOU ♪
>> THE NEW YORKERS FEEL LIKE
THEY OWNED THE BEATLES, THAT'S
WHERE WE LANDED.
IT WAS THE MOST EXCITING MOMENT.
YOU COULD FEEL NEW YORK AS THE
PLANE WENT OVER, AS THE PLANE
WAS GOING OVER NEW YORK, YOU
COULD FEEL THE VIBE, IT WAS SO
GREAT.
IT WAS LIKE A DREAM COME TRUE,
WE'RE ACTUALLY THERE, AND WE'RE
ACTUALLY THERE AT A GOOD TIME.
WE'RE NUMBER ONE.
>> RINGO STARR, THE BEATLES
COMING TO AMERICA AT THE TOP OF
THE CHARTS, ALMOST 50 YEARS AGO.
>>> IT WAS ALSO 50 YEARS AGO
THAT THE EQUAL PAY ACT BECAME
LAW IN THIS COUNTRY.
IT WAS SIGNED BY PRESIDENT JOHN
F. KENNEDY AND WAS AIMED AT
ELIMINATING THE GAP BETWEEN WHAT
MEN AND WOMEN EARNED.
AT THAT TIME, WOMEN MADE 59
CENTS FOR EVERY DOLLAR MEN
EARNED.
TODAY AT A WHITE HOUSE CEREMONY,
PRESIDENT OBAMA NOTED THE GOAL
STILL HASN'T BEEN REACHED, WITH
WOMEN NOW MAKING ABOUT 77 CENTS
FOR EVERY DOLLAR MEN EARN.
THE PRESIDENT SAID THIS IS THE
21st CENTURY, AND IT'S TIME TO
CLOSE THAT GAP.
>>> SOMETHING TO THINK ABOUT
ON YOUR NEXT NIGHT OUT WITH
FRIENDS WHERE ONE IS THE
DESIGNATED WHO ARE SUPPOSED TO
BE THE RESPONSIBLE ONES AND GET
EVERYONE HOME SAFELY AWAY FROM
THE ALCOHOL.
BUT A NEW STUDY NEARLY 40% OF
DESIGNATED DRIVERS ACTUALLY
DRINK.
AND 20% DRINK SO MUCH IT
SIGNIFICANTLY IMPAIRS THEIR
ABILITY TO DRIVE.
RESEARCHERS SAY THE EVIDENCE
SHOWS OFTENTIMES THE DESIGNATED
DRIVER IS CHOSEN BECAUSE THEY
ARE CONSIDERED THE LEAST DRUNK
AMONG THE GROUP, OR BECAUSE THEY
THINK THEY HAVE PREVIOUSLY
DRIVEN DRUNK JUST FINE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, ONE DAD'S
EXTRAORDINARY IDEA TO HELP HIS
SON AND CHANGE A LOT OF LIVES IN
THE PROCESS.
>> TELL ME.
>>> THE BIG IDEA, BROUGHT TO YOU
BY THE BRILLIANT MINDS AND
MACHINES OF GE.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, A NOVEL
IDEA AND CERTAINLY A BIG IDEA.
HIRE PEOPLE WITH AUTISM FOR THE
KINDS OF JOBS THAT MIGHT FIT
THEM WELL AND NOW THESE WORKERS
ARE INCREASINGLY FINDING
THEMSELVES IN DEMAND, AS WE HEAR
FROM NBC'S STEPHANIE GOSK
TONIGHT, IT IS PAYING OFF FOR
EVERYONE.
>> EVEN IT OUT A BIT.
>> Reporter: FOR MANY, THE
HIGH-TECH WORLD OF COMPUTER GAME
DESIGN IS A MYSTERY.
FOR CHERYL O'BRIEN, IT'S SECOND
NATURE.
SHE CREATED THIS DIGITAL ABACUS
FOR THE iPAD.
>> PRETTY COOL, CHERYL.
>> YOU LIKE THAT?
>> Reporter: A COMPUTER
PROGRAMMER, LIKE EVERYONE AT THE
NONPAREIL INSTITUTE, HAS A FORM
OF AUTISM.
HOLDING DOWN A REGULAR JOB HAS
BEEN A STRUGGLE.
>> I WAS THROWING PAPERS JUST TO
SURVIVE, DOING CROSSING GUARD.
>> YOU WERE DELIVERING PAPERS?
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: AT NONPAREIL, SHE
IS A FULL-TIME PAID EMPLOYEE.
THE NONPROFIT INSTITUTE IN
PLANO, TEXAS, TEACHES SOFTWARE
SKILLS AND THEN HIRES MANY OF
THE STUDENTS TO DESIGN GAMES,
APPS, AND E-BOOKS FOR SALE.
>> THAT'S REALLY GOOD.
DID YOU MAKE THAT?
>> YES.
>> Reporter: DAN SELLICK CAME UP
WITH THE IDEA, INSPIRED BY HIS
SON WHO HAS AUTISM.
>> WE PARENTS ARE DESPERATE FOR
ANSWERS FOR OUR KIDS.
>> Reporter: THE SOFTWARE
DEVELOPER STARTED NONPAREIL FOUR
YEARS AGO WITH A HANDFUL OF
STUDENTS.
NOW THEY HAVE 125.
>> WE'RE VERY SUCCESSFUL IN
TECHNOLOGY.
IT SPEAKS TO ALL OF THEIR
STRENGTHS, THE QUIETER
ENVIRONMENT, THE SOUND
ISOLATION.
THROUGH THE PRODUCTS THAT THEY
BUILD, THEY CAN PROVIDE A LIVING
FOR THEMSELVES.
>> Reporter: IN OTHER WORDS, A
FUTURE.
>> TECHNOLOGY CAN BE VERY
PREDICTABLE.
PEOPLE SEEM TO BE GRAVITATED
TOWARDS THOSE KINDS OF AREAS.
AND SO WE'RE STARTING TO SEE
MANY COMPANIES INVOLVED IN
TECHNOLOGY REALLY TAP INTO THIS
POOL OF WORKERS.
>> Reporter: THE SOFTWARE FIRM
S.A.P. ANNOUNCED A GOAL OF
HIRING AS MANY AS 650 EMPLOYEES
WITH AUTISM.
THREE YEARS AGO, ALLIANT DATA
HIRED BERNIE FISH WHO HAS
AUTISM.
>> WHY WOULDN'T ANYBODY DO THIS?
THESE EMPLOYEES SHOW UP TO WORK
ON TIME.
THEY DO A REMARKABLE JOB.
>> KEEP GOING.
>> Reporter: A BIG IDEA THAT
RECOGNIZES SKILLS IN HIGH DEMAND
AND GIVES PEOPLE WITH AUTISM NEW
HOPE FOR A BETTER LIFE.
>> WE'RE A FAMILY HERE.
>> Reporter: STEPHANIE GOSK, NBC
NEWS, PLANO, TEXAS.
>> THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR THIS
MONDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NBC BAY AREA NEWS STARTS
NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING, AND THANKS FOR
JOINING US ON THIS MONDAY.
CUSTOMERS TAKEN FOR A RIDE, A
SOUTH BAY TRAVEL AGENCY APPEARS
TO HAVE EITHER SHUT DOWN WITHOUT
ANY WARNING.
DOZENS OF CUSTOMERS ARE LEARNING
THAT THE TICKETS THEY PAID TO
BUY ARE NO GOOD OR NONEXISTENT.
>> Reporter: A SIGN ON THE FRONT
DOOR HERE AT SUNLIGHT TRAVEL
SAYS THAT THEY'RE CLOSED TO FILE
BANKRUPTCY.
BUT THAT SIGN HAS NO DATE ON IT.
TODAY, A STEADY STREAM OF
CLIENTS STOPPED BY AND FOUND OUT
THE HARD WAY THAT THE BUSINESS
THEY HAD GIVEN MONEY TO BOOK
TRAVEL PLANS MAY HAVE TAKEN THEM
FOR A RIDE.
>> I'M VERY ANGRY.
>> Reporter: DOZENS OF PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN SHOWING UP.
AND ALL OF THEM HAVE A STORY.
>> I LOST MONEY, AND I CANNOT GO
TO VIETNAM TO VISIT MY MOM.
>> TICKETS CANCEL.
HE SAID NO, I PAY IN FULL.
AND SO THE AIRLINE SAY YOU NEED
TO CALL YOUR TRAVEL AGENCY.
>> Reporter: SOME CLIENTS HAVE
BEEN COMING HERE FOR YEAR DOES
BOOK TRIPS TO VIETNAM, AND THIS
IS THE FIRST TIME THEY'VE HAD
PROBLEMS, BUT THESE ARE BIG
PROBLEMS.
THE WEBSITE IS STILL UP, BUT BY
ALL APPEARANCES, THE TRAVEL
AGENCY HAS SHUT DOWN AND FILED
FOR BANKRUPTCY.
THERE IS A THREE DAY NOTICE TO
PAY RENT OR QUIT.
>> I THINK IT'S A SCAM.
YOU DON'T WEAK UP OVERNIGHT AND
SAY I'M GOING TO FILE