THIS WEEKEND.
NO RAIN IN THE FORECAST.
LOOKS PRETTY COMFORTABLE.
>>> THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU BACK AT 6:00.
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT,
OUT OF CONTROL.
VIOLENT CLASHES AS POLICE STORM
THOUSANDS OF PROTESTERS.
FIRES ERUPTING AS THE CRISIS
TAKES A FRIGHTENING TURN FOR A
MAJOR U.S. ALLY OVERSEAS.
OUR RICHARD ENGEL IS THERE.
>>> DID HE ACT ALONE?
WHAT WE'VE LEARNED TONIGHT ABOUT
THE AMERICANONTRACTOR WHO
EXPOSED THE U.S. SPY PROGRAM MAY
HAVE HAD HELP.
>>> PAYING THE PRICE, AN EYE
OPENING NEW LOOK AT HOW THE
NATION'S BIGGEST BANKS ARE
MAKING MORE THAN HALF THEIR FEES
AND A WARNING TONIGHT FOR ANYONE
WITH A BANK ACCOUNT.
>>> SOUNDING THE ALARM FOR
MILLIONS OF AMERICAN BOOMERS
LOSING THEIR HEARING EARLIER
THAN EVER.
WHAT DOCTORS SAY IS TO BLAME AND
WHAT YOU CAN DO TO SLOW IT DOWN.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>> FROM NBC NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS
IS "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH BRIAN
WILLIAMS.
>>> GOOD EVENING, I'M LESTER
HOLT IN FOR BRIAN TONIGHT.
WE BEGIN WITH A FIERY AND
DRAMATIC CRACKDOWN ON
ANTI-GOVERNMENT PROTESTERS IN
TURKEY.
AN IMPORTANT AMERICAN ALLY
FEELING THE HEAT TONIGHT.
IF YOU WERE WATCHING CABLE NEWS
TODAY, YOU SAW IT ALL UNFOLD
LIVE.
POLICE MOVING IN WITH TEAR GAS,
TRYING TO REMOVE PROTESTERS FROM
ISTANBUL'S MAIN PUBLIC SQUARE.
AND PROTESTERS FIGHTING BACK
WITH GASOLINE BOMBS AND
FIREWORKS.
PROTESTS HAVE BEEN HAPPENING IN
TURKEY FOR TWO WEEKS NOW.
REMARKABLE NOT ONLY FOR THEIR
SIZE AND FERVOR, BUT BECAUSE THE
TARGET OF ALL THAT ANGER IS A
THREE-TIME DEMOCRATICALLY
ELECTED PRESIDENT.
TODAY THINGS REACHED A WHOLE NEW
LEVEL.
IN THE MIDDLE OF IT ALL HAS BEEN
OUR CHIEF FOREIGN CORRESPONDENT
RICHARD ENGEL.
HE JOINS US FROM ABOVE
ISTANBUL'S TAKSIM SQUARE WHERE
AT THIS LATE HOUR, THE AIR IS
APPARENTLY STILL THICK WITH TEAR
GAS.
RICHARD?
>> Reporter: IT IS FULL OF TEAR
GAS, AND THAT IS WHY I'M WEARING
THIS MASK.
THE CLASHES HERE ARE ONGOING.
STILL, IT DOESN'T FEEL LIKE AN
ARAB SPRING MOMENT OR A TURNING
POINT.
BUT IF THESE CLASHES CONTINUE,
IT COULD BECOME A MAJOR PROBLEM
FOR TURKEY, ONE OF THE MOST
STABLE COUNTRIES IN THE REGION.
POLICE MOVED IN AROUND 7:00
A.M., AND SPARKED THE WORST
CLASHES IN TURKEY IN A DECADE.
POLICE USED TEAR GAS AND WATER
CANNONS.
THE PROTESTERS, STONES AND
MOLOTOV COCKTAILS.
PROTESTERS SET A POLICE VEHICLE
ON FIRE AND THE POLICE PULLED
BACK.
THE PROTESTERS HERE ARE DIGGING
IN, FORTIFYING THE SQUARE,
BUILDING BARRICADES, PREPARING
FOR A DRAWN OUT STRUGGLE WITH
THE GOVERNMENT.
THIS PROTEST HAS BEEN GOING ON
NOW FOR NEARLY TWO WEEKS.
IT STARTED AS AN EFFORT TO SAVE
THIS PARK, BUT IT'S WELL BEYOND
THAT NOW.
THE DEMONSTRATORS COMPLAIN OF
POLICE BRUTALITY.
AND THAT PRIME MINISTER ERDOGAN
IS IMPOSING AN ISLAMIC AGENDA IN
SECULAR TURKEY.
>> OUR PRIME MINISTER IS A
DICTATOR, LIKE HITLER, LIKE
MUSSOLINI.
>> THEY'RE TRYING TO LIMIT OUR
RIGHTS OF LIBERTY AND SHOWING
OUR IDEAS.
>> Reporter: BY EVENING, TAKSIM
FILLED AGAIN, MORE THAN 10,000
DEMONSTRATORS SHOUTING AGAINST
PRIME MINISTER ERDOGAN.
IT SEEMED LIKE THE VIOLENCE WAS
OVER.
BUT IT TURNED AGAIN.
SUDDENLY IN THE BIGGEST
CRACKDOWN OF THE DAY.
HUNDREDS OF RIOT POLICE AND
THEIR VEHICLES CHARGED IN.
THERE WAS A STAMPEDE AS
PROTESTERS RUSHED TO ESCAPE.
SOME FELL, SOME INJURED.
FIRES, MORE TEAR GAS.
>> IT'S BEING FIRED -- I DON'T
WANT TO SAY AT RANDOM, BUT IT'S
BEING FIRED WITH SUCH INTENSITY,
IT'S EVEN COMING UP TO THE UPPER
BALCONY OF WHAT ARE PRIVATE
HOMES AND PRIVATE BUSINESSES.
A DECISION HAD BEEN TAKEN TO
TAKE BACK THE SQUARE.
THIS IS NOW A CHALLENGE OVER THE
NATURE OF THIS COUNTRY.
ERDOGAN'S ISLAMIC DEMOCRACY.
OR THE SECULAR TRADITION THE
DEMONSTRATORS SAY THEY'RE
DETERMINED TO DEFEND.
MANY WATCHING EVENTS HERE
TONIGHT ARE WITH PRIME MINISTER
ERDOGAN, AND SAY THIS CRACKDOWN
IS SOMETHING THE PROTESTERS
BROUGHT UPON THEMSELVES, THEIR
JUST REWARDS.
LESTER?
>> RICHARD ENGEL IN ISTANBUL
TONIGHT.
RICHARD, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THIS COUNTRY THE
MANHUNT AND FALLOUT FROM A
FORMER NSA CONTRACTOR'S EXPOSURE
OF A GOVERNMENT SECRET
SURVEILLANCE PROGRAM.
AFTER BRIEFLY COMING FORWARD
THIS WEEKEND TO ANNOUNCE HE WAS
THE SOURCE OF THE DAMAGING
ARTICLES IN THE GUARDIAN
NEWSPAPER, EDWARD SNOWDEN HAS
APPARENTLY GONE UNDERGROUND,
LEAVING BEHIND HIM SOME
TROUBLING QUESTIONS.
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL HAS THE
LATEST FROM OUR WASHINGTON
NEWSROOM.
ANDREA?
>> GOOD EVENING, LESTER.
THE GLOBAL MANHUNT FOR EDWARD
SNOWDEN CONTINUES.
WHILE THE FBI NOW FOCUSES ON HOW
HE DID WHAT HE CLAIMS TO HAVE
DONE, AND WHETHER HE HAD HELP.
CALLED ON THE CARPET, THE HEAD
OF THE NATIONAL SECURITY AGENCY
SUMMONED TO THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEES TODAY TO EXPLAIN.
HOW BAD IS THE DAMAGE?
AND HOW DID A 29-YEAR-OLD
CONTRACTOR COPY SO MANY SECRET
DOCUMENTS?
AND THE GUARDIAN'S GLENN
GREENWALD SAYS MORE LEAKS ARE ON
THE WAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A LOT
MORE SIGNIFICANT REVELATIONS
THAT HAVE NOT YET BEEN HEARD
OVER THE NEXT SEVERAL WEEKS AND
MONTHS.
>> Reporter: SNOWDEN IS ON THE
LAM, HIS PICTURE PLASTERED ON
EVERY HONG KONG NEWSPAPER
REPORTS NBC'S IAN WILLIAMS.
>> STAFF HERE AT THE MIRA HOTEL
CONFIRMED THAT ONE EDWARD
SNOWDEN DID CHECK OUT MONDAY
LUNCHTIME.
HE'S NOT BEEN SEEN SINCE, BUT
IS BELIEVED TO BE STILL IN HONG
KONG.
>> Reporter: NBC NEWS HAS
CONFIRMED THAT ACROBATIC DANCER
LINDSAY MILLS IS THE GIRLFRIEND
SNOWDEN LEFT BEHIND IN HAWAII.
IN HER BLOG SINCE TAKEN DOWN,
MILLS REFERS TO HIM AS KUO E",
AND TELLS FRIENDS SHE WAS IN A
STATE OF SHOCK OVER HIS SUDDEN
DEPARTURE.
SNOWDEN FIRST REACHED OUT
ANONYMOUSLY TO AWARD WINNING
FILMMAKER, LAURA POITRAS AFTER
SEEING HER FILM KUO THE PROGRAM"
ON A NEW YORK WEBSITE, SHE TOLD
SALON.COM.
THE FILM PROFILED A
DISILLUSIONED RETIRED NSA
ANALYST WILLIAM BENNING.
>> THE DANGERS HERE, ARE THAT WE
FALL INTO SOMETHING LIKE A
TOTALITARIAN STATE LIKE EAST
GERMANY.
>> Reporter: GREENWALD SAID HE
AND POITRAS FLEW TO HONG KONG TO
MEET THE SOURCE.
HE TOLD THEM TO LOOK FOR A MAN
IN THE HOTEL LOBBY CARRYING A
RUBIK'S CUBE.
THE CONNECTION WAS MADE.
THE FBI IS SEARCHING FOR SNOWDEN
AND HIS COMPUTER TRAIL.
TO BUILD A CASE AGAINST HIM.
EXPERTS ARE NOT SURPRISED HE HAD
SO MUCH ACCESS.
>> HE WAS AN I.T. GUY, AND WHEN
YOU'RE ONE OF THOSE I.T. GUYS,
HAVE YOU A LOT MORE ACCESS TO A
LOT OF DIFFERENT PARTS OF A
NETWORK, BECAUSE YOU'RE MANAGING
IT.
>> Reporter: TODAY, SENATOR RON
WIDEN FILED LEGISLATION TO
DECLASSIFY THE FISA PROGRAM, AND
DEMANDED ANSWERS FROM CHIEF
INTELLIGENCE OFFICER JAMES
CLAPPER FOR DENYING RECORDS WERE
COLLECTED.
>> IT'S NOT POSSIBLE FOR THE
CONGRESS TO DO THE KIND OF
VIGOROUS OVERSIGHT THAT THE
PRESIDENT SPOKE ABOUT, IF YOU
CAN'T GET STRAIGHT ANSWERS.
>> SNOWDEN'S LEAKS PROMPTED THE
ACLU TO FILE SUIT TODAY AGAINST
THE GOVERNMENT, CLAIMING THAT
THE STORING OF ALL TELEPHONE
RECORDS VIOLATES THE RIGHT TO
PRIVACY.
AND GOOGLE HAS WRITTEN THE
ATTORNEY GENERAL, ASKING FOR
PERMISSION TO MAKE PUBLIC THE
NUMBER OF SECRET COURT ORDERS IT
HAS BEEN FORCED TO COMPLY WITH
FOR DATA, WHICH GOOGLE SAYS WILL
SHOW IT IS FAR LESS THAN THE
REPORTS HAVE CLAIMED.
LESTER?
>> ANDREA MITCHELL, THANK YOU.
>>> TONIGHT WE'RE KEEPING A
CLOSE EYE ON THE WEATHER ACROSS
THE MAP.
IT'S BEEN A DANGEROUS 24 HOURS.
AND FORECASTERS ARE PREDICTING A
WILD NIGHT AND DAY AHEAD FOR
MUCH OF THE COUNTRY.
IN FACT, MORE THAN 75 MILLION
AMERICANS ARE AT RISK OF SEVERE
STORMS.
METEOROLOGIST CHRIS WARREN IS
MONITORING IT ALL FROM WEATHER
CHANNEL HEADQUARTERS.
CHRIS, GOOD EVENING.
>> GOOD EVENING, LESTER.
THIS WEEK IS ALREADY OFF TO A
VERY ACTIVE START.
LAST NIGHT WE SAW TORNADOS AND
FLOODING.
IN FACT, PLENTY OF FLOODING
HAPPENING THROUGHOUT PARTS OF
THE NORTHEAST, INCLUDING
MARYLAND, TOUGH TO GET AROUND,
MAKING FOR VERY DANGEROUS
CONDITIONS.
ALSO IN PARTS OF NEVADA.
DEALING WITH SOME OF THE
FLOODING AS WELL.
THEN THERE WERE TORNADOS THAT
WENT ALONG WITH SOME OF THESE
STRONG STORMS.
SEVERAL REPORTS OF TORNADOS FROM
KENTUCKY TO DELAWARE AND NORTH
CAROLINA.
SOME DAMAGE AND INJURIES WERE
REPORTED WITH THAT.
AND THEN THERE'S WILDFIRES
BURNING RIGHT NOW THROUGHOUT
PARTS OF COLORADO.
AND THERE ARE SEVERAL OF THOSE
GOING ON RIGHT NOW RELATED TO
THE RECORD HEAT AND THE HIGH
WINDS.
TEMPERATURES IN THE TRIPLE
DIGITS ALREADY FOR DENVER TODAY
AND FOR PUEBLO.
FOR DENVER, THAT'S THE EARLIEST
THIS SEASON TO REACH 100.
AND YOU'RE LOOKING AT THE
POTENTIAL FOR MORE TRIPLE DIGITS
AND 90 DEGREE TEMPERATURES FOR
TOMORROW.
AND THEN THE SEVERE WEATHER
THREAT ON THE TOP OF THAT,
RIDING OVER THIS RIDGE OF HIGH
PRESSURE.
DAMAGING WINDS WILL BE A MAJOR
CONCERN THAT GOES INTO THE OHIO
VALLEY TOMORROW, AND LESTER,
THAT THREAT ON THURSDAY MOVES
INTO THE EAST.
>> CHRIS WARREN, THANKS.
>>> A GOVERNMENT REPORT OUT
TODAY MAKES IT CLEAR JUST HOW
MUCH THIS COUNTRY'S BANKS ARE
PROFITING FROM YOUR MISTAKES.
WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THOSE HEFTY
OVERDRAFT CHARGES TO COVER
PAYMENTS WHEN CHECKING ACCOUNTS
ARE OVERDRAWN.
TURNS OUT THE BANKS ARE MAKING
MOST OF THEIR FEES FROM THIGHS
THESE PENALTIES.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO HAS MORE FOR
US TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: IT'S ONE OF THE
MOST COMMON FINANCIAL MISTAKES
AMERICANS MAKE, OVERDRAWING FROM
THEIR BANK ACCOUNTS.
MAYBE FORGETTING THE MORTGAGE OR
CAR PAYMENT IS ABOUT TO BE
DEDUCTED.
THEN SLIDING THE DEBIT CARD FOR
GROCERIES OR A CUP OF COFFEE.
SOON THERE'S AN EXTRA $30 OR
MORE TO COUGH UP.
SINCE 2010, CUSTOMERS WHO HAVE
WANTED THEIR BANKS TO COVER
THEIR OVERDRAFTS HAVE HAD TO OPT
IN FOR THE COVERAGE.
NOW THE GOVERNMENT REPORTS THOSE
OVERDRAFT FEES MAKE UP A
STAGGERING 60% OF ALL BANK FEE
REVENUE.
$32 BILLION A YEAR.
RICHARD CORDRAY RUNS THE
GOVERNMENT'S CONSUMER FINANCIAL
PROTECTION BUREAU.
>> WE'RE CONCERNED THAT
CONCERNED THAT THE COMPLEXITY OF
OVERDRAFT PRACTICES MEAN THAT
CONSUMERS MAY NOT BE ABLE TO
ANTICIPATE AND AVOID UNNECESSARY
CHARGES.
>> Reporter: WHILE SOME BANKS
LIMIT OVERDRAFT FEES TO TWO A
DAY, OTHERS CHARGE AS MANY AS 12
PER DAY.
SOME BANKS CHARGE EVEN IF THE
OVERDRAFT IS A PENNY.
OTHERS DON'T CHARGE A FEE IF THE
AMOUNT IS LESS THAN $5.
IN 2011, THE AVERAGE CUSTOMER
WHO PAID OVERDRAFT FEES, PAID
$225 OVER THE COURSE OF THE
YEAR.
>> THE FINE PRINT IS VERY THICK
IN A LOT OF THESE CASES.
THEY THINK ON THE FACE OF IT
IT'S PROTECTION AGAINST ANY
OVERDRAFT.
A LOT OF HIDDEN FEES COME BEHIND
THIS PROTECTION.
>> Reporter: WITHOUT OVERDRAFT
PROTECTION, BANKS SIMPLY REFUSE
TO PAY THE BILL.
WHILE THE FEES CAN BE STEEP, THE
BANKING INDUSTRY INSISTS 20% OF
ITS CUSTOMERS WANT EVEN DEPEND
ON THE COVERAGE.
>> MANY CONSUMERS NEED TO HAVE
THIS PRODUCT TO MAKE ENDS MEET,
TO PAY THE BILLS, WHETHER IT'S
GROCERY STORES OR FILLING UP THE
CAR WITH GAS.
OR PAYING EVERYDAY EXPENSES AS
WELL.
>> TO AVOID PAYING THE FEES,
EXPERTS SUGGEST READING THE FINE
PRINT ON THE OPT-IN COVERAGE.
CLOSELY MONITORING YOUR BANK
ACCOUNT.
AND BACKING UP YOUR CHECKING
ACCOUNT WITH A SAVINGS ACCOUNT
JUST IN CASE YOU GO OVER.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> A LANDMARK IMMIGRATION
REFORM BILL THAT WOULD PUT
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE ON THE PATH
TO CITIZENSHIP CLEARED ITS FIRST
VOTE IN THE SENATE TODAY.
BUT MANY REPUBLICANS MADE IT
CLEAR THEY THINK THE BILL NEEDS
SIGNIFICANT CHANGES FOR IT TO
GAIN FINAL PASSAGE.
NBC'S KELLY O'DONNELL IS AT THE
U.S. CAPITOL FOR US TONIGHT.
HI, KELLY.
>> Reporter: HI, LESTER.
TODAY IS CRITICAL, BECAUSE NO
EFFORT TO FIX THE IMMIGRATION
SYSTEM HAS GOTTEN THIS FAR IN
YEARS.
MORE THAN 80 SENATORS VOTED YES
TO TACKLE AN OVERHAUL OF THE
LAW.
AND THAT WON'T BE EASY.
FLORIDA REPUBLICAN MARCO RUBIO
TOLD ME WINNING OVER CRITICS
WILL REQUIRE ENOUGH BORDER
SECURITY TO CONVINCE THEM THERE
WON'T BE FUTURE WAVES OF ILLEGAL
IMMIGRATION.
NOW, UNDER THE PLAN,
UNDOCUMENTED IMMIGRANTS COULD
EVENTUALLY BECOME CITIZENS IF
THEY MEET REQUIREMENTS THAT
INCLUDE PAYING TAXES, PASSING
BACKGROUND CHECKS, LEARNING
ENGLISH.
THE PRESIDENT TODAY SAID THIS
BILL IS NOT PERFECT.
HE CALLED IT THE BEST CHANCE AT
REFORM IN DECADES.
LESTER?
>> KELLY O'DONNELL IN
WASHINGTON, THANK YOU.
>>> IT APPEARS THE SO-CALLED
MORNING AFTER CONTRACEPTIVE PILL
WILL SOON BE AVAILABLE TO GIRLS
OF ANY AGE WITHOUT A
PRESCRIPTION.
THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION HAS NOW
REVERSED ITSELF AND SAYS IT WILL
COMPLY WITH A JUDGE'S ORDER TO
MAKE THE PILLS READILY
AVAILABLE.
ITS OPPOSITION TO THAT ORDER WAS
STRONGLY CRITICIZED BY ABORTION
RIGHTS GROUPS.
THE MAKER OF THE DRUG WILL
SUBMIT A NEW APPLICATION FOR FDA
APPROVAL.
THE AGENCY SAYS IT INTENDS TO DO
SO PROMPTLY.
>>> AND WE CONTINUE TO MONITOR
THE HEALTH OF FORMER SOUTH
AFRICAN PRESIDENT NELSON
MANDELA, WHO REMAINS IN THE
HOSPITAL FOR A FOURTH DAY.
HE'S BEING TREATED FOR A LUNG
INFECTION.
TWO OF MANDELA'S DAUGHTERS
VISITED HIM TODAY, ALONG WITH
HIS FORMER WIFE WINNIE.
SOUTH AFRICA'S PRESIDENT SAID
TODAY DOCTORS ADVISE HIM
MANDELA'S SITUATION IS VERY
SERIOUS, BUT THAT HIS CONDITION
IS STABLE, AND THAT THEY'RE
DOING ALL THEY CAN FOR HIM.
>>> STILL AHEAD AS WE CONTINUE
HERE TONIGHT, THE BIG RISE IN
BABY BOOMERS LOSING THEIR
HEARING AT YOUNGER AGES THAN
EVER.
WE'LL LOOK AT WHAT'S CAUSING IT
AND WHAT CAN SLOW IT DOWN.
>>> AND LATER, MOVIE MAGIC.
UNDER THE STARS AN ENDURING
AMERICAN TRADITION, STILL A
FAMILY FAVORITE AFTER 80 YEARS.
>>> OUR HEALTH NEWS TONIGHT IS
ABOUT A WARNING FROM DOCTORS
ABOUT THE NUMBER OF AMERICANS
WHO ARE STARTING TO LOSE THEIR
HEARING AT EARLIER AGES THAN
PREVIOUSLY SEEN.
AND DOCTORS SAY THERE'S A VERY
GOOD REASON FOR WHY.
WE GET OUR REPORT TONIGHT FROM
OUR CHIEF MEDICAL EDITOR DR.
NANCY SNYDERMAN.
[ SIREN ]
>> Reporter: FROM THE SOUNDS WE
CAN'T CONTROL, TO THE NOISE WE
ADJUST OURSELVES, THE WORLD IS
GETTING A LOT LOUDER AND IT'S
CATCHING UP WITH THE GENERATION
THAT SPENT ITS YOUTH BLASTING
CAR STEREOS AND ROCKING OUT AT
CONCERTS.
♪
>> THERE ARE OVER 30 MILLION
AMERICANS THAT HAVE A HEARING
LOSS.
AND OF THOSE 30 MILLION, 65% OF
THEM ARE UNDER THE AGE OF 65.
>> NOISE INDUCED HEARING LOSS
HAPPENS WHEN WE ARE EXPOSED TO
SOUNDS THAT ARE TOO LOUD FOR TOO
LONG.
THE SOUND TRAVELS THROUGH THE
DELICATE STRUCTURE OF THE EAR
AND DAMAGES THE SMALL CELLS
DESIGNED TO TRANSMIT THE SOUND
SIGNAL TO THE BRAIN.
ONCE DAMAGED, THESE CELLS CAN'T
GROW BACK.
>> HERE'S A HIGH SCHOOL PICTURE
OF ME.
>> Reporter: THAT'S WHAT
HAPPENED TO THIS 52-YEAR-OLD
BUSINESSMAN MARK TURKOVICH.
>> WHAT HE WOULD DO IS SAY HUH A
LOT, AND I'M NOT VERY PATIENT.
AND THAT USED TO DRIVE ME NUTS,
THAT HE WOULD CONTINUE TO SAY
HUH, HUH?
>> Reporter: HE BLAMES YEARS OF
TARGET SHOOTING, A LAWN MOWING
BUSINESS, AND TURNING UP THE
VOLUME ON HIS CAR STEREO.
BUT HE RESISTED GETTING HEARING
AIDS.
>> I DON'T WANT THAT BIG FLESH
COLOR PLUG IN MY EARS.
I'M TOO YOUNG TO HAVE THAT LOOK.
THEN HE WENT TO AN AUDIOLOGIST
KRISTEN WELLS IN PHOENIX, WHERE
HE WAS RECENTLY FITTED WITH THE
NEWEST TECHNOLOGY IN HEARING
AIDS.
>> HEARING AIDS REALLY LOOK LIKE
THIS NOWADAYS.
>> Reporter: THEY'RE DIGITAL,
DISCRETE, BARELY BIGGER THAN A
DIME, AND COMPATIBLE WITH
BLUETOOTH TECHNOLOGY.
INSURANCE COVERS THE COST FOR
MOST PEOPLE.
BUT MARK HAD TO PAY OUT OF
POCKET ABOUT $4,600 FOR THE
PAIR.
>> THIS IS THE BEST MONEY WE'VE
SPENT.
IT'S BEEN SO NICE TO HAVE HIS
QUALITY OF LIFE BACK.
>> I DON'T FEEL LIKE AN ELDERLY
MAN ANY MORE.
>> A SIMPLE THING TO DO IS TO GO
OUT AND GET A BOX OF REAL FOAM
EARPLUGS LIKE THIS.
YOU CAN GET THEM FOR ABOUT $2.
IT WILL LAST YOU FOR A MONTH OR
TWO.
BUT EVEN MORE IMPORTANT, AVOID
THAT NOISE.
AND FOR MOST OF US, THAT MEANS
THOSE HEADPHONES, THOSE EAR BUDS
THAT USED TO BE NOT VERY GOOD.
THE TECHNOLOGY IS SO GREAT YOU
CAN'T HEAR THE MUSIC FROM THE
PERSON SITTING NEXT TO YOU.
THAT MEANS IT'S GOING RIGHT INTO
YOU.
>> TURN THEM DOWN.
>> I THINK IF YOU LIKE WHERE
YOUR MUSIC, FINE, THEN TURN IT
DOWN EVEN MORE.
>> GOOD ADVICE.
NANCY, THANKS.
>> YOU BET.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
A BIG ADMISSION FROM A LOT OF
MOMS AND DADS ABOUT THEIR KIDS.
For our families...
our neighbors...
and our communities...
America's beverage companies
have created...
a wide range of new choices.
Developing smaller portion sizes
and more..
low and no-calorie
beverages...
adding clear calorie labels so
you know...
exactly what you're choosing...
and in schools, replacing
full-calorie soft drinks...
with lower-calorie options.
With more choices and fewer
calories...
America's Beverage Companies are
delivering.
>>> THIS IS THE 50th ANNIVERSARY
OF A PIVOTAL DAY IN THE HISTORY
OF CIVIL RIGHTS IN THIS COUNTRY.
STARTING IN ALABAMA, THE DEFIANT
GEORGE WALLACE, ALABAMA
GOVERNOR, BLOCKING TWO
AFRICAN-AMERICAN STUDENTS FROM
ATTENDING THE UNIVERSITY OF
ALABAMA.
THAT AFTERNOON PRESIDENT KENNEDY
FEDERALIZED THE ALABAMA NATIONAL
GUARD TO REMOVE THE GOVERNOR.
THE STUDENTS WALKED IN AND MADE
HISTORY.
THAT SAME NIGHT, KENNEDY TOOK A
STAND OF HIS OWN, IN A SPEECH TO
THE NATION, HE PROMISED TO
INTRODUCE COMPREHENSIVE CIVIL
RIGHTS LEGISLATION.
BUT WITHIN HOURS, AT HALF PAST
MIDNIGHT, ANOTHER SIGN OF HOW
STRONG THE OPPOSITION WAS.
THE CIVIL RIGHTS ACTIVIST MEDGAR
EVERS WAS SHOT IN THE BACK AND
KILLED IN THE DRIVEWAY OF HIS
HOME IN JACKSON, MISSISSIPPI.
HE WAS BURIED AT ARLINGTON
NATIONAL CEMETERY WITH FULL
MILITARY HONORS.
>>> TONIGHT WORK IS FINALLY
UNDER WAY TO REPAIR A DAMAGED
AMERICAN ICON.
THE WASHINGTON MONUMENT HAS BEEN
CLOSED SINCE A 5.2 MAGNITUDE
EARTHQUAKE SHOOK THE NATION'S
CAPITOL IN AUGUST 2011, SHIFTING
STONES IN THE MONUMENT AND
LEAVING DEEP CRACKS, ESPECIALLY
NEAR THE TOP.
WITH THE SCAFFOLDING AROUND IT
NOW COMPLETE, WORKERS ARE
BEGINNING THE TASK OF REPLACING
THE STONES WHILE HANGING MORE
THAN 500 FEET ABOVE THE GROUND.
>>> IN CHICAGO, IT WASN'T THE
TYPICAL WEATHER PROBLEM AT THE
BASEBALL GAMES IN THAT CITY LAST
NIGHT.
EVEN A LITTLE RAIN MAY HAVE BEEN
BETTER THAN THIS.
THE CUBS AND REDS HAD TO PLAY IN
AN UNUSUAL FOG THAT SETTLED IN
ON WRIGLEY FIELD.
THE CUBS LOST.
AND IT WAS THE SAME STORY ON THE
SOUTH SIDE AT THE WHITE SOX/BLUE
JAYS GAME.
THE SOX WERE ABLE TO GET THROUGH
IT A BIT BETTER.
THEY ENDED UP WINNING THAT
CONTEST.
>>> NOW PARENTS WILL ALMOST
NEVER ADMIT, TO ANYONE ELSE, AT
LEAST, THAT THEY HAVE A FAVORITE
CHILD.
IT'S JUST NOT DONE.
BUT WHEN A BRITISH WEBSITE FOR
PARENTS PUT THE QUESTION TO MORE
THAN 2000 MOMS AND DADS IN A
SURVEY, IT GOT SOME SHOCKING
RESULTS.
MORE THAN A THIRD OF THE MOTHERS
ADMITTED TO HAVING A FAVORITE
CHILD.
NOT QUITE SO MANY OF THE DADS
WERE WILLING TO GO THAT FAR.
JUST OVER A QUARTER OF THE
FATHERS SAID THEY HAD A
FAVORITE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, WHY WE'RE
CELEBRATING AN OLD FASHIONED
GOOD TIME FOR THE WHOLE FAMILY,
AND AN INEXPENSIVE NIGHT OUT.
A
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, IT WAS THIS
MONTH BACK IN 1933, WHEN A
CONVOY OF EAGER MOTORISTS DROVE
INTO A LOT.
THEY PUT THEIR CARS IN PARK AND
SAT BACK AND ENJOYED THE SHOW.
IT WAS THE OPENING OF THE FIRST
DRIVE-IN CINEMA.
AND OVER THE YEARS THERE WOULD
BE THOUSANDS OF THEM.
THESE DAYS NOT MANY REMAIN, BUT
OF THOSE THAT DO, MEMORIES ARE
STILL BEING MADE.
HERE'S NBC'S KEVIN TIBBLES.
>> Reporter: AS DUSK APPROACHES,
THE CARS LINE UP JUST LIKE
THEY'VE DONE FOR THE LAST HALF
CENTURY.
>> GOOD TO HAVE YOU BACK.
>> Reporter: THE CASCADE WEST OF
CHICAGO, IS ONE OF ONLY 400
DRIVE-IN MOVIE THEATERS LEFT IN
THE COUNTRY.
BUT ON A WARM CLEAR NIGHT,
FAMILIES COME EXTRA EARLY TO
GRAB A GOOD SPOT.
>> WE ENJOY THE OUTDOOR
ATMOSPHERE OF BEING AT A
DRIVE-IN.
>> IT'S A GREAT FAMILY THING.
IT'S GREAT FOR FAMILIES.
>> Reporter: WHERE ELSE CAN YOU
SEE TWO FEATURES FOR UNDER $10.
AND WHEN KIDS UNDER 5 GET IN
FREE, WHO NEEDS A SITTER?
BRING A PICNIC OR GRAB A CORN
DOG AND PULL UP TO ONE OF THOSE
OLD FASHIONED SPEAKERS.
FOR CO-OWNER JEFF KOHLBERG,
THERE'S NOTHING LIKE IT.
>> I'VE BEEN DOING THIS SINCE I
WAS SEVEN OR EIGHT YEARS OLD
WITH MY FATHER.
I KNOW, IT'S IN MY BLOOD.
>> THANK YOU, ENJOY THE SHOW.
>> Reporter: AND, YES, THAT IS
JEFF'S SISTER POPPY OVER IN THE
TICKET BOOTH.
>> WE HAVE CUSTOMERS THAT COME
IN HERE NOW AND SAY, OH, WE WERE
DATING, THESE ARE MY CHILDREN.
AND THEY REMEMBER ME.
THEY DO.
>> Reporter: THE FIRST DRIVE IN
OPENED IN CAMDEN, NEW JERSEY 80
YEARS AGO.
AFTER THE SECOND WORLD WAR WHEN
THE CAR WAS KING.
THERE WERE 4,000 OF THEM.
THE MOVIES MAY HAVE GONE FROM
BLACK AND WHITE TO DIGITAL, BUT
SITTING OUT UNDER THE STARS IN
YOUR FAVORITE CAR WITH A BAG OF
POPCORN IS NEVER GOING TO
CHANGE.
OF COURSE, THE ADVENT OF THE
COLOR TELEVISION CAME AS A BODY
BLOW.
AND SO-CALLED PROGRESS NOW MEANS
FOLKS WATCH MOVIES ON TINY
SCREENS.
SOMETHING POPPY WILL NEVER
FIGURE OUT.
>> WHEN YOU CAN COME OUT HERE
AND SIT IN YOUR CAR AND LOOK AT
THAT GIANT SCREEN --
>> WHY LOOK AT THAT?
>> I KNOW.
>> Reporter: STILL, THE PERFECT
COMBINATION OF GOOD WEATHER AND
A GOOD MOVIE WILL ALWAYS KEEP
THEM COMING.
JUST REMEMBER, NO HIDING UNDER
BLANKETS OR IN THE TRUNK TO
SNEAK IN.
DO YOU BUST THEM?
>> YES.
YES, WE DO.
>> Reporter: EVEN IF IT IS PART
OF THE EXPERIENCE.
KEVIN TIBBLES, NBC NEWS, WEST
CHICAGO ILLINOIS.
>>> THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR
THIS TUESDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> GOOD EVENING, EVERYONE.
>> A 16 YEAR OLD GIRL WAS
KIDNAPPED IN THE EAST BAY.
BUT THIS STORY HAS A HAPPY
ENDING, BECAUSE POLICE SAY SHE
DID EVERYTHING RIGHT.
A MAN WAS HIDING IN THE BACK
SEAT OF HER CAR WHILE SHE
STOPPED AT A LUCKY'S STORE IN
NORTH FREMONT.
HE FORCED HER TO DRIVE TO A
DESERTED PLACE.
THE GIRL FINALLY MANAGED TO GET
AWAY.
>> Reporter: THIS IS WHERE THE
GIRL'S TERRIFYING ORDEAL ENDED
UP, RIGHT HERE IN THIS FREMONTé
NEIGHBORHOOD.
POLICE SAY SHE MANAGED TO ESCAPE
HER ALLEGED KIDNAPPER AND RUN
DOWN THIS STREET HERE.
WE'RE GOING TO SHOW YOU SOME
HOME VIDEO THAT SHOWS THE GIRL
AS SHE RAN FOR HER LIFE.
A NEIGHBOR'S SURVEILLANCE CAMERA
CAPTURED THIS VIDEO OF THE 16
YEAR OLD GIRL SEEN AT THE TOP OF
YOUR SCREEN AS SHE RAN DOWN THE
STREET IN HER FLIP-FLOPS,
SCREAMING, HE HAS A KNIFE.
SHE RAN TO A HOME WHERE SHE SAW
A WOMAN WHO HAD JUST GOTTEN HOME
FROM STARBUCKS.
THAT WOMAN BROUGHT HER TO
SAFETY.
THE TEEN AGER HAD STOPPED AT THE
LUCKIES TO PICK UP A FEW THINGS.
THE MAN GOT INTO HER CAR AND HID
IN THE BACK SEAT.
WHEN SHE RETURNED TO THE CAR, HE
DEMANDED HER TO DRIVE TO A
REMOTE LOCATION.
HE ORDERED HER