OLD LOCATION.
>> HOW FUN.
>> I KNOW.
WE'VE GOT TO GO CHECK IT OUT.
>> NIGHTLY NEWS IS NEXT.
>> SEE YOU AGAIN AT 6:00.
>> GOOD NIGHT, FOLKS.
>>> ON OUR BROADCAST TONIGHT,
CLOSING IN ON A SUSPECT IN
BOSTON.
A DAY OF RAPID DEVELOPMENTS,
SOME FALSE REPORTS TONIGHT BASED
ON IMAGERY FROM THE SCENE.
INVESTIGATORS APPEAR TO KNOW WHO
THEY ARE LOOKING FOR.
>>> DEFEATED.
THE POST-NEWTOWN GUN CONTROL
LEGISLATION GOES DOWN IN THE
SENATE.
THERE ARE CRIES OF "SHAME" FROM
VICTIMS OF GUN VIOLENCE WAHING
FROM THE SENATE GALLERY.
AND THE PRESIDENT REACTS WITH
ANGER.
>>> HIGH ALERT IN WASHINGTON
AFTER AN UNNERVING DAY THERE.
LETTERS SENT TO THE PRESIDENT
AND AT LEAST ONE U.S. SENATOR
HAVE TESTED POSITIVE FOR THE
POISONOUS SUBSTANCE RICIN.
>>> AND MAKING A DIFFERENCE AS
SOME VERY WELCOME RESCUERS COME
TO THE AID OF THE PEOPLE OF
BOSTON.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
NBC-UNIVERSAL TELEVISION
>>> GOOD EVENING.
NOW THE INVESTIGATION IN BOSTON
IS MOVING.
AFTER A DAY OF FITS AND STARTS
AND SEVERAL FALSE REPORTS, IT
APPEARS THAT FROM A MOUNTAIN OF
EVIDENCE HAS EMERGED AN IMAGE, A
SERIES OF IMAGES THAT LIKELY
SHOW THE BOMBER THAT POLICE ARE
LOOKING FOR.
PARTS OF BOSTON ARE STILL SHUT
DOWN.
IT WAS ANOTHER JITTERY DAY THERE
AFTER A BOMB THREAT AT THE
FEDERAL COURTHOUSE THIS
AFTERNOON.
THIS IS THE BOMBING SCENE
TONIGHT.
WE HAVE LEARNED MORE ABOUT THE
DEVICES THEMSELVES AS THIS CASE,
AS WE SAID, NOW PICKS UP SPEED.
WHILE THE FBI IS URGING CAUTION
AND ASKING FOR PATIENCE
ESPECIALLY FROM THE NEWS MEDIA,
IT APPEARS THEY HAVE PICTURES OF
THEIR SUSPECT.
OUR JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS HAS BEEN FOLLOWING THE
INVESTIGATION ALL DAY.
HE'S IN OUR D.C. NEWSROOM
TONIGHT.
PETE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: BRIAN, GOOD
EVENING.
THE FBI IS PURSUING VERY
PROMISING LEADS.
ONE IN PARTICULAR TONIGHT THANKS
TO THE ABUNDANCE OF PICTURES AND
VIDEOS ROUNDED UP IN THE TWO
DAYS SINCE THE BOMBING.
WE ARE GETTING A CLOSE-UP LOOK
AT HOW THE BOMBS WERE MADE.
>> GUYS, GUYS, GUYS.
NO WAY.
>> Reporter: THE FBI SAYS IT IS
GETTING EXACTLY WHAT IT ASKED
FOR.
PICTURES FROM SEVERAL SOURCES
SHOWING SOMEONE CARRYING A HEAVY
BACKPACK OR DUFFEL BAG AND
PLACING IT AT THE SPOT WHERE ONE
BOMB WENT OFF.
ONE OF THE MOST PROMISING
IMAGES, THEY SAY, COMES FROM A
DEPARTMENT STORE SURVEILLANCE
CAMERA HIGH UP ON A BUILDING,
ABLE TO LOOK DOWN AT THE CROWD.
ON A DAY WHEN INCORRECT NEWS
REPORTS OF AN ARREST DISTRACTED
OFFICIALS, INVESTIGATORS WERE
WORKING AGGRESSIVELY TO
DISCOVER, FIND, AND INTERVIEW
THAT PERSON.
THAT'S AT THE SCENE OF THE
SECOND BOMBING FOLLOWING THE
FIRST BY ABOUT 15 SECONDS.
IT'S THAT SECOND SPOT SHOWN ON
THIS PICTURE SENT TO NBC STATION
WHDH SHOWING A GARBAGE BAG NEXT
TO A TRASH CAN.
WHILE INVESTIGATORS CANNOT BE
SURE THAT BAG CONTAINED THE BOMB
FEDERAL OFFICIALS TELL NBC NEWS
THAT IS THE SPOT WHERE THE
SECOND BOMB WENT OFF.
FORMER ATF BOMB INVESTIGATOR JIM
CAVANAUGH SAID IT IS OBVIOUS TO
HIM LOOKING AT THE PICTURES.
>> LARGE INJURIES WERE ON THE
SIDE OF IT.
DEBRIS FIELD TO THE LEFT.
SOME PROTECTED AREAS OVER ON THE
RIGHT SIDE THAT INDICATE THE
BLAST WAS TO ONE SIDE OF THE
TRASH RECEPTACLE.
THIS WAS THE SCENE OF THE BLAST.
>> Reporter: WE ARE ALSO SEEING
CLOSE-UP PHOTOS OF THE ACTUAL
PIECES OF THE BOMB.
SHOWING THE PRESSURE COOKER
DEFORMED BY THE BLAST, ONE OF
ITS LIDS BLOWN TO THE TOP OF A
NEARBY BUILDING.
THEY ARE A FAVORITE OF BOMB
MAKERS BECAUSE EXPLOSIVE
PRESSURE BUILDS UP BEFORE IT IS
RELEASED.
INVESTIGATORS CAN NOW BEGIN TO
TRACE DOWN WHERE COMPONENTS WERE
BOUGHT SINCE THEY KNOW THE MAKER
OF THE PRESSURE COOKER, THE
TYPE OF RECHARGEABLE FLASHLIGHT
BATTERIES USED -- MADE IN CHINA,
BUT WIDELY AVAILABLE --
AND EVEN THE TYPE OF WIRE --
ALSO MADE IN CHINA -- USED TO
HOOK THE MAIN COMPONENTS
TOGETHER.
BOMB TECHNICIANS ARE EXAMINING
TWO ELECTRONIC COMPONENTS
INCLUDED IN THE BOMBS TO SEE
WHETHER THEY WERE PARTS OF
TIMERS OR RECEIVERS FOR A REMOTE
DETONATION SIGNAL.
ALL POTENTIALLY PROMISING LEADS,
SAYS A BOMB EXPERT.
>> IT DEPENDS ON HOW UNIQUE THE
BOMB COMPONENTS ARE, HOW
IDENTIFIABLE THE CHARACTERISTICS
ARE, WHAT OTHER FORENSICS
INVOLVED IN THAT, WHETHER IT BE
FINGERPRINTS, DNA, ET CETERA.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS ARE
OPTIMISTIC THAT THEY ARE CLOSE
TO THE ANSWER OF WHO DID THIS
AND WHY IN AN INVESTIGATION
THAT'S MOVING VERY RAPIDLY ON
SEVERAL FRONTS.
>> ABOUT THAT RAPID SPEED AND
OPTIMISM, PETE WILLIAMS, THANKS.
WE WANT TO BRING IN THE FORMER
DIRECTOR OF THE NATIONAL
COUNTERTERRORISM CENTER.
MICHAEL LEITER IS OUR NBC NEWS
COUNTERTERRORISM ANALYST.
YOU RECEIVED FROM YOUR SOURCES A
CAUTION TODAY THAT THIS PERHAPS
WAS RUNNING ON AHEAD OF ITSELF.
AND THIS CAN HAVE A BAD EFFECT
ON AN INVESTIGATION.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WITH ALL THE MEDIA REPORTING
ABOUT THE POSSIBLE ARRESTS, THEY
ARE VERY WORRIED ABOUT THE
PERSON OR PEOPLE BEING SPOOKED
AND THEY ARE NERVOUS ABOUT
EXPECTATIONS AT THIS POINT.
FOR A WHILE PEOPLE WERE SAYING
IT'S NOT GOING FAST ENOUGH.
NOW PEOPLE EXPECT AN ARREST IN
THE NEAR HOURS AND THE FACT IS
KNOWING THE PERSON IT CAN STILL
TAKE SOME TIME.
>> NOW ABOUT THE EVIDENCE.
WE HAVE A BIG HAYSTACK HERE.
SO FAR WE HAVE FOUND SOME OF THE
NEEDLES DOWN TO THE ZIPPER PULL
ON WHAT COULD HAVE BEEN THE BAG
AND THE WIRES AND THE BATTERY.
WE ALSO HAVE IMAGERY -- TONS OF
IT -- AND THAT HAS TO BE A BIG
EARLY HELP.
>> THAT IS INVALUABLE.
IT'S SOMETHING EVEN THREE OR
FOUR YEARS AGO WE WOULDN'T HAVE
HAD.
ALL OF THAT IMAGERY FROM THE
STORES, THE POLICE AND PEOPLE,
YOU COMBINE THAT WITH THE
FORENSIC EVIDENCE AND THE SECRET
INTELLIGENCE WE ARE NOT HEARING
ABOUT FROM HUMAN INTELLIGENCE
SOURCES, CELL PHONE RECORDS,
THINGS LIKE THAT.
THAT PAINTS THE MOSAIC FROM
WHICH THEY FIND THEIR SUSPECT.
>> YESTERDAY AT THE AIRPORT,
LOGAN AIRPORT IN BOSTON, THEY
WERE TELLING PEOPLE, BEFORE YOU
LEAVE OUR CITY, DO YOU HAVE
ANYTHING, DO YOU REMEMBER
ANYTHING?
ALL OF THAT HELPS.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
EVERY BIT OF IT.
IT DOES ONE MORE THING.
IT SHOWS THAT THE PUBLIC HAS TO
BE INVOLVED IN THIS.
IT ISN'T JUST ABOUT SAYING FBI
WILL GO GET THEM.
PEOPLE BEFORE AN ATTACK, AFTER
AN ATTACK, THE PUBLIC HAS A HUGE
ROLE TO PLAY IN HELPING THEM
FIND SOMEONE AND BEING RESILIENT
AFTER.
>> THE DEFINITION OF SOCIAL
MEDIA.
MICHAEL LEITER, THANK YOU FOR
YOUR REPORTING ALL DAY.
>>> AS WE SAID IT'S BEEN A DAY
OF RAPIDLY MOVING DEVELOPMENTS.
AS INVESTIGATORS CONTINUE TO DO
THEIR WORK, DOCTORS CONTINUE TO
DO THEIRS IN BOSTON.
AFTER SAVING SO MANY LIVES,
AFTER DEALING, REMEMBER, WITH
WHAT LOOKED LIKE COMBAT
INJURIES, SOME VICTIMS ARE NOW
LEAVING THE HOSPITAL TELLING
THEIR STORIES FOR THE FIRST
TIME.
NBC'S ANNE THOMPSON WITH US
TONIGHT FROM BOSTON WITH THAT
ANGLE OF THE STORY.
ANNE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
BRIAN.
TONIGHT THE CITY OF BOSTON IS
PREPARING FOR THE ARRIVAL OF
PRESIDENT OBAMA WHO WILL ATTEND
AN INTERFAITH SERVICE TOMORROW
AND PREPARING FOR WHAT MANY KNOW
WILL BE A LONG, DIFFICULT
JOURNEY TO RECOVERY.
IN BOSTON, VOWS OF RESOLVE
TODAY AMID EMOTIONS THAT ARE
STILL RAW.
A RELIEVED 20-YEAR-OLD SARAH
GERARD LEFT THE HOSPITAL WITH
HER LEG IN A CAST.
>> I HAVE A FRACTURED SHIN BONE
AND A FRACTURED HEEL BONE FROM
THE SHRAPNEL THAT HIT IT.
>> Reporter: FOR LIZ NORDEN,
THERE IS NO RELIEF.
HER TWO SONS, PAUL AND JP, EACH
LOST A LEG AND WERE BURNED.
>> I'M WAITING TO WAKE UP FROM
THIS NIGHTMARE.
I'M HOPING IT'S NOT REAL.
>> Reporter: EVEN SECRETARY OF
STATE JOHN KERRY, MASSACHUSETTS
SENATOR FOR 28 YEARS, STRUGGLED
AS HE TESTIFIED BEFORE CONGRESS.
>> YOU KNOW, BOSTON IS NOT GOING
TO BE INTIMIDATED BY THIS.
BUT WE ARE GOING TO FIND OUT WHO
DID THIS.
>> Reporter: BOSTON IS A CITY
STILL ON EDGE.
A BOMB SCARE FORCED THE
EVACUATION OF THE FEDERAL
COURTHOUSE.
AND IT IS A CITY IN MOURNING.
BOSTON UNIVERSITY STUDENT LINGZI
LU IDENTIFIED AS THE THIRD
VICTIM OF THE BOMBING.
THE 23-YEAR-OLD GRADUATE STUDENT
FROM CHINA WAS WATCHING THE
MARATHON WITH TWO OTHER FRIENDS.
DAVE KING FINISHED THE MARATHON
MONDAY.
AN HOUR LATER HE WAS IN THE
OPERATING ROOM AT MASSACHUSETTS
GENERAL HOSPITAL.
THE TRAUMA SURGEON WHO SERVED IN
IRAQ AND AFGHANISTAN, SUDDENLY
FACED DECISIONS HE THOUGHT HE'D
LEFT ON THE BATTLEFIELD --
WHETHER TO AMPUTATE.
>> NATURALLY, YOU WILL ALWAYS
CHOOSE LIFE OVER LIMB.
>> Reporter: AFTER MULTIPLE
AMPUTATIONS AND THREE GRUELLING
DAYS OF SURGERY, KING IS
ASTONISHED BY HIS PATIENTS'
RESILIENCE.
>> THEY UNDERSTAND THAT LOSING A
A LIMB WAS REQUIRED TO SAVE A
THEIR LIFE.
AND THEY ARE JUST AT PEACE WITH
THAT.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW.
>> Reporter: THE STRENGTH OF THE
VICTIMS INSPIRING THE STRENGTH
OF THE CITY.
>> WE ONLY CARE ABOUT THREE
THINGS IN THIS TOWN -- POLITICS,
SPORTS AND REVENGE.
OUR REVENGE IS TO GO BACK TO
NORMAL.
WHAT HAPPENED TO US THE OTHER
DAY WILL NOT COW US.
IT WILL NOT CHANGE US.
>> Reporter: WHILE MOST OF
BOSTON IS BACK AT ITS NORMAL
ROUTINE, DOCTORS ACKNOWLEDGE
THAT THE PHYSICAL AND EMOTIONAL
RECOVERY WILL TAKE NOT ONLY
MONTHS BUT MOST LIKELY YEARS,
ESPECIALLY FOR THOSE WHO WILL
SUFFER WITH POST TRAUMATIC
STRESS DISORDER.
BRIAN?
>> ANNE THOMPSON AT THE COMMAND
POST IN BOSTON TONIGHT.
ANNE, THANKS.
>>> WHILE ALL OF THIS WAS GOING
ON TODAY A SHORT TIME AGO AT THE
WHITE HOUSE, SURROUNDED BY
VICTIMS OF GUN VIOLENCE
INCLUDING NEWTOWN FAMILIES,
PRESIDENT OBAMA SHOWED A RARE
FLASH OF ANGER BECAUSE THE GUN
CONTROL LEGISLATION THAT WAS
SUPPOSED TO TIGHTEN BACKGROUND
CHECKS WAS DEFEATED TODAY IN THE
U.S. SENATE.
THE PRESIDENT CALLED IT A PRETTY
SHAMEFUL DAY FOR WASHINGTON.
NBC'S KELLY O'DONNELL WITH US
FROM CAPITOL HILL TONIGHT.
KELLY, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
BRIAN.
THE MOOD INSIDE THE SENATE
CHAMBER, WHICH WAS PACKED, WAS
INTENSE WITH EMOTION AS GUN
VICTIMS, SURVIVORS AND MANY OF
THE NEWTOWN FAMILIES WATCHED
SENATORS THEY HAD PERSONALLY MET
WITH VOTE DOWN EXPANDED
BACKGROUND CHECKS.
TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT GAVE THE
ROSE GARDEN MICROPHONE OVER TO A
NEWTOWN DAD, MARK BARDEN.
>> WE'LL RETURN HOME NOW,
DISAPPOINTED BUT NOT DEFEATED.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT,
CLEARLY ANGRY --
>> THE GUN LOBBY AND ITS ALLIES
WILLFULLY LIED ABOUT THE BILL.
>> Reporter: -- LASHED OUT AT
CONGRESS.
>> THIS WAS A PRETTY SHAMEFUL
DAY FOR WASHINGTON.
THIS EFFORT IS NOT OVER.
I WANT TO MAKE IT CLEAR TO THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE.
WE CAN STILL BRING ABOUT
MEANINGFUL CHANGES THAT REDUCE
GUN VIOLENCE SO LONG AS THE
AMERICAN PEOPLE DON'T GIVE UP ON
IT.
>> Reporter: FROM THE STEPS OF
AIR FORCE ONE LAST WEEK TO THE
U.S. CAPITOL AGAIN TODAY,
NEWTOWN FAMILIES WHO KNOW THE
PAIN OF GUN VIOLENCE HAD BEEN
UNWILLING TO GIVE UP.
>> OUR HEARTS ARE BROKEN.
OUR SPIRIT IS NOT.
>> Reporter: GABBY GIFFORDS, WHO
HAS PERSONALLY LOBBIED SENATORS,
CALLED THE FAILURE TO PASS
EXPANDED BACKGROUND CHECKS
UNTHINKABLE.
TODAY BEING HEARD OR CONSOLED
WAS NOT ENOUGH FOR PATRICIA.
TUCSON SHOOTING SURVIVOR WHO
SHOUTED AT SENATORS, "SHAME ON
YOU."
>> SHAME ON YOU!
>> ORDER IN THE SENATE.
>> THEY HAVE NO COMPASSION.
>> Reporter: SOME NEWTOWN
FAMILIES HELD MORE PRIVATE
MEETINGS.
NO MEDIA COVERAGE.
REPUBLICAN SENATOR MARK KIRK'S
STAFF TOOK THESE PICTURES.
THE LATEST NBC MARIS POLL SHOWS
NEARLY 9 OF 10 SURVEYED WANT
TIGHTER RESTRICTIONS ON GUN
SALES.
FOUR REPUBLICANS VOTED YES TO
EXTEND BACKGROUND CHECKS TO
COMMERCIAL SALES AT GUN SHOWS
AND THE INTERNET.
>> EXPANDED BACKGROUND CHECKS
WOULD NOT HAVE PREVENTED
NEWTOWN.
>> Reporter: CONSERVATIVE
OPPOSITION WAS STRONG.
>> THIS IS THE FIRST STEP IN THE
EROSION OF OUR RIGHTS UNDER THE
SECOND AMENDMENT.
>> WE ARE TRYING TO TAKE IT TO
THE VIOLENT CRIMINAL.
RATHER THAN TAKING IT TO THE
INNOCENT SECOND AMENDMENT LAW
ABIDING CITIZEN.
>> Reporter: USUALLY A VICE
PRESIDENT ARRIVES TO PRESIDE
OVER A WINNING VOTE.
BIDEN WAS HERE TO WITNESS ITS
DEFEAT.
>> THE AMENDMENT IS NOT AGREED
TO.
>> Reporter: FOUR DEMOCRATS FROM
RED STATES WITH HIGH GUN
OWNERSHIP ALSO VOTED NO.
IN TALKING TO THOSE DEMOCRATS
WHO VOTED NO, THEY SAY THEY HAD
INTENSE PRESSURE FROM THEIR HOME
STATE CONSTITUENTS WHO DID NOT
WANT TO SEE EXPANDED BACKGROUND
CHECKS.
ALSO TONIGHT, SENATORS VOTED
DOWN AN ASSAULT WEAPONS BAN AND
LIMITS ON HIGH CAPACITY
AMMUNITION.
IT IS POSSIBLE THAT DEMOCRATS
WILL SIMPLY SHELVE THIS
LEGISLATION IN ORDER TO TRY
AGAIN SOME DAY DOWN THE LINE.
BRIAN?
>> AGAIN, THE PRESIDENT CALLING
THIS ROUND ONE.
KELLY O'DONNELL ON THE HILL
TONIGHT AFTER AN EVENTFUL DAY
THERE.
KELLY, THANKS.
>>> STILL AHEAD FOR US THIS
EVENING, THE UNSETTLING
DEVELOPMENT ELSEWHERE IN
WASHINGTON.
WHO SENT LETTERS LACED WITH
RICIN TO THE PRESIDENT AND AT
LEAST ONE U.S. SENATOR?
EVACUATIONS THERE TODAY AS
MEMORIES OF THE ANTHRAX ATTACKS
CAME RUSHING BACK.
>>> LATER, MAKING A DIFFERENCE.
THEY ARE HERE WITH THE HELP OF
SOME VERY COMFORTING VISITORS AT
A HOSPITAL IN BOSTON.
>>> WE'RE BACK.
AS WE SAID, CONTRIBUTING TO AN
OVERALL FEELING OF UNEASE TODAY
WAS THIS WORD OUT OF WASHINGTON
STARTING LAST NIGHT THAT THE
POISONOUS SUBSTANCE RICIN, WHICH
MOST OF US FIRST GOT A LESSON IN
IN THE DAYS AFTER 9/11.
RICIN HAS BEEN FOUND ON LETTERS
MAILED TO THE PRESIDENT AND AT
LEAST ONE U.S. SENATOR.
THE LETTERS WERE STOPPED AT A
SORTING FACILITY AND NEVER WERE
ALLOWED THROUGH.
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL IN OUR
WASHINGTON NEWSROOM HAS BEEN
COVERING THIS TODAY.
ANDREA, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
BRIAN.
NERVES WERE ALREADY ON EDGE IN
THE CAPITOL BECAUSE OF BOSTON
WHEN THOSE LETTERS POSSIBLY
CONTAINING LETHAL POISONS WERE
INTERCEPTED.
ONE ADDRESSED TO A SENATOR.
ANOTHER TO THE PRESIDENT OF THE
UNITED STATES.
FOR AN HOUR AND A HALF THIS
MORNING ALERTS WERE SOUNDED ON
CAPITOL HILL.
>> CLOSE THE OTHER SIDE OF THE
STREET.
WE ARE CLOSING OFF THE SIDEWALK.
>> Reporter: SOME SENATE OFFICES
WERE CLEARED.
STAFF IN OTHERS WERE TOLD TO
STAY INSIDE.
AFTER TWO LETTERS -- ONE TO
MISSISSIPPI REPUBLICAN SENATOR
ROGER WICKER, THE SECOND TO
PRESIDENT OBAMA -- TESTED
PRELIMINARILY FOR RICIN.
BOTH WERE QUARANTINED AT A
POST OFFICE SCREENING FACILITY
MILES AWAY IN MARYLAND.
BUILT AFTER THE ANTHRAX ATTACKS
THAT KILLED FIVE AND INJURED 17
ACROSS THE NATION IN 2001.
>> THE PRESIDENT -- I'M SURE YOU
WILL ASK THIS.
THE PRESIDENT HAS, OF COURSE,
BEEN BRIEFED ON THESE LETTERS.
HE WAS BRIEFED LAST NIGHT AND
AGAIN THIS MORNING.
>> Reporter: THE FBI SAID BOTH
WERE POSTMARKED MEMPHIS,
TENNESSEE, ON APRIL 8.
THEY USED THE SAME LANGUAGE.
QUOTE, TO SEE A WRONG AND NOT
EXPOSE IT IS TO BECOME A SILENT
PARTNER TO ITS CONTINUANCE.
A PHRASE OFTEN USED BY RADICAL
GROUPS.
BOTH LETTERS ARE SIGNED, I AM KC
AND I APPROVE THIS MESSAGE.
A THIRD LETTER WENT TO
DEMOCRATIC SENATOR CARL LEVIN'S
OFFICE IN SAGINAW, MICHIGAN.
A STAFFER WHO OPENED THE LETTER
THERE HAS BEEN HOSPITALIZED
PROTECTIVELY UNTIL TESTS ARE
DONE.
HAZ-MAT TEAMS SEARCHED JEFF
FLAKE'S OFFICE IN PHOENIX BUT
FOUND NOTHING SUSPICIOUS.
>> WE HAVE HAD SITUATIONS WHERE
THERE HAVE BEEN RICIN SCARES.
UNTIL THIS DATE THERE'S NEVER
BEEN ANY PROVED TO HAVE GONE
THROUGH THE SYSTEM.
>> Reporter: RICIN, THE POISON
MADE FROM CASTOR BEANS WAS USED
BY THE SOVIETS IN 1978 TO
ASSASSINATE A BULGARIAN
DISSIDENT IN LONDON BY PUTTING
IT ON THE TIP OF AN UMBRELLA AND
STABBING HIM IN THE LEG.
ONLY A DROP CAN KILL IN 36 TO 48
HOURS.
>> IF YOU PURIFY IT, IT CAN
BECOME MUCH MORE LETHAL.
IN FACT, DEADLY IN VERY MINUTE
QUANTITIES.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT FEDERAL
OFFICIALS SAY A SUSPECT NAMED
PAUL KEVIN CURTIS HAS BEEN
ARRESTED IN MISSISSIPPI AND WILL
BE CHARGED WITH SENDING THE
LETTERERS.
THE FBI SEES NO RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE BOMBINGS IN BOSTON.
STILL THERE IS AN EERIE
COINCIDENCE WITH THE ANTHRAX
ATTACKS AFTER 9/11.
ALSO UNRELATED BUT FRIGHTENING
NONETHELESS.
BRIAN?
>> ANDREA MITCHELL IN
WASHINGTON.
ANDREA, THANKS.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
A BIG APOLOGY FROM AN AIRLINE
CEO AFTER A BIG NIGHTMARE DAY
FOR TRAVELLERS.
>>> THE UNITED KINGDOM SAID
GOOD-BYE TO MARGARET THATCHER
TODAY.
THE FUNERAL AT ST. PAUL'S
CATHEDRAL ATTENDED BY THE QUEEN,
DIGNITARIES FROM 170 COUNTRIES
AROUND THE WORLD, AND ALL FOUR
OF MAGGIE THATCHER'S SUCCESSORS
INCLUDING THE CURRENT PRIME
MINISTER, DAVID CAMERON.
THATCHER'S 19-YEAR-OLD
AMERICAN-BORN GRANDDAUGHTER
AMANDA GAVE A READING FROM THE
BIBLE.
THOUSANDS OF LONDONERS LINED THE
ROUTE TO SHOW RESPECT AND SOME
PROTESTED AMID HEAVY SECURITY.
MARGARET THATCHER, THE SO-CALLED
IRON LADY, DIED LAST WEEK AT 87.
WE HAVE POSTED A FULL REPORT ON
THE DAY IN LONDON BY KIER
SIMMONS ON OUR WEBSITE TONIGHT.
>>> THE ASSASSINATIONS OF TWO
PROMINENT PUBLIC OFFICIALS HAVE
BEEN IN THE NEWS.
FOR A TIME THEY HAD
INVESTIGATORS BAFFLED.
THEY LEFT THE ENTIRE STATE OF
TEXAS ON EDGE.
TONIGHT WE CAN REPORT POLICE SAY
THE WIFE OF A FORMER TEXAS
JUSTICE OF THE PEACE HAS
CONFESSED SHE WAS INVOLVED IN
THE SHOOTING DEATHS OF A
DISTRICT ATTORNEY, HIS WIFE AND
A COUNTY PROSECUTOR.
ACCORDING TO AN AFFIDAVIT SHE
SAYS HER HUSBAND ERIC WILLIAMS
PULLED THE TRIGGER.
HE HAS NOT YET BEEN CHARGED.
THE TWO MEN WHO WERE KILLED IN
THESE CASES HAD PROSECUTED ERIC
WILLIAMS LAST YEAR FOR THEFT.
HE WAS CONVICTED AND FIRED FROM
HIS JOB AND SENTENCED TO
PROBATION AS A RESULT.
>>> BECAUSE AMERICAN AIRLINES
HAD A VERY BAD DAY YESTERDAY
WHEN ITS COMPUTER SYSTEM WENT
DOWN AND THE ENTIRE FLEET WAS
GROUNDED FOR A TIME, TODAY THEY
SAY MOST OF THE SYSTEM IS BACK
TO NORMAL.
THERE ARE STILL SOME AIRCRAFTS
THAT HAD TO PUT DOWN IN SOME
UNINTENDED LOCATIONS.
WELL, BECAUSE OF ALL OF IT THEIR
CEO TOM HORTON POSTED AN APOLOGY
VIDEO ON YOUTUBE.
HE BLAMED IT ON A SOFTWARE
PROBLEM.
ABOUT A THOUSAND FLIGHTS WERE
CANCELLED.
ABOUT 1,200 WERE DELAYED.
>>> BASEBALL FANS AND ESPECIALLY
RED SOX FANS KNOW THE NEIL
DIAMOND MODERN-DAY CLASSIC
"SWEET CAROLINE" IS THE ANTHEM
OF FENWAY PARK.
OVER THE PAST 24 HOURS AS A SHOW
OF RESPECT AND SUPPORT FOR
BOSTON, THE SONG HAS BEEN PLAYED
AT BASEBALL GAMES ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
NOWHERE WAS IT MORE IMPACTFUL
THAN WHEN THEY PLAYED IT AT
YANKEE STADIUM.
JUST CALLING THE HOUSE THAT RUTH
BUILT NORMALLY ANGERS SOX FANS.
LAST NIGHT THE YANKS WERE
PLAYING THEIR SONG.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, MAKING A
DIFFERENCE WITH SOME VERY GOOD
DOGS PROVIDING MUCH-NEEDED
COMFORT TO THE PEOPLE OF BOSTON.
>>> THIS IS THE CORNER OF
BOYLSTON AND BERKELEY STREETS IN
BOSTON WHERE A MEMORIAL HAS
SPROUTED UP ABOUT A BLOCK FROM
WHERE THE BOMBINGS TOOK PLACE.
IT WAS STARTED BY A MAN FROM
CAPE COD WANTING TO EXPRESS HIS
SADNESS.
FOLKS SAW IT.
THEY HAVE BEEN STOPPING BY ALL
DAY DROPPING OFF FLOWERS AND
CARDS.
A LOT OF THE SIGNS WE HAVE SEEN
FEATURE THE SLOGAN OF THE MOMENT
IN THAT CITY -- BOSTON STRONG.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT OUR MAKING A
DIFFERENCE REPORT.
WE HAVE SEEN IT ALL TOO MANY
TIMES LATELY.
THEY ARE A WELCOME SIGN WHEN
THEY ARRIVE ON THE SCENE -- THE
THERAPY DOGS WHO SHOW UP TO
COMFORT THE HUMANS WHO HAVE BEEN
THROUGH A TRAUMA.
WELL, THEY ARE ON THE JOB
TONIGHT IN BOSTON.
WE GET THE STORY TONIGHT FROM
NBC'S KERRY SANDERS.
>> Reporter: FOR TWO DAYS ALL
15-YEAR-OLD DAVID YEPEZ HAS
HEARD AND THOUGHT ABOUT ARE HIS
INJURIES FROM THE SECOND
EXPLOSION.
>> THIS IS RUTHIE.
>> Reporter: BUT TODAY, DAVID
SMILED.
>> WE HAVE A DOG AT HOME.
HE'S A SMALL YORKIE TERRIER.
>> Reporter: FOR JUST A MOMENT
LUTHER AND RUTHIE MADE THE
SHRAPNEL THAT TORE THROUGH HIS
LEFT LEG AND THE PAINFUL
SECOND-DEGREE BURNS ALMOST AN
AFTERTHOUGHT.
>> IT'S RELAXING.
TAKES MY MIND AWAY FROM
EVERYTHING GOING ON.
>> Reporter: TODAY LUTHERAN
CHURCH CHARITIES DEPLOYED THE
COMFORT BRIGADE AT TUFTS MEDICAL
CENTER.
DOGS THAT HAVE BEEN WORKING WITH
OTHER RECOVERING CHILDREN IN
NEWTOWN, CONNECTICUT.
>> COME ON, PUPPY.
>> Reporter: QUIET PEACEFUL
VISITORS WHO LEEANN SAYS SET HER
NERVES AT EASE HOURS BEFORE THE
SURGERY ON HER WOUNDED LEG.
>> ANIMALS, YOU KNOW, THEY JUST
HAVE A DIFFERENT SENSE, YOU
KNOW.
THEY DON'T TALK BACK TO YOU.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS!
HI!
>> Reporter: THE COMFORT DOGS
ARE LIKE FURRY THERAPISTS AND IT
IS NOT JUST THOSE WHO WERE
INJURED THAT NEED RELIEF.
HOW NICE IS IT FOR YOU TO HAVE
JUST A DIFFERENT MOMENT WITH A
DOG?
>> MY STRESS LEVEL HAS GONE WAY
DOWN.
>> THEY SENSE LOVE.
THEY SENSE THAT SOMEBODY IS
CARING.
AND THEY SENSE THAT IN THE MIDST
OF DARKNESS THERE IS LIGHT.
>> THIS IS LUTHER.
>> Reporter: COMPANIONSHIP,
COMPASSION, AND COMFORT, WHEN IT
IS NEEDED THE MOST.
>> YOU ARE A BIG PUPPY FOR 2.
>> Reporter: KERRY SANDERS, NBC
NEWS, BOSTON.
>> THANK GOODNESS FOR GOOD DOGS.
THAT'S OUR BROADCAST ON A
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE WITH
US.
I'M BRIAN WILLIAMS.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M JESSICA AGUIRRE.
>> AND I'M RAJ MATHAI.
IT HAS BEEN A FRANTIC DAY OF
DEVELOPMENT, DISCOVERIES AND
FAMILY STORIES AND CONTINUES
INTO THE NIGHT BOTH IN BOSTON
AND HERE IN THE BAY AREA.
WE HAVE A SERIES OF REPORTS
TONIGHT.
TERRY McSWEENEY IS IN BOSTON
WHERE FRIENDS AND FAMILY MEMBERS
ARE COPING WITH THE TERROR.
WE BEGIN WITH JODI HERNANDEZ IN
FREMONT WITH THE LOCAL
CONNECTION TO THE BOMB MATERIAL.
>> UNSETTLING DEVELOPMENT FOR
THIS FREMONT BATTERY
DEVELOPMENT.
THE FOLKS AT TENERGY ARE VERY
UPSET TO HEAR THAT THEIR BATTERY
MAY HAVE BEEN USED FOR THE BOMB.
A FAR CRY FROM WHAT THE
BATTERIES ARE DESIGNED TO BE
USED FOR.
TENERGY SAYS IT IS WIDELY USED
FOR HOBBIESTS MAINLY REMOTE
CONTROL CARS AND TRUCKS AND SOLD
AT HUNDREDS OF MOM AND POP HOBBY
SHOPS AND SOLD ONLINE.
THE COMPANY'S VICE PRESIDENT OF
TECHNOLOGY SAYS THEY ARE
HORRIFIED TO FIND OUT THEIR
BATTERIES CAN BE USED IN SUCH AN
ACT.
>> HORRIFIED, APPALLED, SHOCKED.
BATTERIES USED FOR TOYS, RC CARS
AND TRUCKS AND TO SEE IT USED IN
SUCH A WAY IS