AND LOOK OVER YOUR PLAN.
>> WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THE
TORNADO COMING UP IN JUST A FEW
SECONDS.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> THERE IS BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT.
A MASSIVE TORNADO JUST OUTSIDE
OKLAHOMA CITY.
AN ENORMOUS, PERHAPS HISTORIC
PATH OF DESTRUCTION AFTER A
DIRECT HIT FROM A TORNADO
ESTIMATED AT A MILE WIDE.
MUCH OF THE CITY OF MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, HAS BEEN WIPED OUT.
ENTIRE NEIGHBORHOODS ARE GONE,
INCLUDING TWO ELEMENTARY SCHOOLS
WHERE CHILDREN HAD TO BE PULLED
OUT OF THE WRECKAGE.
TONIGHT, A MASSIVE SEARCH FOR
SURVIVORS IS JUST GETTING UNDER
WAY.
OUR TEAM IS THERE ON THE GROUND.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
NBC-UNIVERSAL TELEVISION
>>> A SPECIAL GOOD EVENING TO
OUR VIEWERS IN THE WESTERN PART
OF THE UNITED STATES THIS
EVENING.
IT APPEARS WE ARE COVERING A
HISTORY-MAKING TORNADO IN
OKLAHOMA THIS EVENING.
IT'S EARLY YET.
IT HAPPENED JUST A FEW HOURS AGO
IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA, JUST TO THE
SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA CITY.
BUT SO FAR THE STATE MEDICAL
EXAMINER HAS TOLD THE ASSOCIATED
PRESS THE INITIAL DEATH TOLL IS
37 FROM THIS ONE TORNADO.
FROM THE AIR, IT IS HARD TO KNOW
AT TIMES JUST WHAT IT IS WE ARE
LOOKING AT.
BELIEVED TO HAVE BEEN EITHER AN
F4 OR F5, THE STRONGEST
INTENSITY ON EARTH, IT WAS OVER
A MILE WIDE AT THE BASE OF THE
STORM.
IT WAS IN THIS SAME TOWN --
MOORE, OKLAHOMA -- BACK IN 1999
WHEN THE HIGHEST EVER TORNADO
WINDS WERE RECORDED, 302 MILES
AN HOUR.
AGAIN, EARLY PICTURES FROM MOORE
SHOW SCHOOL CHILDREN STAGGERING
INTO THE ARMS OF TEACHERS AND
PARENTS.
THERE ARE FIRES BURNING FROM
OPEN GAS LINES.
THERE ARE MILES OF DEVASTATION.
IT HAS BEEN HARD TO LISTEN TO,
BUT LOCAL REPORTERS HAVE BEEN
BREAKING UP ON THE AIR TODAY,
OVERCOME WITH EMOTION BECAUSE,
AFTER ALL, THEY ARE COVERING
THEIR OWN COMMUNITY.
ESPECIALLY FOLLOWING THE REPORT
THAT MANY SCHOOL CHILDREN MAY
HAVE BEEN TRAPPED INSIDE ONE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
HERE NOW IS SOME OF THE EARLY
REPORTING FROM THAT SCHOOL, OUR
FIRST INDICATION WE MAY HAVE HAD
A DEVASTATING SITUATION THERE.
THIS IS JESSE WELLS FROM OUR NBC
TELEVISION STATION KFOR.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE FRONT
OF PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
YOU CAN SEE AGAIN -- WE HAVE
SAID IT BEFORE FROM THE AIR --
THIS SCHOOL IS BASICALLY GONE.
IT'S TOTALLY DESTROYED.
MOST OF THE WALLS COLLAPSED.
AS YOU CAN SEE THERE ARE A
NUMBER OF CARS THAT WERE THROWN
INTO THE FRONT OF THIS BUILDING.
IT'S AN OFFICE ON THE FRONT OF
THIS SCHOOL.
THERE IS A TRUCK, SUV OF SOME
KIND THROWN INTO THE FRONT OF
THE SCHOOL.
OVER HERE TO THE SOUTH EMERGENCY
CREWS HAVE BEEN CONTINUING TO
WORK ON GETTING KIDS OUT OF THE
SCHOOL BUILDING.
AGAIN, I TOLD YOU A FEW MINUTES
I TALKED TO A COUPLE OF KIDS
THAT WERE IN THIS SCHOOL AT THE
TIME.
THEY WERE LITERALLY HUGGING THE
WALLS OF THE INTERIOR HALLWAYS
AS THAT TORNADO WENT OVERHEAD,
TRYING TO SURVIVE.
THEY WERE BEING PROTECTED BY
SOME OF THE TEACHERS THAT WORKED
IN THIS SCHOOL BUILDING.
AGAIN, RIGHT NOW I DO NOT KNOW
HOW MANY KIDS WERE INSIDE OR ARE
STILL INSIDE.
AGAIN, APPARENTLY THERE MAY
STILL BE KIDS INSIDE THE SCHOOL.
WE REALLY DON'T KNOW.
THE INFORMATION IS VERY SPARSE
DOWN HERE.
YOU CAN SEE SEARCH AND RESCUE
CREWS CONTINUING TO TREAT THE
KIDS THAT WERE IN THIS SCHOOL.
THE SEARCH FOR KIDS, THERE MAY
STILL BE KIDS INSIDE.
HONESTLY IT'S NOT JUST THE
SCHOOL THAT GOT HIT.
AS WE PAN AROUND FURTHER YOU
WILL BE ABLE TO SEE ALL AROUND,
360 DEGREES AROUND WHERE I'M
STANDING ALL OF THE HOMES
LITERALLY LEVELLED TO THE
GROUND.
>> THERE WAS STILL DAYLIGHT
THERE.
JESSE WELLS FOR KFOR FOR THAT
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WHERE WE MAY
HAVE A VERY, VERY GRIM SITUATION
AS THE SEARCH AND RESCUE GOES
ON.
WEATHER CHANNEL METEOROLOGIST
MIKE BETTES MADE HIS WAY TO
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
MIKE, WHAT DO YOU SEE AROUND
YOU?
>> Reporter: BRIAN, THE SCENE IS
AS DEVASTATING AS IT GETS FROM A
HISTORY-MAKING TORNADO IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
I CAN GIVE YOU A BRIEF UPDATE OF
WHAT WE ARE HEARING FROM THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
AT LEAST SIX CHILDREN HAVE
DROWNED IN THE BASEMENT.
AS MANY NOW AS 30 SCHOOL
CHILDREN UNACCOUNTED FOR AND MAY
HAVE INDEED PERISHED IN THE
SCHOOL AS IT WAS DIRECTLY STRUCK
BY THE TORNADO.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU THE
PERSPECTIVE OF WHAT HAS HAPPENED
HERE.
WE BELIEVE ABOUT A MILE-WIDE
TORNADO HAS JUST LEVELLED THE
COMMUNITIES IN MOORE.
THIS IS A NEIGHBORHOOD ON THE
OUTSIDE OF MOORE.
THESE ARE WELL BUILT FRAME
HOMES, BRICK HOMES.
THERE IS NOTHING LEFT.
THESE HOMES ARE FLATTENED.
CARS ON TOP OF HOMES.
CARS ON TOP OF CARS.
THEY ARE MANGLED BEYOND BELIEF.
SEARCH AND RESCUE IS ONGOING AT
THIS POINT.
THEY ARE GATHERING RIGHT NOW,
SETTING UP COMMAND POSTS, TRYING
TO BE ORDERLY IN HOW THEY
RESPOND TO THIS.
THEY ARE GOING TO NEED TO GO
HOME TO HOME TO HOME AND MAKE
SURE EVERYONE IS ACCOUNTED FOR.
WHAT YOU SEE BEHIND ME HERE IS
THEM ESTABLISHING A COMMAND POST
AT THIS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
THIS IS BRIARWOOD ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL THAT ALSO TOOK A DIRECT
HIT FROM THE TORNADO.
WE TALKED TO ONE SCHOOL TEACHER
A LITTLE BIT AGO.
HE SAID THE TEACHERS TOOK ALL
THE SCHOOL KIDS INTO THE MIDDLE,
THE CENTER PART OF THE SCHOOL,
PUT THEM ON INTERIOR WALLS AND
AS FAR AS HE KNOWS EVERY SINGLE
TEACHER AND STUDENT IS ACCOUNTED
FOR.
THAT IS GREAT NEWS.
SEARCH AND RESCUE WILL STILL GO
THROUGH THE BUILDING THROUGH
NIGHT, WE ARE TOLD BY
FIREFIGHTERS, TO MAKE SURE
EVERYTHING IS OKAY.
WE SPOKE WITH A YOUNG WOMAN THAT
LIVES IN THIS HOME.
SHE WAS NOT HOME AT THE TIME,
THANK GOODNESS.
SHE'S OKAY.
HER FAMILY IS OKAY.
HER NEIGHBORS ARE ACCOUNTED FOR.
NOW IT IS THE HARD TASK OF
TRYING TO PUT YOUR LIFE BACK
TOGETHER AND TRYING TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT HAPPENED WHEN SO MUCH
CHANGED FOR YOU IN AN INSTANT.
WE ARE WITH DR. GREG FORBES, AN
EXPERT IN SURVEYING DAMAGE.
HE'S DONE HUNDREDS OF DAMAGE
SURVEYS IN HIS LONG CAREER.
DR. FORBES, HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS BEFORE?
>> NO.
THIS IS THE WORST I HAVE EVER
SEEN.
THE EXPANSE OF THE DAMAGE,
PROBABLY THREE BLOCKS IN THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD.
IT GOES ON AT LEAST A MILE DOWN
THERE.
I HAVE NEVER SEEN DESTRUCTION SO
TOTAL OVER SUCH AN EXPANSIVE
AREA.
>> Reporter: DR. FORBES, IS
THERE A QUESTION IN YOUR MIND
SINCE YOU HAVE DONE THIS MORE
THAN ANYBODY ON THE TALENT THAT
THIS TORNADO WILL NOT BE AN
EF-5?
>> I WOULD GIVE IT AN EF-5
RATING.
WE HAVE TREES DEBARKED, CARS
TOSSED LONG DISTANCE.
STRUCTURES BROKEN INTO PIECES,
UNRECOGNIZABLE AND TOSSED AS
DEBRIS DOWNWIND.
IT IS A SCENE OF UTTER
DESTRUCTION, ALMOST BEYOND
WORDS.
>> Reporter: BRIAN, YOU KNOW,
THESE ARE THE TYPES OF STORIES
WE HATE TO COME TO YOU WITH.
WE KNOW THIS IS A SCENE THAT'S
HAPPENED BEFORE.
WE SAW THIS TWO YEARS AGO IN
JOPLIN, MISSOURI.
CONJECTURE IS SOMETHING WE DON'T
LIKE TO DO.
AT THAT TIME EARLY ON IN THAT
TORNADO THE FATALITY COUNT WAS
29.
OVERNIGHT IT WENT TO 92.
RIGHT NOW WE HAVE A CONFIRMED
FATALITY OF 37.
THIS IS A NEIGHBORHOOD THAT'S
BEEN FLATTENED.
I'M AFRAID OF WHAT WE'LL END UP
SEEING TOMORROW WHEN MORE
NUMBERS COME OUT, WHEN THERE IS
A MORE COMPREHENSIVE TALLY OF
WHAT'S HAPPENED HERE.
SEARCH AND RESCUE WILL GO ON
THROUGH THE NIGHT.
THERE IS A PUNGENT ODOR TO HAVE
NATURAL GAS AND GASOLINE.
WE ARE JUST HOURS INTO THIS.
I'M TRULY STUNNED BY WHAT I SEE.
>> MIKE BETTES ALONG WITH DR.
GREG FORBES IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
AS MIKE SAYS, IT IS EARLY YET.
WE COULD BE IN FOR SOME DARK
HOURS AND DARK DAYS AHEAD FOR
THAT COMMUNITY AS THEY COME TO
GRIPS WITH WHAT'S BEEN LOST
HERE.
MIKE, THANK YOU.
OUR THANKS TO DR. FORBES AS
WELL.
>>> WE HAVE AN INTERVIEW WITH A
SURVIVOR, SOMEONE WHO WAS
EVACUATED AND MADE IT THROUGH
THIS STORM IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
I'M WONDERING IF WE CAN GET TO
THAT NOW.
>> WE THOUGHT WE DIED.
WE WERE INSIDE THE CELLAR DOOR.
LOCKED THE CELLAR DOOR WHEN WE
SAW IT COMING.
IT GOT LOUDER AND NEXT THING YOU
KNOW, YOU SEE THE LATCH COMING
UNDONE.
WE COULDN'T REACH FOR IT.
IT RIPPED OPEN THE DOOR AND JUST
GLASS AND DEBRIS STARTED
SLAMMING ON US.
WE THOUGHT WE WERE DEAD, TO BE
HONEST.
>> AGAIN, WHEN YOU HEAR A
SURVIVOR STORY IT MEANS, ALMOST
BY DEFINITION IN THE HEART OF
THIS STORM THAT THEY HAD
SOMEWHERE TO GO.
LOCAL WEATHER AUTHORITIES WERE
SAYING THE ONLY WAY THIS WAS
SURVIVABLE WAS TO BE UNDER
GROUND AT A SECURE UNDER GROUND
SHELTER.
IT MAY FIGURE THAT SOME OF THE
PEOPLE WHO SURVIVED THIS WERE
INDEED ABLE TO GET TO SHELTERS
AND THE OPPOSITE WAS NOT TRUE.
JANET SHAMLIAN HAS MADE HER WAY
TO MOORE, OKLAHOMA, THIS
EVENING.
JANET, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: BRIAN, GOOD EVENING
TO YOU.
WHAT HAS HAPPENED IN MOORE HAS
BASICALLY PARALYZED EVERYTHING
NEAR AND AROUND IT.
WHAT YOU SEE OVER MY SHOULDER IS
THE AGONIZING WAIT OF PEOPLE
TRYING TO GET BACK INTO THE
COMMUNITY.
WITH FEW EXCEPTIONS, MOST OF
THEM ARE BEING TURNED AWAY.
JUST TO GET TO THIS POINT, THIS
ROAD GOES ABOUT TWO MILES TO THE
INTERSTATE.
IT IS ABOUT AN HOUR TO GET THOSE
TWO MILES.
MOST OF THESE PEOPLE ARE NOT
BEING ALLOWED BACK INTO THEIR
HOMES.
MANY OF THEM HAVE BEEN TRYING
FOR HOURS.
THEY REPORT COMMUTES OF TWO OR
THREE HOURS TO GET 12 OR 14
MILES.
THE ONLY VEHICLES WE ARE SEEING
GO IN ARE AMBULANCES, STATE
TROOPERS, POLICE, UTILITY
COMPANIES.
AND THE ONLY ONES WE HAVE SEEN
COME OUT ARE TWO AMBULANCES WITH
THEIR SIRENS FLASHI INING ABOUT
HOUR AGO.
THAT BROUGHT HOPE TO US HERE.
SPEAKING OF THE PARALYSIS, THE
USAGE OF CELL PHONES HAS MADE
TRYING TO USE THE CELL PHONES
BASICALLY USELESS.
YOU CANNOT GET A CELL CALL IN OR
OUT.
PEOPLE TRYING TO COMMUNICATE ARE
STRUGGLING IN THAT WAY AS WELL.
AS WE SEE THE AERIALS OF THE
SEARCH CREWS GOING HOUSE TO
HOUSE TO HOUSE THEY ARE
DEFINITELY TRYING TO KEEP PEOPLE
OUT OF THE COMMUNITY INCLUDING
SOME WHO ARE DESPERATELY TRYING
TO MAKE THEIR WAY HOME, BRIAN.
>> JANET, I DID CEE LO CALL -- E
SEE LOCAL OFFICIALS TELLING
PEOPLE TO TRY TEXTING.
THEY WILL DIVIDE UP THE
COMMUNITY INTO GRIDS.
IT'S HARD TO KNOW WHERE TO
BEGIN.
YOU HAVE TO SET UP SOME
STRUCTURE AND SEARCH PROPERTY BY
PROPERTY.
IN SOME CASES IT WILL BE
IMPOSSIBLE TO FIND ADDRESSES.
>> YEAH.
YOU KNOW, WE REALLY HAVEN'T BEEN
ABLE TO TALK TO ANYBODY COMING
OUT.
PEOPLE ARE TRYING TO MAKE CALLS
IN NOW ASKING US, DO OUR PHONES
WORK, AND THEY DON'T EITHER.
WE HAVE NOT BEEN ABLE TO GET
MUCH COMMUNICATION.
WE KNOW EVERYONE IS AFFECTED IN
THE SAME WAY AT THIS POINT.
>> JANET SHAMLIAN PART OF OUR
TEAM ON THE GROUND IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
>> WE GO TO THE WEATHER CHANNEL
HEADQUARTERS.
TO BE HONEST.
WE HAVE PEOPLE ON THE GROUND --
WE HAD A LONG WIND-UP ON SEVERE
WEATHER.
WE KNEW THIS SYSTEM WAS COMING.
AT LEAST IT STRUCK DURING THE
DAY AND NOT IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
NIGHT.
SO I'M HOPING THAT SIRENS WERE
BLARING FOR A GOOD, LONG TILE.
>> THERE IS NO PLACE BETTER
PREPARED FOR A STORM LIKE THIS
THAN MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
BECAUSE OF THE STORM 14 YEARS
AGO.
AS YOU MENTIONED, THE EF-5
TORNADO THAT WENT THROUGH THERE,
JUST NORTH OF WHERE THIS ONE
TRACKED ACROSS THE CITY OF
MOORE.
THAT ONE WAS MEASURED AT 302
MILES PER HOUR.
THE STRONGEST WINDS EVER
MEASURED ON THE PLANET BECAUSE
THAT OCCURRED JUST AFTER THE
TECHNOLOGY CAME INTO PLAY THAT
ALLOWED US TO MEASURE TORNADOES.
WE DON'T KNOW.
IN FACT, I DOUBT IT WAS.
LET ME SHOW YOU THIS AS IT WENT.
THE DOT YOU SAW ON SCREEN WITH
THE RADAR, THAT'S WHERE THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WAS.
LET ME GO TO 3:15.
WATCH THE TIME.
THAT'S CENTRAL TIME.
UNFORTUNATELY IF YOU LOOK AT THE
PURPLE HERE, THAT'S THE TORNADO
INTENSI
INTENSIFYING.
IT JUST INTENSIFIED TO ITS WORST
AT THE TIME THAT IT CROSSED NEAR
THAT ELEMENTARY SCHOOL AND THEN
MOVED ACROSS I-35 AND WEAKENED
AS IT WENT ON THROUGH MOORE.
THE LIFETIME OF THE TORNADO,
BRIAN, WAS ONLY ABOUT 40 MINUTES
AND THE CORE PEAK TIME WAS ABOUT
15 MINUTES AND IT WAS IN THAT
PERIOD IN THE POPULATED PART OF
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, SOUTH OF
OKLAHOMA CITY, THAT THE STORM
PEAKED OVER TOP OF WHERE THE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WAS AND WHERE
A WELL KNOWN HORSE BARN IS THERE
SOUTH OF OKLAHOMA CITY.
THE FAMILY FARM WHERE A NUMBER
OF HORSES PERISHED AS WELL IN
THIS TORNADO.
AS MIKE BETTES SAID I'M SURE
WE'LL HEAR MORE BAD NEWS, BRIAN?
>> SADLY, I FATHER YOU ARE
RIGHT.
BRIAN NORCROSS AT WEATHER
CHANNEL HEADQUARTERS.
IT DOESN'T GET MORE INTENSE ON
PLANET EARTH THAN AN EF-5
TORNADO.
BRIAN, THANKS.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A BREAK.
MORE OF OUR COVERAGE OF THIS
DEVASTATING STORM IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, RIGHT AFTER THIS.
[ Lisa ] MY NAME'S LISA,
AND CHANTIX HELPED ME QUIT.
I HONESTLY LOVED SMOKING,
AND I HONESTLY DIDN'T THINK
I WOULD EVER QUIT.
[ Male Announcer ]
ALONG WITH SUPPORT,
CHANTIX (VARENICLINE) IS PROVEN
TO HELP PEOPLE QUIT SMOKING.
IT REDUCES THE URGE TO SMOKE.
IT PUT ME AT EASE THAT YOU COULD
SMOKE ON THE FIRST WEEK.
[ Male Announcer ] SOME PEOPLE
HAD CHANGES IN BEHAVIOR,
THINKING OR MOOD,
HOSTILITY, AGITATION,
DEPRESSED MOOD AND SUICIDAL
THOUGHTS OR ACTIONS
WHILE TAKING
OR AFTER STOPPING CHANTIX.
IF YOU NOTICE ANY OF THESE
STOP TAKING CHANTIX AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ANY HISTORY OF DEPRESSION
OR OTHER
MENTAL HEALTH PROBLEMS,
WHICH COULD GET WORSE
WHILE TAKING CHANTIX.
DON'T TAKE CHANTIX IF
YOU'VE HAD A SERIOUS ALLERGIC
OR SKIN REACTION TO IT.
IF YOU DEVELOP THESE
STOP TAKING CHANTIX
AND SEE YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
AS SOME CAN BE
LIFE-THREATENING.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HISTORY
OF HEART OR BLOOD VESSEL
PROBLEMS,
OR IF YOU DEVELOP
NEW OR WORSE SYMPTOMS.
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
OF A HEART ATTACK OR STROKE.
USE CAUTION WHEN DRIVING
OR OPERATING MACHINERY.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS
INCLUDE NAUSEA,
TROUBLE SLEEPING
AND UNUSUAL DREAMS.
WITH CHANTIX AND WITH THE
SUPPORT SYSTEM IT WORKED FOR ME.
[ Male Announcer ]
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF CHANTIX
IS RIGHT FOR YOU.
ARE PROVEN TO BE
EFFECTIVE PAIN RELIEVERS
Tylenol WORKS BY BLOCKING
PAIN SIGNALS TO YOUR BRAIN
Bayer Back & Body's
DUAL ACTION FORMULA
INCLUDES ASPIRIN,
WHICH BLOCKS PAIN AT THE SITE.
TRY THE POWER
OF Bayer
Back & Body.
GLASS ON FLOORS. DAILY CHORES.
FOR THE LITTLE MISHAPS YOU FEEL
USE NEOSPORIN TO HELP YOU HEAL.
IT KILLS GERMS
SO YOU HEAL
FOUR DAYS FASTER.
NEOSPORIN.
USE WITH BAND-AID BRAND
BANDAGES.
BJORN EARNS UNLIMITED REWARDS
FOR HIS SMALL BUSINESS.
TAKE THESE BAGS
TO ROOM 12 PLEASE.
[ Garth ] BJORN'S SMALL BUSINESS
EARNS DOUBLE MILES
ON EVERY PURCHASE EVERY DAY.
PRODUCE DELIVERY.
[ Bjorn ] JUST PUT IT
ON MY Spark Card.
[ Garth ]
WHY SETTLE FOR LESS?
AHH, OH!
[ Garth ] GREAT BUSINESSES
DESERVE UNLIMITED REWARDS.
HERE'S
YOUR WAKE UP CALL.
[ Male Announcer ]
GET THE Spark Business Card
FROM Capital One
AND EARN UNLIMITED REWARDS.
CHOOSE DOUBLE MILES
OR 2% CASH BACK
ON EVERY PURCHASE EVERY DAY.
WHAT'S IN YOUR WALLET?
[ crows ]
NOW WHERE'S THE SNOOZE BUTTON?
>>> LIVE PICTURES COMING INTO US
TONIGHT.
OF COURSE THEY ARE GOING TO LOSE
DAYLIGHT.
IT'S ALREADY DIFFICULT FOR
PEOPLE IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA, TO
FIGURE OUT WHERE THEY LIVED.
WHEN YOU ARE AT GROUND LEVEL IN
THIS DEBRIS FIELD IT ALL LOOKS
THE SAME.
IT WILL BE MONTHS BEFORE THE
BELONGING, SOME MILES AWAY.
ABSOLUTE DEVASTATION AT
DIFFERENT POINTS IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, IS EARTH HAS BEEN
WIPED CLEAN.
THOSE PICTURES, SO MUCH COVERAGE
FROM KFOR AND HERE NOW A
COLLECTION OF THEIR EARLY
COVERAGE FROM THE STORM'S FIRST
MOMENT OF ARRIVAL.
>> Reporter: THERE IT IS.
IT'S A MILE RIGHT THERE ON THE
BAILEY WHERE IT TURNS DOWN
SOUTH.
THAT'S WHERE IT IS RIGHT THERE.
MAN, IT'S ABOUT A MILE RIGHT AT
OUR TAIL.
>> DON'T LOSE YOUR LIFE.
GO GET AWAY FROM IT OR GO BELOW
GROUND.
STORM CELLAR, BASEMENT OR SAFE
ROOM.
THAT'S THE ONLY OPTION YOU HAVE.
>> IT'S ABSOLUTELY MASSIVE, JUST
SHREDDING EVERYTHING IN FRONT OF
IT.
VIOLENT, VIOLENT MOTION, A HUGE
DEBRIS CLOUD AROUND IT.
>> THIS THING HASN'T DECREASED
IN SIZE ANY.
I'M ACTUALLY KIND OF GETTING
CLOSER THAN I WANT TO BE TO IT
RIGHT NOW.
THIS THING IS SUCKING US IN AT
ABOUT 50 TO 60 MILES AN HOUR
RIGHT NOW.
LOOK AT THAT SCHOOL, GUYS.
OH, MY GOD.
IF YOU GUYS CAN SEE THIS, I
DON'T KNOW HOW TO EXPLAIN IT,
HOW TO DESCRIBE IT.
THIS IS -- THIS IS TERRIBLE.
THIS IS WAR ZONE TERRIBLE.
IT IS LIKE YOU SEE COMPLETELY
DESTROYED AS KIDS RUN UP TO
HOPEFULLY THEIR LOVED ONES.
BUT THIS WHOLE AREA RIGHT HERE,
GUYS, IT'S COMPLETELY DESTROYED.
>> OH, NO.
OH, MY.
>> THAT'S ANOTHER SCHOOL.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
THAT ONE LOOKS HARDER HIT THAN
ANY OF THEM BEFORE.
>> OH, MY GOODNESS.
>> AS A PARENT THIS IS KIND OF
HARD TO REPORT ON.
>> HORRIFIC.
>> WE'RE GOING TO STAY IN THE
AIR.
>> YOU LOOK AT THE SCENE OF
DESTRUCTION THERE AND THE SMALL
FIGURES OF THE RESCUERS WORKING
FRANTICALLY AND WHERE DO YOU
BEGIN?
THAT'S THE QUESTION.
WHERE DO YOU BEGIN ON SOMETHING
LIKE THIS?
>> REMEMBER, LOCAL NEWS COVERAGE
IN OKLAHOMA CITY MEANS THESE ARE
REPORTERS COVERING THEIR OWN
COMMUNITY.
IT'S BEEN AN EMOTIONAL DAY INTO
THIS EVENING IN OKLAHOMA CITY IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, TO BE SPECIFIC.
OUR FRIENDS AT KFOR, THE MEDICAL
EXAMINER PUTTING THE EARLY DEATH
TOLL AT 37 SOULS TONIGHT.
WE'LL TAKE A BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WEATHER
CHANNEL METEOROLOGIST MIKE
SEIDEL HAS COME ACROSS A FAIRLY
GRIM SCENE THERE IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, TONIGHT.
♪
OH.
LET'S GO.
FROM THE CRACK,
OFF THE BACKBOARD.
[ laughs ]
DAD!
WHOO!
OH!
YOU'RE UP!
SO CLOSE!
NOW WHERE WERE WE?
OK, THIS ONE'S
GOOD FOR TWO.
SCORE!
[ Male Announcer ]
SHARE WHAT YOU LOVE
WITH WHO YOU LOVE.
Kellogg's Frosted Flakes.
THEY'RE GR-R-EAT!
YEAH...
TRY NEW Alka Seltzer
Fruit Chews.
THEY WORK FAST ON HEARTBURN
AND TASTE AWESOME.
THESE ARE GOOD.
TOLD YA!
I'M FEELING BETTER ALREADY.
[ Male Announcer ]
NEW Alka Seltzer Fruits Chews.
ENJOY THE RELIEF!
[ Male Announcer ]
NEW Alka Seltzer Fruits Chews.
LA's congestion,itely
ffor it's smog.,
But there are a lot of people
that do ride the bus.
And now that the busses are
running on natural gas,
they don't throw out as
much pollution to the earth.
So I feel good.
I feel like I'm doing my part
to help out the environment.
AS SOON AS YOU FEELON
IT, TRY MIRALAX.
IT WORKS
DIFFERENTLY
THAN OTHER
LAXATIVES.
IT DRAWS WATER INTO YOUR COLON
TO UNBLOCK YOUR
SYSTEM NATURALLY.
DON'T WAIT TO FEEL GREAT.
MIRALAX.
CAN YOU START THE DAY
THE WAY YOU WANT?
CAN ORENCIA (ABATACEPT) HELP?
COULD YOUR "I WANT"
BECOME "I CAN"?
TALK TO YOUR RHEUMATOLOGIST.
ORENCIA REDUCES
MANY RA SYMPTOMS
LIKE PAIN, MORNING STIFFNESS
AND THE PROGRESSION
OF JOINT DAMAGE.
IT'S HELPED NEW RA PATIENTS
AND THOSE NOT HELPED ENOUGH
BY OTHER TREATMENTS.
DO NOT TAKE ORENCIA
WITH ANOTHER BIOLOGIC MEDICINE
FOR RA
DUE TO AN INCREASED RISK
OF SERIOUS INFECTION.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS CAN OCCUR
INCLUDING FATAL INFECTIONS.
CASES OF LYMPHOMA AND
LUNG CANCER HAVE BEEN REPORTED.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR IF YOU ARE
PRONE TO OR HAVE ANY INFECTION
LIKE AN OPEN SORE OR THE FLU
OR A HISTORY OF COPD,
A CHRONIC LUNG DISEASE.
ORENCIA MAY WORSEN YOUR COPD.
[ Male Announcer ]
NOW LEARN ABOUT A PROGRAM
COMMITTED TO YOU
AND COPAY ASSISTANCE THAT CAN
REDUCE MONTHLY ORENCIA
OUT-OF-POCKET
DRUG COST TO $5.
IF YOU'RE
NOT SATISFIED
AFTER 6 MONTHS,
YOU GET
THAT MONEY BACK.
CALL 1-800-ORENCIA.
YOU GET
THAT MONEY BACK.
Foour neighbors....
and our communities...
America's beverage companies
have created...
a wide range of new choices.
Developing smaller portion sizes
and more..
low and no-calorie
beverages...
adding clear calorie labels so
you know...
exactly what you're choosing...
and in schools, replacing
full-calorie soft drinks...
with lower-calorie options.
With more choices and fewer
calories...
America's Beverage Companies are
delivering.
TEST TEST TEST TEST
>>> I HAD TO HOLD ONTO THE WALL
TO KEEP MYSELF SAFE BECAUSE I
DIDN'T WANT TO FLY AWAY IN THE
TORNADO.
>> WE HAD TO PULL A CAR OUT OF
THE FRONT HALLWAY OFF A TEACHER.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT THAT LADY'S
NAME IS BUT SHE HAD THREE LITTLE
KIDS UNDERNEATH HER.
GOOD JOB, TEACH.
I STILL HAVE A LITTLE GIRL
BURIED IN THERE.
I'VE GOT TO GO.
>> WE ARE IN FOR A LONG MARCH OF
SADNESS AS THE NEWS AND THE
NUMBERS EMERGE FROM MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
WE HAVE A LATE UPDATE FROM THE
ASSOCIATED PRESS.
HOSPITALS ARE TREATING MORE THAN
120 PATIENTS AFTER THIS TORNADO
INCLUDING ABOUT 70 CHILDREN.
AS WE MENTIONED WEATHER CHANNEL
METEOROLOGIST MIKE SEIDEL IS ON
FOOT IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
MIKE, EVERYTHING WE HAVE BEEN
TALKING ABOUT, PEOPLE UNABLE TO
FIND ADDRESSES, UNABLE TO LOCATE
WHERE THEY ONCE LIVED.
IT'S HARD TO DESCRIBE IT, BUT
THIS IS, I THINK YOU WILL AGREE,
THE MOST INTENSE WEATHER SYSTEM
THE EARTH CAN PRODUCE.
>> IT IS, BRIAN.
IT'S THE WORST I HAVE EVER SEEN.
I WAS NOT IN JOPLIN, BUT AS FAR
AS I CAN SEE LEFT AND RIGHT,
ABOUT 150 TO 200 YARDS, THERE IS
NOTHING LEFT.
ALL YOU SEE IS CONCRETE SLABS.
OUT OF EVERY CONCRETE SLAB YOU
SEE WATER GEYSERS.
THERE IS STILL GAS.
I WALKED FROM THE SCHOOL OVER
HERE AND I HEAR A HISSING SOUND
AND REALIZE, LET'S GET OUT OF
HERE.
THERE ARE A LOT OF GAS LEAKS.
I'M LOOKING AT THE PLAZA TOWERS
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL AND THE LATEST
I GOT FROM NURSES AND DOCTORS AT
TRIAGE ARE AT LEAST 24 CHILDREN
ARE STILL MISSING.
THERE ARE ABOUT 150 RESPONDERS
OVER THERE TRYING TO COMB
THROUGH THE WRECKAGE.
THEY HAVE ALREADY SET UP THE
LIGHTS.
YOU KNOW THIS IS GOING WELL INTO
THE NIGHT.
THERE ARE SEVEN OR EIGHT
AMBULANCES WAITING.
MORE THAN LIKELY WE ARE GOING TO
HAVE MORE FATALITIES.
THEY CAN'T GET INTO THE RUBBLE.
THE SCHOOL IS JUST BLOWN APART.
SOME OF THE CONCRETE WALLS,
BRICK WALLS ARE STANDING.
AS I WALKED THROUGH MOORE I SAW
PEOPLE WALKING DOWN THE STREETS
WITH THEIR PETS, BLOODIES.
ONE GIRL CAME BACK TO SAVE HER
DOG AND GOT INTO THE BATHTUB.
SHE SHOWED US WHERE SHE WAS.
IT'S A PURE MIRACLE SHE WAS ABLE
TO SAVE HERSELF AND THE DOG AND
GET OUT OF THAT TUB.
WE'VE GOT THE PICTURES.
WE'LL SHOW YOU LATER.
I DON'T KNOW HOW SHE E MADE IT.
SHE'S BANGED UP PRETTY GOOD.
SHE'S GOT BLOOD ALL OVER HER,
BUT SHE'S OKAY AND HER DOG IS
OKAY, TOO.
IT'S TOTAL DEVASTATION.
THE TORNADO CAME THROUGH LIKE A
BUZZ SAW AND SCRAPED THE EARTH
CLEAN.
IT REMINDS ME OF WHAT WE SAW
AFTER KATRINA WHEN THE 25-FOOT
STORM SURGE HIT THE COAST.
NOTHING WAS LEFT EXCEPT BIG
TREES AND STEEL GIRDERS.
THAT'S ALL WE SEE HERE.
TREES DEBARKED.
AS DR. FORBES MENTIONED, AND
HE'S THE EXPERT, BUT THIS HAS TO
BE EF-5 DAMAGE.
WIND EASILY OVER 200 MILES PER
HOUR.
THE GRIM SITUATION CONTINUES AT
THIS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL WHERE
FROM THE NURSES AND DOCTORS AT
THE TRIAGE, THEY ARE TELLING US
THAT THE COUNT NOW IS 24 MISSING
CHILDREN.
BRIAN, AS THE SUN GOES DOWN,
IT'S GOING TO GET DARK AND MAKE
IT TOUGH TO FIND ANYTHING.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU JUST CAN'T FIND ADDRESSES
OUT HERE.
EVERYTHING IS GONE.
PILES OF RUBBLE.
WITH THE HOUSES WHERE I'M
STANDING THERE'S NOTHING.
THE RUBBLE IS GONE.
WE PROBABLY WALKED A MILE AND A
HALF.
EVEN OUT WHERE WE PARKED ON THE
FRINGE NEAR I-35 IT'S NOT BIG
DEBRIS, BUT THERE IS DEBRIS
EVERYWHERE.
THIS IS A HUGE, MONSTER TORNADO.
>> MIKE SEIDEL, NOT MUCH LEFT IN
MOORE, OKLAHOMA.
MIKE, THANKS FOR YOUR REPORTING
FROM THE SCENE.
ANOTHER BREAK.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
ENTRUM SILV.
BOTH OF US ACTUALLY.
OUR PHARMACIST
RECOMMENDED IT.
AND THAT MAKES ME FEEL
PRETTY GOOD ABOUT IT.
AND THEN I HEARD ABOUT A STUDY
LOOKING AT MULTIVITAMINS
AND THE LONG TERM
HEALTH BENEFITS.
AND WHAT DO YOU KNOW?
THEY USED CENTRUM SILVER
IN THE STUDY.
MAKES ME FEEL EVEN BETTER,
THAT'S WHAT I TAKE.
SORRY, WE TAKE.
[ Male Announcer ] CENTRUM.
THE MOST RECOMMENDED.
MOST PREFERRED. MOST STUDIED.
CENTRUM,
ALWAYS YOUR MOST COMPLETE.
[ slap! ]
[ Male Announcer ] YOUR
FAVORITE FOODS FIGHTING YOU?
FIGHT BACK FAST WITH TUMS.
CALCIUM-RICH TUMS
STARTS WORKING SO FAST
YOU'LL FORGET
YOU HAD HEARTBURN.
♪ TUM TUM TUM TUM TUMS
YOU KNOW, FROM OUR 4,000
TELEVISION COMMERCIALS.
YEP, THERE I AM WITH FLO.
HOO-HOO! WATCH IT!
[Chuckles] ANYHOO, 3 MILLION
PEOPLE SWITCHED TO ME LAST YEAR,
SAVING AN AVERAGE
OF $475.
[Sigh] IT FEELS GOOD
TO HELP PEOPLE SAVE...
WITH GREAT DISCOUNTS LIKE
SAFE DRIVER, MULTICAR,
AND MULTIPOLICY.
SO CALL ME TODAY.
YOU'LL BE GLAD YOU DID.
CANNONBOX!
[SPLASH!]
SEE, I KNEW TESTOSTERONE
COULD AFFECT SEX DRIVE,
BUT NOT ENERGY
OR EVEN MY MOOD.
THAT'S WHEN I TALKED
WITH MY DOCTOR.
HE GAVE ME SOME BLOOD TESTS...
SHOWED IT WAS LOW T.
THAT'S IT. IT WAS A NUMBER.
[ Male Announcer ]
TODAY, MEN WITH LOW T
HAVE ANDROGEL 1.62%
TESTOSTERONE GEL.
THE #1 PRESCRIBED
TOPICAL TESTOSTERONE
REPLACEMENT THERAPY
INCREASES TESTOSTERONE
WHEN USED DAILY.
WOMEN AND CHILDREN SHOULD AVOID
CONTACT WITH APPLICATION SITES.
DISCONTINUE ANDROGEL
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU SEE UNEXPECTED SIGNS
OF EARLY PUBERTY IN A CHILD,
OR SIGNS IN A WOMAN,
WHICH MAY INCLUDE
CHANGES IN BODY HAIR
OR A LARGE INCREASE IN ACNE,
POSSIBLY DUE
TO ACCIDENTAL EXPOSURE.
MEN WITH BREAST CANCER
OR WHO HAVE OR MIGHT HAVE
PROSTATE CANCER,
AND WOMEN WHO ARE OR MAY BECOME
PREGNANT OR ARE BREAST-FEEDING,
SHOULD NOT USE ANDROGEL.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
WORSENING OF
AN ENLARGED PROSTATE,
POSSIBLE INCREASED RISK
OF PROSTATE CANCER,
LOWER SPERM COUNT, SWELLING
OF ANKLES, FEET, OR BODY,
ENLARGED OR PAINFUL BREASTS,
PROBLEMS BREATHING
DURING SLEEP,
AND BLOOD CLOTS IN THE LEGS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICAL CONDITIONS
AND MEDICATIONS,
ESPECIALLY INSULIN,
CORTICOSTEROIDS, OR MEDICINES
TO DECREASE BLOOD CLOTTING.
IN A CLINICAL STUDY, OVER 80%
OF TREATED MEN HAD THEIR
T LEVELS RESTORED TO NORMAL.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT ALL YOUR SYMPTOMS.
GET THE BLOOD TESTS.
CHANGE YOUR NUMBER. TURN IT UP.
ANDROGEL 1.62%.
>>> TONIGHT IN MOORE, OKLAHOMA,
THE NATIONAL GUARD ARE COMING
OUT.
THERE IS NO POWER, NO LIGHTS, NO
COMMUNICATIONS.
ALL WE KNOW IS THE DEATH TOLL
WILL RISE.
THE "TODAY" SHOW WILL ORIGINATE
FROM MOORE, OKLAHOMA, TOMORROW
MORNING.
SO WILL THIS BROADCAST TOMORROW
NIGHT.
THERE WILL BE MORE LATER ON YOUR
LATE LOCAL NEWS AND THE WEATHER
CHANNEL COVERAGE WILL GO ALL
NIGHT OBVIOUSLY.
FOR OUR ENTIRE TEAM AND FOR NOW
I'M BRIAN WILLIAMS.
NBC NEWS IN OUR LOS ANGELES
BUREAU.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
>>> WE'LL TELL YOU HOW LONG
HE'LL BE IN PRISON.
>> ALSO, CONGRESS ISSUES A
SCATHING REPORT AND ALLEGATIONS
THAT WILL HAVE CEO TIM COOK
TESTIFYING TOMORROW.
>> THE HISTORY OF THE SHOWDOWN.
>>> THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>> WE'RE FOLLOWING BREAKING NEWS
IN THE NATION'S MIDSECTION.
UNIMAGINABLE DEVASTATION AFTER
THIS MONSTER TORNADO ROARED
THROUGH THE SUBURBS OF OKLAHOMA
CITY.
THAT TWISTER LEVELLED
NEIGHBORHOODS, SET BUILDINGS ON
FIRE AND TORE THROUGH TWO
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, ONE SUFFERING
A DIRECT BLOW.
AT LEAST 51 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
KILLED SO FAR.
MUCH OF THE SUBURB IS IN RUINS
THIS EVENING.
MOORE LOCATED JUST SOUTH OF
OKLAHOMA CITY.
THE MAYOR SAYS THE CITY LOOKS
LIKE A DEBRIS FIELD.
WANT TO SHOW YOU SOME CELL PHONE
VIDEO OF SOME OF THE
DESTRUCTION.
RIGHT NOW, FIRST RESPONDERS ARE
SEARCHING 30 SQUARE MILES OF
WRECKAGE FOR ANY SURVIVORS.
THE TORNADO WAS AT LEAST A MILE
WIDE, TOUCHING DOWN FOR NEARLY
AN HOUR, TEARING UP EVERYTHING
IN ITS PATH.
>> SEEMS LIKE THE MOVIE TWISTER,
THERE WAS HORSES AND STUFF
FLYING EVERYWHERE.
IT'S UNDES