AND ALSO, THURSDAY.
>> ALL RIGHT, ONE LAST LOOK AT
THE RIM FIRE.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
"THE NIGHTLY NEWS" IS NEXT.
>> BYE-BYE, SEE YOU AT 6:00.
READY TO STRIKE?
THE BIG DEBATE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE OVER WHAT TO DO ABOUT
SYRIA.
>>> PLUS, AN NBC NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
A DOCTOR ON THE FRONT LINES
THERE TELLING US WHAT HE SAYS
IS REALLY GOING ON.
>>> STATE OF EMERGENCY.
IN CALIFORNIA, TONIGHT AN
OUT-OF-CONTROL WILDFIRE THE SIZE
OF DENVER NOW RAGING INSIDE OF
YOSEMITE.
>>> PLUS, A FREAK HAILSTORM AND
NOW THE THREAT OF FLASH FLOODS.
A WILD WEEKEND AHEAD FOR
MILLIONS.
>>> JUDGMENT DAY FOR THE ARMY
MAJOR ACCUSED OF A MASSACRE AT
FT. HOOD.
THE DEADLIEST MASS MURDER ON A
BASE IN U.S. HISTORY.
>>> AND GIFT OF TIME.
THERE'S NEVER ENOUGH OF IT.
AND WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF
SUDDENLY YOU HAD THE TIME TO DO
ALL OF THE THINGS YOU REALLY
WANT?
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>> FROM NBC NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS
IS "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH BRIAN
WILLIAMS.
>> GOOD EVENING.
BRIAN IS OFF TONIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
>>> THERE IS WORD TONIGHT THE
PENTAGON IS DRAWING UP MILITARY
OPTIONS TO RESPOND TO THIS
WEEK'S ATROCITIES IN SYRIA, AS
THE WHITE HOUSE COMES UNDER
INCREASING PRESSURE TO ACT.
THOSE HORRIBLE IMAGES OF
LIFELESS CIVILIANS KILLED BY
WHAT THE REBELS SAY WERE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS
HAS SPARKED INTERNATIONAL
OUTRAGE.
AS THE U.S. OFFICIALS ARE TRYING
TO CONFIRM THE NATURE OF THE
ATTACK, NBC NEWS HAS SPOKEN TO
ONE OF THE DOCTORS ON THE GROUND
TREATING THE VICTIMS.
HE SAYS THE WORLD IS IGNORING
THEM.
LET'S GET RIGHT TO CHUCK TODD AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
CHUCK, IRAQ, AFGHANISTAN.
IS AMERICA ABOUT TO GET INVOLVED
IN SYRIA?
>> Reporter: WELL, LESTER, IT
LOOKS LIKE IN SOME FORM.
THE PRESIDENT SEEMS TO BE
LEANING EVERY ON SENDING SOME
SORT OF STRIKE.
THE QUESTION IS, WHAT DOES THAT
MILITARY OPTION LOOK LIKE?
RIGHT NOW THAT'S UNCLEAR AND THE
PRESIDENT'S CLOSEST ADVISERS
ARE DIVIDED ON THE OPTIONS THAT
ARE IN FRONT OF THEM.
IT IS THESE HEART-WRENCHING
IMAGES OUT OF SYRIA,
LIFELESS BODIES, MANY OF THEM
CHILDREN, ALLEGEDLY
VICTIMS OF BRUTAL CHEMICAL
WEAPON ATTACKS THAT ACCELERATED
THE DEBATE IN WASHINGTON.
>> WE ARE RIGHT NOW GATHERING
INFORMATION ABOUT THIS
PARTICULAR EVENT.
WHAT WE HAVE SEEN INDICATES THAT
THIS IS CLEARLY A BIG EVENT OF
GRAVE CONCERN.
>> Reporter: JUST HOW GRAVE
BECOMING MORE CLEAR TONIGHT.
ANN CURRY SPOKE WITH A DOCTOR
INSIDE SYRIA TREATING SOME OF
THOSE VICTIMS.
FEARING FOR HIS OWN LIFE, HE
WOULD NOT GO ON CAMERA.
>> DIED VIOLENTLY WHILE SLEEPING
AND DIED HUNGRY.
>> DOCTOR, AFTER THIS
EXPERIENCE, WHAT IS YOUR MESSAGE
TO THE OUTSIDE WORLD?
>> CHEMICAL WEAPONS IS A SHAME
ON THE FACE OF HUMANITY.
I CAN'T IMAGINE THAT THE
INTERNATIONAL COMMUNITY CANNOT
DO ANYTHING EXCEPT MEETING AND
PROMISING.
IS THIS THE TRUTH?
IS THIS REAL?
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT IS
CONSIDERING A VERY NARROW RANGE
OF MILITARY OPTIONS.
BOOTS ON THE GROUND OR A NO-FLY
ZONE, BOTH ARE OUT OF THE
QUESTION.
WHAT IS ON THE TABLE, LIMITED
AIR STRIKES, MOST LIKELY CRUISE
MISSILES LAUNCHED FROM NAVY
DESTROYERS TARGETING
KEY ASSAD MILITARY
COMMAND POSTS AND WHILE THE U.S.
AND WHILE THE U.S.
IS STILL GATHERING EVIDENCE,
EMOTIONS ARE HIGH.
>> THIS IS QUITE POWERFUL AND
CLEARLY IT'S SOMETHING THAT HAS
NOT BEEN FAKED.
RELATIONSHIP THE PRESIDENT
SAID REPEATEDLY THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS BY BASHAR
AL ASSAD WOULD CROSS THE RED
LINE.
AND IT IS THE PUBLIC PLEDGE
COUPLED WITH THE HORRIFIC
PICTURES THAT PROMPTED SENIOR
OFFICIALS TO CONSIDER SPECIFIC
MILITARY RESPONSES, EVEN AS THE
PRESIDENT PREACHES CAUTION.
>> SOMETIMES WHAT WE HAVE SEEN
IS THAT FOLKS WILL CALL FOR
IMMEDIATE ACTION, JUMPING INTO
STUFF THAT DOES NOT TURN OUT
WELL.
>> Reporter: BUT DEMAND TO DO
SOMETHING IS GROWING.
>> WHEN DOES THE UNITED STATES,
WITH VERY LITTLE COST, STAND UP
FOR THESE PEOPLE?
>> Reporter: ONE PENTAGON
OFFICIAL TOLD NBC'S JIM
MIKLASZEWSKI, IF THE PRESIDENT
WANTS TO SEND A MESSAGE, WE ARE
GOOD AT SENDING MESSAGES.
BUT IF HE WANTS REGIME CHANGE,
WE'RE NOT ABLE TO DO THAT
EASILY.
KEY PRESIDENTIAL AIDES ARE SPLIT
OF HOW TO RESPOND.
AS THE INTERNAL DEBATE
ABOUT SYRIA HAS
DEVELOPED OVER MONTH,
NATIONAL SECURITY ADVISER
SUSAN RICE AND
AND DENIS McDONOUGH HAVE URGED
AGGRESSIVE ACTION.
DEMPSEY EXPRESSED RELUCTANCE.
SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN KERRY
INITIALLY AGGRESSIVE AND
SOFTENED UNTIL THE LATEST
PICTURES EMERGED AND TODAY IS
ADVOCATING AN AGGRESSIVE
RESPONSE.
BUT NOTHING HAPPENS UNTIL THERE
ARE TWO THINGS THAT ARE
DETERMINED.
NUMBER ONE, THAT THE U.S. GETS
ACTUAL PROOF THAT ASSAD USED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
THEY'RE TRYING TO DO THAT AND,
SECOND, THEY NEED TO HAVE A
LEGAL JUSTIFICATION.
LESTER, FOR INSTANCE, IN LIBYA,
THERE WAS A U.N. RESOLUTION TO
ENFORCE.
HERE IN SYRIA RIGHT NOW, THERE
IS NOTHING LIKE THAT ON THE
TABLE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
CHUCK TODD LEADING US OFF
TONIGHT.
THANKS.
>>> NOW TO THE WAR AT HOME AND
THE SHIFTING BATTLE FRONT IN
THIS SEASON OF WILDFIRES.
TONIGHT, THE MASSIVE
MOBILIZATION OF EQUIPMENT AND
MANPOWER WE HAVE BEEN WITNESSING
ACROSS THE WEST THE LAST FEW
WEEKS IS ON THE MOVE TO
CALIFORNIA AND WHAT HAS NOW
BECOME THE COUNTRY'S MOST
DANGEROUS WILDFIRE.
OFFICIALS SAY THE BLAZE BEING
FOUGHT AT THE EDGE OF YOSEMITE
HAS TAKEN TOP PRIORITY HAVING
JUST EXPLODED IN SIZE SINCE OUR
REPORT LAST NIGHT.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER IS THERE.
HE IS SURVEYING THE DESTRUCTION
FOR US.
MIGUEL, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER, GOOD
EVENING.
THE MOONSCAPE HERE SPREADS FOR
MILES.
THIS FIRE IS MASSIVE.
SO FAR MORE THAN 106,000 ACRES
HAVE BEEN CHARRED, AND THE FIRE
IS GROWING LARGER AND LARGER
LIVE
TO PUT THAT INTO PERSPECTIVE THE
BURN ZONE IS THREE TIMES THE
CITY OF SAN FRANCISCO.
AND TODAY THE BLAZE IS MOVING IN
MULTIPLE DIRECTIONS.
THE INFERNO HAS ALREADY CREPT IN
TO YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
FOR NOW HAVE IT REMAINS SOME 20
MILES AWAY FROM YOSEMITE VALLEY,
ONE OF THE COUNTRY'S GREATEST
TREASURES.
A WALL OF FLAMES, THE RIM FIRE
IS ON THE RUN IN NEARLY
INACCESSIBLE TERRAIN.
IT SHOWS NO SIGN OF SLOWING
DOWN.
OVERNIGHT, QUADRUPLING IN SIZE,
THE INFERNO IS NOW CLOSING IN ON
165 SQUARE MILES.
>> THE BIGGEST CHALLENGE IS THE
FIRE ITSELF.
I MEAN, IT'S MAKING ITS OWN
WEATHER.
THE 40,000-FOOT COLUMNS ARE
JUST UNREAL.
>> Reporter: WHIPPING ACROSS
DRIED OUT HILLS, WHIPPED BY
GUSTY CANYON WINDS, THE
CALIFORNIA GOVERNOR HAS DECLARED
A STATE OF EMERGENCY, OPENING
THE DOOR FOR ADDITIONAL HELP.
>> WE ARE REACHING OUT.
CANADA OFFERED UP FIVE OF THEIR
CREWS TODAY.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN 2,000
FIREFIGHTERS ARE HERE, BUT THEY
ARE LOSING GROUND.
EVEN THE AIR ATTACKS CAN'T SLOW
THIS BLAZE.
>> IF YOU WATCH THOSE TREES
SPONTANEOUSLY BURST, IT'S NOT
1, IT'S 10, 15 OF THEM, IT IS
PRETTY FRIGHTENING.
>> Reporter: WE FOUND STRIKE
TEAM CHARLIE, THE TACTICAL UNIT
OF 16, TRYING TO DEFEND THEIR
HOMETOWN.
WHEN CONDITIONS TURN IN
FIREFIGHTERS' FAVOR, LIKE THE
WIND RIGHT NOW, THEY ARE ABLE TO
SET BACKFIRES TO MAKE THIS BLAZE
CLOSE IN ON ITSELF TO SUFFOCATE
ITSELF OUT.
THE WORK SHIFT WILL LAST 36
HOURS, THEN A BREAK WHERE THEY
WILL SLEEP IN THE DIRT.
>>YOU GET PRETTY TIRED, BUT
IT'S WHAT YOU HAVE TO DO.
>> Reporter: SAFETY FIRST, THIS
IS DANGEROUS, EVEN DEADLY WORK.
>> WHY DIDN'T YOU PUT
FIREFIGHTERS DOWN THERE AND I
SAY, WHY DIDN'T YOU PUT YOUR
CHILDREN DOWN THERE?
WOULD YOU?
>> Reporter: EVACUATIONS
CONTINUE IN TOWNS NEAR YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK.
4500 HOMES ARE THREATENED.
ONE CAMPGROUND IS NOW BEING
CLOSED.
BUT IN THE ICONIC YOSEMITE
VALLEY, 20 MILES AWAY, TOURISTS
ENJOY VIEWS OF HALF DOME.
>> AWESOME.
>> GORGEOUS.
WE WERE COMING TO YOSEMITE NO
MATTER WHAT HAPPENS.
>> Reporter: STILL, THERE ARE
WARNING SIGNS EVERYWHERE.
MOTHER NATURE'S BEAUTY IS
THREATENED BY HER FURY.
TONIGHT, FIRE OFFICIALS TELL US
SEVERAL COMMUNITIES ARE IN
IMMEDIATE DANGER.
AS A MATTER OF FACT, THIS
AFTERNOON, THEY ARE WORRIED THEY
WILL LOSE HOMES.
THIS BLAZE IS ROUGHLY 2%
CONTAINED AND COST $5 MILLION TO
FIGHT SO FAR.
LESTER?
>> MIGUEL, THANKS.
PUTTING THIS ALL IN PERSPECTIVE
FOR US.
>>> THE FIRE DANGER CONTINUES IN
TO THE WEEKEND ACROSS A HUGE
PART OF THE COUNTRY WHERE
SUDDENLY IT IS LIKE THE WILD,
WILD WEST.
A MASSIVE DUST STORM, A FREAK
HAILSTORM AND NEW FLASH FLOOD
WARNINGS TONIGHT, ALL HITTING AT
ONCE.
FOR MORE ON THAT, WE GO TO
METEOROLOGIST JIM CANTORE AT
WEATHER CHANNEL HEADQUARTERS.
HI, JIM.
>> HEY, LESTER.
HOW ARE YOU DOING?
YOU KNOW, THE IMPORTANT THING
ABOUT CALIFORNIA RIGHT NOW, WE
HAVEN'T EVEN GOTTEN INTO WHAT IS
KNOWN AS THE SANTA ANA SEASON
FOR SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA.
SO YOU DON'T SEE MANY RED DOTS.
IN THROUGH HERE.
ALL OF THESE DOTS REPRESENT ALL
OF THE LARGE FIRES
OUT THERE,
THE DOZENS OF LARGE FIRES OUT
THERE.
BUT AS WE GET IN TO THIS
WEEKEND, A DEEP SURGE OF
TROPICAL MOISTURE WILL COME
NORTH, ACROSS THE WEST.
IT WON'T GET IN THE FIRE ZONES,
UNFORTUNATELY.
IT MAY HELP A COUPLE OF THESE,
BUT WE DON'T THINK IT WILL HELP
MANY.
LOOK AT THIS.
LOCALLY 2 TO 3 INCHES OF RAIN.
YOU MAY NOT THINK THAT IS MUCH
BUT THERE ARE SOME PLACES IN
CALIFORNIA AND ARIZONA THAT GET
2 TO 3 INCHES IN A YEAR, SO
THIS IS A TREMENDOUS FLOOD
THREAT FOR THE WEST.
LET ME SHOW YOU THE KIND OF
WEATHER THAT ACCOMPANIES
MOISTURE ONCE YOU GET IT INTO
THE WEST.
LITTLETON, COLORADO, THIS
IS A STORM THAT GOT
UP TO EIGHT TO TEN MILES HIGH.
INSTEAD OF PRODUCING RAIN, WHEN
IT COLLAPSED, IT PRODUCED HAIL
AND TONS OF HAIL, ENOUGH IT HAD
TO BE REMOVED BY SNOWPLOWS IN
LITTLETON, COLORADO.
OFF TO YUMA, ARIZONA, NO RAIN OR
NO HAIL HERE.
WE'RE ACTUALLY TALKING
ABOUT DUST THAT FELL AND WAS
PUSHED FROM THESE STORMS BECAUSE
BASICALLY AS THESE STORMS
COLLAPSE, THE AIR BELOW IT IS
TOO DRY.
SO AS WE GO HURRICANELESS IN THE
ATLANTIC BASIN, A SERIOUS
TROPICAL FLOOD THREAT FOR THE
WEST THIS WEEKEND AND BEYOND.
>> JIM CANTORE, THANKS.
>>> ARMY MAJOR NIDAL HASAN, THE
FORMER ARMY PSYCHIATRIST ON
TRIAL FOR A SHOOTING RAMPAGE AT
FT. HOOD HAS BEEN FOUND GUILTY
BY A MILITARY JURY.
IT DIDN'T TAKE LONG.
LESS THAN SEVEN HOURS OF
DELIBERATIONS OVER TWO DAYS.
NBC'S MARK POTTER WAS AT FT.
HOOD, TEXAS, TONIGHT WITH MORE.
MARK, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
LESTER.
THE TRIAL THAT WAS EMOTIONAL FOR
THE VICTIMS' FAMILIES TOOK THREE
WEEKS.
IN FEWER THAN SEVEN HOURS, THE
JURY FOUND NIDAL HASAN GUILTY OF
ALL CHARGES.
[ SIRENS ]
THE VERDICT COMES NEARLY FOUR
YEARS AFTER THE SHOOTING RAMPAGE
AT A FT. HOOD MEDICAL PROCESSING
CENTER.
MAJOR NIDAL HASAN WHO ADMITTED
HE WAS THE GUNMAN WAS FOUND
GUILTY OF ALL 13 COUNTS OF
PREMEDITATED MURDER AND 32
COUNTS OF PREMEDITATED ATTEMPTED
MURDER.
AS THE VERDICT WAS READ IN
COURT, HASAN, ACTING AS HIS OWN
LAWYER, SHOWED NO EMOTION.
PROSECUTORS ARE SEEKING THE
DEATH PENALTY.
16 FAMILY MEMBERS REPRESENTING
THE MURDER VICTIMS WILL BE
ALLOWED TO ADDRESS THE COURT AND
HASAN.
>> I THINK IT IS ALSO IMPORTANT
THAT THESE VICTIMS FINALLY HAVE
THE OPPORTUNITY TO EXPRESS TO
THIS JURY THE MAGNITUDE
OF THE SUFFERING THAT HE
INFLICTED ON THEM AND THE WAY HE
DESTROYED THEIR LIVES.
>> Reporter: HASAN PARALYZED IN
THE SHOOTOUT PUT ON NO DEFENSE
CASE, BUT AT SENTENCING, HE IS
EXPECTED TO SPEAK.
HE HAS ALREADY SAID HE SWITCHED
SIDES TO PROTECT ISLAM AND
LEADERS OF THE TALIBAN.
>> THERE IS A RELIGIOUS,
AND A POLITICAL COMPONENT TO IT
AND IN HIS CASE,
A PERSONAL, MORAL COMPONENT TO
IT.
>> Reporter: DURING THE TRIAL,
PROSECUTORS PRESENTED 89
WITNESSES, MANY OF WHOM GAVE
GRAPHIC ACCOUNTS OF THE BLOODY
MASSACRE.
ONE TOLD OF HEARING ARMY PRIVATE
FIRST CLASS FRANCHESKA VELEZ
SCREAMING, MY BABY, MY BABY, MY
BABY BEFORE SHE WAS KILLED.
PROSECUTORS SAY HASAN
CAREFULLY PLANNED THE ATTACK AND
FIRED 150 ROUNDS INSIDE THE ARMY
MEDICAL BUILDING.
IF HASAN IS SENTENCED TO DIE AND
HIS CASE SURVIVES THE LENGTHY
APPEALS, LEGAL EXPERTS SAY HE
COULD BECOME THE FIRST SOLDIER
EXECUTED BY THE MILITARY IN MORE
THAN 50 YEARS.
LESTER?
>> MARK POTTER TONIGHT, THANKS.
>>> ALSO, A U.S. SOLDIER WHO
MASSACRED 16 AFGHAN CIVILIANS
LAST YEAR WAS SENTENCED
TODAY TO LIFE IN PRISON WITHOUT
PAROLE.
STAFF SERGEANT ROBERT BALES
PLEADED GUILTY TO AVOID THE
DEATH PENALTY.
EVEN THOUGH HE GOT THE HARSHEST
SENTENCE POSSIBLE, IT WAS
DEEPLY DISSATISFYING TO THE
AFGHAN VILLAGERS WHO WERE
WOUNDED OR LOST LOVED ONES.
SOLVE OF THEM TRAVELED NEARLY
7,000 MILES TO
WASHINGTON STATE TO MAKE SURE
JUSTICE WAS SERVED, AND TONIGHT
THEY SAY IT WAS NOT.
>>> TONIGHT THERE IS LATE WORD
FROM SAN DIEGO WHERE EMBATTLED
MAYOR BOB FILNER, FACING
ALLEGATIONS OF SEXUAL HARASSMENT
FROM AT LESAT 18 WOMEN, HAS
RESIGNED.
NBC'S JOE FRYER JOINS US WITH
DETAILS.
JOE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER, THE SAN
DIEGO CITY COUNCIL HAS VOTED TO
ACCEPT BOB FILNER'S RESIGNATION
BY A 7-0 VOTE AND THAT
RESIGNATION IS
EFFECTIVE AUGUST 30th, WHICH IS
A WEEK FROM TODAY.
AFTER THE VOTE, FILNER DID BREAK
HIS SILENCE.
HE APOLOGIZED TO ANYONE HE
OFFENDED, TO THE CITY AND HIS
EX-FIANCE BUT HE ALSO SAID HE
NEVER SEXUALLY HARASSED ANYONE
AND CALLED IT REMOVAL OF MAYOR
BY RUMOR AND INNUENDO.
>> I THINK I LET YOU DOWN.
>> Reporter: THE CITY
MET BEHIND CLOSED DOORS THIS
AFTERNOON AFTER A PUBLIC
HEARING.
OPINIONS ON ALL SIDES OF THIS
ISSUE BUT IN THE END THEY VOTED
7-0 TO ACCEPT THE RESIGNATION.
A SPECIAL ELECTION WILL NOW BE
HELD IN THE NEXT 90 DAYS TO NAME
SAN DIEGO'S NEXT MAYOR.
LESTER?
>> JOE FRYER FROM SAN DIEGO,
LATE WORD, THANKS.
>>> THE STING IS STILL AHEAD.
AUTHORITIES INFILTRATE AN
ALLEGED PLOT TO KIDNAP AND
EXECUTE POLICE OFFICERS.
TONIGHT WE'VE GOT A CLOSER LOOK
AT WHAT THE FBI CALLS A GROWING
DOMESTIC TERROR THREAT TO LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
>>> AND LATER, THE BACKLASH OVER
BATMAN.
THE BIG ANNOUNCEMENT THAT SET
OFF A FIRESTORM.
>>> A STING OPERATION IN LAS
VEGAS IS GETTING ATTENTION
BECAUSE OF AN ALLEGED PLOT TO
KILL POLICE OFFICERS IS PART OF
A NATIONWIDE MOVEMENT THAT MANY
PEOPLE MAY NOT KNOW ABOUT.
IT'S CALLED THE SOVEREIGN
CITIZEN MOVEMENT, AND THE
AMERICANS WHO ARE PART OF IT
REJECT THE AUTHORITY AND THE
COURTS THAT WILL TRY THEM.
MORE TONIGHT FROM OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE WILLIAMS.
>> Reporter: LAS VEGAS OFFICIALS
SAY THE PLAN TO DETAIN AND KILL
POLICE OFFICERS WAS HATCHED BY
TWO PEOPLE WHO CLAIM POLICE LACK
THE POWER TO MAKE ARRESTS.
AUTHORITIES CHARGED DAVID ALLEN
BRUTSCHE, AGE 42 AND DEVON
CAMPBELL NEWMAN WITH ATTEMPTED
MURDER.
>> THESE TWO INDIVIDUALS WERE
EXTREMISTS IN THEIR BELIEVES AND
WERE ACTIVELY PLOTTING TO KIDNAP
AND KILL AT LEAST ONE SOUTHERN
NEVADA POLICE OFFICER.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS SAY
THE TWO PLANNED TO FOLLOW POLICE
ON PATROL WHEN AN OFFICER MADE A
TRAFFIC STOP, THE TWO WOULD TAKE
THE POLICEMAN AWAY TO A LAS
VEGAS HOUSE WHERE THE OFFICER
WOULD BE TIED UP AND ULTIMATELY
KILLED.
NEWMAN TOLD REPORTER CHRISTINE
KIM OF NBC AFFILIATE KSNV THAT
SHE IS NOT VIOLENT.
>> I NEVER INTENDED TO HARM OR
KIDNAP ANYONE.
>> Reporter: THOUGH SHE SAID THE
POLICE OFTEN ACT WITHOUT
AUTHORITY.
>> I FEEL THAT THEY ARE GOING
FAR BEYOND WHAT THE CONSTITUTION
ALLOWS.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY THE TWO
WERE MEMBERS OF AN EXTREMIST
MOVEMENT CALLED SOVEREIGN
CITIZENS.
IT HAS ABOUT 100,000 FOLLOWERS
NATIONWIDE WHO BELIEVE THAT MOST
OF THE GOVERNMENT DOES IS
ILLEGITIMATE.
A ROUTINE TRAFFIC STOP OF A
MINIVAN THREE YEARS AGO THE
TURNED VIOLENT WHEN A FOLLOWER
OF SOVEREIGN CITIZENS
JUMPED OUT AND BEGAN SHOOTING.
WHEN IT WAS OVER, TWO OFFICERS
WERE KILLED.
>> THE SOVEREIGN BELIEVERS ARE
SO LOOPY THAT A SMALL PERCENTAGE
CANNOT CONTROL THEMSELVES AND
RESORT TO VIOLENCE AGAINST THE
POLICE OR LOCAL AUTHORITIES.
>> Reporter: THE FBI SAYS MOST
SOVEREIGN CITIZENS ARE
NONVIOLENT, MANY CHARGED WITH
TAX EVASION LIKE JAMES TURNER OF
ALABAMA SENTENCED LAST MONTH TO
18 YEARS IN PRISON.
>> YOU CAN BE A U.S. CITIZEN OR
YOU CAN BE
AN AMERICAN BUT
YOU CANNOT BE BOTH.
IT IS IMPOSSIBLE.
>> Reporter: THE TWO IN LAS
VEGAS APPEARED BRIEFLY IN COURT
TODAY CHALLENGING ITS AUTHORITY.
>> I OBJECT TO THE ENTIRE
PROCEEDINGS OF THIS COURT.
>> Reporter: BOTH REMAIN IN JAIL
UNTIL A COURT HEARING IN TWO
WEEKS.
PETE WILLIAMS, NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
AN AMERICAN LEGEND.
A PART OF SO MANY MEMORABLE
MOMENTS COMING BACK FOR ANOTHER
SEASON.
♪ AND WE DANCE ALL NIGHT AND
WE'RE ALL TOGETHER ♪
>>> THEY PERFORMED THEIR SMASH
HIT "BEST SONG EVER" IN FRONT OF
THE BIGGEST CROWD EVER TO PACK
THE PLAZA FOR A "TODAY" SHOW
CONCERT THIS MORNING.
18,000 SCREAMING FANS, MANY
OF THEM CAMPING
OUT FOR DAYS TO ROCK OUT WITH
ONE DIRECTION, INCLUDING A MOM
AND HER TWO DAUGHTERS WHO WAITED
IN LINE SINCE LAST FRIDAY.
>>> THE NEW BATMAN HAS BEEN
UNMASKED, AND THE BACKLASH OVER
THE CHOICE OF BEN AFFLECK TO
REPLACE CHRISTIAN BALE AS THE
CAPED CRUSADER HAS BEGUN.
HE WILL JOIN A LONG LIST OF
BATMEN, SOME OF THEM LOVED,
SOME OF THEM LOATHED, FROM
MICHAEL KEATON TO
ADAM WEST TO GEORGE CLOONEY, WHO
WORE WHAT CRITICS SAID WAS THE
TOO ANATOMICALLY CORRECT BAT
SUIT AND LET' JUST SAY THE
INTERNET IS DIVIDED OVER
AFFLECK'S STARRING ROLE IN THE
HIGHLY ANTICIPATED "BATMAN VS.
SUPERMAN" BLOCKBUSTER AND A
PETITION URGING THE FILMMAKERS
TO RECONSIDER.
APPARENTLY BAT FANS ARE
PASSIONATE ABOUT WHO GETS TO
PLAY THE DARK KNIGHT JUST LIKE
THERE IS ALWAYS CONTROVERSY
WHENEVER THERE IS A NEW JAMES
BOND.
>>> HE IS MORE THAN LEGENDARY.
HE IS PERHAPS THE FINEST
BROADCASTER IN BASEBALL.
>> HIGH FLY BALL INTO RIGHT
FIELD.
SHE IS GONE.
>> Reporter: YOU KNOW HIM,
THAT'S THE VOICE OF VIN SCULLY,
THE PLAY-BY-PLAY MAN FOR THE
L.A. DODGERS AND IT WAS
ANNOUNCED HE WILL BE BACK FOR A
RECORD 65th SEASON IN 2014.
WHEN SCULLY, NOW 85, MADE HIS
DEBUT WITH THE BROOKLYN DODGERS
BACK IN 1950, NO ONE ON HIS
BLOCK EVEN HAD A TELEVISION.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, TIME OFF, A LOT OF IT,
WITH PAY.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO IF YOUR BOSS
GAVE YOU THAT GIFT?
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, WHILE MOST
OF US HERE HAVE SPENT THE SUMMER
WORKING, SAY FOR MAYBE A WEEK OR
TWO OF VACATION, A GROUP OF
CO-WORKERS IN MINNEAPOLIS HAVE
SPENT THEIR SUMMER AWAY FROM THE
OFFICE DOING WHAT THEY LOVE.
AND HERE'S THE CLINCHER, AT FULL
PAY.
BOYD HOOVER, A
REPORTER AT OUR NBC AFFILIATE IN
MINNEAPOLIS, KARE-TV
HAS MORE ON A PRECIOUS GIFT,
TIME OFF.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER SUMMER
RACING BY.
SO MANY PLANS, SO LITTLE TIME.
>> THIS IS CREEPING TIME.
>> Reporter: BUT FOR JANIE
WALDREN, THIS SUMMER IS
DIFFERENT.
>> BLOWN AWAY, MY NEIGHBOR GOES,
DID YOU WIN THE LOTTERY OR
SOMETHING AND I'M LIKE KIND OF.
I SORT OF DID.
I WON THE TIME LOTTERY.
>> I THINK PEOPLE WERE STUNNED
MORE THAN ANYTHING ELSE.
>> Reporter: STEWART D' ROZARIO
IS JANIE'S BOSS AT BARRY
D'ROZARIO MURPHY.
AFTER A LULL,
THE AGENCY GATHERED WORKERS AND
GAVE THEM TIME.
>> YOU HAVE 500 HOURS OF YOUR
LIFE BACK.
AND FIGURE OUT WHAT YOU ARE
PASSIONATE ABOUT AND GO AND DO
IT.
>> COME ON, JAKE.
>> Reporter: KIM SCHMIDT GREW UP
WANTING A HORSE SHE NEVER GOT.
SHE SPENT HER 500 PAID HOURS
VOLUNTEERING AT A HORSE SHELTER.
>> HI, HOW ARE YOU?
SO WHY NOW?
IT'S BECAUSE I HAD THE
OPPORTUNITY AND BECAUSE I WAS --
IT WAS -- THE
THE OPPORTUNITY WAS PUSHED ON
ME.
>> Reporter: PUSHED ON ALL 18 OF
THEIR EMPLOYEES WHO SPENT THE
SUMMER TRAVELING, MAKING MUSIC
AND PUTTING PAINT TO CANVAS.
STEVE COMMUTES FROM MINNESOTA TO
SEATTLE.
>> I'M ON MY DECK.
>> Reporter: INSTEAD STAYED HOME
FOR THE SUMMER RECORDING MOMENTS
WITH HIS CHILDREN.
>> MY PROJECT IS BASICALLY
REPLACING "I WISH I HAD" WITH "I
DID."
>> IT'S A DREAM.
>> Reporter: WHILE TALIA MOLDED
HER DAUGHTERS INTO HER FIRST
SCULPTURE.
>> THE TRUST PEOPLE TO DO
SOMETHING WITH THIS TIME.
>> Reporter: A FEW DAYS BACK
THEIR 500 HOURS ENDED.
THE RACE OF COMMERCE BACK ON.
>> A GROWING PERIOD.
>> Reporter: BUT SCATTERED
THROUGHOUT THE OFFICE ARE SUBTLE
REMINDERS.
>> GOT A LITTLE BLISTER.
>> Reporter: OF A SUMMER
LANDSCAPING A YARD.
>> VERY ROUGH RIGHT THERE.
>> Reporter: TENDING HORSES.
>> THAT IS UNDERWATER.
>> Reporter: AND MAKING MEMORIES
WITH KIDS.
>> MY HOPE IS NOW THEY WILL
BACK, PEOPLE WILL REALIZE THE
THINGS YOU WANTED TO DO YOU
COULD ALWAYS BE DOING AND FIND A
PLACE FOR IN YOUR LIFE.
>> Reporter: DAY AFTER DAY WE
LET THE SUN GO DOWN ON OUR
DREAMS BECAUSE WE CAN'T TAKE
TIME.
MAYBE IT'S TIME TO START GIVING.
BOYD HOOVER FOR
NBC NEWS, MINNEAPOLIS.
>> AND OUR THANKS TO BOYD AND
OUR FRIENDS AT KARE-TV
FOR BRINGING US THAT REPORT.
THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR THIS
FRIDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
I'LL SEE YOU LATER ON
"DATELINE," BUT FOR NOW, GOOD
NIGHT AND HAVE A GREAT WEEKEND.
>>> NBC BAY AREA NEWS STARTS
NOW.
>>> THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I'M TERRY McSWEENEY.
>> WE BEGIN WITH THE DEVELOPING
STORY, THE ASSAULT FROM THE AIR
TO CONTROL A MASSIVE FIRE THAT
HAS NOW ENCROACHED INTO YOSEMITE
NATIONAL PARK.
WANT TO SHOW YOU THE VIEW OF THE
RIM FIRE NOW BURNING FOR SIX
DAYS, CHARRING MORE THAN 165
SQUARE MILES.
THIS IS THE VIEW FROM THE GROUND
NOW WHERE THE INFERNO IS
INTENSE.
THE FLAMES HAVE NOW PUSHED INTO
THE PARK.
AND WHILE THE PARK IS SAFE FOR
NOW, CLOSE TO 5,000 HOMES ARE IN
THE LINE OF FIRE.
NBC JODI HERNANDEZ IS LIVE FROM
GROVE LAND.
SHE JOINS US NOW.
>> Reporter: JESSICA, THAT FIRE
IS A MONSTER.
NUMEROUS FIREFIGHTERS SAY THEY
HAVE NEVER SEEN ANYTHING QUITE
LIKE THIS.
AS YOU LOOK OVER THIS RING YOU
CAN SEE ALL THIS SMOKE COMING
UP.
THAT IS WHERE THE FIRE IS
BURNING HOT AND HEAVY TONIGHT.
WE ARE TOLD IT IS WALL TO WALL
FLAMES OUT THERE. AND AS OF
RIGHT NOW, THIS FIRE IS EXPECTED
TO JUST KEEP ON GROWING.
>> THIS FIRE IS VERY DYNAMIC,
AND THIS FIRE DOES HAVE A MIND
OF ITS OWN.
THE RESOURCES HERE HAVE DOUBLED.
AND RIGHT NOW, WE'RE AT 105,000
ACRES, PLUS.
AND WE'VE GOT OVER 2,000
PERSONNEL HERE FIGHTING THE
FIRE.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN BURNING
FOR SIX DAYS NOW, BUT THE RIM
FIRE'S NOT SHOWING ANY SIGN OF
SLOWING DOWN.
>> YOU'VE GOT TERRAIN.
YOU'VE GOT THE HEAT, THE TRY
CONDITIONS.
IT