DEVAL PATRICK DOES WHAT NO
GOVERNOR IN MODERN U.S. HISTORY
HAS EVER DONE.
HE ORDERS NEARLY A MILLION
PEOPLE TO STAY HOME.
THE GREATER BOSTON AREA
SHUT DOWN.
HEAVILY ARMED OFFICERS IN
WATERTOWN SEARCHED FOR THE
SUSPECT, HOUSE TO HOUSE.
RESIDENTS TRAPPED IN THEIR
HOMES, BUT ANXIOUS TO TALK,
COMMUNICATE BY PHONE, TEXT AND
THE INTERNET.
>> ALL DAY LONG, WE JUST KEPT
LOOKING AT EACH OTHER, MY
HUSBAND AND I, SAYING, IS THIS
REALLY HAPPENING?
AND WE'RE WATCHING THE TV AND IT
JUST FELT LIKE WE WERE INSIDE
THIS STRANGE NIGHTMARE.
>> 6:08 P.M.
OFFICIALS TELL RESIDENTS THE
IMMINENT THREAT IS OVER AND
THEY'RE FREE TO LEAVE THEIR
HOMES.
>> WE DO NOT HAVE AN
APPREHENSION OF OUR SUSPECT THIS
AFTERNOON, BUT WE WILL HAVE ONE.
>> Reporter: NO ONE COULD HAVE
GUESSED HOW QUICKLY THAT WOULD
HAPPEN.
[ GUNFIRE ]
6:55 P.M.
47 MINUTES AFTER THE ORDER WAS
LIFTED, SHOTS FIRED.
POLICE CONVERGED ON A HOUSE A
HALF MILE FROM WHERE THEY HAD
LAST SEEN THE SUSPECT MORE THAN
16 HOURS EARLIER.
WATERTOWN RESIDENT
DAVE HENNEBERRY HAD SEEN
SOMETHING SUSPICIOUS IN THE BOAT
IN HIS BACKYARD.
>> HE LOOKS INSIDE JUST UNDER
THE TARP, SEES A SMALL POOL OF
BLOOD AT THAT POINT.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST 12 MORE
SHOTS ARE FIRED AS S.W.A.T.
TEAMS AND A POLICE HELICOPTER
TAKE UP POSITIONS AROUND AND
ABOVE THE BOAT.
NEW PICTURES RELEASED BY
MASSACHUSETTS STATE POLICE TODAY
SHOW WHAT THEY SAY IS THE
SUSPECT HIDING IN THE BOAT.
UNDER COVER OF DARKNESS, A
NEGOTIATOR IS RUSHED TO THE
SCENE.
AND MUCH TO THE RELIEF OF THE
NATION, AT 8:45 P.M., THE
SUSPECT IS CAPTURED.
TONIGHT, THE AREA AROUND THE
BOAT AND THE BOAT ITSELF REMAIN
SEALED OFF BY POLICE.
LESTER?
>> KERRY SANDERS, THANKS.
>>> AND WHILE THE CRISIS IS
OVER, THE INVESTIGATION OF WHAT
MOTIVATED THE SUSPECTS IS JUST
BEGINNING.
NBC'S NATIONAL INVESTIGATIVE
CORRESPONDENT, MICHAELIS
ISAKOFF, HAS SPENT THE DAY
LOOKING INTO THE MATTER.
>> INVESTIGATORS ARE INTENSELY
FOCUSED ON THE BACKGROUND OF THE
TSARNAEV BROTHERS AND WHAT DROVE
THEM TO TERRORISM.
MEANWHILE, FEDERAL PROSECUTORS
ARE PREPARED TO FILE CRIMINAL
TERRORISM CHARGES THAT COULD
CARRY THE DEATH PENALTY AGAINST
THE SURVIVING 19-YEAR-OLD
SUSPECT.
THE YOUNGER SUSPECT, DZHOKHAR
TSARNAEV, CAPTURED LIVE LAST
NIGHT, IS UNDER GUARD AT A
BOSTON HOSPITAL.
FEDERAL AGENTS ARE WAITING TO
QUESTION HIM.
AS SOON AS HIS MEDICAL CONDITION
ALLOWS, ABOUT WHETHER HE HAD ANY
ACCOMPLICES OR OVERSEAS
CONNECTIONS.
AUTHORITIES BELIEVE HIS OLDER
BROTHER, TAMERLAN, KILLED IN A
GUN BATTLE EARLY FRIDAY MORNING
WHILE WEARING EXPLOSIVES
STRAPPED TO HIS CHEST, MAY HAVE
INSTIGATED THE PLOT AND
PERSUADED DZHOKHAR TO JOIN HIM,
BUT WHY?
THE BROTHERS ORIGINALLY FROM
CHECHNYA, WERE RAISED IN THE
U.S., LIVING IN THE SAME HOUSE,
AND SEEMED TO FIT IN.
BOTH WERE ATHLETIC.
DZHOKHAR, A WRESTLER, AND
TAMERLAN, A BOXER.
WHO HOPED TO BE ON THE U.S.
OLYMPIC TEAM.
BUT IN RECENT YEARS, TAMERLAN
HAD CHANGED AND BECAME
RADICALIZED, ACCORDING TO HIS
UNCLE, WHO SAYS HE THEN SPOKE TO
A FAMILY FRIEND.
>> HE SAID THERE IS SOMEONE WHO
BRAINWASHED HIM, SOME NEWLY
CONVERT TO ISLAM.
>> Reporter: IN 2011, RUSSIAN
INTELLIGENCE, CONCERNED ABOUT
THE THREAT OF CHECH KNOWIAN
TERRORISM ASKED THE FBI TO
INVESTIGATE TAMERLAN,
BASED ON INFORMATION THAT HE WAS
A FOLLOWER OF RADICAL ISLAM AND
THAT HE HAD CHANGED DRASTICALLY
SINCE 2010, ACCORDING TO AN FBI
STATEMENT.
THE FBI SAYS A CHECKED
DATABASES, INTERVIEWED TAMERLAN
AND FAMILY MEMBERS, BUT QUOTE
DID NOT FIND ANY TERRORISM
ACTIVITY, DOMESTIC OR FOREIGN.
THE FBI SAYS IT ASKED THE
RUSSIANS FOR MORE, BUT NEVER GOT
ANSWERS.
>> WITHOUT ANY STRONG DEROGATORY
INFORMATION, THE FBI WOULD STILL
BE LIMITED IN WHAT IT COULD DO.
>> Reporter: IN JANUARY, 2012,
TAMERLAN FLEW TO RUSSIA FOR SIX
MONTHS.
WITHIN A MONTH OF HIS RETURN,
IN AUGUST 2012, TAMERLAN SET UP
THIS YOUTUBE ACCOUNT FULL OF
ISLAMIE JIHADI POSTINGS, MANY IN
RUSSIAN, REFLECTING HIS FORMER
LIFE IN CHECHNYA.
IN THIS VIDEO, A RADICAL
PROPHECY.
>> NO ONE CAN STOP THE JIHAD.
>> Reporter: HIS PARENTS SAY
THEIR SONS ARE NOT TERRORISTS
AND HAVE BEEN FRAMED BY THE FBI.
>> Translator: SOMEBODY CLEARLY
FRAMED THEM.
I DON'T KNOW WHO EXACTLY FRAMED
THEM, BUT THEY DID.
THEY FRAMED THEM AND THEY WERE
SO COWARDLY THAT THEY SHOT THE
BOY DEAD.
>> Reporter: FEDERAL AGENTS ARE
DETERMINED TO FIND OUT WHAT
MOTIVATED TAMERLAN AND HIS
BROTHER BUT CONGRESSIONALS HAVE
TOUGH QUESTIONS FOR FBI
OFFICIALS ABOUT WHETHER THEY
COULD HAVE DONE MORE TO STOP
THEM.
THE JUSTICE DEPARTMENT HAS
DECIDED TO HAVE THE YOUNGER
TSARNAEV QUESTIONED FOR THE
FIRST 48 HOURS BY A SPECIAL HIGH
VALUED INTERROGATION TEAM
WITHOUT ADVISING HIM OF HIS
RIGHTS TO COUNSEL UNDER WHAT IT
CALLS A PUBLIC SAFETY EXCEPTION,
BUT SENATOR JOHN McCAIN AND TWO
REPUBLICAN COLLEAGUES TONIGHT
SAYS THAT DOESN'T GO FAR ENOUGH.
THEY WANT TSARNAEV TREATED AS AN
ENEMY COMBATANT UNDER THE LAWS
OF WAR.
LESTER?
>> MICHAEL ISAKOFF, THANK YOU.
FOR MORE ON THE GOVERNMENT'S
ATTEMPTS TO FIND OUT WHAT
MOTIVATED THESE SUSPECTS,
WE'RE JOINED BY NBC'S CHIEF
FOREIGN AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT,
ANDREA MITCHELL.
IN OUR WASHINGTON BUREAU,
ANDREA?
>> GOOD EVENING, LESTER.
INTELLIGENCE OFFICIALS, THE FBI,
A GLOBAL SEARCH FOR WHAT
MOTIVATED TAMERLAN TSARNAEV'S
TERRORISM.
WAS IT CHECHNYAN NATIONALISM, AT
THE WHITE HOUSE TODAY, THE
PRESIDENT MET AGAIN IN THE
SITUATION ROOM WITH HIS NATIONAL
SECURITY ADVISERS.
HE WAS BRIEFED BY THE FBI
DIRECTOR AND TOP
COUNTERTERRORISM OFFICIALS AND
OTHERS FOR 0 MINUTES.
AN OFFICIAL TELLS US AFTERWARDS
THAT SO FAR, THERE IS NO
EVIDENCE OF FOREIGN INVOLVEMENT,
BUT THEY'RE LOOKING.
THEY ALSO SAY THEY ARE GETTING
GOOD COOPERATION NOW FROM
RUSSIA, WITH WHOM AS YOU KNOW
THE U.S. HAS HAD VERY ROCKY
RELATIONS OVER THE LAST FEW
YEARS.
RUSSIA'S PRESIDENT
VLADIMIR PUTIN SPOKE WITH
PRESIDENT OBAMA LAST NIGHT AND
THE TWO LEADERS ARE DISCUSSING
THE IMPORTANCE OF WORKING MORE
CLOSELY TOGETHER ON
COUNTERTERRORISM IN THE FUTURE.
THE FBI AS YOU HEARD SAID AFTER
INTERVIEWING TAMERLAN AT
RUSSIA'S REQUEST IN 2011, THEY
SOUGHT AND FAILED TO GET MORE
INFORMATION FROM RUSSIA'S
INTELLIGENCE AND STATE SECURITY
AGENCIES, SO A LOT OF QUESTIONS
STILL TO ANSWER.
DID THESE BROTHERS JOIN EXISTING
SEPARATE CHECHEN FACTIONS?
IF SO, WHY WEREN'T THEY ATTACK
ING RUSSIAN TARGETS?
WHY DID THEY GO AFTER THEIR NEW
HOMELAND, THE U.S.?
THIS IS A BIG MYSTERY.
TONIGHT THE PRESIDENT IS
COMMENDING HIS FEDERAL
OFFICIALS, ALSO STATE AND LOCAL
OFFICIALS, BUT THEY
ARE STILL ASKING WHY DID SOMEONE
WHO WAS ALREADY IN THE FBI'S
DATABASE GET THROUGH THE CRACKS.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT, ANDREA MITCHELL,
THANK YOU.
>>> THE POLICE DEPARTMENT OF
WATERTOWN WHERE THIS ALL ENDED
IS ONLY ABOUT 60 OFFICERS STRONG
AND OVER THE LAST TWO DAYS, IT
WAS TESTED IN WAYS THAT EVEN THE
BIGGEST POLICE FORCES WILL
RARELY OR EVER EXPERIENCE.
THIS AFTERNOON, I SPOKE WITH
WATERTOWN POLICE CHIEF ED DEVOE
ABOUT THE LARGER IMPLICATIONS OF
WHAT HIS OFFICERS ACCOMPLISHED.
BASED ON WHAT YOU'VE SEEN NOW,
THE WEAPONS, THE FACT THEY HAD
OTHER EXPLOSIVES, IN YOUR MIND,
DO YOU THINK THEY WERE PREPARED
TO ATTACK AGAIN SOMEWHERE ELSE?
>> OH, YOU KNOW, I DON'T KNOW
FOR SURE, BUT MY GUT TELLS ME
THAT YES.
I MEAN, IF THEY HAVE ANOTHER YOU
KNOW, PRESSURE COOKER BOMB, THEY
WEREN'T SAVING THAT FOR THE
WATERTOWN POLICE.
THEY WERE SAVING THAT FOR
SOMETHING SIMILAR TO THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
>> Reporter: YOUR OFFICERS MAY
HAVE STOPPED ANOTHER ATTACK.
>> I STRONGLY BELIEVE THAT.
>> CHIEF DEVOE SAYS HE GETS
CHOKED UP WHEN HE THINKS ABOUT
THE CHEERS AND THANKS HIS MEN
AND WOMEN GOT FROM THE CROWDS OF
GRATEFUL RESIDENTS LAST NIGHT
FOR THEIR JOB WELL DONE.
>>> THE SUSPECT IS BEING HELD
AND TREATED IN THE SAME HOSPITAL
AS SOME OF THE VICTIMS OF
MONDAY'S BOMBINGS, AND A POLICE
OFFICER WHO WAS INJURED.
KATY TUR IS AT BETH ISRAEL
HOSPITAL HERE IN BOSTON WITH
MORE ON THAT TONIGHT.
KATY?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
LESTER.
THE SUSPECT IS IN SERIOUS, BUT
STABLE CONDITION HERE AT BETH
ISRAEL AND YES, HE IS IN THE
VERY SAME HOSPITAL AS MANY OF
THE PEOPLE THE FBI SAYS HE TRIED
TO KILL.
CHEERS OF JOY, TO A MOMENT OF
SILENCE.
THE CITY OF BOSTON MAY BE
RELIEVED, BUT IT IS STILL IN
MOURNING.
FOR 8-YEAR-OLD MARTIN RICHARD,
FOR 29-YEAR-OLD KRIS.
CAMP KRYSTLE CAMPBELL, FOR BU
GRAD STUDENT LINGZI LU, AND SEAN
KOHL YEARS, THE M.I.T. POLICE
OFFICER SHOT AND KILLED IN HIS
PATROL CAR THURSDAY NIGHT, JUST
ARE 55 MINUTES BEFORE HIS SHIFT
WOULD HAVE ENDED.
>> HE WAS A GREAT YOUNG MAN.
HE WAS WISE BEYOND HIS YEARS.
HIS GOAL WAS ALWAYS TO BECOME A
POLICE OFFICER.
>> Reporter: HIS FAMILY WRITING
OUR ONLY SOLACE IS THAT SEAN
DIED BRAVELY DOING WHAT HE
COMMITTED TO DO, SERVING AND
PROTECTING OTHERS."
THEN THERE ARE THOSE STILL
FIGHTING TO SURVIVE.
OFFICIALS SAY 33-YEAR-OLD
TRANSIT OFFICER RICHARD DONOHUE
WAS SHOT MULTIPLE TIMES DURING
THE GUNFIGHT WITH THE TSARNAEV
BROTHERS IN WATERTOWN, TONIGHT,
IN SERIOUS CONDITION.
LIZ NORDEN'S TWO SONS EACH LOST
A LIMB NEAR THE FINISH LINE.
>> IT WAS A NIGHTMARE.
IT'S RUNNING BETWEEN TWO
HOSPITALS, TRYING TO BE EACH OF
THEM AS SICK AS THEY ARE OR HURT
AS THEY ARE, IT'S, I COULDN'T BE
IN BOTH PLACES AT BOTH TIMES.
IT'S A NIGHTMARE.
>> Reporter: TODAY, 31-YEAR-OLD
PAUL OPENED HIS EYES FOR THE
FIRST TIME SINCE HE LOST HIS
LEG.
>> WELL, FOR A LOUSY SITUATION,
I JUST THANK MY LUCKY STARS
THEY'RE ALIVE, SO IT'S A GREAT
DAY.
FEELS LIKE THE FIRST DAY OF MY
LIFE.
>> Reporter: LIZ NORDEN'S OTHER
SON JUST YOU GOT OUT OF
YESTERDAY ANOTHER SURGERY TODAY.
AS OF NOW, THERE ARE 53 PEOPLE
STILL IN THE HOSPITAL.
SEVEN -- THREE ARE STILL IN
CRITIC
CRITICAL CONDITION AND LESTER
THAT DOES INCLUDE A 7-YEAR-OLD
GIRL.
>> KATY TUR WITH US IN BOSTON
TONIGHT, THANK YOU.
>>> AND WHEN "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
CONTINUES ON THIS SATURDAY, AS
BOSTON BREATHES A SIGH OF
RELIEF, HEIGHTENED ALERTS OF
PUBLIC EVENTS AROUND THE COUNTRY
TODAY.
>>> AND LATER, STATES OF
EMERGENCY AS MAJOR FLOODING HITS
THE MIDWEST.
000 THE RELIEF THAT THIS
FRIGHTENING CHAPTER MAY BE OVER
HAS NOT ERASED THE SENSE OF
VULNERABILITY THAT THIS BROUGHT
ON, A REMINDER TERROR CAN STRIKE
ANYWHERE, ANYTIME, AND THE
RESPONSE WAS EVIDENT TODAY AT
PUBLIC EVENTS THROUGHOUT THE
COUNTRY.
MICHELLE FRANZEN HAS THAT STORY
FOR US TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: AT THE RUN APALOOZA
IN ASBURY PARK, RUNNERS STARTED
THE DAY WITH BOMB SNIFFING DOGS
AND POLICE PATROLS.
UNPRECEDENTED MEASURES FOR A
FOOT RACE IN THIS HISTORIC
JERSEY SHORE TOWN.
>> WE MADE SURE PUBLIC SAFETY
WAS A PARAMOUNT SITUATION HERE.
>> Reporter: ALL AROUND THE
COUNTRY, RECREATIONAL EVENTS ARE
ON PARALLEL TRACK WITH A NATION
ON GUARD.
IN CALIFORNIA AT THE ANNUAL LONG
BEACH GRAND PRIX, MORE MANPOWER
AND VIGILANCE TO HANDLE THE
170,000 SPECTATORS ATTENDING THE
CELEBRITY CHARITY RACE.
>> I DO THINK THE POLICE
PRESENCE IS NECESSARY.
>> Reporter: SECURITY EXPERTS
SAY THERE ARE NO CREDIBLE
THREATS, BUT THE BOSTON BOMBING
STRIPPED AWAY ANOTHER LAYER OF
INNOCENCE TO EVERYDAY AMERICAN
LIFE.
>> IT DOESN'T MEAN YOU CANCEL
EVENTS, BUT YOU WANT TO BE
MONITORING CROWDS.
YOU WANT TO HAVE PERHAPS MORE
DOGS, MORE UNDERCOVER AGENTS.
>> Reporter: AT MIAMI
INTERNATIONAL, A SECURITY
DIRECTOR ORDERED EVERYONE TO PAY
EVEN CLOSER ATTENTION TO THEIR
SURROUNDINGS.
>> TO BE ON THE LOOKOUT FOR ANY
SUSPICIOUS BEHAVIOR OR
UNATTENDED BAGS.
>> Reporter: OVERSEAS, LONDON
WILL DEPLOY MORE THAN 700 POLICE
OFFICERS FOR TOMORROW'S
MARATHON, THE FIRST BIG RACE
SINCE BOSTON.
>> I'VE INCREASED BY POLICING
OPERATION WITH HIGH VISIBILITY
PATROLS.
>> BACK IN NEW YORK, A CITY
USED TO BEING ON HIGH ALERT,
NYPD OFFICERS WILL BE OUT IN
FULL FORCE AT TWO RACES
TOMORROW, INCLUDING THE ANNUAL
9/11 MEMORIAL 5K.
>> WHATEVER THEY HAVE TO DO
THAT'S NECESSARY.
>> Reporter: A NEW SENSE OF
SECURITY AND A NEW NORMAL TAKING
SHAPE.
MICHELLE FRANZEN, NBC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, THE LATEST ON WHAT MAY
HAVE CAUSED THAT HUGE EXPLOSION
IN TEXAS.
MORE THAN 5,700.
>>> OVERSEAS, A RACE AGAINST
TIME IN CHINA AFTER A
DEVASTATING EARTHQUAKE KILLED AT
LEAST 157 PEOPLE AND INJURED
MORE THAN 5,700.
IT HAPPENED OVERNIGHT IN SICHUAN
PROVINCE WHERE A MASSIVE QUAKE
STRUCK FIVE YEARS AGO.
NBC'S IAN WILLIAMS NOW THE
LATEST FROM BEIJING.
>> Reporter: THE POWERFUL 6.6
MAGNITUDE QUAKE STRUCK SHORTLY
AFTER 8:00 THIS MORNING.
FOR A FULL MINUTE, IT SHOOK
TOWNS AND VILLAGES IN CHINA'S
SICHUAN PROVINCE.
THIS IN AN AREA WHERE MEMORIES
ARE STILL RAW OF A DEVASTATING
QUAKE FIVE YEARS AGO THAT KILLED
MORE THAN 90,000 PEOPLE.
THE GOVERNMENT IMMEDIATELY
DISPATCHED THOUSANDS OF SOLDIERS
AND RESCUE WORKERS TO THE SCENE.
THOUGH MANY ROADS IN THIS
MOUNTAINOUS AREA WERE BLOCKED.
IN VILLAGES NEAR THE EPICENTER,
AUTHORITIES SAID NEARLY ALL THE
BUILDINGS HAD COLLAPSED.
THERE WERE EXTRAORDINARY SCENES
AS RESCUE WORKERS SCRAMBLED TO
FREE PEOPLE TRAPPED IN THE
RUBBLE.
THERE WERE AT LEAST 700
AFTERSHOCKS.
EXCAVATORS AND HEAVY MACHINERY
ARE MOVING IN, AS WELL AS TENTS,
BLANKETS AND OTHER EMERGENCY
SUPPLIES.
CHINA'S NEW PRIME MINISTER HAS
FLOWN IN TO DIRECT THE
OPERATION.
TONIGHT, RESCUE WORKERS ARE
STILL STRUGGLING TO REACH SOME
OF THE MORE REMOTE AREAS HIT BY
THE QUAKE, AND THE NUMBER OF
CASUALTIES SEEMS CERTAIN TO
RISE.
IAN WILLIAMS, NBC NEWS, BEIJING.
>>> AN UPDATE ON ANOTHER BIG
STORY WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING THIS
WEEK, THAT HUGE EXPLOSION AT A
FERTILIZER FACILITY IN TEXAS.
THE DEATH TOLL REMAINS AT 14
WITH MORE THAN 200 PEOPLE
INJURED.
NBC'S GABE GUTIERREZ NOW THE
LATEST IN THE TOWN OF WEST,
TEXAS, TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TODAY IN WEST,
TEXAS, THE AGONIZING DRIVE HOME.
THREE DAYS AFTER THE EXPLOSION
THAT CHANGED EVERYTHING.
THIS AFTERNOON, POLICE ALLOWED
SOME RESIDENTS TO RETURN TO THE
BLAST AREA.
>> I DON'T KNOW I GOT A HOUSE
THERE.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT HOUSE IT'S
GOING TO BE, WHAT KIND OF SHAPE
IT'S IN.
>> Reporter: WITH 80 HOMES
DAMAGED OR DESTROYED, THE
PRESIDENT HAS DECLARED A STATE
OF EMERGENCY.
>> AND I WANT THEM TO KNOW THAT
THEY ARE NOT FORGOTTEN.
>> Reporter: THE DEATH TOLL
INCLUDES FIVE FIREFIGHTERS AND
FOUR EMERGENCY MEDICS.
>> IT'S PRETTY BAD.
WE'VE GOT A LOT OF FIREMEN DOWN.
>> Reporter: OFF-DUTY
FIREFIGHTER KENNY HARRIS SAW THE
INITIAL FLAMES AND RUSHED TO
HELP THE VOLUNTEER FIRE
DEPARTMENT.
>> HE WAS MY BEST FRIEND.
WE -- WE DID EVERYTHING
TOGETHER.
>> Reporter: 96-YEAR-OLD ADOLPH
LANDER HAD BEEN INSIDE A HEAVILY
DAMAGED NURSING HOME.
HE SURVIVED THE EXPLOSION, BUT
THEN HIS HEART GAVE OUT.
>> MY DAD DIED WHEN I WAS 3
MONTHS OLD, SO HE WAS THE FATHER
FIGURE IN MY LIFE.
>> Reporter: IN A WRITTEN
STATEMENT THE FERTILIZER
FACILITY'S OWNER,
SAYS WE PLEDGE TO DO EVERYTHING
WE CAN TO UNDERSTAND WHAT
HAPPENED.
ALREADY, SOME LAWMAKERS ARE
ASKING WHETHER CHEMICAL STORAGE
REGULATIONS SHOULD BE
STRENGTHENED.
>> THOSE ARE LEGITIMATE AND
APPROPRIATE QUESTIONS TO BE
ASKING.
>> Reporter: A STATE FILING LAST
YEAR SHOWS THE FERTILIZER
FACILITY HAD MORE THAN 540,000
POUNDS OF AMMONIUM NITRATE.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS ARE LOOKING
INTO WHETHER THAT AMOUNT SHOULD
RAISED RED FLAGS.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC NEWS, WEST,
TEXAS.
>>> IN PARTS OF THE MIDWEST
TONIGHT, FLOOD SEASON HAS
ARRIVED WITH A VENGEANCE,
LEADING TO AT LEAST TWO DEATHS
AND PUTTING THOUSANDS OF HOMES
AND BUSINESSES UNDER WATER.
NOT FAR FROM CHICAGO IN DES
PLAINS, THE RIVER HIT RECORD
LEVELS, FORCING DOZENS OF
EVACUATIONS AND CAUSING
FLOODINGS IN MORE THAN 700
BUILDINGS.
>>> UP NEXT HERE ON "NBC NIGHTLY
NEWS," THE SPIRIT OF BOSTON, IN
THIS CITY AND BEYOND.
>>> IN ANOTHER TIME, IT WAS THE
11-MONTH SIEGE OF BOSTON THAT
MARKED THE BEGINNING OF THE
REVOLUTIONARY WAR.
TONIGHT, THIS CITY HAS EMERGED
FROM ANOTHER SIEGE, SHOWING THE
WORLD IT WON'T BACK DOWN FROM
ANOTHER CHALLENGE IN THIS DAY
AND AGE.
NBC'S ANNE THOMPSON JOINS ME
TONIGHT WITH THE SPIRIT OF
BOSTON ALIVE AND WELL TONIGHT.
>> IT CERTAINLY IS LESTER AND
YOU KNOW HOW BOSTON
LOVES ITS TRADITIONS FROM THE
MARATHON TO THE SWAN BOATS TO
THE SONGS THEY SING AT FENWAY
PARK.
WELL, THIS WEEK, THE NATION
ADOPTED SOME OF THOSE TRADITIONS
AND IT'S HELPING THE CITY MOVE
FORWARD.
TODAY, BOSTON LOOKED THE SAME,
BUT IT IS NOT THE SAME.
CHILDREN STILL FLOCKED TO MRS.
MALLARD AND HER DUCKLINGS IN THE
PUBLIC GARDEN, BUT PARENTS ARE
NOT AS CAREFREE.
RICH AND AND YVONNE BROUGHT
2-YEAR-OLD DYLAN WITH A MIXTURE
OF RELIEF AND RESERVATION.
>> IT JUST FELT WRONG THAT THIS
HAPPENED TO US.
>> Reporter: AT FENWAY PARK --
>> GET YOUR FREE BELIEVE IN
BOSTON FLAG WITH TODAY'S
PROGRAM!
>> Reporter: GOING TO TODAY'S
RED SOX GAME WAS AN ACT OF
DEFIANCE.
>> WE DON'T BACK DOWN.
>> WE WERE ALL TALKING ABOUT
THAT LAST NIGHT, REGARDLESS OF
WHAT HAPPENS TODAY WE'RE GOING
TO COME TO THE GAME ANYWAY.
WE JUST DON'T WANT THOSE TYPES
OF ACTIVITIES TO RUN OUR LIVES.
>> Reporter: TODAY PEOPLE
WEREN'T JUST RED SOX FANS, THEY
WERE BOSTON FANS.
LIKE BO GRIFFIN WHO BROUGHT HIS
FAMILY FROM SOUTH CAROLINA.
>> BELIEVE IN EACH OTHER AND
WE CARE FOR EACH OTHER AND
BOSTON IS STRONG, IT'S SYMBOLIC
OF THAT, WHETHER WE'RE FROM
SOUTH CAROLINA OR MASSACHUSETTS.
>> Reporter: EVEN THE TEAM
ITSELF SHOWED ITS PRIDE IN THE
CITY, WEARING SPECIAL JERSEYS
THAT REPLACED RED SOX WITH
BOSTON.
>> AND NOBODY'S GOING TO
DICTATE.
STAY STRONG!
>> Reporter: BOSTON STRONG IS
NOW A RALLYING CRY ACROSS THE
COUNTRY.
AT A ROAD RACE IN ASBURY PARK,
NEW JERSEY, STILL RECOVERING
FROM SUPERSTORM SANDY.
ON THE ICONIC GOLD HELMETS OF
NOTRE DAME'S FOOTBALL TEAM
DURING HIS SPRING GAME.
AND IN MAJOR LEAGUE BALLPARKS.
FANS SANG THE RED SOX ANTHEM,
"SWEET CAROLINE," WHEN WORD
SPREAD THE SUSPECT WAS IN
CUSTODY.
LED BY NEIL DIAMOND.
♪ SWEET CAROLINE
♪ DA, DA, DA
♪ GOOD TIMES NEVER SO GOOD
♪ SO GOOD, SO GOOD, SO GOOD
>> Reporter: BUT GOOD TIMES THAT
WILL NEVER BE QUITE THE SAME.
APRIL 20th IS AN IMPORTANT DAY
IN BOSTON HISTORY.
IT'S THE DAY FENWAY PARK OPENED,
THE DAY TED WILLIAMS FIRST SWUNG
A BAT FOR THE RED SOX, AND
TODAY, IT'S THE DAY WHEN VICTORY
WAS IN MORE THAN JUST BASEBALL.
LESTER?
>> YOU WIN.
BEST ASSIGNMENT OF THE DAY.
THANKS VERY MUCH.
THAT'S "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" FOR
THIS SATURDAY.
I'M LESTER HOLT, REPORTING FROM
BOSTON.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW MORNING ON
"TODAY," THEN OF COURSE TOMORROW
NIGHT.
GOOD NIGHT, EVERYONE.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
>>> THE SEARCH FOR ANSWERS
CONTINUES TODAY IN BOSTON AFTER
THE SECOND BOMBING SUSPECT WAS
CAPTURED AS THE WORLD WATCHED.
GOOD EVENING.
I'M DIANE DWYER.
PRESIDENT OBAMA CALLED IN HIS
TEAM TODAY FOR A 90 MINUTE
MEETING IN THE SITUATION ROOM.
THEY ARE ANSWERING THE LINGERING
QUESTIONS ABOUT THE ATTACK AND
MOTIVE.
THIS PHOTOGRAPH WAS RELEASED, A
NIGHT IMAGE SHOWING THE BODY
HEAT FROM THE IS THE-YEAR-OLD
DZHOKHAR VAR NOVEMBER HIDING IN
A BOAT.
>> CRAZY TO THINK IT WAS IN THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD AND, YOU KNOW,
HAVING FACEN THE POLICE AND THAT
EVERYTHING WAS GOING TO BE OKAY.
IT'S SURREAL, VERY SURREAL.
>> I'M HAPPY WITH THE FACT THAT
EVERYBODY WAS, YOU KNOW, THEY
WERE ABLE TO CATCH THESE GUYS
QUICKLY.
>> THAT NEIGHBORHOOD IS SLOWLY
RETURNING TO NORMAL IN THE WAKE
OF A MANHUNT.
INVESTIGATORS ARE COMBING
THROUGH THE QUIET STREET WHERE
HE WAS HIDING LAST NIGHT.
THERE'S WORD HE KEPT UP WHAT
APPEARED TO BE A NORMAL LIFE
AFTER THE BOMBINGS.
WE BEGIN WITH JAY GRAY IN BOSTON
WITH NEW INFORMATION ON HOW THE
MANHUNT CAME TO AN END.
JAY?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING, THE
DAY AFTER A SEARCH THAT SHUT
DOWN AMERICA'S BIGGEST CITY,
BOSTON CAME OUT FROM BEHIND THE
LOCKED DOORS.
WE BEGIN TO LEARN MORE ABOUT HOW
THE INTENSE STAND OFF FINALLY
CAME TO AN END.
HUNDREDS OF POLICE RUSHED IN
AFTER A CALL FROM A HOMEOWNER
WHO NOTICED SOMETHING DIFFERENT
ABOUT THE BOAT IN HIS BACKYARD.
IT WAS A MASSACHUSETTS STATE
CHOPPER THAT FIRST SPOTTED
DZHOKHAR TSARNAEV.
HE WAS ALIVE AND HIDING INSIDE
THE BOAT.
WE ARE LEARNING HOW THE SEARCH
FOR THE MOST WANTED MAN IN
AMERICA FINALLY CAME TO AN END.
AGENTS RUSHING IN ENGAGED IN A
STAND OFF FOR MORE THAN 90
MINUTES.
NEGOTIATORS SHOUTED TO HIM TO
COME OUT ON YOUR OWN TERMS.
MINUTES LATER, HE WAS IN
CUSTODY.
TODAY, HE REMAINS IN SERIOUS
CONDITION IN THE HOSPITAL WHERE
AUTHORITIES SAY HE COULD BE
CHARGED FOR TERRORISM AND MURDER
AND QUESTIONED BY THE FBIs ELITE
HIGH VALUE SUSPECT INTERROGATION
TEAM.
THE FBI WILL FOCUS ON THREATS
THAT HE MIGHT BE AWARE OF.
ARE THERE OTHER DEVICES?
WERE OTHER PEOPLE WORKING IN THE
NETWORK?
>> Reporter: AS THE
INVESTIGATION CONTINUES, SO DOES
THE PUSH TOWARD NORMALCY HERE.
>> WE DON'T WANT ACTIVITIES TO
RUN OUR LIVES.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEE