FILTERS.
IT WORKS JUST LIKE SNAPCHAT.
>> A LITTLE COMPETITION FOR
SNAP.
>> FOR SURE.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP ASKED
FBI DIRECTOR COMEY TO
DROP THE INVESTIGATION
INTO MICHAEL FLYNN
ACCORDING TO A MEMO
WRITTEN BY THE FBI
DIRECTOR HIMSELF.
IS IT OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE?
A STUNNING DEVELOPMENT
AS WE COME ON THE AIR.
>>> ALSO, SECRET
INTELLIGENCE SHOCK
WAVES.
NBC NEWS HAS LEARNED
ISRAEL WAS THE SOURCE
OF THE INFORMATION
THAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
GAVE THE RUSSIANS.
THE FALLOUT FAR
REACHING FROM CAPITOL
HILL TO ALLIES ARP THE
WORLD.
>>> A BETTER NIGHT'S
SLEEP.
NEW HELP FOR MILLIONS
UNABLE TO REST EASY.
A REVOLUTIONARY DEVICE
PATIENTS SAY IS LIFE
CHANGING.
>>> AND INSPIRING
AMERICA.
TRIUMPHING OVER A
TRAGIC ACCIDENT, AN
ACROBAT SOARING TO NEW
HEIGHTS.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING TO
OUR VIEWERS IN THE
WEST.
THERE IS BREAKING NEWS
ON MULTIPLE FRONTS
TONIGHT INVOLVING
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
NEW DETAILS ABOUT THE
SENSITIVE INTELLIGENCE
THE PRESIDENT
APPARENTLY SHARED WITH
RUSSIAN DIPLOMATS IN A
MEETING LAST WEEK.
WE'LL HAVE MORE ON
THAT IN A MOMENT.
BUT FIRST TO THE NEW
BOMBSHELL THAT LANDED
ON THE WHITE HOUSE
JUST A SHORT TIME AGO.
POSSIBLE EVIDENCE THAT
THE PRESIDENT ASKED
FBI DIRECTOR JAMES
COMEY TO DROP HIS
INVESTIGATION INTO THE
PRESIDENT'S FORMER
NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER, MICHAEL
FLYNN.
FLYNN'S CONTACTS WITH
RUSSIA ARE THE SUBJECT
OF AN ONGOING FBI
PROBE THAT COMEY WAS
LEADING UP UNTIL HE
WAS FIRED BY THE
PRESIDENT A WEEK AGO.
BUT TONIGHT MULTIPLE
SOURCES CONFIRM TO NBC
NEWS THE EXIST EPENCE OF
A COMEY MEMO DETAILING
THE PRESIDENT'S
REQUEST.
LET'S GET DETAILS FROM
OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS.
>> Reporter: ACCORD
ING TO A MEMO COMEY
WROTE IN HIS OWN FILES
IN FEBRUARY PRESIDENT
TRUMP SUGGESTED COMEY
SHOULD END ANY FBI
INVESTIGATION OF
WHETHER MICHAEL FLYNN
LIED TO THE FBI WHEN
HE DENIED MEETING WITH
RUSSIA'S AMBASSADOR TO
THE U.S.
ACCORDING TO THE MEMO
THE PRESIDENT MADE HIS
COMMENT THE DAY AFTER
FLYNN STEPPED DOWN AS
NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER.
"I HOPE YOU CAN LET
THIS GO," THE
PRESIDENT SAID
ACCORDING TO THE ME
MEMO."
HE IS A GOOD GUY."
THE PRESIDENT TOLD
LESTER HOLT LAST WEEK
HE HAD HIGH REGARD FOR
FLYNN.
>> THIS MAN HAS SERVED
FOR MANY YEARS.
HE'S A GENERAL.
HE'S, IN MY OPINION, A
VERY GOOD PERSON.
>> Reporter: THE WHITE
HOUSE SAYS THIS
ACCOUNT FIRST REPORTED
BY "THE NEW YORK
TIMES" AND CONFIRMED
BY FORMER ASSOCIATES
THE OF COMEY'S IS
INCORRECT.
QUOTE, THE PRESIDENT
HAS NEVER ASKED MR.
COMEY OR ANYONE ELSE
TO END ANY
INVESTIGATION A WHITE
HOUSE OFFICIAL SAID IN
A STATEMENT.
THE WHITE HOUSE POINTS
TO A STATEMENT MADE IN
A SENATE HEARING BY
THE ACTING FBI
DIRECTOR.
ASKED IF MR. COMEY'S
FIRING AS FBI DIRECTOR
HAD INTERFERED WITH
ITS INVESTIGATIONS.
>> THE WORK OF THE MEN
AND WOMEN OF THE FBI
CONTINUES DESPITE ANY
CHANGES IN
CIRCUMSTANCE, ANY
DECISIONS.
SO THERE HAS BEEN NO
EFFORT TO IMPEDE OUR
INVESTIGATION TO DATE.
>> Reporter: FROM ALL
INDICATIONS THE
INVESTIGATION OF FLYNN
HAS NEVER STOPPED HIS
CONTACTS WITH THE
RUSSIANS.
A FEDERAL GRAND JURY
HAS ISSUED SUBPOENAS
IN THE CASE.
NONE OF THIS COMES
FROM MR. COMEY
DIRECTLY.
HE HAS YET TO SAY
ANYTHING PUBLICLY
SINCE HE WAS FIRED A
WEEK AGO TONIGHT, BUT
HE DID TELL FRIENDS
AND A FEW PEOPLE AT
THE FBI ABOUT WHAT HE
WROTE IN THAT MEMO AT
THE TIME, AND THEY'RE
THE ONES DESCRIBING IT
NOW.
AND PEOPLE AT THE FBI
STRONGLY BELIEVE THAT
COMEY WAS FIRED
BECAUSE HE WOULDN'T
SHUT DOWN THE ENTIRE
RUSSIA INVESTIGATION,
LESTER.
>> PETE, I NKNOW YOU'VE
BEEN TALKING TO LEGAL
EXPERTS AND SOURCES.
WHAT ARE THEY SAYING
ABOUT POSSIBLE
CRIMINAL ACTION HERE?
>> WELL NOT
SURPRISINGLY THEY SAY
IT ALL DEPEND.
FIRST IS TO TRY TO GET
THE ACTUAL COMEY MEMO
AND NOT RELY ON PEOPLE
WHO CAN TELL US WHAT
IT SAID TO SEE WHAT IT
SAID, THEN PERHAPS
TALK TO MR. COMEY.
IT ALL COMES DOWN TO
THE PERSON'S INTENT.
WHAT DID THE PRESIDENT
HAVE IN MIND.
DID HE ACTUALLY INTEND
TO TRY TO SHUT DOWN
THE INVESTIGATION, OR
WAS HE JUST SAYING HE
HOPED IT WOULD END.
>> PETE WILLIAMS
TONIGHT STARTING US
OFF.
THANKS.
WE WANT TO BRING IN
OUR POLITICAL
DIRECTOR, THE
MODERATOR OF "MEET THE
PRESS," CHUCK TODD.
CHUCK, WHAT DO YOU
MAKE OF ALL OF THIS?
>> Reporter: LOOK,
THIS IS A GUT CHECK
MOMENT NOW FOR
CONGRESSIONAL
REPUBLICANS.
THEY'VE ALREADY BEEN
TAKING ON A LOT OF
WATER POLITICALLY
EITHER HAVING TO
DEFEND OR DEFLECT
ACTIONS BY PRESIDENT
TRUMP, YOU KNOW, JUST
TODAY MANY REPUBLICANS
WERE NOT WANTING TO
SEE ANY CAMERAS
RUNNING AROUND CAPITOL
HILL, NOT WANTING TO
COMMENT ON THE STORY
YOU'RE ABOUT TO REPORT
ON NEXT, WHICH IS THIS
ISSUE OF THE PRESIDENT
SHARING CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION FOR THE
RUSSIANS.
THIS RAISES THE
STAKES, THOUGH, TO A
WHOLE NEW LEVEL.
THIS BECOMES THIS
INTRODUCES THE IDEA OF
OBSTRUCTION OF
JUSTICE.
IF THERE'S A MEMO, NOW
CONGRESSIONAL
REPUBLICANS EVEN
THOUGH IT'S THEIR OWN
PARTY'S PRESIDENT,
THEY'LL HAVE NO CHOICE
BUT TO START ISSUING
SUBPOENAS AND, BY THE
WAY, THE PRESIDENT
HIMSELF MADE THAT
VEILED THREAT TO
DIRECTOR COMEY, THEN
FORMER DIRECTOR COMEY,
SAYING HE'D BETTER
HOPE THERE AREN'T
TAPES.
WELL, IF THE WHITE
HOUSE'S VERSION OF
EVENTS IS TO BE
BELIEVED, THEN THE
PRESIDENT BETTER HOPE
HIS TAPES ABLE TO DO
THAT BECAUSE THIS NOW
BECOMES COMEY VERSUS
THE PRESIDENT.
AND I CAN TELL YOU
THIS RIGHT NOW, COMEY
PROBABLY HAS MORE
CREDIBILITY ON CAPITOL
HILL THAN THE
PRESIDENT.
>> ALL RIGHT, CHUCK
TODD.
APPRECIATE THE
ANALYSIS.
NOW TO THAT OTHER
MAJOR STORY YOU
REFERRED TO SWIRLING
AROUND THE WHITE
HOUSE, CONCERN OVER
THE EXTENT OF THE
INTELLIGENCE SECRETS
PRESIDENT TRUMP SHARED
WITH RUSSIAN
DIPLOMATS.
WAS THE INFORMATION
CLASSIFIED?
THE WHITE HOUSE WON'T
SAY.
HAD IT BEEN SHARED
WITH OUR ALLIES BEFORE
IT WAS GIVEN TO THE
RUSSIANS?
AGAIN, THE WHITE HOUSE
WON'T SAY.
WHAT COUNTRY GAVE THE
U.S. THE INTEL, AND
WAS THE U.S.
AUTHORIZED TO SHARE
IT?
SAME ANSWER.
THOUGH MULTIPLE
SOURCES ARE TELLING
NBC NEWS IT CAME FROM
ISRAEL.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HALLIE
JACKSON HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE WHITE HOUSE
DODGING, DEFLECTING,
BUT NOT DENYING THE
PRESIDENT SHARED
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
WITH RUSSIA AND
NEITHER IS HE.
>> WE HAD ACTUALLY A
GREAT MEETING WITH THE
FOREIGN MINISTER, SO
WE'RE GOING TO HAVE A
LOT OF GREAT SUCCESS
OVER THE NEXT COMING
YEARS.
>> Reporter: NOW NBC
NEWS HAS LEARNED THE
INTELLIGENCE HE TALKED
ABOUT CAME FROM
ISRAEL.
ACCORDING TO THREE
GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS
FAMILIAR WITH THE
MATTER NAMING THAT
COUNTRY AS THE KEY
PARTNER WHICH PROVIDED
THE ISIS-RELATED
INFORMATION.
DIPLOMATIC DYNAMITE,
JUST SIX DAYS BEFORE
THE PRESIDENT'S SET TO
VISIT JERUSALEM.
THE ISRAELI AMBASSADOR
SAYS HIS COUNTRY HAS
FULL CONFIDENCE IN OUR
INTELLIGENCE SHARING
RELATIONSHIP WITH THE
UNITED STATES.
>> I'M OBVIOUSLY
PLEASED TO SEE
AMBASSADOR DERMER'S
COMMENTS.
WE APPRECIATE THE
RELATIONSHIP THAT WE
HAVE WITH ISRAEL AND
APPRECIATE THE
EXCHANGE OF
INFORMATION THAT WE
HAVE WITH THEM.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP ACKNOWLEDGES HE
DID DISCUSSION WITH
THE RUSSIANS FACTS
PERTAINING TO
TERRORISM AND AIRLINE
FLIGHT SAFETY.
BUT "THE WASHINGTON
POST" SAYS IT WENT
FURTHER WITH THE
PRESIDENT DESCRIBING
ELEMENTS OF A
PARTICULAR PLOT BY
ISIS, NAMING THE CITY
IN IS THE ISLAMIC'S
STATE WHERE THE PA
PARTNER DETECTED THE
THREAT.
OFFICIALS WARNING THE
PAPER REVEALING THAT
WOULD JEOPARDIZE
IMPORTANT INTELLIGENCE
CAPABILITIES.
THE NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER WOULDN'T
CONFIRM SPECIFICS
TODAY BUT ARGUES THE
PRESIDENT DID NOTHING
ILLEGAL, WHICH IS
TRUE, AND, HE SAYS,
NOTHING IMPROPER
EITHER.
>> WHAT THE PRESIDENT
DISCUSSED WITH THE
FOREIGN MINISTER WAS
WHOLLY APPROPRIATE.
THAT CONVERSATION WAS
>> Reporter: TWO
INTELLIGENCE SOURCES
TELL NBC NEWS THEY'RE
NOT BUYING THAT,
WORRIED THE
PRESIDENT'S
CONVERSATION XR
COMPROMISED A KEY
SOURCE.
H.R. McMASTER SAYS THE
LEAKS ARE THE REAL
DANGER POINTING OUT
THE PRESIDENT COULD
NOT HAVE PUT SOURCES
AT RISK BECAUSE HE
HADN'T BEEN TOLD ABOUT
THEM.
>> HE WASN'T BRIEFED
ON THE SOURCE OR
METHOD OF THE
INFORMATION EITHER.
>> IT'S NOT UNUSUAL
FOR A PRESIDENT TO
CONVEY CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION TO ANOTHER
HEAD OF STATE.
BUT THAT'S USUALLY
DONE IN A SCRIPTED
WAY.
IT APPEARS THE
PRESIDENT SIMPLY DID
IT ON HIS OWN AND
WITHOUT A STRATEGY OR
SCRIPT IN HAND.
>> Reporter: THE NEW
QUESTIONS OVER
CLASSIFIED MATERIAL
VIKING GIVEN THE
PRESIDENT'S CRITICISMS
AS A CANDIDATE.
>> I DON'T THINK IT'S
SAFE TO HAVE HILLARY
CLINTON BE BRIEFED ON
NATIONAL SECURITY
BECAUSE THE WORD WILL
GET OUT.
WE CAN'T HAVE SOMEONE
IN THE OVAL OFFICE WHO
DOESN'T UNDERSTAND THE
MEANING OF THE WORD
CONFIDENTIAL OR
CLASSIFIED.
>> Reporter: NOW
ALREADY IN NEAR
PERPETUAL CRISIS
MANAGEMENT MODE, HIS
EMBATTLED TEAM'S
SCRAMBLING TO RESPOND,
RUMORS OF A STAFF
SHAKE-UP LED BY A
FRUSTRATED PRESIDENT
LEARNING ON THE JOB.
>> HE HAD BEEN A
LEADER BY FIAT
BASICALLY.
NOW HE HAS TO LEAD BY
GOVERNING, AND THAT
MEANS INVITING PEOPLE
TO BE PART OF THE
SOLUTION INCLUDING
THOSE WHO WORK FOR
HIM.
>> Reporter: SO WHERE
DOES THIS STORY GO
NEXT?
A U.S. COU
COUNTERTERRORISM
OFFICIAL EXPECTS THERE
WILL BE A DAMAGE
ASSESSMENT NOW TO
FIGURE OUT ANY FALLOUT
FOR THE INTELLIGENCE
COMMUNITY.
LESTER?
>> HALLIE JACKSON,
THANK YOU.
>>> THE FALLOUT FROM
THIS NEWS HAS BEEN
SWIFT ON CAPITOL HILL
WHERE SOME TOP
REPUBLICANS APPEAR TO
BE LOSING PATIENCE
WITH THE PRESIDENT.
WE GET THAT FROM NBC'S
KRISTEN WELKER.
>> Reporter: ALARM
BELLS ON CAPITOL HILL
TONIGHT AS MEMBERS OF
THE PRESIDENT'S OWN
PARTY BECOME
INCREASINGLY CRITICAL
OF HIM, THE SENATE'S
HIGHEST RANKING
REPUBLICAN UNLEASHING
THIS SHARP REBUKE.
>> I THINK IT WOULD BE
HELPFUL TO HAVE LESS
DRAMA EMANATING FROM
THE WHITE HOUSE.
>> Reporter: PRIVATELY
REPUBLICAN AIDES ON
CAPITOL HILL TELL NBC
NEWS THE PRESIDENT'S
LATEST CONTROVERSY IS
RAISING SERIOUS
QUESTIONS ABOUT HIS
ABILITY TO GOVERN, BUT
PUBLICLY THEY'RE NOT
YET BREAKING RANKS.
ARE YOU STARTING TO
LOSE CONFIDENCE IN
PRESIDENT TRUMP?
>> NO.
>> Reporter:
REPUBLICAN SENATOR BOB
CORKER, WHO CAMPAIGNED
WITH CANDIDATE DONALD
TRUMP, CALLING IT A
DOWNWARD SPIRAL.
CAN YOU TELL ME WHAT
YOU MEANT BY THAT?
>> I THINK I WAS --
THEY OBVIOUSLY HAVE
SOME ORGANIZATIONAL
ISSUES THAT THEY NEED
TO WORK THROUGH.
>> Reporter: AND
TONIGHT LEADERS OF THE
HOUSE AND SENATE
INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEES ARE
DEMANDING MORE
INFORMATION.
SOME SAYING THEIR
FAITH IN THE WHITE
HOUSE DEPENDS ON IT.
>> ONCE MARK AND I
HAVE AN OPPORTUNITY TO
TALK TO INDIVIDUALS
THAT WERE IN THE
MEETING, THAT WILL
EITHER CONFIRM OUR
CONFIDENCE OR POSSIBLY
SHAKE THE CONFIDENCE.
>> Reporter: IS YOUR
CONFIDENCE SHAKEN AT
ALL?
>> WE ALSO WANT TO SEE
IF THERE ARE, AGAIN,
THESE SUPPOSED
TRANSCRIPTS.
>> Reporter: THE WHITE
HOUSE PHONING
LAWMAKERS AND
DISPATCHING CIA
DIRECTOR MIME POMPEO
TO BRIEF SOME MEMBERS
OF CONGRESS TONIGHT,
BUT MANY EXPRESSING
CONCERNS THE DAMAGE IS
ALREADY DONE.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR
CONCERNS?
>> I THINK THEY'RE
OBVIOUS, RIGHT?
THE HANDLING OF
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
IS A CRITICAL THING.
>> IF IT'S ACCURATE
IT'S VERY CONCERNING.
>> Reporter: ONLY FEW
REPUBLICANS COME TO
THE PRESIDENT'S
DEFENSE.
>> I THINK IT'S
SOMETHING WAY BLOWN
OUT OF PROPORTION.
>> Reporter: SO WHAT
COULD CAUSE
REPUBLICANS TO BREAK
WITH MR. TRUMP?
>> THE WHITE HOUSE IS
UNDOUBTEDLY ON AN
UNSUSTAINABLE PATH OF
DIPPING AND DODGING
AND WEAVING CRISES
AFTER CRISES THAT THEY
CREATE.
>> Reporter: ALL OF IT
GIVING DEMOCRATS A
POLITICAL OPENING.
>> GIVEN THE GRAVITY
OF THE MATTER WE NEED
TO BE ABLE TO QUICKLY
ASSESS WHETHER OR NOT
THIS REPORT IS TRUE.
>> Reporter: AND
TONIGHT REACTION IS
POURING IN TO OUR LEAD
STORY ABOUT THE COMEY
MEMO.
THE TOP DEFENSEMMOCRAT ON
THE HOUSE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE, ADAM
SCHIFF, CALLING THAT
REPORT DISTURBING.
IF TRUE, NANCY PELOSI
CALLING IT BRAZEN, IF
TRUE.
ALL ADDING TO THE
CONSTERNATION HERE ON
CAPITOL HILL.
LESSER?
>> A LOT OF MOVING
PIECES TONIGHT,
KRISTEN.
THANK YOU.
THERE'S CONCERN OVER
HOW PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
REPORTED DISCLOSURE OF
THAT INTEL TO THE
RUSSIANS MAY IMPACT
RELATIONSHIPS WITH
AMERICA'S ALLIES.
WILL THEY NOW BE MORE
RELUCTANT TO SHARE THE
KIND OF CRUCIAL INTELL
GENERALS THE U.S. HAS
USED IN THE PAST TO
THWART TERRORIST
ACTIVITY.
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL
HAS MORE ON THAT.
>> Reporter: OCTOBER
2010.
AUTHORITIES FIND A
PRINTER CARTRIDGE
LOADED WITH EXPLOSIVES
ON A U.P.S. PLANE
THANKS TO A TIP FROM
THE SAUDIS ABOUT AN AL
QAEDA BOMBMAKER.
JUNE 2009, IRAN'S
CRITICAL EQUIPMENT
MISFIRES THE RESULT OF
A COMPUTER VIRUS
CREATED BY ISRAEL IN
PARTNERSHIP WITH THE
CIA.
APRIL 2012, A SAUDI
AND BRITISH SPY GIVES
THE CIA PLANS FOR AN
AL QAEDA BOMB DESIGNED
TO BRING DOWN A
PASSENGER PLANE.
THE FEAR NOW FOREIGN
INTELLIGENCE SERVICES
WILL NOT SHARE
TOP-SECRET PLOTS LIKE
THOSE WITH THE U.S.
BECAUSE THEY DO NOT
TRUST THE PRESIDENT OF
THE UNITED STATES TO
KEEP A SECRET.
>> THIS REINFORCES A
CONCERN THEY'VE HAD
FOR A LONG TIME BUT IT
TAKES IT TO ANOTHER
LEVEL, I THINK.
>> Reporter: TODAY
BRITAIN'S PRIME
MINISTER DEFLECTING
QUESTIONS BUT THEY SAY
THEY ARE WORRIED.
>> IT'S NOT UP TO ME
WHAT PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAYS.
>> Reporter: THE
GERMANS NOT HAPPY THE
WAY THE PRESIDENT
TREATED THEIR LEADER,
ANGELA MERKEL, NOW
ANGRY HE IS SHARING
INTELLIGENCE WITH
RUSSIA.
>> IT SENDS A VERY BAD
SIGNAL THAT PRESIDENT
TRUMP VALUES OUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH
RUSSIA MORE THAN HE
VALUES OUR
RELATIONSHIP WITH OUR
TRADITIONAL ALLIES.
>> Reporter: AND WHEN
IT COMES TO FIGHTING
ISIS AND AL QAEDA, THE
CIA DEPENDS ON MIDDLE
EAST ALLIES.
>> SOMEONE WHO LOOKS
LIKE ME IS NOT GOING
TO BLEND IN.
WE NEED THEM ON THIS
ISSUE IN PARTICULAR
PERHAPS MORE THAN THEY
NEED US.
>> Reporter: ALL THIS
CASTING A SHADOW OVER
HIS TRIP STARTING WITH
SAUDI ARABIA, THEN
ISRAEL, ROME, NATO AND
BRUSSELS.
AND A G7 SUMMIT IN
ITALY.
ALREADY DIPLOMATIC
SOURCES SAY NATO
LEADERS ARE BEING TOLD
KEEP YOUR SPEECHES
BRIEF, TAILORED TO
WHAT THEY CALL MR.
TRUMP'S SHORT
ATTENTION SPAN.
PRESIDENT TRUMP WITH
HIS OFF THE CUFF
REMARKS AND HIS
TWEETING BRINGS A
WHOLE NEW LEVEL OF
UNCERTAINTY TO A
FOREIGN TRIP THAT
COULD PROVE DAUNTING
EVEN FOR AN
EXPERIENCED COMMANDER
IN CHIEF.
LESTER?
>> ANDREA MITCHELL IN
IT WASHINGTON.
ANDREA, THANK YOU.
THERE IS A LOT MORE TO
TALK ABOUT TONIGHT.
STILL AHEAD, GET A
BETTER NIGHT'S SLEEP.
NEW HOPE FOR MILLIONS
OF AMERICANS WHO
SUFFER FROM SOMETHING
THAT KEEPS THEM
TOSSING AND TURNING
AND INCREASES THEIR
RISK OF HEART ATTACK
OR STROKE.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH NEWS ABOUT
SOMETHING THAT KEEPS
SO MANY FROM GETTING A
GOOD NIGHT'S SLEEP.
SOME 18 MILLION
AMERICANS SUFFER FROM
SLEEP APNEA, A
DISORDER THAT CAUSES
SUFFERERS TO STOP
BREATHING WHILE THEY
SLEEP.
BUT NOW THERE'S A NEW
DEVICE THAT MAY
FINALLY HELP A LOT OF
PEOPLE GET BETTER
REST.
NBC'S DR. JOHN TORRES
EXPLAINS.
>> Reporter: ANDREA
TURN EARP SAYS FOR THE
LAST FIVE YEARS SHE
COULDN'T GET A GOOD
NIGHT'S SLEEP.
>> I WAS EXHAUSTED ALL
THE TIME.
HOW CAN I MAKE IT
THROUGH THIS DAY
BECAUSE I AM SO TIRED.
>> THIS IS FIVE
MINUTES.
>> Reporter: THE
69-YEAR-OLD UNDERWENT
A SLEEP STUDY WHERE
DOCTORS MEASURED
EVERYTHING FROM BRAIN
WAVES TO BREATHING.
SHE WAS DIAGNOSED WITH
SLEEP APNEA AND WHAT
DOCTORS FOUND WAS
SHOCKING.
>> SIGNIFICANT DROPS
IN IT OXYGEN.
>> Reporter: WHILE SHE
SLEPT, SHE WOULD STOP
BREATHING AND IT WAS
HAPPENING AS MANY AS
41 TIMES EVERY HOUR.
>> THIS CAN LEAD YOU
TO HAVE THREE TO FOUR
TIMES HIGHER CHANCE OF
HAVING HEART ATTACKS
OR STROKE.
>> Reporter: SLEEP
APNEA HAPPENS WHEN THE
MUSCLES IN THE BACK OF
THE THROAT COLLAPSE
WHICH CUTS OFF
BREATHING.
THE GOLD STANDARD OF
TREATMENT IS A CPAP
MAN.
LIKE HALF OF PATIENTS,
SHE COULDN'T TOLERATE
IT.
NOW A NEW OPTION, A
DEVICE CALLED INSPIRE.
IT'S IMPLANTED UNDER
THE SKIN AND IS TURNED
ON EVERY NIGHT WITH A
REMOTE CONTROL.
IT SENSES WHEN
BREATHING SLOWS DOWN
AND SEND AN ELECTED
TR
TRYCAL PULSE TO THE
TONGUE WHICH
STIMULATES THE AIRWAY
TO OPEN.
>> IT LOOKS LIKE A
PACEMAK
PACEMAKER.
>> IT IS THE SAME TE
TECHNOLOGY.
IT IS JUST ADAPTED TO
STIMULATE A NERVE IN
THE NECK.
>> Reporter: THE MAIN
SIDE EFFECT, PEOPLE
CAN WAKE UP WITH A
SORE TONGUE AND
INSURANCE DOESN'T
ALWAYS PAY FOR THE
DEVICE WHICH CAN COST
$20,000.
BUT ANDREA SAYS FOR
HER A GOOD NIGHT'S
SLEEP IS PRICELESS.
>> IT'S CHANGED MY
LIFE.
>> Reporter: A NEW
SOLUTION FOR A COMMON
PROBLEM THAT COULD
HELP MILLIONS OF
PEOPLE REST EASIER.
DR. JOHN TORRES, NBC
NEWS, BERKELEY,
CALIFORNIA.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A
MOMENT WITH A MYSTERY
IN THE BERMUDA
TRIANGLE.
A PRIVATE PLANE
VANISHES WITH A MOM
AND HER TWO CHILDREN
ONBOARD.
>>> WE TURN NOW TO A
MISSING PLANE MYSTERY
IN THE BERMUDA
TRIANGLE, IN THE AIR
AND ON THE WATER
SEARCHING FOR FOUR
AMERICANS INCLUDING
TWO CHILDREN VANISHED
SINCE THEIR AIRCRAFT
DISAPPEARED NOW MORE
THAN 24 HOURS AGO.
NBC'S KERRY SANDER HAS
THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE U.S. COAST GUARD
AND THE AIR FORCE
SCOURING THE ATLANTIC.
LATE THIS AFTERNOON
SEARCH TEAMS SPOTTED
DEBRIS FLOATING JUST
15 MILES OFF THE COAST
OF THE BAHAMAS BUT
OFFICIALS SAY IT'S
STILL TOO EARLY TO
CONFIRM IT'S THE
MISSING PLANE.
>> MITSUBISHI --
>> Reporter: ONBOARD
WAS THE PILOT, A
ONE-TIME MEMBER OF THE
COAST GUARD AUXILIARY,
HIS FRIEND JENNIFER,
AND HER TWO SMALL
CHILDREN, 4 AND 3
YEARS OLD.
>> AND I'M JENNIFER,
FOUNDER AND CEO --
>> Reporter: A
SUCCESSFUL CEO FROM
NEW YORK CITY AND HER
FAMILY FEATURED IN THE
SHOW "OPEN HOUSE NYC."
ACCORDING TO FLIGHT
RECORDS THEIR PLANE
LEFT PUERTO RICO AT
11:08 A.M. MONDAY.
DESTINATION
TITUSVILLE, FLORIDA.
BUT 2:22 INTO THE
FLIGHT AT AN ALTITUDE
OF 24,000 FEET, THE
PLANE DISAPPEARED FROM
RADAR.
THE SEARCH FALLS IN
THE AREA OF THE FABLED
BERMUDA TRIANGLE.
NOW DISCOUNTED AS
MYTH, IT WAS LONG
BELIEVED IN THE
BERMUDA TRIANGLE
NAVIGATIONAL
INSTRUMENTS WOULD NOT
ENGAGE PROPERLY
LEADING TO CRASHES AND
SINKINGS.
>> AS OF NOW WE'VE
COVERED 100 SQUARE
MILES, A LITTLE MORE
THAN THAT, AND THE
SEARCH IS ONGOING.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE FAMILIES OF THE
MISSING ARE ASKING FOR
PRIVACY AS THE COAST
GUARD COORDINATES A
DESPERATE ROUND THE
CLOCK SEARCH.
KERRY SANDERS, NBC
NEWS, MIAMI BEACH.
>>> THE ACROBAT WHO
OVERCAME PERSONAL
TRAGEDY TO FLY HIGHER
THAN EVER BEFORE
INSPIRING AMERICA IS
NEXT.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, A
STORY ABOUT NEVER
GIVING UP ON YOUR
DREAMS.
A PERFORMER WHO LANDED
THE ROLE HE ALWAYS
WANTED ONLY TO HAVE IT
RIPPED AWAY BY TRAGEDY
BEFORE HE COULD TAKE
THE STAGE.
BUT WHILE IT FOREVER
CHANGE D HIS LIFE IT
COULDN'T TAKE AWAY HIS
DETERMINATION.
OUR "INSPIRING
AMERICA" REPORT.
>> Reporter: IN THE
WORLD OF PERFORMERS,
MONTGOMERY WAS A
TRIPLE THREAT.
HE COULD DANCE, HE
COULD ACT, HE COULD
DEFY GRAVITY.
HIS DREAM TO PERFORM
IN ONE OF THE MOST
PHYSICALLY DEMANDING
SHOWS IN THE WORLD IN
LAS VEGAS.
>> I SAW IT AND I KNEW
IT WAS THE SHOW THAT I
HAD TO BE A PART OF.
>> Reporter: BUT FOUR
DAYS AFTER THE
AUDITION, A DRIVER
CRASHED INTO HIS
MOTORCYCLE.
>> MY DOCTOR HAS
BASICALLY TOLD ME THAT
AMPUTATION SEEMS TO BE
THE BEST OPTION.
>> Reporter: HE LOST
HIS LEG BELOW THE
KNEE.
HE WAS DEVASTATED.
>> I'M NOT READY TO
LET GO, YOU KNOW.
>> Reporter: AND THEN
DETERMINED.
AFTER THE ACCIDENT HIS
CASTING DIRECTOR TOLD
ANDREW HE GOT THE PART
AND THEY WOULD GIVE
HIM ANOTHER SHOT EVEN
WITH THE PROSTHETIC.
>> I GOT A TEXT FROM
A.J. WITH A LITTLE
VIDEO CLIP ATTACHED,
AND HE'S DOING A
ROUNDOFF BACK
HANDSPRING.
>> Reporter: AFTER
EIGHT MONTHS OF HARD
REHAB HE WAS READY TO
DRY AGAIN.
>> AND I MADE IT.
CAME IN A PHONE CALL.
I STARTED RUNNING
AROUND THE HOUSE.
I WAS RUNNING, OH, MY
GOSH.
I HAVE SO MUCH STUFF I
HAVE TO PACK.
I HAVE TO SHAVE MY
HEAD.
WHAT IS HAPPENING?
I DON'T KNOW.
>> Reporter: NOW
ANDREW IS PUSHING THE
LIMITS OF PROSTHETICS.
IN THEATER THEY SAY
BREAK A LEG.
SO FAR ANDREW HAS
BROKEN FOUR.
WITH EXPERTS AT HANGER
CLINIC KEEPING HIM ON
HIS FEET.
HE DOES TWO SHOWS A
NIGHT FIVE DAYS A
WEEK.
HIS GOAL TO BLEND IN
WITH THE OTHERS.
>> I WOULD LOVE
NOTHING MORE THAN
PEOPLE TO COME WATCH
THE SHOW AND AT THE
END OF IT, WAIT, THERE
WAS AN AMPUTEE IN THE
SHOW?
I HAD NO IDEA.
>> Reporter: YOU WOULD
BE HAPPY WITH PEOPLE
LEAVING NOT KNOWING
EVERYTHING IT TOOK YOU
TO GET HERE.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
I'M DOING THINGS AND
I'M NOT JUST DOING
THEM, I'M DOING THEM
TO THE POINT WHERE YOU
DON'T KNOW THAT I'M
DISABLED.
>> Reporter: ANDREW
SPRUNG BACK FROM A
CRUSHING LOSS TO NOW
STAND AMONG THE BEST.
NBC NEWS, LAS VEGAS.
>> WHAT A TERRIFIC
STORY.
THAT'S GOING TO DO IT
FOR US ON THIS TUESDAY
NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
RIGHT NOW AT 6:
>>> IT'S A MATTER OF
CULPABILITY.
AND SO IT DOESN'T HAPPEN AGAIN.
>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00.
A DEATH TRAP THAT CONTAINED A
MAZE OF MAKE-SHIFT ROOMS.
TONIGHT A NEW LAWSUIT FILED SIX
MONTHS AFTER THE DEADLY
WAREHOUSE FIRE IN OAKLAND.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
GOOD EVENING AND THANKS FOR
JOINING US.
I AM JESSICA AGUIRRE.
>> I'M RAJ MATHAI.
FROM THE ASHES COMES A NEW TWIST
ABOUT THE TROUBLED GHOST SHIP
WAREHOUSE.
FAMILIES ARE SUING THE OWNER OF
THE CONVERTED WAREHOUSE AND
PG&E.
THEY PLACE PART OF THE BLAME ON
THE UTILITY COMPANY.
CHUCK COPPOLA JOINS US IN
OAKLAND.
MORE TROUBLE FOR PG&E.
DO THE FAMILIES HAVE A CASE
HERE?
>> Reporter: WE'LL SEE.
LAWYERS ARE SAYING THAT THIS
POWER POLE BEHIND ME SHOULD HAVE
BEEN A BIG TIPOFF TO P&G THAT
SOMETHING WASN'T RIGHT.
ELECTRICITY COMES INTO THE
BUILDING HERE AND SNAKES THROUGH
A LOT OF HOLES CUT IN THE WALL
TO GET TO THE GHOST SHIP THAT,
OF COURSE, CAUGHT FIRE ON
DECEMBER 2nd.
THE LIST OF DEFENDANTS IN THE
LAWSUIT INCLUDES THE OWNERS.
LEASEHOLDERS AND CONCERT
ORGANIZERS WHO DREW MORE THAN
100 PEOPLE INTO A MAZE OF
TAPESTRIES, WOODEN PALLETS WITH
NO EXIT SIGNS, FIRE
EXTINGUISHERS OR A WAY OUT.
>> PEOPLE'S 22-YEAR-OLD CHILDREN
SHOULD NOT BE DYING BECAUSE THEY
WANT TO LISTEN TO MUSIC.
>> Reporter: LAWYERS SAY THEY
FOUND SMART METERS AND OTHER
DEVICES INSIDE THE