IT'S UNHABITABLE.
IT HAS TO BE TORN DOWN.
MAKE YOUR BIDS NOW.
>> FOR THE PROPERTY, FOR THE
LAND.
THANKS SO MUCH.
>>> BREAKING NEWS TONIGHT.
DOUBLE DISASTERS UNFOLDING AS WE
COME ON THE AIR.
HURRICANE MARIA HAMMERING PUERTO
RICO WITH A DIRECT HIT.
STILL A MONSTER STORM.
THE STRONGEST TO SLAM ASHORE ON
THAT AMERICAN ISLAND IN NEARLY A
CENTURY.
POWER REPORTEDLY KNOCKED OUT TO
100% OF THE ISLAND.
TORRENTIAL RAIN, AS MUCH AS TWO
FEET.
LIFE-THREATENING FLOODS TURNING
ROADS INTO RAGING RIVERS.
OUR TEAM IS THERE, AND AL ROKER
IS TRACKING THE DANGER.
WHILE IN MEXICO, A RACE AGAINST
TIME AFTER THAT POWERFUL
EARTHQUAKE.
FIRST RESPONDERS AND VOLUNTEERS
DIGGING TO RESCUE SURVIVORS IN
THE RUBBLE, INCLUDING CHILDREN
TRAPPED WHEN THEIR SCHOOL
COLLAPSED.
THE DEATH TOLL SOARING INTO THE
HUNDREDS FROM THE QUAKE THAT
LEVELED BUILDINGS AND SPARKED
EXPLOSIONS.
TONIGHT WE'RE LIVE FROM BOTH
DISASTER ZONES.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS RIGHT NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS
IS NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
GOOD EVENING, AS WE COME ON THE
AIR ON THE WEST COAST.
HORRIFIC IMAGES OF DESTRUCTION
AND MISERY ARE COMING OUT OF
MEXICO AND PUERTO RICO TONIGHT
FRAMING MUCH OF THIS NEWSCAST
THIS EVENING.
TWO MAJOR NATURAL DISASTERS
STILL UNFOLDING AND IMPACTING
MILLIONS LIVING HERE OUTSIDE THE
DISASTER ZONE.
FAMILIES ANXIOUS TO KNOW THE
FATES OF LOVED ONES.
IN A FEW MOMENTS WE'LL TAKE YOU
TO EARTHQUAKE-STRICKEN MEXICO
CITY WHERE RESCUERS ARE INTENTLY
LISTENING FOR SOUNDS OF LIFE IN
THEIR DESPERATE SEARCH FOR
SURVIVORS.
BUT FIRST TO PUERTO RICO WHERE
HUNDREDS OF HOMES ARE DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED, STREETS ARE FLOODED
AND 100% OF THAT U.S. ISLAND IS
WITHOUT POWER AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA SLAMMED ASHORE WITH
115-MILE-AN-HOUR WINDS TODAY.
OUR TEAM IS ON THE GROUND.
WE WANT TO GET RIGHT TO GABE
GUTIERREZ WHO LEADS OFF OUR
COVERAGE TONIGHT.
GABE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER, GOOD
EVENING.
THE POWER OF THIS STORM WAS
IMMENSE.
WE'VE BEEN SEEING OVERTURNED
CARS AND COLLAPSED BUILDINGS.
IT IS DIFFICULT TO GET AROUND
SAN JUAN TONIGHT.
MANY STREETS ARE FLOODED.
OTHERS ARE JUST SIMPLY
IMPASSABLE.
THE GOVERNOR HAS IMPOSED A
CURFEW, AND THE MAYOR SAYS
SEARCH AND RESCUE MISSIONS ARE
GETTING UNDER WAY.
NO FIRM NUMBER ON THE NUMBER OF
DEAD OR INJURED AS THIS ISLAND
BEGINS WHAT WILL NO DOUBT BE A
LONG RECOVERY.
IT SHOWED LITTLE MERCY.
TONIGHT MARIA'S DESTRUCTIVE PATH
IS ONLY STARTING TO BECOME
CLEAR.
SWATHS OF PUERTO RICO UNDER
WATER.
ROADS TURNED TO RAGING RIVERS.
ROOFS RIPPED OFF.
TREES TOPPLED.
CARS OVERTURNED.
POWER OUT TO VIRTUALLY THE
ENTIRE ISLAND.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN ANYTHING LIKE
THIS?
>> ME?
NEVER.
>> Reporter: THIS MAN SAYS HE
FEARED FOR HIS LIFE AS THE
RELENTLESS STORM SLAMMED INTO
HIS HOME THIS MORNING AS A
FEROCIOUS CATEGORY 4 HURRICANE.
THE SITUATION HERE IN SAN JUAN
IS DIRE.
THE WINDS HERE HAVE BEEN
INTENSIFYING AND THE WORST IS
YET TO COME.
WE HAVE SOUGHT SHELTER IN A
CONCRETE STRUCTURE, BUT AS YOU
CAN SEE, IT IS A SCENE OF UTTER
CHAOS.
AFTER DODGING MOST OF HURRICANE
IRMA'S WRATH DAYS AGO, PUERTO
RICO AND ITS 3.5 MILLION
AMERICAN CITIZENS BORE THE BRUNT
OF MARIA FOR HOURS.
AS THE STORM PASSED WE GOT OUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE DAMAGE.
SOME HOMES OBLITERATED.
RESIDENTS IN SHOCK.
>> IT WAS REAL SCARY.
>> Reporter: MARIA, THE
STRONGEST STORM TO RAVAGE PUERTO
RICO IN NEARLY A CENTURY, FIRST
SLICED THROUGH THE CARIBBEAN.
OVERNIGHT IT BATTERED ST. CROIX,
THE LARGEST OF THE U.S. VIRGIN
ISLANDS.
>> VERY SCARY.
THE WIND AND THE DOORS AROUND
YOU.
>> Reporter: IN ST.
THOMAS WIDESPREAD FLOODING AS
RESIDENTS WERE JUST BEGINNING TO
CLEAN UP AFTER HURRICANE IRMA'S
DIRECT HIT.
THE STORM'S TRAIL OF DEVASTATION
LEAVING MUCH OF THE REMOTE
ISLAND OF DOMINICA IN RUINS.
THIS AERIAL VIDEO THE FIRST TO
EMERGE AFTER MARIA'S FURY CUT
OFF COMMUNICATIONS.
TONIGHT AS PUERTO RICO BEGINS TO
ASSESS ITS DAMAGE, MANY
RESIDENTS, LIKE MARIA ARAGON,
DON'T KNOW IF THEY'LL HAVE HOMES
TO RETURN TO.
HOW HORRIBLE IS IT TO LOOK
AROUND AND SEE THIS ISLAND LIKE
THIS?
>> IT'S VERY SAD.
IT'S VERY, VERY SAD.
VERY HEARTBROKEN.
>> Reporter: AN ISLAND WITHOUT
POWER AND NOW SEEMINGLY WITHOUT
ENOUGH RESOURCES TO COPE WITH AN
UNFOLDING DISASTER.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC NEWS, SAN
JUAN, PUERTO RICO.
>>> THIS IS GADI SCHWARTZ.
IN THE DARK HALLS OF THIS SAN
JUAN SPORTS COLISEUM, ONE OF
PUERTO RICO'S STURDIEST
HURRICANE SHELTERS.
HERE HUDDLED SHAPES HUNCH OVER
RADIOS.
CHILDREN PLAY IN SHADOWS.
AND OUTSIDE HURRICANE MARIA'S
WINDS AND RAIN RAVAGE PUERTO
RICO.
>> IT'S AN AWAKENING, A RUDE
AWAKENING.
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE LAST 24
HOURS FOR FAMILIES LIKE THIS
WOMAN'S TAKING SHELTER FROM THE
STORMS.
>> WHAT'S GOING TO HAPPEN WHEN
WE GET OUT OF HERE?
WHAT WILL WE END UP SEEING?
IT'S VERY HARD.
>> Reporter: AT FIRST IN COTS
SPREAD OUT ACROSS THE MASSIVE
CONCRETE COLISEUM FLOOR, BUT
THEN THE WORST OF HURRICANE
MARIA BURSTING METAL DOORS OPEN.
PEOPLE JOINING HANDS TO PRAY.
QUICKLY THEY MOVE TO THE SAFETY
OF THE OUTER WINGS AS WATER AND
DEBRIS RAIN DOWN FROM THE ROOF.
AND THROUGH THE STORM ONE VOICE
TRYING TO CALM THE REFUGEES.
THIS IS THE MAYOR OF SAN JUAN,
CARMEN YULIN CRUZ, WHO STAYED
HERE WITH HER FAMILY AT THE
COLISEUM.
>> I UNDERSTAND HOW DIFFICULT IT
IS.
>> Reporter: SHE'S GOTTEN
REGULAR REPORTS OF WHAT LIES
OUTSIDE, AND HER HEART BREAKS
FOR THOSE THEY COULDN'T REACH.
>> I'M JUST CONCERNED THAT WE
MAY NOT GET TO EVERYBODY IN
TIME.
AND THAT IS A GREAT WEIGHT ON MY
SHOULDERS.
>> Reporter: SHE'S AMONG THOSE
WHO WILL FIND THEIR HOMES AND
NEIGHBORHOODS DEVASTATED, BUT
FOR NOW SHE CAN'T THINK OF THAT.
SHE CAN ONLY THINK OF KEEPING
HER CITY TOGETHER.
>> WE NEED EACH OTHER.
I NEED THEM MORE THAN THEY NEED
ME.
>> Reporter: A FEELING SHARED
AMONG MANY HOLDING ON TO EACH
OTHER FOR STRENGTH IN WHAT'S TO
COME.
AND A VERY GRIM REALITY FOR SOME
OF THE FAMILIES THAT ARE GOING
TO BE LEAVING THIS SHELTER AFTER
24 HOURS.
MANY OF THEM ARE GOING TO FIND
THEIR HOMES IN RUIN, AND THEY'RE
GOING TO HAVE TO COME BACK TO
SHELTERS LIKE THIS TO SPEND
ANOTHER NIGHT, ANOTHER WEEK AND
POSSIBLY EVEN MONTHS.
LESTER?
>> GADI SCHWARTZ, SOME OF THAT
DAMAGE IS INCREDIBLE, THANK YOU.
>>> THIS HURRICANE THREAT IS FAR
FROM OVER.
WE'RE JOINED HERE BY AL ROKER
WHO IS TRACKING THE STORM.
WHAT'S THE LATEST?
AND IS THE U.S. EAST COAST IN
JEOPARDY?
>> IT'S STILL UP IN THE AIR
RIGHT NOW.
WE CAN TELL YOU THAT MARIA IS A
CATEGORY 2 BUT WILL PROBABLY
REINTENSIFY LATER THIS EVENING.
75 MILES EAST OF PUNTA CANA,
DOMINICAN REPUBLIC.
IT'S MOVING NORTHWEST AT 12,
WITH 110-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS.
THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC TOMORROW
GETS ABOUT 75 MILES PER HOUR.
4 TO 6 FEET OF SURGE, 8 TO 16
INCHES OF RAIN.
TURKS AND CAICOS MAY BE THE NEXT
REALLY BIG DEVASTATED AREA WITH
125-MILE-PER-HOUR WINDS, A STORM
SURGE OF 9 TO 12 FEET AND 9 TO
16 INCHES.
AND THEN IT CONTINUES UP INTO
THE ATLANTIC BY MONDAY
AFTERNOON.
WE PUT THE ENSEMBLE MODEL INTO
PLAY.
YOU SEE THOSE SPAGHETTI STRANDS
WE CALL.
AND BASICALLY FOR THE MOST PART
THEY KEEP IT OFF THE COAST, BUT
YOU CAN SEE THERE'S SOME
DISAGREEMENT ON THE WESTERN SIDE
OF THIS.
SO LESTER, RIGHT NOW WE STILL
CAN'T GIVE YOU A DEFINITIVE
ANSWER WHETHER THIS THING STAYS
OFF SHORE OR NOT.
>> WE'LL KEEP WATCHING.
AL ROKER, THANKS VERY MUCH.
>>> LET'S TURN NOW TO THAT OTHER
MAJOR DISASTER STILL UNFOLDING
AT THIS HOUR.
IN CENTRAL MEXICO, HUNDREDS ARE
DEAD, THOUSANDS ARE STILL
MISSING AFTER THAT DEVASTATING
7.1 MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE STRUCK
THERE.
NOW A DESPERATE SEARCH IS ON FOR
SURVIVORS AT SITES THAT INCLUDE
A SCHOOL THAT COLLAPSED WITH
STUDENTS INSIDE.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER IS THERE
AND HAS THE LATEST.
MIGUEL, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER, GOOD
EVENING.
THEY ARE ASKING US TO WHISPER
BECAUSE IT APPEARS THEY HAVE
DONE IT AGAIN.
TWO RESCUES MIGHT BE UNDER WAY
RIGHT NOW AT THIS HOUR AT THAT
SCHOOL YOU MENTIONED.
THEY'RE LISTENING FOR SIGNS OF
LIFE.
DOZENS OF BODIES HAVE BEEN
RECOVERED THERE, BUT DOZENS HAVE
ALSO BEEN SAVED.
THE DEATH TOLL STANDS AT 225 AND
GROWING, BUT THIS IS A SIGN OF
HOPE.
TONIGHT, THIS IS THE
HEART-POUNDING DRAMA PLAYING OUT
ACROSS MEXICO CITY.
RESCUE TEAMS AT AN ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL FINDING CHILDREN BURIED
BENEATH PILES OF DEBRIS.
ONE BY ONE, PULLING THEM TO
SAFETY.
THIS WAS THE SCHOOL BEFORE.
NOW LITERALLY FLATTENED.
THEY CALL THIS THE MIRACLE IN
THE RUBBLE.
THE CRISIS STILL UNFOLDING
TODAY.
JUST MOMENTS AFTER THE CHEERS --
>> SILENCIO.
>> Reporter: FISTS GO UP, THE
SIGNAL FOR SILENCE.
SEARCH TEAMS CAN FAINTLY HEAR A
NEW CRY FOR HELP.
THIS TIME TWO LITTLE GIRLS
RESCUED.
THIS SEARCH COMMANDER SAYS HE
HAS CHILDREN OF HIS OWN.
THESE KIDS ARE MY FAMILY.
I WANT TO BRING THEM HOME.
BUT MORE THAN 20 STUDENTS HERE
DIDN'T MAKE IT.
LUIS CARLOS SAYS HE HAS NO IDEA
HOW HE GOT OUT.
I SAW THE WHOLE SCHOOL FALL
DOWN, BUT I NEVER FOUND MY
FRIENDS.
ACROSS THIS SHATTERED COUNTRY,
THERE IS MORE HEARTBREAK THAN
DEBRIS.
THESE ARE THE FACES OF ANGUISH.
PARENTS DESPERATELY CLINGING TO
HOPE.
GLORIA HERNANDEZ CLUTCHES THE
PHOTO OF HER 24-YEAR-OLD SON
IVAN BURIED BENEATH SIX FLOORS
OF RUBBLE IN HIS OFFICE.
TIME IS SLIPPING AWAY RIGHT
BEFORE HER EYES.
SHE SAYS, I'M PLEADING TO THE
GOVERNMENT FOR HELP.
MY SON HAS BEEN BURIED FOR
HOURS.
NOBODY WILL TELL ME A THING.
TUESDAY'S MASSIVE 7.1 EARTHQUAKE
LEVELED 38 BUILDINGS AND AN
UNTOLD NUMBER OF HOMES AND
THREATENED TO SING TOUR BOATS IN
THE WATER.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Reporter: 75 MILES AWAY, THE
EPICENTER IS A DISASTER.
CHURCHES HAVE CRUMBLED, MANY ARE
LOSING FAITH.
SOCIAL MEDIA IS INUNDATED WITH
DESPERATE PLEAS FOR HELP FOR
THOSE LOOKING FOR LOVED ONES.
WHILE THE NAMES OF THOSE PULLED
FROM THE RUBBLE ARE WRITTEN DOWN
ON PAPER FOR WAITING FAMILIES TO
SEE.
BUT TONIGHT THERE IS NO MATCH
FOR THIS MOM.
IVAN REMAINS AMONG THE MISSING.
AN EARTHQUAKE SHATTERING HOMES
AND NOW SO MANY LIVES.
TONIGHT ON THE HEELS OF THOSE
TWO GIRLS THAT WERE RESCUED, IT
APPEARS TWO MORE PEOPLE ARE
BEING PULLED FROM THE RUBBLE.
OFFICIALS SAY AT LEAST 54 PEOPLE
HAVE BEEN PULLED FROM THIS
DEBRIS FIELD.
IT IS A GLIMMER OF HOPE ACROSS A
REGION SURROUNDED BY SO MUCH
LOSS.
LESTER?
>> MIGUEL, OUR HATS OFF TO THOSE
BRAVE RESCUERS.
WE WISH THEM GREAT SUCCESS AS
THEY CONTINUE THEIR WORK.
THANK YOU.
>>> THE WELL KNOWN ROMA NORTE
NEIGHBORHOOD, OF MEXICO CITY WAS
HARD HIT BY THE EARTHQUAKE.
AND TODAY NBC'S JOSE DIAZ-BALART
GOT CLOSE TO ONE OF THE RESCUE
EFFORTS GOING ON THERE IN A
COLLAPSED BUILDING.
>> Reporter: GOOD AFTERNOON.
WHAT IS HAPPENING RIGHT HERE IS
HAPPENING THROUGHOUT THE CITY OF
MEXICO.
THIS IS ONE OF AT LEAST 44
STRUCTURES AND BUILDINGS THAT
COLLAPSED AFTER THIS EARTHQUAKE
STRUCK MEXICO CITY AND OTHER
PARTS OF THIS COUNTRY.
AND WHAT YOU'RE SEEING NOW ARE
ACTUALLY EXPERTS IN FINDING
SURVIVORS BURIED THROUGH RUBBLE.
THEY LITERALLY BURROW THROUGH
TONS OF CONCRETE, STEEL AND
CABLES SEARCHING FOR VICTIMS
THAT MAY HAVE SURVIVED THIS.
THIS IS GOING ON THROUGHOUT THE
CITY.
IT'S AN EXTREMELY DANGEROUS JOB.
THERE ARE SOME GAS LEAKS AROUND
HERE.
PEOPLE ARE VERY CONCERNED ABOUT
THAT.
AND THE WHOLE PROCESS IS BEING
HANDLED HERE AS THERE ARE
LITERALLY THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
THAT HAVE COME OUT HERE TO
VOLUNTEER, TO DO WHAT THEY CAN
TO HELP.
THAT'S THE VERY LATEST FROM
MEXICO CITY.
LESTER, BACK TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, JOSE, THANK YOU.
>>> THE QUAKE IN MEXICO WAS A
JARRING REMINDER OF THE BIG ONE
THAT EXPERTS WARN MAY BE IN
CALIFORNIA'S NOT TOO DISTANT
FUTURE.
SMALL QUAKES ARE A FACT OF LIFE
ALONG THE WEST COAST.
THE MOST RECENT A 3.6 MAGNITUDE
THAT RATTLED NEIGHBORHOODS ON
L.A.'S WEST SIDE LATE MONDAY
NIGHT.
BUT HISTORY SUGGESTS A MAJOR
QUAKE IS COMING.
THE QUESTIONS ARE WHEN AND WILL
CALIFORNIA BE READY.
NBC'S JO LING KENT REPORTS.
>> Reporter: IT'S NOT A MATTER
OF IF BUT WHEN.
AS MEXICO REELS FROM ITS 7.1
MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE,
CALIFORNIA, FROM LOS ANGELES TO
SAN FRANCISCO, IS ANXIOUS AND ON
EDGE ABOUT WHAT SO MANY FEAR
WILL BE THE BIG ONE.
>> DID YOU FEEL THAT?
>> Reporter: A SMALL EARTHQUAKE
SHOOK L.A.
EARLIER THIS WEEK.
BUT A STUDY FROM THE U.S.
GEOLOGICAL SURVEY SAYS THE
CHANCE OF A QUAKE MAGNITUDE 8 OR
LARGER IN THE NEXT 30 YEARS HAS
DOUBLED SINCE 2008.
EXPERTS SAY A MAJOR QUAKE ALONG
THE SAN ANDREAS FAULT IN
SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA COULD KILL
1800 PEOPLE, INJURE 53,000,
DESTROY 1500 BUILDINGS AND
DAMAGE 300,000 MORE.
A SERIOUS QUAKE COULD ALSO
CRIPPLE THE CITY'S WATER SUPPLY
AND TAKE AS LONG AS SIX MONTHS
TO REPAIR.
>> WHO THINKS ABOUT THE PIPES IN
THE GROUND?
WE DON'T WANT TO SPEND MONEY ON
THAT.
IT'S OUT OF SIGHT, OUT OF MIND.
>> Reporter: WHILE NEARLY $14
BILLION HAS BEEN SPENT ON
SEISMIC UPGRADES TO
TRANSPORTATION INFRASTRUCTURE
INCLUDING BRIDGES, THE CITY OF
LOS ANGELES NOW REQUIRES
PROPERTY OWNERS TO RETROFIT
BUILDINGS THAT CANNOT WITHSTAND
A STRONG EARTHQUAKE.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE L.A.
IS READY?
>> L.A. IS GETTING READY AND IS
PROBABLY FAR MORE READY THAN A
LOT OF OTHER CITIES, BUT
THERE'S -- L.A.'S HUGE.
THERE'S A LOT OF OLD STRUCTURES.
>> Reporter: A NEW PREPAREDNESS
PLAN HAS LANDED ON MAYOR ERIC
GARCETTI'S DESK AND HAS NOT YET
BEEN RELEASED.
THE U.S. HOUSE RECENTLY APPROVED
FEDERAL FUNDING FOR AN
EARTHQUAKE EARLY WARNING SYSTEM
AS CALIFORNIA PREPARES NOW FOR A
WORST-CASE SCENARIO THAT MAY
COME WITH NO WARNING AT ALL.
JO LING KENT, NBC NEWS, LOS
ANGELES.
>>> THERE'S STILL MORE AHEAD ON
THIS DEADLY DISASTER.
THE URGENT RESCUE MISSION WITH
VOLUNTEERS COMING FROM FAR AND
WIDE TO HELP SAVE LIVES.
>>> ALSO THE DAY'S OTHER
HEADLINES INCLUDING WHY ONE
LATE-NIGHT HOST IS ACCUSING A
SENATOR OF LYING TO HIS FACE.
HOPE YOU CAN STAY WITH US.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH A NEW BATTLE
HEATING UP IN THE HEALTHCARE
WARS.
THE LATEST ATTEMPT BY
REPUBLICANS TO REPEAL OBAMACARE.
THEY PLAN TO PUT THEIR NEW BILL
TO A VOTE NEXT WEEK AND ALREADY
IT IS HIGHLY CONTROVERSIAL.
NBC'S KASIE HUNT TONIGHT ON WHAT
THE BILL WOULD DO AND A
CELEBRITY RIGHT IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE FIGHT.
>> HE GOT TO THE HOSPITAL --
>> Reporter: FOR LATE-NIGHT
COMIC JIMMY KIMMEL, THE NEW PUSH
TO REPEAL OBAMACARE IS DEEPLY
PERSONAL.
>> BILLY WAS BORN WITH A HEART
DISEASE.
>> Reporter: IN MAY, KIMMEL TOLD
THE WORLD HIS SON WAS BORN WITH
A PRE-EXISTING CONDITION.
SENATOR BILL CASSIDY HEARD THE
STORY AND MADE IT HIS LITMUS
TEST.
>> I WANT IT TO PASS THE JIMMY
KIMMEL TEST.
>> WELL, I DO, TOO.
I THINK THAT'S A GOOD THING.
>> Reporter: AFTER REPUBLICANS
FAILED TO REPEAL OBAMACARE IN
JULY, THEY'RE NOW UNDER INTENSE
PRESSURE FROM MAJOR DONORS TO
SHOW THEY'RE ACTUALLY DOING
SOMETHING.
AND CASSIDY IS SPEARHEADING THE
EFFORT.
LAST NIGHT JIMMY KIMMEL SAID
HE'S HAD ENOUGH.
>> THIS GUY, BILL CASSIDY, JUST
LIED RIGHT TO MY FACE.
>> Reporter: DO YOU THINK THIS
LEGISLATION PASSES THE JIMMY
KIMMEL TEST?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THERE WILL BE PEOPLE IN STATES
LIKE --
>> Reporter: HE CALLED YOU A
LIAR LAST NIGHT.
>> IT WAS A PERSONAL ATTACK.
AND I CAN'T HELP THAT.
>> Reporter: CASSIDY'S BILL WITH
LINDSEY GRAHAM WOULD ELIMINATE
THE INDIVIDUAL MANDATE TO BUY
INSURANCE, REDISTRIBUTE MEDICAID
EXPANSION AND OBAMACARE SUBSIDY
MONEY TO INDIVIDUAL STATES TO
LET THEM IMPLEMENT THEIR OWN
PLANS, BUT STATES COULD OPT OUT
OF COVERING PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS, THOUGH THEY WOULD
HAVE TO EXPLAIN HOW THEY INTEND
TO KEEP THOSE PEOPLE COVERED.
BUT EXPERTS WARN --
>> THAT IS THE ONLY BILL WE'VE
SEEN SO FAR THAT EFFECTIVELY
LETS STATE JUST DUMP THAT
PRE-EXISTING CONDITION
REQUIREMENT.
IT ALLOWS INSURERS TO
DISCRIMINATE AGAINST YOU IF
YOU'RE SICK.
>> Reporter: FORMER PRESIDENT
OBAMA TODAY DEFENDING HIS
SIGNATURE LEGISLATION.
>> IT'S CERTAINLY FRUSTRATING TO
HAVE TO MOBILIZE EVERY COUPLE OF
MONTHS TO KEEP OUR LEADERS FROM
INFLICTING REAL HUMAN SUFFERING
ON OUR CONSTITUENTS.
>> Reporter: LATE TODAY THE
PRESIDENT WEIGHING IN.
>> I THINK IT'S MUCH BETTER THAN
THE PREVIOUS SHOT.
>> Reporter:
REPUBLICANS HAVE UNTIL SEPTEMBER
30th TO FIND 50 VOTES, AND ALL
EYES WILL BE ON SENATORS LISA
MURKOWSKI AND JOHN McCAIN WHEN
THE BILL COMES TO THE FLOOR NEXT
WEEK.
KASIE HUNT, NBC NEWS, THE
CAPITOL.
>>> WE'LL TAKE A SHORT BREAK AND
BE BACK IN A MOMENT WHAT
AIRLINES ARE CHARGING YOU FOR AT
A RECORD BREAKING RATE.
♪
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP SAYS HE'S
MADE UP HIS MIND ABOUT THE IRAN
NUCLEAR DEAL, BUT HE'S NOT
SAYING IF THE U.S.
WILL STAY IN THE AGREEMENT.
NBC NEWS HAS LEARNED FROM FOUR
SOURCES FAMILIAR WITH THE
DISCUSSIONS THAT THE PRESIDENT
IS LEANING AGAINST RECERTIFYING
IRAN'S COMPLIANCE WITH THE DEAL.
THAT WOULD MOVE IT TO CONGRESS
AND LIKELY BEGIN THE DIFFICULT
TASK OF TRYING TO CONVINCE
AMERICA'S ALLIES AND IRAN TO
RENEGOTIATE.
THE ALLIES STRONGLY OPPOSE A
U.S. EXIT AND THE SOURCES WARN
THAT NO DECISION IS FINAL.
>>> HE WAS A BOXING LEGEND WHO
INSPIRED A CLASSIC AMERICAN
MOVIE.
TODAY WE LEARNED THAT JAKE
LaMOTTA HAS DIED AFTER BATTLING
PNEUMONIA.
LaMOTTA WAS A FORMER
MIDDLEWEIGHT CHAMPION WHOSE
TURBULENT LIFE IN AND OUT OF THE
RING WAS CAPTURED IN THE 1980
FILM "RAGING BULL."
ROBERT DE NIRO, WHO WON A BEST
ACTING OSCAR FOR PORTRAYING
LaMOTTA, SAID TODAY REST IN
PEACE, CHAMP.
JAKE LaMOTTA WAS 95.
>> AND AIRLINE TRAVELERS THOSE
EXTRA FEES YOU ARE PAYING ARE
ADDING UP TO A RECORD AMOUNT.
PASSENGERS PAID $7 BILLION LAST
YEAR ALONE
TO CHECK BAGS AND CHANGE FLIGHTS
SAYS A NEW REPORT.
THE AIRLINES, OF COURSE, HAVE
ALL KINDS OF OTHER FEES, BUT
THOSE ARE THE ONLY TWO TYPES
THEY'RE REQUIRED TO REPORT TO
THE GOVERNMENT.
>>> UP NEXT HERE TONIGHT,
DISASTER STRUCK AND THEY'RE
ANSWERING THE CALL.
LIFE-SAVING HELP FROM ALL OVER
THE WORLD IN THE AFTERMATH OF
MEXICO'S DEADLY EARTHQUAKE.
COLLAPSES DURING THE
EARTHQUAKE... AND CREWS
DESPERATELY SEARCH THROUGH THE
RUBBLE. ===JESS VO===
NBC BAY AREA )S DAMIAN TRUJILLO
IS LIVE IN MEXICO CITY -- WITH
THE
RESCUE EFFORT AND WHY THERE )S
HOPE THAT SOMEBODY IS STILL
ALIVE IN THERE.
===NEXT CLOSE===
NEXT AT 6
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT WE HAVE BEEN
WATCHING A REMARKABLE EFFORT
UNFOLD IN MEXICO CITY TODAY
AFTER THE EARTHQUAKE.
THE RESCUE MISSION IS NOT JUST
ONE MISSION BUT HUNDREDS,
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE JOINING THE
EFFORT TO SAVE PEOPLE.
TEAMS ARE ALSO ON THEIR WAY
TONIGHT FROM OTHER COUNTRIES
INCLUDING THE UNITED STATES.
NBC'S RON MOTT TONIGHT FROM
MEXICO CITY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT ACROSS THE
EARTHQUAKE ZONE, THE FIRST
RESPONDERS WERE OFTEN THOSE WHO
JUST SHOWED UP FIRST.
SO MANY EVERYDAY CITIZENS
RUNNING IN TO HELP.
A SEA OF HANDS IN MOTION MOVING
WATER WHERE IT'S NEEDED.
THIS IS QUITE AN ORGANIZATIONAL
FEAT HERE.
>> I WAS 5 YEARS OLD WHEN THE
LAST EARTHQUAKE HAPPENED, THE
BIG ONE.
AND WE HAVE BEEN TAUGHT AND WE
HAVE BEEN DRILLING FOR THIS.
>> Reporter: MEXICO CITY WAS
ROCKED BY A DEADLY QUAKE IN
1985.
YESTERDAY MORNING THEY HELD A
ROUTINE EARTHQUAKE DRILL TO
PREPARE FOR THE NEXT DISASTER.
THE DRILL FINISHING JUST HOURS
BEFORE THE REAL NIGHTMARE BEGAN.
ANOTHER QUAKE HITTING ON THE
SAME DAY 32 YEARS LATER.
AND NOW WAVES OF VOLUNTEERS
MOBILIZING, COMING FAR AND WIDE,
INCLUDING AN URBAN SEARCH AND
RESCUE TEAM DEPLOYING FROM L.A.
ISRAEL SENDING 25 ENGINEERS.
A NUMBER OF BUILDINGS HAVE
COLLAPSED IN THIS NEIGHBORHOOD.
AND WHAT FOLKS ARE DOING NOW IS
FERRYING LITERALLY WATER BY
HAND, BY HUMAN HAND.
A HUMAN CHAIN.
A LONG CHAIN OF HUMANITY HERE
TAKING WATER SEVERAL BLOCKS THIS
WAY TO A HIGH SCHOOL WHERE
THEY'RE GOING TO BE GIVING OUT
THAT WATER.
PEOPLE KNOW THESE ARE THE
CRITICAL HOURS TO FIND
SURVIVORS.
SO MANY ARE NOW ANSWERING THE
CALL.
>> THIS IS MEXICO CITY AT ITS
BEST.
>> Reporter: WHILE THE TOLL IS
HEAVY, ALONG WITH HEARTS, A
SENSE OF PURPOSE REIGNS SUPREME.
OUT OF ONE DISASTER, MANY AT THE
READY DOING WHATEVER IT TAKES.
RON MOTT, NBC NEWS, MEXICO CITY.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO
FOLLOW THE DEVELOPMENTS IN
MEXICO AND THE DISASTROUS
HURRICANE IN PUERTO RICO.
YOU CAN SEE MORE ON THE "TODAY"
SHOW TOMORROW MORNING.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS" FOR THIS
WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
AND FOR ALL OF US AT NBC NEWS,
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
RESCUES AND RECOVERY.
WE )RE LIVE IN MEXICO CITY AS IT
REELS FROM THE POWERFUL
EARTHQUAKE.
==RAJ/2-SHOT==
THE NEWS AT 6 STARTS NOW.
GOOD EVENING AND THANKS FOR
JOINING US.
I )M RAJ MATHAI.
==JESS/2-SHOT==
AND I )M JESSICA AGUIRRE.
JESS/VO
ONE DAY AFTER THE 7-POINT-1
EARTHQUAKE SHOOK MEXICO TO
ITS CORE... THE SEARCH
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US.
>> ONE DAY AFTER THE 7.1
EARTHQUAKE SHOOK MEXICO TO ITS
CORE THE SEARCH FOR SURVIVORS
HAS INTENSIFIED.
MORE THAN 50 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
PULLED FROM THE DEBRIS ALIVE.
WE LEARNED THAT 230 PEOPLE ARE
NOW CONFIRMED DEAD.
ONE OF THE MORE GUT WRENCHING
DEVELOPMENTS IS THAT 21 CHILDREN
AND FOUR ADULTS WERE KILLED AT
AN ELEMENTARY SCHOOL IN MEXICO
CITY.
DESPERATE RESCUE WORKERS
CONTINUED TO SIFT THROUGH THE
RUBBLE LOOKING FOR SURVIVORS.
THE PARENTS THERE ARE CLINGING
TO HOPE THAT THEIR CHILDREN WILL
BE FOUND ALIVE.
THAT'S BECAUSE RESCUE CREWS SAY
A TEACHER AND TWO STUDENTS DID
SEND A TEXT MESSAGE TO EACH
OTHER FROM WITHIN THE RUBBLE.
>> WE BEGIN OUR TEAM COVERAGE
WITH NBC BAY AREA DAMON WHO
JOINS US ON THE PHONE NOW.
TELL US WHAT YOU'RE SEEING NOT
JUST AT THE SCHOOL BUT AROUND
TOWN AS YOU DROVE THROUGH.
>> Reporter: I'M ABOUT A BLOCK
AWAY AND IT'S VERY HECTIC HERE.
THE VOLUNTEERS WILL RAISE THEIR
RIGHT HAND, SOMETIMES BOTH HANDS
AND FORM A FIST.
THAT MEANS THEY NEED EVERYBODY
TO BE KWHOOQU