>> THANKS FOR JOINING US.
"THE NIGHTLY NEWS" IS NEXT.
>> SEE YOU AT 6:00.
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT --
OUT OF CONTROL AND RUNNING OUT
OF CASH TO FIGHT THE WORST FIRE
>>> EYES OF THE WORLD ON THE
ATROCI IN SYRIA.
NEW BOMBINGS IN THE VILLAGES
WHERE SO MANY CHILDREN DIED.
AND TONIGHT, WHAT COULD BE NEW
EVIDENCE.
>>> THE SURPRISE MOMENT LIVE ON
THE "TODAY" SHOW.
THE REVELATION THAT THE MAN WHO
EXPOSED U.S. MILITARY SECRETS
NOW SAYS HE IS A WOMAN.
SHOULD HE GET HORMONE TREATMENT
IN PRISON?
>>> AND TELLING HER STORY.
AN NBC NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
KIDNAPPING SURVIVOR HANNAH
ANDERSON SETS THE RECORD
STRAIGHT FOR THE FIRST TIME
SINCE HER HARROWING ORDEAL.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>> Announcer: FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK,
THIS IS "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS WITH
BRIAN WILLIAMS".
>>> GOOD EVENING TO OUR VIEWERS
IN THE WEST.
I'M LESTER HOLT SITTING IN FOR
BRIAN.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH A MASSIVE
FIREFIGHT ACROSS A HUGE PART OF
THE COUNTRY.
RIGHT NOW AT LEAST 51 WILDFIRES
ARE BURNING OUT OF CONTROL, AND
THERE'S WORD TONIGHT THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT IS RUNNING OUT OF
MONEY AND RESOURCES TO FIGHT
THEM.
WHILE IN CALIFORNIA TONIGHT
THERE ARE NEW EVACUATIONS NEAR
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK AS A HUGE
FIRE THERE CLOSES IN.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER HAS MADE
HIS WAY NEAR YOSEMITE.
HE STARTS UNITED STATES OFF WITH
LATE-BREAKING DETAILS.
GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
84 SQUARE MILES.
THAT'S WHAT'S BEEN LOST HERE
BECAUSE CONDITIONS IN THIS
FOREST ARE SO DRY THE GROWTH
POTENTIAL FOR THIS FIRE IS
EXTREME, AND IT COULDN'T COME AT
A WORSE TIME.
NEAR YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK,
1,300 FIREFIGHTERS ARE ON THEIR
HEELS, FACE TO FACE WITH A
FIRESTORM.
THE RIM FIRE RAGING OUT OF
CONTROL, TRIPLING IN SIZE
OVERNIGHT.
WITH TWO HOMES LOST SO FAR,
2,500 STRUCTURES ARE THREATENED.
THOUSANDS HAVE FLED THEIR HOMES,
AND SUMMER CAMPS FORCED CHILDREN
R CHILDREN TO LEAVE TOO.
DON MATTER ISN'T READY TO GO.
HE WATCHES FLAMES CLOSE IN AS
HIS FAMILY OF SEVEN ANXIOUSLY
WAITS.
>> IT IS WHAT IT IS.
WE LIVE WHERE WE LIVE BECAUSE WE
ENJOY IT.
BUT THERE'S ALSO RISK.
>> READY, DROP.
>> Reporter: RIPPING ACROSS
FOREST LAND, SMOKE AND FLAMES
ARE HEADED EAST.
WE'RE JUST 15 MILES AWAY FROM
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK.
NBC NEWS IS EMBEDDED WITH THE
PIKE HOTSHOTS ON THE BEAVER
CREEK FIRE IN IDAHO.
TODAY ANOTHER 16-HOUR SHIFT.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHERE THEY'LL BE
NEEDED NEXT.
>> THAT RIDGE COMES DOWN.
>> Reporter: THE BOOTS ON THE
GROUND ARE A SIGN FROM THE
NATIONAL INTERAGENCY
COORDINATION FIRE CENTER IN
BOISE.
THIS IS MISSION CONTROL, THE
MORNING MEETING.
>> THEY WERE REPORTING MORE THAN
THE 29 FIRES.
>> Reporter: WITH 33,000 FIRES
SO FAR THIS YEAR, SCORCHING
ALMOST AS MUCH LAND AS THE STATE
OF CONNECTICUT, THE U.S. FOREST
SERVICE IS QUICKLY RUNNING OUT
OF CASH.
AFTER SPENDING ALMOST A BILLION
DOLLARS FOR FIRE SUPPRESSION
THIS YEAR, THE AGENCY ONLY HAS
$50 MILLION LEFT, JUST ENOUGH TO
LAST A FEW DAYS.
THE FOREST SERVICE FORCED TO
DIVERT $600 MILLION FROM AREAS
LIKE RECREATION TO KEEP CREWS ON
THE FRONT LINES.
>> WHEN ONE POT RUNS LOW, WE
HAVE TO REALLOCATE JUST LIKE YOU
WOULD WITH YOUR HOME BUDGET.
>> Reporter: C-130s ARE READY,
BUT IT COSTS $12,000 AN HOUR TO
FLY THESE PLANES.
FOR THE MOMENT, THEY'RE STAYING
ON THE TARMAC.
TONIGHT, MONEY IS SHORT,
RESOURCES SPREAD THIN, AS FIRE
SEASON CONTINUES TO GROW WITH
THE DRY MONTHS OF SEPTEMBER AND
OCTOBER STILL AHEAD.
THE COST TO FIGHT THE RIM FIRE
HERE HAS ALREADY TOPPED NEARLY
$3 MILLION.
THIS BLAZE IS ONLY 2% CONTAINED.
IT WILL BURN FOR DAYS, IF NOT
WEEKS.
THE GOOD NEWS, YOSEMITE NATIONAL
PARK IS OPEN AND SMOKE-FREE.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT, MIGUEL, THANKS.
>>> WE TURN OVERSEAS NOW TO
SYRIA AND SOME HORRIFYING IMAGES
THAT WILL INSTINCTIVELY MAKE YOU
WANT TO LOOK AWAY.
YET THEY CANNOT BE IGNORED.
VIDEO EVIDENCE OF WHAT MAY HAVE
HAPPENED NOW INSIDE SYRIA.
A MASS CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK.
HAS SHOCKED THE WORLD.
HUNDREDS, MANY OF THEM CHILDREN,
ARE DEAD.
TONIGHT THE CLAIMS OF A CHEMICAL
ATTACK HAVE STILL NOT BEEN
VERIFIED.
FROM THE SYRIAN REGIME DENIALS,
AS THE OBAMA WHITE HOUSE WHICH
FOR A YEAR HAS CALLED THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS IN SYRIA A RED
LINE, IS BEING CAUTIOUS AS IT
NOW CALLS FOR AN INVESTIGATION.
YOU'RE ABOUT TO SEE WHAT THE
REBELS SAY IS THE EVIDENCE.
SOME OF IT IS VERY GRAPHIC.
OUR CHIEF FOREIGN CORRESPONDENT
RICHARD ENGEL JOINS US NOW WITH
THAT.
RICHARD?
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
LESTER.
MORE VIDEOS EMERGE FROM SYRIA
TODAY.
THEY ARE UNCONFIRMED BY NBC
NEWS, BUT THEY ARE CONSISTENT
WITH THE ACCOUNTS OF WITNESSES
WE SPOKE TO.
AND AGAIN, THESE IMAGES ARE
GRAPHIC.
THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT BOMBED
VILLAGES OUTSIDE DAMASCUS TODAY,
THE SAME VILLAGES HIT YESTERDAY
BY WHAT LOOKS LIKE A WAR CRIME.
AN OUTRAGE.
HUNDREDS KILLED BY CHEMICAL
WEAPONS, THE REBELS SAY, MANY OF
THEM BURIED TODAY IN MASS
GRAVES.
A SYRIAN CAMERAMAN CONTRACTED BY
OUR PARTNER ITN FILMED PEOPLE
LOOKING AT AN EXPLODED ROCKET.
NEAR IT, DEAD BODIES.
NBC NEWS HAS NO WAY TO CONFIRM
THAT THE CASUALTIES WERE CAUSED
BY THIS WEAPON.
THERE IS STILL NO DEFINITIVE
PROOF THAT CHEMICAL WEAPONS WERE
USED OR BY WHOM.
BUT HOW CAN ANYONE FAKE ROWS OF
DEAD CHILDREN?
NO APPARENT INJURIES.
NO BLOOD.
JUST LIFELESS BODIES, THEIR ARMS
FOLDED.
SO MANY THEY'RE NOT EVEN NAMED,
BUT NUMBERED.
THIS IS BABY 11 FROM THE VILLAGE
OF DUMA, THE NUMBER WRITTEN ON A
BURIAL SHROUD.
IN SYRIA OUTRAGES HAVE LONG GONE
UNPUNISHED.
A VICIOUS CIVIL WAR NOW IN ITS
THIRD YEAR, MORE THAN 100,000
DEAD, NEARLY 2 MILLION REFUGEES.
>> THERE'S NO END IN SIGHT.
THERE IS NO LIGHT AT THE END OF
THE TUNNEL.
>> Reporter: CAN ANYTHING BE
DONE?
OPTIONS INCLUDE A NO-FLY ZONE TO
GROUND ASSAD'S AIR POWER.
EXPENSIVE AND A LONG-TERM
COMMITMENT, NOT ACTIVELY BEING
CONSIDERED.
ARMING THE REBELS.
BUT WASHINGTON WORRIES, WHO
WOULD GET THE WEAPONS?
THE REBELS ARE DIVIDED WITH SOME
LINKED TO AL QAEDA.
WHAT ABOUT A MILITARY INVASION?
U.S. BOOTS ON THE GROUND.
FOR WAR-WEARY AMERICANS, THAT'S
NOT EVEN UNDER CONSIDERATION.
TODAY A SENIOR ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIAL SAID THE U.S. MUST BE,
QUOTE, HUMBLE ABOUT WHAT WE CAN
AND CANNOT DO.
AND WITH ASSAD BACKED BY RUSSIA,
IRAN, AND HEZBOLLAH, THERE IS
LITTLE THE WORLD CAN DO.
THE U.N. HAS PROVEN TO BE
UTTERLY POWERLESS.
IT HAS INSPECTORS IN DAMASCUS
RIGHT NOW, JUST A FEW MILES FROM
WHERE SO MANY DIED YESTERDAY,
BUT THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT WON'T
LET THEM SEE WHAT COULD BE THE
WORST ATROCITY IN SYRIA'S
ATROCIOUS WAR.
IT'S UNCLEAR, LESTER, IF THIS
WILL BE A TURNING POINT OR JUST
ANOTHER HORROR IN A WAR NO ONE
WANTS TO -- SEEMS TO WANT TO
HAVE ANYTHING TO DO WITH.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT.
RICHARD ENGEL IN CAIRO, THANK
YOU.
>>> EGYPT'S FORMER PRESIDENT
HOSNI MUBARAK DRIVEN OUT DURING
THE ARAB SPRING IS OUT OF PRISON
TONIGHT, A DAY AFTER A COURT
RULED HE HAD TO BE RELEASED.
WEARING A WHITE T-SHIRT, HE WAS
MOVED FROM THE PRISON WHERE HE
SPENT THE LAST TWO YEARS TO A
MILITARY HOSPITAL WHERE HE'LL
RECEIVE MEDICAL TREATMENT AND BE
HELD UNDER HOUSE ARREST.
>>> THERE'S A BIG CONTROVERSY
TONIGHT AFTER A SURPRISE MOMENT
THAT MADE NEWS THIS MORNING.
ON NBC'S "TODAY," WHEN THE ARMY
PRIVATE AT THE CENTER OF THE
WIKILEAKS SCANDAL, BRADLEY
MANNING, DECLARED HE IS A WOMAN,
AS HE HEADS OFF TO BEGIN HIS
SENTENCE AT A MILITARY PRISON.
SO THE QUESTION TONIGHT, WILL HE
GET HORMONE TREATMENTS AT FT.
LEAVENWORTH?
NBC'S JIM MIKLASZEWSKI JOINS US
NOW FROM THE PENTAGON.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
LESTER.
BRADLEY MANNING ARRIVED AT THE
ARMY PRISON IN FT. LEAVENWORTH,
KANSAS LATE TODAY.
CONVICTED IN THE BIGGEST LEAK IN
U.S. SECRETS IN HISTORY.
BUT IT APPEARS MANNING HAD ONE
LAST SECRET LEFT.
JUST ONE DAY AFTER BRADLEY
MANNING WAS SENTENCED TO 35
YEARS IN A MILITARY PRISON, THE
ARMY PRIVATE DROPPED A BOMBSHELL
ON NBC'S "TODAY," IN A STATEMENT
READ BY SAVANNAH GUTHRIE.
>> I WANT EVERYONE TO KNOW THE
REAL ME.
I AM CHELSEA MANNING.
I AM A FEMALE.
>> Reporter: FROM THIS DAY ON,
MANNING ASKED TO BE CALLED ONLY
BY THE NAME CHELSEA AND THE
FEMALE PRONOUN "SHE," NOT "HE."
THE EVIDENCE WAS ALREADY OUT
THERE.
THIS PHOTO OF MANNING WEARING A
WOMAN'S WIG AND LIPSTICK WAS
PRESENTED BY DEFENSE LAWYERS
DURING MANNING'S MILITARY TRIAL
FOR LEAKING U.S. SECRETS AS
PROOF OF TRANSGENDER ISSUES.
BUT MANNING WANTS TO TAKE IT ONE
STEP FURTHER TOWARD ACTUALLY
BECOMING A WOMAN.
>> GIVEN THE WAY THAT I FEEL AND
HAVE FELT SINCE CHILDHOOD, I
WANT TO BEGIN HORMONE THERAPY AS
SOON AS POSSIBLE.
>> Reporter: A STATEMENT FROM
THE MILITARY PRISON AT FT.
LEAVENWORTH SAYS THE ARMY DOES
NOT PROVIDE FEMALE HORMONE
TREATMENT OR SEX REASSIGNMENT
SURGERY.
MANNING'S LAWYER PROMISES TO
TAKE IT TO COURT.
>> IT IS CRUEL AND UNUSUAL
PUNISHMENT NOT TO PROVIDE
NECESSARY MEDICAL TREATMENT.
>> Reporter: TRANSGENDER
ADVOCATES ARGUE THAT THE
ULTIMATE DECISION FOR HORMONE
TREATMENT SHOULD BE UP TO
MANNING AND A DOCTOR, NOT THE
WARDEN.
>> PRIVATE MANNING IS
TRANSGENDER AND HAS A GENDER
IDENTITY OF FEMALE REGARDLESS OF
WHAT THE ARMY DOES OR DOESN'T DO
OR THINKS IT WILL OR WON'T DO.
>> Reporter: BUT THERE'S ALSO
CONCERN ABOUT MANNING'S SAFETY.
THE ARMY REPORTS THAT
TRANSGENDER PRISONERS ARE MORE
LIKELY TO BE ASSAULTED BY OTHER
INMATES.
OFFICIALS AT LEAVENWORTH INSIST
THEY'VE TAKEN STEPS TO PROTECT
THOSE PRISONERS LIKE MANNING WHO
MAY BE AT HIGH RISK.
AS FOR THE NAME CHANGE, THE
ARMY'S NOT BUYING IT.
LETTERS SENT TO MANNING AT FT.
LEAVENWORTH HAVE TO BE ADDRESSED
TO BRADLEY.
CHELSEA WON'T MAKE IT.
LESTER?
>> JIM MIKLASZEWSKI TONIGHT,
THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO A BIG MYSTERY THIS
EVENING AFTER HOURS OF CHAOS ON
WALL STREET.
A GLITCH THAT HALTED TRADING ON
THE NATION'S SECOND LARGEST
STOCK EXCHANGE WHERE PEOPLE
TRADE HUGE COMPANIES LIKE APPLE
AND FACEBOOK.
EXPERTS ARE CALLING IT
UNPRECEDENTED, AND TONIGHT IT'S
RAISING A LOT OF QUESTIONS.
CNBC'S BRIAN SULLIVAN IS LIVE AT
THE NASDAQ WITH LATE DETAILS ON
ALL OF THIS.
BRIAN, WHAT HAPPENED?
>> WELL, LESTER, WHAT HAPPENED
WAS WHAT BEGAN AS A RELATIVELY
SLOW SUMMER DAY TURNED INTO
ANYTHING BUT.
RIGHT AROUND 12:30 EASTERN TIME,
AN UNEXPECTED HALT TO TRADING
BEGAN.
YOU MENTIONED SOME OF THE NAMES.
APPLE, YOU'VE GOT GOOGLE,
MICROSOFT, EVEN FACEBOOK.
IT WAS A GLITCH, AND WE'VE
FINALLY GOTTEN A STATEMENT FROM
THE NASDAQ ABOUT AN HOUR AGO,
BUT THEY DID NOT GO INTO DETAIL
ABOUT EXACTLY WHAT HAPPENED.
ALL WE KNOW IS THAT STOCK
TRADING FOR NASDAQ-LISTED STOCKS
DID CEASE FOR ABOUT THREE HOURS
TODAY.
NOW, PRICES IN THE NAMES THAT
YOU MENTIONED, THOSE NAMES WERE
NOT IMPACTED.
AND WITH ABOUT 30 MINUTES LEFT
TO GO IN TRADING THERE WAS A
RESUMPTION.
HOWEVER, MANY MARKET
PARTICIPANTS ARE CALLING THIS
YET ANOTHER BLACK EYE FOR NOT
ONLY THE NASDAQ BUT FOR THIS
HIGHLY TECHNICAL STYLE OF
TRADING THAT WE HAVE DRIVEN
INTO.
REMEMBER WITH FACEBOOK AND THEIR
IPO THERE WAS A PROBLEM.
WE HAD, OF COURSE, THE BIG FLASH
CRASH ON MAY 6th IN 2010.
SO MANY SAYING THAT WHILE
UNDERLYING PRICES, LESTER, MAY
NOT HAVE BEEN AFFECTED, IT IS
YET PERHAPS ANOTHER BLACK EYE TO
ELECTRONIC TRADING AS WELL AS
CONFIDENCE.
I SHOULD NOTE, THE DOW, S&P AND
NASDAQ ACTUALLY ALL DID END THE
DAY HIGHER.
BACK TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT.
BRIAN SULLIVAN.
THANK YOU.
>>> A TOUR BUS HEADED FOR A
CASINO OVERTURNED ON A SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA FREEWAY TODAY.
55 PEOPLE WERE INJURED, ALTHOUGH
MOST OF THE INJURIES HAPPILY
WERE NOT SERIOUS.
AT ONE POINT, WITH THE FREEWAY
CLOSED IN BOTH DIRECTIONS AND
EMERGENCY CREWS HELPING THE
INJURED, THE BACKUP OF TRAFFIC
WAS SAID TO BE 30 MILES LONG.
SOME PEOPLE GOT SO TIRED OF
SITTING STILL THEY GOT OUT OF
THEIR CARS AND WALKED AROUND
RIGHT THERE ON THE FREEWAY.
>>> IN SAN DIEGO, AFTER WEEKS OF
SCANDAL OVER MULTIPLE
ALLEGATIONS OF SEXUAL
HARASSMENT, MAYOR BOB FILNER MAY
BE IN THE FINAL HOURS OF HIS
JOB.
THERE ARE MULTIPLE REPORTS HE IS
RESIGNING TOMORROW.
AFTER NEGOTIATIONS BEHIND CLOSED
DOORS OVER THE PAST THREE DAYS,
FILNER HAS REPORTEDLY AGREED TO
QUIT IN EXCHANGE FOR THE CITY
HANDLING SOME OF HIS LEGAL
COSTS.
CITY COUNCIL IS SAID TO VOTE ON
THE DEAL TOMORROW.
>>> STILL AHEAD, OUR EXCLUSIVE
CONVERSATION WITH KIDNAPPING
SURVIVOR HANNAH ANDERSON.
SETTING THE RECORD STRAIGHT ON
HER ABDUCTION AND COPING TONIGHT
WITH TERRIBLE LOSS.
>>> AND LATER, SHE COMES FROM
RACING ROYALTY.
NOW SHE'S ON TRACK TO FOLLOW
THEIR LEAD WHILE LEAVING A LOT
OF BOYS IN THE DUST.
>>> WE ARE HEARING MORE TONIGHT
FROM HANNAH ANDERSON, THE
16-YEAR-OLD HELD HOSTAGE IN THE
IDAHO WILDERNESS FOR NEARLY A
WEEK BY A FAMILY FRIEND.
SHE SPOKE OUT EXCLUSIVELY TO NBC
NEWS, AND TONIGHT A LOT OF
PEOPLE ARE REACTING TO HER
STORY.
NBC'S KATE SNOW HAS OUR REPORT
FROM SAN DIEGO TONIGHT.
>> IT'S KIND OF HARD, BUT I'M
HANGING IN THERE.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN LESS THAN
THREE WEEKS SINCE HANNAH
ANDERSON WAS ABDUCTED BY FAMILY
FRIEND JAMES DiMAGGIO.
>> THIS GENTLEMAN THAT WAS A
FRIEND OF OURS FOR A LONG TIME
HAS TAKEN EVERYTHING.
>> Reporter: HANNAH DIDN'T HAVE
ANY IDEA THERE WAS AN AMBER
ALERT STRETCHING ACROSS THE
WEST.
>> I LOVE HER DEARLY.
>> Reporter: SHE DIDN'T KNOW
DiMAGGIO HAD ALREADY KILLED HER
MOTHER AND 8-YEAR-OLD BROTHER,
ETHAN.
>> HE HAD A REALLY BIG HEART
AND --
>> Reporter: THE FAMILY HAD
CLEARLY TRUSTED THE MAN THEY
CALLED UNCLE JIM.
AT HIS BURNED-OUT HOME
INVESTIGATORS FOUND LETTERS
HANNAH WROTE TO HIM.
>> THE LETTERS WERE FROM LIKE A
YEAR AGO WHEN ME AND MY MOM
WEREN'T GETTING ALONG VERY WELL.
ME AND HIM WOULD TALK ABOUT HOW
TO DEAL WITH IT.
>> Reporter: DiMAGGIO WOULD
OFTEN GIVE HANNAH RIDES TO AND
FROM ACTIVITIES.
THAT, SHE EXPLAINS, IS WHY THE
TWO EXCHANGED 13 TEXT MESSAGES
ON THE DAY OF HER KIDNAPPING.
>> HE WAS PICKING ME UP FROM
CHEER CAMP, AND HE DIDN'T KNOW
THE ADDRESS.
>> Reporter: BUT AFTER PICKING
HER UP, HE DROVE HER TO THIS
REMOTE PART OF IDAHO WHERE A
GROUP OF HORSEBACK RIDERS SAW
THE ODD COUPLE AND ALERTED
AUTHORITIES.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF WE SAVED HER
LIFE.
I KNOW WE SET THE STAGE FOR
SOMEBODY ELSE TO SAVE HER LIFE.
>> I'D LIKE TO SAY THANK YOU
BECAUSE WITHOUT THEM I PROBABLY
WOULDN'T BE HERE RIGHT NOW.
>> Reporter: WITHIN DAYS, HANNAH
APPEARED AT A CAR WASH
FUND-RAISER FOR HER FAMILY,
POSTED PHOTOS AND MESSAGES
ONLINE.
>> IT JUST HELPS ME GRIEVE, LIKE
POST PICTURES AND TO SHOW HOW
I'M FEELING.
AND I'M A TEENAGER.
I'M GOING TO GO ON IT.
>> Reporter: BUT THAT OPENED HER
UP TO JUDGMENT FROM COMPLETE
STRANGERS.
>> I DIDN'T KNOW PEOPLE COULD BE
SO CRUEL.
THEY DON'T REALLY KNOW THE
STORY, SO THEY KIND OF HAVE
THEIR OWN OPINION ON WHAT THEY
HEAR.
>> Reporter: EVEN TODAY, WHILE
SOME OFFERED PRAYERS AFTER
SEEING HANNAH ON THE "TODAY"
SHOW, MANY WERE SKEPTICAL.
HANNAH SAYS HER MOTHER RAISED
HER TO BE STRONG.
>> THIS WAS A HARD TIME, AND
THERE'S GOING TO BE HARDER TIMES
IN LIFE.
BUT IF I COULD GET THROUGH THIS,
I'M SURE I CAN GET THROUGH A LOT
MORE.
>> Reporter: WHEN WE ASK WHAT
SHE'S LEARNED, SHE HINTS AT PAIN
AND REGRET.
>> TO JUST NOT HOLD A GRUDGE
BECAUSE YOU NEVER KNOW WHEN
SOMEONE CAN BE GONE.
>> Reporter: HANNAH SAYS SHE'S
GETTING READY TO GO BACK TO HIGH
SCHOOL THE DAY AFTER LABOR DAY.
IT WILL BE OVERWHELMING, SHE
SAYS, BECAUSE SO MANY PEOPLE NOW
KNOW HER STORY AND ARE SO
VOCALLY CRITICAL OF HER.
BUT SHE SAYS HER FRIENDS HAVE
HER BACK AND, LESTER, ONE THING
SHE EMPHASIZED IS THAT SHE DOES
NOT WANT ANYONE TO SEE HER AS A
VICTIM BUT AS A SURVIVOR.
LESTER?
>> WELL, SHE IS STRONG AND
CERTAINLY A REMARKABLE YOUNG
LADY.
KATE SNOW, THANKS.
AND "DATELINE" WILL HAVE A FULL
HOUR ON THIS CASE TOMORROW NIGHT
AT 9:00/8:00 CENTRAL.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
AN UNBELIEVABLE SIGHT FOR
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE OUT FOR A DAY
AT THE BEACH.
>>> WHEN HE STARTED THE JOB AS
HEAD OF THE FBI, NOBODY
INCLUDING ROBERT MUELLER HIMSELF
EVER IMAGINED WHAT WAS ABOUT TO
HAPPEN JUST A WEEK LATER.
IT CHANGED AMERICA, THE FBI, AND
THE WORLD.
TONIGHT, AS HE PREPARES TO LEAVE
THE JOB, THE LONGEST-SERVING FBI
DIRECTOR SINCE J. EDGAR HOOVER
SPEAKS WITH OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE WILLIAMS.
>> Reporter: ROBERT MUELLER
BECAME FBI DIRECTOR A WEEK
BEFORE THE SEPTEMBER 11th TERROR
ATTACKS AND DOUBLED THE NUMBER
OF AGENTS ASSIGNED TO TERRORISM.
BUT SOME QUESTIONED THE STING
CASES, PEOPLE WHO HAVE EXPRESSED
ONLY A DESIRE TO ATTACK.
>> I WOULD ASK A DIFFERENT
QUESTION.
HOW DO YOU KNOW WHEN THAT PERSON
WHO HARBORS THE INTENT TO KILL
AMERICAN CITIZENS IS GOING TO
MOVE FROM HARBORING THE INTENT
TO ACTUALLY PICKING UP A PISTOL
AND KILLING 13 PEOPLE?
>> I WAS LOOKING AT YOUR PICTURE
IN THE LOBBY OUT HERE, AND YOU
HAVE MORE GRAY HAIR NOW THAN YOU
DID WHEN YOU BECAME DIRECTOR.
>> I'LL ALSO MENTION, SO DO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, FAIR ENOUGH.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS IT'S BEEN
AN INTENSE 12 YEARS AND
REMEMBERS THE TOUGHEST TIMES.
>> THE HARDEST DAYS THAT YOU
HAVE ARE THOSE WHEN YOU LOSE AN
AGENT IN THE COURSE OF DUTY.
>> Reporter: AND THE MOMENTS OF
UNCERTAINTY, LIKE THE CHAOTIC
HOURS AFTER THE BOSTON MARATHON
BOMBING.
>> THE INVESTIGATION HAD MORE
TWISTS AND TURNS IN THAT VERY
SHORT PERIOD OF TIME THAN IN
MANY INVESTIGATIONS.
YOU WERE UP IN THE AIR IN TERMS
OF WHETHER YOU WERE DOING THE
RIGHT THING, MAKING THE RIGHT
DECISIONS.
>> Reporter: AS FOR THREATS,
MUELLER SAYS CONCERN REMAINS
HIGH THAT TERROR GROUPS MIGHT
TARGET AN AIRLINER USING
IMPLANTED EXPLOSIVES.
ARE YOU GOING TO MISS ALL THIS?
>> YES.
GREAT PEOPLE, GREAT CHALLENGE.
IT'S BEEN A GREAT OPPORTUNITY.
>> Reporter: PETE WILLIAMS, NBC
NEWS AT THE FBI IN WASHINGTON.
>>> WE HAVE SOME PICTURES
TONIGHT YOU HAVE TO SEE TO
BELIEVE.
IN WESTERN RUSSIA IT WAS A QUIET
DAY AT THE BEACH.
SUDDENLY, THIS SHOWED UP, AN
AMPHIBIOUS LANDING CRAFT THAT
SEEMED TO BE COMING IN FOR THAT
LANDING AT FULL SPEED.
SUNBATHERS SCRAMBLED TO GET OUT
OF THE WAY.
THEY WERE SURPRISED.
NOBODY WAS INJURED, THOUGH.
RUSSIAN OFFICIALS SAY THE SHIP
WAS ON A REGULAR TRAINING
EXERCISE.
>>> TAKE A LOOK AT THIS
INCREDIBLE VIDEO FROM THE
LOUISIANA BAYOU.
IT WAS SHOT BY A LOCAL
EMERGENCY MANAGEMENT OFFICIAL,
AS A MASSIVE SINKHOLE DEVOURED
AN ENTIRE ROW OF CYPRUS TREES IN
A MATTER OF SECONDS.
THE SINKHOLE WAS DISCOVERED LAST
SUMMER.
IT HAS SINCE GROWN TO AT LEAST
24 ACRES, NOW FILLED WITH WATER.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, A YOUNG
LADY WITH A NEED FOR SPEED.
NO WONDER.
IT'S IN HER BLOOD.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, A YOUNG
LADY WITH A LEGENDARY NAME NOW
GOING INTO THE FAMILY BUSINESS.
MORE THAN 12 YEARS AGO WHEN THE
GREAT DALE EARNHARDT DIED IN A
CRASH AT THE DAYTONA 500, HE WAS
JUST 49 YEARS OLD, AND HIS
GRANDDAUGHTER CARSON WAS JUST 5
MONTHS OLD.
TONIGHT, NBC'S KATY TUR
INTRODUCES US TO THE NEWEST
MEMBER OF THE EARNHARDT RACING
FAMILY.
>> Reporter: ON THE OUTSIDE,
12-YEAR-OLD CARSON MAY LOOK LIKE
YOUR TYPICAL PRETEEN.
RIDING BIKES, STYLING HAIR, AND
SNAPPING SELFIES.
BUT ON THE INSIDE, SHE'S AN
EARNHARDT, RACE CAR ROYALTY.
DALE EARNHARDT WAS HER
GRANDFATHER, DALE JR. IS HER
UNCLE.
>> IT'S LIKE I'VE GOT CARS GOING
THROUGH MY BLOOD VEINS.
I KNOW IT SOUNDS CRAZY BUT IT'S
TRUE.
>> Reporter: PEDAL TO THE METAL,
45 MILES AN HOUR ON A DIRT
TRACK.
WHY DO YOU LIKE RACING SO MUCH?
>> I LIKE RACING BECAUSE I LIKE
GOING FAST.
>> YOU LIKE A LITTLE DANGER.
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: FOR THE LAST THREE
MONTHS, CARSON TOURED THE WEST
RACING WITH HER DAD.
CALL IT HER SUMMER SCHOOL.
>> I KNEW THAT MY GRANDFATHER
AND MY UNCLE WERE RACE CAR
DRIVERS, FAMOUS ONES, BUT IT
DIDN'T ALL START REALLY SINKING
IN AND I DIDN'T START REALLY
THINKING ABOUT IT UNTIL I WAS
11.
>> SHE REMINDS ME OF MY DAD AND
ESPECIALLY HER AGGRESSIVE NATURE
ON THE TRACK.
>> Reporter: CARSON HAS
LITERALLY GROWN UP ON THE
TRACKS, BUT A FEW YEARS AGO SHE
DECIDED IT WAS TIME SHE TOOK THE
WHEEL, RACING AND WINNING WITH
HER GRANDDAD'S LEGENDARY NUMBER
3.
NICKELODEON NOTICED IN JUNE AND
SPONSORED HER CART.
HERE CARSON IS UNRIVALED BY BOTH
THE GIRLS AND THE BOYS.
ARE THEY INTIMIDATED BY YOU, DO
YOU THINK?
>> PROBABLY.
MOST LIKELY.
>> Reporter: WHY IS THAT?
>> BECAUSE I COME ON STRONG.
>> GO GET THEM, GIRL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT'S RACE IS
HER LAST BEFORE SCHOOL, AND SHE
IS LAPPING THE COMPETITION UNTIL
CARSON CLIPS ANOTHER CART AND
GOES HEADFIRST INTO THE WALL.
A SCARY MOMENT FOR THE PRE-TEEN,
EVEN SCARIER FOR MOM, WHO RAN TO
HER SIDE.
BUT CARSON WAS OKAY, ONE CRASH
NOT ENOUGH TO STOP HER FROM
RACING.
>> ACCIDENTS CAN HAPPEN
ANYWHERE, AND YOU CAN'T LIVE
LIFE IN A BUBBLE TRYING TO
PREVENT SOMETHING FROM HAPPENING
OR YOU'RE GOING TO LOSE WHAT
LIFE IS ABOUT.
>> Reporter: BY MONDAY, THE
CRASH IS OLD NEWS.
FOR NOW, IT'S BACK TO SCHOOL BUT
NEVER QUITE BACK TO NORMAL FOR A
GIRL WITH THE LEGACY OF
CHAMPIONS AND THE DRIVE TO LIVE
UP TO IT.
KATY TUR, NBC NEWS, SALISBURY,
NORTH CAROLINA.
>>> THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR
THIS THURSDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NBC BAY AREA NEWS STARTS
NOW.
>>> THANKS FOR JOINING US.
>>> WE BEGIN WITH A DEVELOPING
STORY WE'VE BEEN FOLLOWING FOR
DAYS.
WE SHOW YOU THIS WILDFIRE STILL
BURNING NEAR YOSEMITE.
RIGHT NOW IT IS TWICE THE SIZE
OF SAN FRANCISCO.
IT'S FORCED THE GOVERNOR TO
DECLARE A STATE OF EMERGENCY SO
HE CAN FREE UP MONEY AND ALSO SO
HE CAN FREE UP RESOURCES.
WE TOLD YOU YESTERDAY THIS FIRE
WAS AT 5% CONTAINED.
BUT IT BLEW UP OVERNIGHT.
AT THIS POINT, THOUSANDS OF
AT RISK.
NBC'S JODI HERNANDEZ HAS BEEN
FOLLOWING THE FIRE.
>> Reporter: FIREFIGHTERS ARE
THROWING EVERYTHING THEY HAVE AT
THIS FIRE, BUT THEY'VE MADE
LITTLE PROGRESS.
TO SAY THAT THE FIRE CONDITIONS
ARE EXTREME OUT HERE IS A MAJOR
UNDERSTATEMENT.
FIREFIGHTERS ARE BATTLING THE
HEAT, THE WIND, AND A FIRE THAT
THEY SAY HAS A MIND OF ITS OWN.
NOW FIREFIGHTERS ARE ACTUALLY
LOSING GROUND TODAY.
YESTERDAY THEY HAD THE FIRE 5%
CONTAINED.
TODAY, THAT HAS SLIPPED BACK TO
JUST 2%.
MORE THAN÷fx 54,000 ACRES HAVE
BURNED.
AND THAT FIGURE IS MOST
DEFINITELY IS GOING TO GO UP
WHEN THEY HAVE A CHANCE TO GO UP
AND DO AN AERIAL SURVEY.
ABOUT 1500 HOMES REMAIN
THREATENED AND HUNDREDS OF
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN EVACUATED.
THE FIRE HAS CROSSED HIGHWAY 120
SEVERAL TIMES.
WE SAW CREWS WORKING TO REMAYOR