HAVE DRIZZLE AND OTHERWISE, FOG
FOR YOUR MORNING COMMUTE.
>> GOOD-BYE.
THIS SUNDAY NIGHT --
NATIONAL SECURITY.
BUT AT WHAT PRICE?
THE FIRESTORM OVER THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION'S
COUNTERTERRORISM PROGRAM.
NOW IN AN NBC NEWS EXCLUSIVE, A
VIGOROUS DEFENSE FROM THE
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE.
>>> WATCHING AND WAITING.
WE'RE LIVE IN SOUTH AFRICA
TONIGHT AS CONCERNS GROW ABOUT
THE FAILING HEALTH OF FORMER
PRESIDENT NELSON MANLA.
>>> ON TRIAL.
JURY SELECTION BEGINS TOMORROW
IN THE CASE AGAINST GEORGE
ZIMMERMAN, ACCUSED OF MURDERING
TRAYVON MARTIN, AS NEW QUESTIONS
EMERGE ABOUT THE VOICES ON THAT
911 TAPE.
>>> PAIN AT THE PUMP.
GAS PRICES SOARING IN THE
MIDWEST.
TONIGHT, WHY THE HEARTLAND IS
FEELING THE PINCH.
>>> AND BATTLE BUDDIES.
UNCONDITIONAL LOVE FOR RETURNING
VETS LIVING WITH STRESSFUL
DISORDERS.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THE APPARENT SOURCE WHO EXPOSED
THE GOVERNMENT'S TOP-SECRET
COLLECTION OF PHONE RECORDS HAS
REVEALED HIMSELF.
SO SAYS THE PUBLICATION THAT
BROKE THE STORY LAST WEEK.
"THE GUARDIAN" PULLED THE COVERS
OFF AN ONGOING U.S. INTELLIGENCE
PROGRAM THAT'S QUIETLY COLLECTED
THE PHONE RECORDS OF MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS IN THE NAME OF
NATIONAL SECURITY.
TONIGHT THE SELF-IDENTIFIED
SOURCE OF THAT STORY HAS STEPPED
FORWARD TO EXPLAIN HIMSELF.
WHILE THE U.S. DIRECTOR OF
NATIONAL INTELLIGENCE IN AN
EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEW WITH NBC
NEWS IS DISPUTING SOME OF HIS
CLAIMS.
CHIEF FOREIGN AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT ANDREA MITCHELL
SPOKE TO JAMES CLAPPER AND JOINS
US FROM OUR WASHINGTON NEWSROOM.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
TONIGHT "THE GUARDIAN" POSTED
THE INTERVIEW WITH THE
INTELLIGENCE CONTRACTOR WHO
WANTS TO GO PUBLIC, TO THAT
NEWSPAPER AS WELL AS "THE
WASHINGTON POST".
>> MY NAME IS ED SNOWDEN.
I'M 29 YEARS OLD.
I WORK FOR BOOZ ALLEN HAMILTON
AS AN INFRASTRUCTURE ANALYST FOR
NSA IN HAWAII.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS HE COPIED
TOP-SECRET DOCUMENTS, PACKED HIS
BAGS AND WENT TO HONG KONG TO
SHARE WITH THE GUARDIAN'S GLEN
GREENWALD.
>> I CERTAINLY SITTING AT MY
DESK HAD THE AUTHORITY TO
WIRETAP ANYONE FROM YOU, YOUR
ACCOUNTANT, TO A FEDERAL JUDGE,
OR EVEN THE PRESIDENT IF I HAD A
PERSONAL E-MAIL.
>> Reporter: HIS CLAIM IS
CONTRADICTED BY WHAT THE
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE TOLD US EXCLUSIVELY
ON SATURDAY.
>> WE ARE UNDER STRICT COURT
SUPERVISION.
THE NOTION THAT WE'RE TROLLING
THROUGH EVERYONE'S E-MAILS AND
VOYEURISTICALLY READING THEM OR
LISTENING TO EVERYONE'S PHONE
CALLS IS, ON ITS FACE, ABSURD.
WE COULDN'T DO IT EVEN IF WE
WANTED TO.
I ASSURE YOU, WE DON'T WANT TO.
>> Reporter: WHY DID HE DO IT?
SNOWDEN SAYS HE BECAME
DISENCHANTED WHILE WORKING FOR
THE CIA AND LATER GOT HARDENED
WHILE AT THE NSA.
>> I'M JUST ANOTHER GUY WHO SITS
THERE DAY TO DAY IN THE OFFICE
WATCHES WHAT'S HAPPENING AND
GOES, THIS IS SOMETHING THAT'S
NOT OUR PLACE TO DECIDE.
THE PUBLIC NEEDS TO DECIDE
WHETHER THESE PROGRAMS AND
POLICIES ARE RIGHT OR WRONG.
>> Reporter: ANALYSTS LIKE
SNOWLEN USE THE WORLD'S MOST
SOPHISTICATED COMPUTERS TO SIFT
THROUGH A HUGE AMOUNT OF DATA.
EVEN MORE WILL BE STORED IN THIS
NEW FACILITY IN UTAH, ALL LEGAL
SINCE 2008, RE-AUTHORIZED BY
CONGRESS IN 2012 AND REVIEWED
EVERY THREE MONTHS BY A SECRET
COURT.
CRITICS SAID TODAY MORE
OVERSIGHT IS NEEDED.
>> THE FACT THAT EVERY CALL I
MAKE TO MY FRIENDS AND FAMILY IS
NOTED, WHERE I AM, THE LENGTH OF
IT, THE DATE, THAT CONCERNS ME.
PARTICULARLY BECAUSE AMERICANS
DIDN'T KNOW THIS.
THAT'S WHY MANY'S CALLING FOR
REOPENING THE PATRIOT ACT.
>> Reporter: BEFORE SNOWLEN
REVEALED HIMSELF, I ASKED THE
INTELLIGENCE CHIEF ABOUT THE
LEAKER.
>> THIS IS SOMEONE WHO, FOR
WHATEVER REASON, HAS CHOSEN TO
VIOLATE A SECRET TRUST FOR THIS
COUNTRY.
DAMAGE THAT THESE REVELATIONS
INCUR ARE HUGE.
>> Reporter: CAN I ASSUME FROM
THAT, INFER THAT THERE HAS BEEN
A REFERRAL TO TRACK DOWN THE
LEAK?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WE HAVE -- NSA HAS FILED A
CRIMES REPORT ON THIS ALREADY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT BOOZ ALLEN
CONFIRMED HE WORKED FOR THE
COMPANY LESS THAN THREE MONTHS.
THEY SAID IF THE REPORTS ARE
ACCURATE ABOUT THE LEAKS THEY
ARE SHOCKED AND THEY WOULD WORK
CLOSELY WITH THE AUTHORITIES ON
THE INVESTIGATION.
>>> TONIGHT WHILE WE'VE LEARNED
WHO THE APPARENT GUNMAN WAS IN
THE DEADLY RAMPAGE AT SANTA
MONICA COMMUNITY COLLEGE IN
CALIFORNIA FRIDAY, POLICE ARE
TRYING TO DETERMINE HIS MOTIVE.
THIS AS A FIFTH VICTIM, A
STUDENT, HAS DIED FROM HER
WOUNDS.
NOW THE LATEST ON THE
INVESTIGATION.
>> Reporter: THIS WAS THE MOMENT
POLICE SAY THE GUNMAN ENTERED
THE LIBRARY AT SANTA MONICA
COLLEGE ARMED TO KILL.
THE SHOOTER IS A 23-YEAR-OLD
STUDENT ONCE ENROLLED AT THE
COLLEGE.
>> THE POLICE DEPARTMENT DID
HAVE CONTACT WITH THIS
INDIVIDUAL IN 2006.
HOWEVER, BECAUSE THE INDIVIDUAL
WAS A JUVENILE AT THE TIME, I AM
NOT AT LIBERTY TO DISCUSS
CIRCUMSTANCES OF THE CONTACT.
>> Reporter: POLICE ARE
INVESTIGATING WHAT MAY HAVE
MOTIVATED THE GUNMAN TO GO ON
A CALCULATED SHOOTING RAMPAGE.
>> I WOULD PRESUME THAT ANY TIME
SOMEONE PUTS ON A VEST, COMES
OUT WITH A BAG FULL OF LOADED
MAGAZINES, HAS A HANDGUN, HAS A
SEMI-AUTOMATIC RIFLE AND CAR
JACKS FOLKS, GOES TO A COLLEGE,
KILLS MORE PEOPLE, I WOULD SAY
THAT'S PREMEDITATED.
>> Reporter: IT BEGAN FRIDAY
AROUND NOON WHEN SHOTS WERE
REPORTED NEAR A HOUSE ON FIRE.
LAW ENFORCEMENT SOURCES SAY
ZAWAHIRI ALLEGEDLY TARGETED AND
KILLED HIS FATHER AND BROTHER
INSIDE THAT HOME, THEN HIJACKED
THE CAR DEMANDING THE DRIVER
TAKE HIM TO THE COLLEGE CAMPUS.
ALONG THE WAY OPENING FIRE ON A
CITY BUS.
ONCE ON CAMPUS OFFICIALS SAY
ZAWAHIRI ENTERED THE SCHOOL'S
LIBRARY AND FIRED MORE THAN 70
ROUNDS.
IT WAS THERE ZAWAHIRI WAS SHOT
AND KILLED BY POLICE.
SOME OF THE 1,300 ROUNDS OF
AMMUNITION, WEAPONS AND GEAR THE
SUSPECT WERE CARRYING WERE
RECOVERED ON CAMPUS.
TODAY THE COLLEGE COMMUNITY
MOURNED TWO OF ITS OWN --
26-YEAR-OLD MARCELLA FRANCO, A
STUDENT, AND HER FATHER, CARLOS,
A GROUNDSKEEPER.
>> HER FATHER WAS VERY WELL
LIKED AND RESPECTED.
>> Reporter: THE TWO WERE
DRIVING TO THE CAMPUS WHEN THEIR
CAR WAS ATTACKED.
NOW COUNSELORS HAVE CALLED TO
HELP GRIEVE STUDENTS AS FINAL
EXAMS GO AHEAD ON MONDAY.
NBC NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> IN SOUTH AFRICA THERE IS
GROWING CONCERN TONIGHT ABOUT
THE FAILING HEALTH OF FORMER
PRESIDENT NELSON MANDELA.
THE 94-YEAR-OLD IS IN THE
HOSPITAL AGAIN, THE FOURTH TIME
SINCE DECEMBER, WITH A RECURRING
LUNG INFECTION.
UNLIKE PREVIOUS HOSPITAL VISITS,
THIS TIME PUBLIC STATEMENTS
ABOUT HIS CONDITION HAVE BEEN
LESS ENCOURAGING.
NBC'S KIER SIMMONS IS OUTSIDE
THE HOME IN JOHANNESBURG FOR US
HERE.
WHAT'S THE LATEST?
>> Reporter: THIS IS THE FIRST
TIME THAT NELSON MANDELA'S
CONDITION HAS BEEN DESCRIBED AS
SERIOUS, THOUGH DOCTORS SAY HE
IS STABLE AND SAID TO BE ABLE TO
BREATHE INDEPENDENTLY.
TODAY SOME OF HIS CHILDREN AND
GRANDCHILDREN VISITED THE
HOSPITAL WHERE HE IS SAID TO BE
BEING TREATED FOR THE RECURRENT
LUNG INFECTION.
AND HIS DAUGHTER LEFT TONIGHT
SMILING, SAYING THERE HAS BEEN
NO NEWS OF ANY IMPROVEMENT FROM
HIS FAMILY OR FROM THE SOUTH
AFRICAN GOVERNMENT SINCE HE WAS
RUSHED TO THE HOSPITAL IN EARLY
HOURS OF SATURDAY MORNING.
THE LAST TIME WE SAW NELSON
MANDELA IN PUBLIC HE WAS LOOKING
FRAIL.
FILMED BY THE SOUTH AFRICAN
BROADCASTING CORPORATION.
PEOPLE WERE SHOCKED BY THE
PICTURES BUT ARE NOW TOLD TO
PRAY FOR NELSON MANDELA.
ONE LIFE-LONG FRIEND HAS TOLD A
NEWSPAPER THAT IT IS TIME TO LET
NELSON MANDELA GO.
STILL, MANY ARE PRAYING FOR HIS
SWIFT RECOVERY.
>>> IN TURKEY, A TENTH STRAIGHT
DAY OF UNREST AS RIOT POLICE USE
TEARGAS AND WATER CANNONS
TO BATTLE PROTESTERS DEMANDING
THE GOVERNMENT HOLD NEW
ELECTIONS.
NBC'S CHIEF FOREIGN
CORRESPONDENT RICHARD ENGEL IS
IN ISTANBUL TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: IT IS THE BIGGEST
PROTEST MOVEMENT AGAINST PRIME
MINISTER ERDOWAN IN HIS DECADE
RULING TURKEY.
TENS OF THOUSANDS IN ISTANBUL
ALONE.
FEELING MORE LIKE OCCUPY WALL
STREET THAN EGYPT'S TAHRIR
SQUARE.
THE PROTESTS WERE TRIGGERED BY
PLANS TO BULLDOZE A PARK.
BUT WHEN POLICE MOVED IN IN
FORCE, PROTESTS GREW WAY BEYOND
THE DISPUTE OVER URBAN PLANNING.
PROTESTERS HERE SAY ERDOWAN IS
TRYING TO IMPOSE AN ISLAMIC
AGENDA AND OVERTURN 90 YEARS OF
SECULAR GOVERNMENT IN THIS
COUNTRY.
IT IS A DEMONSTRATION ABOUT THE
VERY NATURE OF TURKEY AND A
REJECTION OF ERDOWAN'S VISION
OF A ISLAMIC DEMOCRACY.
TURKEY'S TRADITION IS EMBODIED
BY THE FOUNDER AFTER THE
REPUBLIC AFTER WORLD WAR I.
HIS PORTRAIT STILL HANGS IN
NEARLY EVERY STORE.
IT IS ON ALL OF THE CURRENCY.
BUTTERED BUT ERDOWAN HAS BEEN
BRINGING CHANGE, BANNING SALES
OF ALCOHOL.
ENCOURAGING WOMEN TO HAVE LARGE
FAMILIES, CHALLENGING ABORTION
RIGHTS.
THE PROTESTERS SAID ENOUGH IS
ENOUGH.
BUT ERDOWAN HAS HIS SUPPORTERS,
TOO.
HE WAS, AFTER ALL, ELECTED THREE
TIMES AND, UNDER HIM, TURKEY'S
ECONOMY HAS BOOMED WITH BUILDING
EVERYWHERE.
NEW BRIDGES, A NEW AIRPORT.
ERDOWAN SUPPORTERS TODAY
DEMONSTRATED IN ANKARA, STICKING
WITH THE MAN CRITICS ARE CALLING
TURKEY'S NEW SULTAN.
RICHARD ENGEL, NBC NEWS,
ISTANBUL.
>>> PRESIDENT OBAMA AND CHINA'S
PRESIDENT JINPING WRAPPED UP A
MEETING TODAY.
THEY MOVED CLOSER ON PRESSURING
NORTH KOREA'S NUCLEAR PROGRAM.
THEY ALSO REACHED AN AGREEMENT
ABOUT CLIMATE CHANGE BUT
DIVISIONS REMAIN OVER CHINA'S
ALLEGED CYBER HACKING.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYING CONTINUED
CYBER ATTACKS COMING FROM CHINA
COULD STRAIN ECONOMIC RELATIONS
BETWEEN THE WORLD'S TWO BIGGEST
ECONOMIES.
>>> JURY SELECTION IS SET TO
BEGIN TOMORROW IN THE TRIAL OF
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN ACCUSED OF
MURDERING OF TEENAGER TRAYVON
MARTIN.
THERE SEEMS TO BE UNFINISHED
BUSINESS THAT COULD IMPACT THE
OUTCOME OF THIS CASE.
IT INVOLVES WHOSE VOICE CAN BE
HEARD SCREAMING FOR HELP ON A
911 CALL, GEORGE ZIMMERMAN OR
TRAYVON MARTIN.
>> Reporter: FOR THE LAST THREE
DAYS --
>> IN ORDER TO RUN THE TEST, I
HAD TO DOUBLE UP THE ACTUAL
SCREAMS.
>> Reporter: PROSECUTORS AND
LAWYERS FOR GEORGE ZIMMERMAN
HAVE SPARRED OVER VOICE
ANALYSIS.
>> THE SCREAMS DON'T MATCH AT
ALL.
THAT'S WHAT TELLS ME THAT, OKAY,
IT'S NOT GEORGE ZIMMERMAN.
>> THAT RECORDING ISN'T EVEN
REMOTELY SUITABLE FOR COMPARISON
PURPOSES.
>> Reporter: THE CENTRAL
QUESTION -- EXACTLY WHO IS
YELLING IN A 911 CALL WHILE
GEORGE ZIMMERMAN AND 17-YEAR-OLD
TRAYVON MARTIN ENGAGED IN A
PHYSICAL STRUGGLE BEFORE MARTIN
WAS SHOT AND KILLED IN FEBRUARY
OF LAST YEAR.
>> IS HE YELLING HELP?
>> YES.
>> WHAT IS YOUR NAME AND PHONE
NUMBER?
>> YOU JUST HEARD GUNSHOTS?
>> YES.
>> HOW SFM.
>> JUST ONE.
>> Reporter: RATHER THAN DELAY
MONDAY'S SCHEDULED START OF JURY
SELECTION IN ZIMMERMAN'S MURDER
TRIAL, THE JUDGE POSTPONED A
HEARING TO DETERMINE WHETHER
VOICE RECOGNITION EXPERTS WILL
BE ALLOWED TO TESTIFY DURING THE
TRIAL.
>> WE'LL FILE A MOTION.
>> Reporter: ZIMMERMAN'S
ATTORNEY SAYS HER DECISION COULD
BE CRUCIAL.
>> THEN THE POINT BECOMES THE
THRESHOLD WHETHER IT IS GOING TO
CONFUSE THE JURY OR ASSIST THEM.
IF THERE IS A CHANCE OF
CONFUSING THEM, WE SHOULDN'T DO
IT.
IF IT IS GOING TO ASSIST THEM,
WE SHOULD.
>> HE SAID YOU HAVE A PROBLEM?
I TURNED AROUND.
I SAID NO, I DON'T HAVE A
PROBLEM, MAN.
>> Reporter: THE DAY AFTER
THE SHOOTING, ZIMMERMAN TOLD
POLICE HE SHOT MARTIN AFTER
BEING KNOCKED TO THE GROUND AND
HAVING HIS HEAD BEATEN IN TO THE
SIDEWALK BY THE TEEN.
>> I FELT MY ARM GOING DOWN MY
SIDE.
I GRABBED MY FIREARM AND SHOT IT
ONE TIME.
>> HE WASN'T CHARGED UNTIL SIX
WEEKS LATER.
BY A SPECIAL OUTSIDE PROSECUTOR.
SPARKING PROTESTS ABOUT THE
HESITATION OF LOCAL AUTHORITIES
TO ARREST HIM.
HE'S PLEADED NOT GUILTY TO
SECOND DEGREE MURDER.
MARTIN'S PARENTS CONTEND THEIR
SON DID NOTHING UNLAWFUL THAT
NIGHT, HE WAS SIMPLY RETURNING
TO THE CONDO WHERE HIS DAD WAS
STAYING AFTER BUYING CANDY AND A
SOFT DRINK AT A CONVENIENCE
STORE.
>> YOU HAVE GEORGE ZIMMERMAN
WHO'S ALIVE.
HAVE YOU TRAYVON MARTIN WHO'S
NOT HERE TO TELL HIS STORY.
OF COURSE YOU'RE GOING TO BLAME
THE VICTIM.
>> IT COULD TAKE UP TO SIX WEEKS
BEFORE A PANEL OF SIX IS
ULTIMATELY SEATED.
>> GEORGE ZIMMERMAN HAS SUED NBC
UNIVERSAL FOR DEFAMATION.
THE COMPANY HAS STRONGLY DENIED
HIS ALLEGATIONS.
>>> TONIGHT THE MAN AT THE
CONTROLS OF THE EXCAVATOR IN THE
PHILADELPHIA BUILDING COLLAPSE
THAT KILLED SIX PEOPLE HAS
SURRENDERED TO AUTHORITIES AND
IS BEING HELD WITHOUT BAIL THE
242-YEAR-OLD NASS MULTIPLE
COUNTS OF INVOLUNTARY
MANSLAUGHTER, RECKLESS
ENDANGERMENT AND RISK IS A
CATASTROPHE.
TOXICOLOGY REPORTS SHOW HE HAD
MARIJUANA AND PAINKILLERS IN HIS
SYSTEM AT THE TIME OF THE
ACCIDENT.
>>> WHEN "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
CONTINUES ON THIS SUNDAY -- GAS
PRICES STABLE IN SOME PLACES BUT
SOARING IN OTHERS.
WHO'S TAKING THE BEATING AT THE
PUMP AND WHY.
>>> IT IS THAT TIME OF YEAR FOR
THE TIME HONORED TRADITION OF
HAILING TO THE VALEDICTORIAN,
ALL 21 OF THEM, IN THIS CASE.
>>> THE PRICE OF GASOLINE,
ALWAYS A CONCERN AT THE START OF
THE SUMMER DRIVING SEASON.
BUT NOW FOCUS HAS SHIFTED TO THE
MIDWEST WHERE PRICES AT THE PUMP
ARE SOARING.
NBC'S JOHN YANG EXPLAINS WHY.
>>> RIDICULOUS!
>> Reporter: FORGET STICKER
SHOCK.
>> $4.60 -- THAT'S A LOT.
>> Reporter: ACROSS THE MIDWEST,
IT'S GAS PUMP SHOCK.
>> WHAT'S GOING ON?
WHAT'S HAPPENING?
>> Reporter: IN THE HEARTLAND,
THE START OF THE SUMMER VACATION
SEASON IS SEEING A PRICE SURGE
IN SOME PLACES CLOSE TO RECORD
LEVELS.
>> THAT'S $4.
THAT MAKES YOU FEEL LIKE YOU'RE
BEING STRANGLED.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING TO AAA,
THE NATIONAL AVERAGE FOR A
GALLON OF REGULAR IS $3.63.
BUT IN FOUR MIDWESTERN STATES,
THE AVERAGE IS MORE THAN $4.
IN MICHIGAN -- $4.23, UP 17
CENTS IN JUST THE LAST WEEK TO
THE HIGHEST IN THE CONTINENTAL
UNITED STATES.
SOME MOTORISTS ARE TRYING TO CUT
BACK.
>> INSTEAD OF DRIVING THE KIDS
TO SCHOOL, I WALK THEM.
>> Reporter: ANALYSTS BLAME
TIGHT SUPPLIES BROUGHT ON BY
PROBLEMS AT REFINERIES IN THE
REGION, INCLUDING AN APRIL
EXPLOSION AND FIRE AT THIS PLANT
IN DETROIT.
OTHERS ARE CLOSED FOR SCHEDULED
MAINTENANCE THAT'S TAKING LONGER
THAN EXPECTED.
>> DECLINING NUMBER OF
REFINERIES THAT MEANT, THAT,
ONE, A FACILITY HAS GONE OFFLINE
AND IT IS A BIG DEAL.
>> Reporter: IT COULD TAKE
SEVERAL WEEKS FOR SOME
REFINERIES IN THE MIDWEST TO GET
RUNNING AND PRICES TO FALL.
NATIONWIDE SOME PRICES ARE
RELATIVELY STABLE AND HAVE EVEN
DROPPED IN AREAS OF THE
SOUTHEAST.
>> THIS SUMMER SHOULD NOT BE AS
BAD AS LAST YEAR.
>> Reporter: BUT FOR NOW, MANY
MIDWEST MOTORISTS ARE FRUSTRATED
AND FUMING AT THE PUMP.
>> THERE GOES ALL MY VACATION
MONEY.
>> Reporter: ANIMAL LIS SAY THE
SHRINKING NUMBER OF REFINERIES
IN THE UNITED STATES MAKES THIS
KIND OF REGIONAL PRICE
VOLATILITY MORE COMMON.
JOHN YANG, NBC NEWS, CHICAGO.
>>> WHEN "NIGHTLY NEWS"
CONTINUES ON THIS SUNDAY, WE'LL
TAKE YOU TO THE HEAD OF THE
CLASS WHERE THERE'S ALWAYS ROOM
AT THE TOP FOR MORE.
>>> IT IS THAT TIME OF YEAR WHEN
WE RECOGNIZE THE HARD WORK OF
OUR HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATES AND
ACADEMIC ACHIEVEMENT OF THAT ONE
SPECIAL VALEDICTORIAN.
BUT AS NBC'S MIKE TAIBBI FOUND
OUT, IN SOME PLACES IT IS PRETTY
CROWDED AT THE TOP.
>> Reporter: PART OF THE RITUAL
OF HIGH SCHOOL GRADUATION IS THE
GRADUATION REHEARSAL.
INCLUDING THE SPEECH BY THE
CLASS VALEDICTORIAN.
BUT AT SOUTH MEDFORD HIGH SCHOOL
IN SOUTHERN OREGON, THERE ISN'T
JUST ONE VALEDICTORIAN.
THERE ARE 21.
PART OF A TREND THAT'S BEEN
SPREADING NATIONWIDE.
34 IN ONE ALABAMA HIGH SCHOOL.
NINE IN A SMALL OHIO SCHOOL WITH
ONLY 84 SENIORS.
THE PRINCIPAL SAYS HIS 21
MEDFORD SOUTH STARS ALL DESERVE
THE DISTINCTION.
>> OUR SYSTEM IS IF EVERYBODY IS
A 4.0, EVERYBODY IS A
VALEDICTORIAN.
>> Reporter: IT IS CONTROVERSIAL
THOUGH.
ONE EXPERT IN COLLEGE ADMISSIONS
SAYING THOSE BIG NUMBERS DILUTE
THE VALEDICTORIAN BRAND, RAISE
QUESTIONS, IF NOT SUSPICIONS.
>> IT DOES MAKE US WONDER AT A
CERTAIN POINT IS THERE A LOT OF
RIGOR TO THE WAY THAT SCHOOL
GIVES OUT AIDS?
>> Reporter: MEDFORD'S
DISTINGUISHED 21 ARE BEING
ATTACKED SAYING ALL THEY'VE DONE
IS ALL THEY'VE BEEN ASKED TO
NUMERICAL PERFECTION.
LIKE BREA WHO INHALED COLLEGE
PREP COURSES.
>> WE ALL HAVE THE VALUE OF OUR
OWN PERSONAL EDUCATION AND WE
KNOW THE CHALLENGES THAT WE'VE
TAKEN ON.
>> LUIS WITH NO ENGLISH WHEN HE
ARRIVED HERE.
>> TO MAKE THIS A ACCOMPLISHMENT
OF BEING A 4.0 STUDENT NOW IS A
GREAT ACCOMPLISHMENT FOR MYSELF
AND MY FAMILY.
>> Reporter: AND ZACH SNYDER,
COMPUTER WHIZ.
>> WE'VE BEEN IN ALL OF THESE
STRUGGLES TOGETHER.
OUR PARENTS AND WE ALIKE ALL
AGREE THAT WE'VE ALL EARNED THIS
TITLE.
>> Reporter: AND WHETHER IT IS
ONE OR 21, BEING A VOICE FOR
YOUR GRADUATING CLASS MATTERS.
I STILL REMEMBER MY
VALEDICTORIAN'S SPEECH AT MY K
THROUGH 6 GRAMMAR SCHOOL.
YEAH, THAT'S ME.
IT STARTED --
THERE ARE SEVEN DAYS OF THE
WEEK, THERE ARE SEVEN WONDERS OF
THE WORLD, THERE ARE SEVEN HOLES
IN YOUR HEAD, AND THERE ARE
SEVEN PLAYS TO LENDER PLACE
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL.
YOU HAD TO BE THERE.
NO JOKES ON THEIR BIG NIGHT.
THIS IS NOT GRAMMAR SCHOOL, IT
IS HIGH SCHOOL.
>> THE ONLY WAY TO BE THE BEST
IN THE WORLD IS TO COMMIT
YOURSELF TO WHAT YOU CARE ABOUT
AND LIVING WITH PURPOSE.
>> Reporter: GOOD STUFF FROM 21
SENIORS WHO CAN EACH SAY I'M
NUMBER ONE -- AND FORGET THE AS
TERISK.
>>> HISTORY MAKING DAY AT FRENCH
OPEN TODAY.
RAFAEL NADAL BECAME THE ONLY MAN
TO WIN EIGHT GRAND SLAM TITLES.
ADDING TO THE DRAMA,
A PROTESTER HELD A FLARE TO JUMP
FROM THE STANDS ON TO THE COURT
AND WAS SUBDUED.
YESTERDAY SERENA WILLIAMS TOPPED
MARIA SHARAPOVA TO WIN HER 16th
GRAND SLAM TITLE.
>>> IN A MOMENT, WHEN THE BATTLE
ENDS AND A NEW ONE BEGINS --
DOGS COME TO THE RESCUE OF SOME
RETURNING VETERANS.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT -- HELPING
OUR COMBAT VETERANS FACE THE
DIFFICULT TRANSITION WHEN THEY
RETURN HOME.
NBC'S DAVE GUTIERREZ REPORTS ON
A NEW KIND OF THERAPY THAT'S
COME TO THE RESCUE.
>> Reporter: AT FT. BRAGG, NORTH
CAROLINA --
>> LOOK AT THAT FACE!
>> Reporter: -- A RESCUE
OPERATION IS UNDER WAY.
DOGS AT THIS SHELTER ARE STRAYS.
OR, LIKE ZOE, HAD TO BE LEFT
BEHIND BY DEPLOYED SOLDIERS.
BUT RESCUING THEM IS ONLY THE
FIRST PART OF THE MISSION
THROUGH A PROGRAM CALLED
GUARDIANS OF RESCUE, THEY'LL
BECOME THERAPY DOGS.
BUDDIES FOR SOLDIERS RETURNING
FROM BATTLE WITH POST TRAUMATIC
STRESS.
>> QUITE SURE SHE'LL MAKE
SOMEBODY HAPPY.
>> Reporter: JOHN WALLACE KNOWS.
A GUARDIAN VOLUNTEER AND FORMER
ARMY INFANTRY MAN IN
AFGHANISTAN, HE'S RECOVERING
FROM PTSD HIMSELF AND GOT HIS
DOG TOMMY LAST FALL.
>> HAVING A DOG HAS COMPLETELY
BROUGHT ME OUT OF THE HELL THAT
I WAS LIVING IN.
>> Reporter: TO HELP OTHERS LIKE
JOHN, ZOE AND THE OTHER DOGS
ARE BROUGHT IN NORTH CAROLINA TO
NEW YORK FOR SOME INTENSIVE
TRAINING.
AND AFTER THREE MONTHS, ZOE IS
BATTLE READY.
>> WHENEVER WE SEND A DOG AWAY
TO ITS NEW HOME IT IS VERY
BITTERSWEET.
>> Reporter: BITTER -- BECAUSE
THEY'RE GIVING ZOE UP.
BUT SWEET, BECAUSE SHE'LL BE
HELPING OTHERS IN WAYS NO
THERAPIST OR FAMILY MEMBER HAS
BEEN ABLE TO.
ZOE IS ASSIGNED TO ARMY VETERAN
MICHAEL METSINGER.
>> I HAVE BEEN DIAGNOSED WITH
PTSD.
I HAVE LOWER BACK PAIN AND LOWER
BACK ISSUES AS WELL.
THEN THE MIGRAINES.
>> Reporter: AFTER AFGHANISTAN
HE'S HAD A TOUGH TIME
READJUSTING TO LIFE AT HOME WITH
HIS FIANCE.
HE HOPES A BATTLE BUDDY CAN EASE
HIS PAIN.
>> I'M REALLY EXCITED BUT I'M
NERVOUS AT THE SAME TIME.
>> Reporter: THIS VOLUNTEER
DRIVES 1,200 MILES TO DELIVER
ZOE.
>> I'M TRAVELING A LOT FOR THIS
MOMENT BUT IT IS WELL WORTH IT.
>> HI, BABY.
AW!
>> Reporter: A DOG RESCUED FROM
A SHELTER, RESCUING A SOLDIER
FROM THE SCARS OF BATTLE.
>> I JUST FEEL GREAT RIGHT NOW.
HI, BABY.
>> TODAY I CAN SAY THAT, KNOW
WHAT?
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
>> Reporter: GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, VENICE, FLORIDA.
>>> THAT'S "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS SUNDAY EVENING.
I'M LESTER HOLT REPORTING FROM
NEW YORK.
FOR ALL OF US HERE AT NBC NEWS,
GOOD NIGHT.
For our families...
our neighbors...
and our communities...
America's beverage companies
have created...
a wide range of new choices.
Developing smaller portion sizes
and more..
low and no-calorie
beverages...
adding clear calorie labels so
you know...
exactly what you're choosing...
and in schools, replacing
full-calorie soft drinks...
with lower-calorie options.
With more choices and fewer
calories...
America's Beverage Companies are
delivering.
>>> NBC BAY AREA NEWS STARTS
NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING, I'M DIANE
DWYER.
>> AND I'M TERRY McSWEENEY.
WE BEGIN WITH A DEVELOPING STORY
IN THE EAST BAY, AND THAT IS
WHERE A LIMOUSINE BURST INTO
FLAMES THIS MORNING AS A DRIVER
WAS PICKING UP A GROUP OF WOMEN
TO TAKE THEM TO A BIRTHDAY
PARTY.
THE OWNER OF THE LIMO COMPANY
SAYS THE VEHICLE WAS IDLING WHEN
IT STARTS SMOKING.
THERE WERE FOUR TO FIVE ELDERLY
WOMEN INSIDE, HE GOT THEM OUT.
NO ONE WAS HURT.
THE OWNER SAYS IT WAS A 2008
LINCOLN TOWN CAR LIMOUSINE THAT
HAD BEEN REGULARLY INSPECTED.
THIS MAY REMIND YOU, AS IT DID
US, TO A SIMILAR