SLIGHTLY COOLER THEN BACK UP.
>> YOU WILL STILL HAVE MAIL JUST
NO THE THE INSTANT MESSENGER.
>> LESTER HOLT NEXT WITH NIGHTLY
NEWS.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT, STATE
OF EMERGENCY.
THEY'RE BRACING FOR
IMPACT FROM
NEW ORLEANS TO BILOXI
TO
PENSACOLA.
IT COULD HIT AS A
HURRICANE.
>> DID ANY ONE ELSE
KNOW ABOUT THE PLOT TO
KILL IN LAS VEGAS.
NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN
THE INVESTIGATION.
POLICE NOT CONVINCED
THAT THE ATTACKER KEPT
IT TO HIMSELF.
>> BIRTH CONTROL
BATTLE.
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION ROLLS
BACK OBAMA ERA RULES,
ALLOWING MORE
EMPLOYERS TO OPT OUT
OF PAYING FOR
CONTRACEPTION
COVERAGE.
>>> SHOCK WAVES,
RIPPLING ACROSS
HOLLYWOOD AND NEW
FALLOUT FOR A POWERFUL
MOVIE MOGUL FACING A
STORM OF ACCUSATIONS
OF SEXUAL MISCONDUCT
INCLUDING FROM A MAJOR
STAR.
>> AND SONG AND A
PRAYER.
LIN MANUEL MIRANDA
LEADS AN ALL-STAR
TRIBUTE FOR POUERTO
RICO.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
BEGINS RIGHT NOW.
GOOD EVENING TO OUR
VIEWERS IN THE WEST.
THANK YOU FOR BEING
WITH US.
LATE TODAY, THE GULF
COAST BRACES FOR
ANOTHER POSSIBLE
HURRICANE.
THIS ONE IS CALLED
NATE.
TROPICAL STORM NOW,
THREATENING TO BUILD
TO HURRICANE STRENGTH
BEFORE HITTING THE
GULF COAST THIS
WEEKEND.
POSING A MAJOR FLOOD
DANGER AFTER LEAVING
NEARLY TWO DOZEN DEAD
ACROSS CENTRAL
AMERICA.
HURRICANE AND TROPICAL
STORM WARNINGS ARE
POSTED TO NIGHT FROM
LOUISIANA TO THE
FLORIDA PANHANDLE.
OUR KERRY SANDERS HAS
THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: NATE HIT
CENTRAL AMERICA AS A
WEAK TROPICAL STORM,
BUT THE IMPACT
POWERFUL.
IN HEART-HIT
NICARAGUA, UP TO
15-INCH ELSE OF RAIN
TURNS ROADS LIKE THIS
INTO RIVERS.
THIS WOMAN SAID THE
STORM HAS LEFT SO MANY
CHILDREN CRYING,
THEY'RE HUNGRY AND
THIRSTY.
IN MOUNTAINOUS COSTA
RICA MAJOR MUDSLIDES
AND WIDE-SPREAD POWER
OUTAGES.
THOUSANDS NOW
HOMELESS.
AT LEAST 22 DEAD,
AMONG THEM TWO KIDS
SWEPT AWAY IN
FAST-RISING WATERS.
HURRICANE WARNING NOW
IN PLACE FOR PARTS OF
LOUISIANA, MISSISSIPPI
AND ALABAMA.
IN NEW ORLEANS, A RACE
TO SANDBAG TONIGHT.
RESIDENTS HERE NOT
WORRIED SO MUCH ABOUT
THE LEVY SYSTEM GIVING
WAY AS HAPPENED
12 YEARS AGO DURING
KATRINA, RATHER FEARS
THE CITY'S CRIPPLED
PUMPING SYSTEM WILL
FAIL.
>> IT WAS RECENTLY
TESTED, YOU KNOW.
THE SYSTEM ITSELF, IT
JUST DIDN'T HOLD.
>> Reporter: IN
AUGUST 17TH CRITICAL
PUMPS IN THE CITY LOST
POWER.
ONLY EIGHT INCHES OF
RAIN TURNING INTO A
CALAMITY.
>> I WANT TO BE REALLY
CLEAR.
WE HAVE SUFFICIENT
PUMPS POWER AND
MANPOWER TO HANDLE
THIS THREAT IF THE
RAIN TOTALS REMAIN AS
FORECAST AND THE
INTENSITY IS DIRECTED.
>> Reporter: ALL
ATTENTION IS NOW ON
THOSE PUMPS LIKE THE
ONE OVER MY SHOULDER
HERE WITH THE
EXPECTATION THAT NATE
WILL BECOME A
HURRICANE.
AS YOU NOTED AT THE
TOP HERE, LESTER, THE
MAYOR OF NEW ORLEANS
HAS ISSUED MANDATORY
EVACUATIONS FOR
CERTAIN PARTS OF THE
DIE.
>> KERRY SANDERS
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU AND LET'S
TURN TO AL ROKER WITH
THE LATEST FORECAST
TRACK WHICH HAS
SHIFTED SLIGHTLY SINCE
LAST NIGHT, AND
WHETHER IT HITS AS A
TROPICAL STORM OR
CATEGORY 1 HURRICANE
DOESN'T MAKE A LOT OF
DIFFERENCE TO FOLKS
ALONG THE GULF COAST
AFTER WHAT THEY'VE
SEEN THIS STORM
SEASON.
>> ABSOLUTELY RIGHT,
LESTER.
THE TRACK HAS SHIFTED
A LITTLE TO THE WEST.
RIGHT NOW 80 MILES
EAST OF COZUMEL,
MEXICO,
60-MILE-PER-HOUR
WINDS.
WE'RE
TALKING A MOVEMENT OF
NORTH/NORTHWEST,
BOOKING AT 21 MILES AN
HOUR.
AT THIS POINT IT IS
ABOUT 200 MILES AWAY
FROM NEW ORLEANS,
SATURDAY AT 1:00 P.M.
70-MILE PER HOUR
WINDS.
IT MAKES LANDFALL
ABOUT 1:00 A.M. AND
CONTINUES TO MOVE
RATHER RAPIDLY, ABOUT
140 MILES OF THAT CONE
OF UNCERTAINTY, AND
MOVES VERY QUICKLY OUT
TO SEA.
HOWEVER, HERE IS WHAT
WE LOOK FOR.
HURRICANE WARNING
RIGHT NOW FROM
LOUISIANA ALL THE WAY
TO ABOUT THE
PENSACOLA/MOBILE,
ALABAMA AREA.
HEAVY RAIN, FLASH
FLOODING, TROPICAL
FORCE WINDS.
LOOK AT THE STORM
SURGE, LOUISIANA, FOUR
TO SIX FEET, FOUR TO
SIX FOR PENSACOLA,
FLORIDA.
WE HAVE TO WATCH
THIS AND WAIT
BECAUSE A TRACK CHANGE
OF 50 MILES CAN MAKE A
BIG DIFFERENCE.
>> AL ROKER, THANK
YOU.
>>> NEW DEVELOPMENTS
FOR THE MASS SHOOTING
IN LAS VEGAS.
INVESTIGATORS
EMPHASIZING LATE TODAY
THEY DON'T BELIEVE
THERE WAS A SECOND
SHOOTER, BUT A LOT OF
QUESTIONS REMAINED
ABOUT WHO ELSE MAY
HAVE KNOWN ABOUT THIS
PLOT.
MEANWHILE, ALL 58
VICTIMS KILLED HAVE
NOW BEEN IDENTIFIED.
WE'LL GET THE LATEST
FROM NBC'S MIGUEL
ALMAGUER.
>> Reporter: REPLACING
THE WINDOWS WHERE
STEVEN PADDOCK
UNLEASHED THE MURDER,
THE NIGHTMARE.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE
NEW SCOURED MULTIPLE
CRIME SCENES, THE
HOTEL, THE CONCERT
TURNED KILLING FIELD
AND THE HOMES WHERE HE
LIVED.
>> WHAT CAN YOU TELL
US ABOUT MOTIVE?
I DON'T HAVE AN ANSWER
FOR MOTIVE.
HE ITS THE ONLY
SHOOTER,
I'M CONFIDENT HE WAS
THE ONLY PERSON
INVOLVED AND THE ONLY
PERSON IN THE ROOM.
BUT DID ANYBODY ELSE
KNOW WHAT HE WAS
PLANNING AND WHY?
THAT IS THE MAIN FOCUS
OF OUR INVESTIGATION
TODAY.
>> Reporter: IRS
RECORDS SHOW PADDOCK
EARNED AT LEAST
$5 MILLION GAMBLING IN
2015.
TWO SOURCES SAY THE
GUNMAN BOUGHT SOME
AMMO  FROM A RECENT
GUN SHOW IN PHOENIX.
AND SOUGHT TO PURCHASE
TRACER ROUNDS, BULLETS
THAT LEAVE A VISIBLE
TRAIL IN THE DARK.
SHOT FOUR TIMES,
SAMANTHA FERANDA WAS
ABLE TO GO HOME TODAY.
>> I'M GRATEFUL I
DIDN'T HAVE TO
COMPLETELY SAY GOODBYE
TO ALL OF THE PEOPLE
THAT I LOVE.
>> Reporter: WHAT
HAPPENED IN VEGAS IS
BEING FELT NATIONWIDE.
TODAY IN CHICAGO AND
AUSTIN, STEPPED-UP
SECURITY AS THOUSANDS
GATHER FOR CONCERTS
AND BASEBALL GAMES.
TONIGHT WE NOW KNOW
THE NAMES OF ALL 58
VICTIMS, 30 WITH TIES
TO SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA.
THE YOUNGEST JUST 20.
BAILEY SCHWEITZER,
THE OLDEST, 67-YEAR
OLD PATI MESTAS, LOVED
LIFE AND HER EIGHT
GRANDCHILDREN.
♪ >> Reporter: LAS
VEGAS POLICE OFFICER
CHARLESTON HARTFIELD
SERVED 16 YEARS IN THE
MILITARY, DYING ON A
BATTLEFIELD AT HOME IN
THE CITY HE LOVED.
♪ AMAZING GRACE
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
GROWING MEMORIALS IN
LAS VEGAS AS 58
FAMILIES BEGIN TO PLAN
FUNERALS.
>> Reporter: AS
INVESTIGATORS POUR
OVER THE CRIME SCENE
BEHIND ME THEY SAY
THEY ARE CONFIDENT THE
GUNMAN ACTED ALONE.
WHAT THEY'RE UNCERTAIN
ABOUT IS AFTER MONTHS,
POSSIBLY EVEN YEARS OF
METICULOUS PLANNING,
HOW COULD NO ONE ELSE
KNOW ABOUT THE
MURDEROUS PLAN?
LESTER.
>> MIGUEL ALMAGUER IN
LAS VEGAS TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
WE'RE LEARNING OF
ANOTHER PLOT TO ATTACK
CONCERT VENUES IN
OTHER CROWDED AREAS
SUCH AS TIMES SQUARE
HERE IN NEW YORK CITY.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS
SAY THREE MEN WERE
ARRESTED FOR THE
ISIS-INSPIRED PLAN
THAT WAS BROKEN UP
THANKS IN PART TO AN
UNDERCOVER FBI AGENT.
NBC JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS IS FOLLOWING
THAT.
PETE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER,
PROSECUTORS SAY THAT
THE DISCOVERY OF THIS
PLOT INSPIRED BY ISIS
WAS KEPT SECRET UNTIL
TONIGHT BECAUSE THE
FBI WANTED TO FIND OUT
IF OTHERS WERE
INVOLVED.
COURT DOCUMENTS SAY
THREE MEN FROM CANADA,
PAKISTAN AND THE
PHILIPPINES PLANNED TO
SET OFF BOMBS IN TIMES
SQUARE AND SHOOT AT
PEOPLE ATTENDING
CONCERTS AROUND THE
CITY.
THEY TALKED ABOUT THE
2015 ATTACKS IN FRANCE
AT THE BATACLAN
THEATER AND SAID, "WE
JUST WALK IN WITH GUNS
IN OUR HANDS, THAT'S
HOW THE PARIS GUYS DID
IT."
THEY ALSO TALKED ABOUT
SETTING OFF BOMBS IN
THE CROWDED NEW YORK
SUBWAY AND IDENTIFIED
WHICH LINES THEY WOULD
FOCUS ON.
THIS PLOT WAS ACTUALLY
BROKEN UP IN MAY OF
2016.
PROSECUTORS SAY WHEN
THE MEN WERE
DISCOVERED
COMMUNICATING ABOUT
TERRORISM AN FBI
UNDERCOVER AGENT SOON
JOINED IN AND THE
THREE WERE UNDER CLOSE
SURVEILLANCE.
ONE HAS NOW PLEADED
GUILTY, THE OTHER TWO
ARE UNDER ARREST.
LESTER.
>> PETE WILLIAMS IN
OUR WASHINGTON
NEWSROOM.
THANK YOU, PETE >>>
TONIGHT, A NEW TURN IN
THE BATTLE OVER BIRTH
CONTROL AND RELIGIOUS
FREEDOMS IN
WASHINGTON.
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS
ROLLING BACK OBAMA ERA
RULES AND ALLOWING
MORE EMPLOYERS TO OPT
OUT OF PAYING FOR
CONTRACEPTION
COVERAGE.
AN ANNOUNCEMENT THAT
HAS WOMEN'S HEALTH
ADVOCATES VOWING TO
FIGHT BACK.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HALLIE
JACKSON HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
IT IS GETTING HARDER
FOR SOME WOMEN TO GET
BIRTH CONTROL THROUGH
THEIR INSURANCE AFTER
A SWEEPING CHANGE BY
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION THAT
WILL LET MORE
EMPLOYERS OPT OUT OF A
REQUIREMENT TO PAY FOR
CONTRACEPTIVE
COVERAGE.
THE NEW RULE NOW
ALLOWS MORE BUSINESSES
WHO DON'T WANT TO
SUBSIDIZE BIRTH
CONTROL FOR EMPLOYEES
TO ASK FOR EXEMPTIONS
FOR MORAL OR RELIGIOUS
REASONS, NOT JUST
RELIGIOUS
ORGANIZATIONS BUT
BUSINESSES OF ALL
SIZES, SCHOOLS AND
UNIVERSITIES, AND
NONPROFITS, TOO.
THE DECISION TODAY
CELEBRATED BY
RELIGIOUS LIBERTIES
ADVOCATES.
>> WHAT IT DOES DO IS
CREATE A NARROW AND
TARGETED EXEMPTION FOR
THOSE WHO CANNOT IN
GOOD CONSCIENCE
PROVIDE THIS AS PART
OF THEIR HEALTH CARE
PLAN.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP FULFILLING A
CAMPAIGN PLEDGE.
>> THE FIRST PRIORITY
OF MY ADMINISTRATION
WILL BE TO PRESERVE
AND PROTECT OUR
RELIGIOUS LIBERTY.
>> Reporter: HIS
ADMINISTRATION SAYS
THE NEW EXEMPTIONS
MIGHT ONLY APPLY TO
200 COMPANIES AND WILL
NOT AFFECT THE VAST
MAJORITY OF WOMEN, BUT
THAT'S ONLY BASED ON
GROUPS THAT SO FAR
HAVE SUED THE
GOVERNMENT TO BE ABLE
TO OPT OUT OF
OBAMACARE'S
CONTRACEPTIVE
REQUIREMENT.
WHAT'S UNKNOWN IS WHO
ELSE MIGHT ASK FOR
EXEMPTIONS.
ADVOCATES FOR BROADER
ACCESS TO BIRTH
CONTROL DESCRIBE THIS
AS A SETBACK WITH THE
ACLU ALREADY
ANNOUNCING A LAWSUIT.
>> WHAT THIS RULE DOES
IS PUT THAT COVERAGE
IN JEOPARDY BECAUSE IT
PUTS CONTROL IN THEIR
BOSS'S HANDS AS TO
WHETHER THEY HAVE
ACCESS TO BIRTH
CONTROL COVERAGE THAT
IS CURRENTLY
GUARANTEED.
>> Reporter: AS FOR
TIMING, THE NEW RULE
GOES INTO EFFECT
IMMEDIATELY.
LESTER.
>> HALLIE JACKSON AT
THE WHITE HOUSE.
THANKS >>> NOW TO THE
CRYPTIC COMMENT FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP THAT
IS RIPPLING ACROSS
WASHINGTON TONIGHT.
SURROUNDED BY MILITARY
LEADERS AND THEIR
SPOUSES, THE PRESIDENT
TOLD REPORTERS THAT
THEY MIGHT BE SEEING
"THE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM," A REMARK THAT
PROMPTED MANY TO ASK
WAS HE REFERRING TO
SOMETHING SPECIFIC.
THE WHITE HOUSE ISN'T
SAYING.
NBC'S PETER ALEXANDER
HAS MORE.
>> THANK YOU VERY
MUCH, EVERYBODY.
>> Reporter: FROM THE
OVAL OFFICE TONIGHT
PRESIDENT TRUMP WITH A
WINK AND A TEASE.
>> THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: REVEALING
NO NEW DETAILS ABOUT
THE MEANING OF THIS
CRYPTIC COMMENT DURING
A RECEPTION WITH
MILITARY LEADERS AND
THEIR SPOUSES THURSDAY
NIGHT.
>> YOU GUYS KNOW WHAT
THIS REPRESENTS?
>> TELL US, SIR.
>> MAYBE IT IS THE
CALM BEFORE THE STORM.
>> WHAT'S THE STORM?
>> COULD BE THE CALM,
THE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM.
>> WHAT STORM, MR.
PRESIDENT?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S HE
TALKING ABOUT?
THE WHITE HOUSE
INSISTING PRESIDENT
TRUMP NEVER TIPS HIS
HAND.
>> WE'RE NEVER GOING
TO SAY IN ADVANCE WHAT
THE PRESIDENT IS GOING
TO DO.
>> Reporter: IT IS
UNCLEAR WHETHER THE
PRESIDENT WAS JUST
TOYING AROUND,
DEFLECTING FROM THE
POLITICAL STORM AND
HOPING HIS
ADMINISTRATION OR
PREVIEWING SOME NEW
ACTION.
TONIGHT MULTIPLE U.S.
OFFICIALS TELLING NBC
NEWS PRESIDENT TRUMP
WILL LIKELY ANNOUNCE
NEXT WEEK HE WON'T
CERTIFY IRAN IS
COMPLYING WITH THE
NUCLEAR DEAL, A MOVE
THAT COULD LEAD TO NEW
SANCTIONS.
HIS PRESS SECRETARY,
UNPROMPTED, ALSO
BRINGING UP NORTH
KOREA.
>> WE'RE CONTINUING TO
PUT MAXIMUM ECONOMIC
AND DIPLOMATIC
PRESSURE ON COUNTRIES
LIKE NORTH KOREA.
WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO DO THAT.
>> Reporter: WHITE
HOUSE VETERANS WARN
WORDS MATTER.
>> THOSE WORDS THAT
COME OUT OF THE
PRESIDENT'S MOUTH HAVE
AN IMPACT ALL AROUND
THE GLOBE, AND
SOMETIMES THERE ARE
UNINTENDED
CONSEQUENCES BECAUSE
OF THE WORDS THAT ARE
SPOKEN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE FORMER REALITY TV
STAR TURNED PRESIDENT
IS LEAVING AMERICAN
ALLIES AND ADVERSARIES
WITH A CLIFFHANGER.
PETER ALEXANDER, NBC
NEWS, THE WHITE HOUSE
>>> NOW TO THE LATE
CONFIRMATION FROM THE
PENTAGON A FOURTH
AMERICAN SOLDIER WAS
KILLED IN NIGER, LEFT
BEHIND AFTER ISLAMIC
MILITANTS AMBUSHED A
U.S. SPECIAL FORCES
PATROL ON WEDNESDAY.
WE GET THE LATEST FROM
NBC NEWS PENTAGON
CORRESPONDENT HANS
NICHOLS.
>> Reporter: THE
BODIES OF THREE FALLEN
GREEN BERETS BACK HOME
TONIGHT AFTER THEY
WERE KILLED IN AN
AMBUSH IN THE WEST
AFRICAN NATION NIGER.
STAFF SERGEANT BRYAN
BLACK, 35, A SHARP
SHEETER FROM
WASHINGTON.
STAFF SERGEANT DUSTIN
WRIGHT FROM LYONS,
GEORGIA, JUST 29 YEARS
OLD.
STAFF SERGEANT JAIR
MINA JOHNSON, 39, FROM
SPRINGBORO, OHIO,
WHERE THE COMMUNITY IS
DEVASTATED.
>> WE KNEW WHERE HE
WAS AND HE WASN'T IN A
GOOD PLACE, AND --
>> YEAH.
>> -- IT WAS JUST
HEARTBREAKING.
>> Reporter: THE GREEN
BERETS JUST A FEW OF
THE 800 AMERICAN
TROOPS IN NIGER WHERE
U.S. STATIONS DRONES
TO WATCH ISLAMIC
EXTREMIST ACROSS THE
SAHARA.
TRAINED LOCAL NIGER
TROOPS ENCOUNTER
TERRORISM, BUT A
ROUTINE MISSION TURNED
INTO FULL-FLEDGED
COMBAT WHEN NEARLY A
DOZEN U.S. AND NIGER
FORCES WERE SURPRISED
BY ISLAMIC MILITANT
ALSO.
A DEADLY FIRE FIGHT
ENSUED.
FRENCH HELICOPTERS
EVACUATED THE
CASUALTIES.
IN THE CHAOS OF
BATTLE, ONE WAS
MISSING.
U.S. SPECIAL OPERATORS
WERE FLOWN IN FROM
ACROSS THE GLOBE, BUT
IT WAS TOO LATE.
HIS BODY FOUND TODAY
BY NIGERIAN TROOPS.
>> YOU TRY NEVER TO
LEAVE A SOLDIER
BEHIND.
IT IS UNUSUAL TO DO
SO.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN ONE
HECK OF A FIRE FIGHT
FOR THAT TO HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: MILITARY
OFFICIALS TELL NBC
NEWS THAT THE GREEN
BERETS DID KILL SOME
ISLAMIC EXTREMISTS BUT
THEY CAN'T SAY HOW
MANY, WHERE THEY CAME
FROM OR IF THEY'LL
STRIKE AGAIN.
HANS NICHOLS, NBC
NEWS, THE PENTAGON.
>>> THERE IS MIXED
NEWS ON
THE ECONOMY THIS
EVENING.
THE U.S. LOST 33,000
JOBS IN SEPTEMBER, THE
FIRST DECLINE IN
MONTHLY JOBS NUMBERS
GOING BACK SIX YEARS.
BACK-TO-BACK
HURRICANES LIKELY HAD
A SIGNIFICANT IMPACT
ON THE SLOW DOWN IN
HIRING, BUT THE
UNEMPLOYMENT RATE
ACTUALLY DECLINED TO
4.2%.
THAT IS THE LOWEST
SINCE FEBRUARY OF 2001
AND A SIGN THE JOB
MARKET REMAINS STRONG.
>>> STILL AHEAD AS WE
CONTINUE HERE TONIGHT,
THE SCANDAL ROCKING
HOLLYWOOD.
NEW FALLOUT FROM A
SEXUAL HARASSMENT
ACCUSATIONS AGAINST
ONE OF THE MOVIE
INDUSTRIES BIGGEST
POWER PLAYERS.
>>> ALSO CAUGHT ON
CAMERA, THE WORLD'S
BIGGEST PASSENGER
PLANE COMING IN FOR A
TERRIFYING LANDING.
STAY WITH US.
♪ >>> BACK NOW WITH
NEW FALLOUT FROM THE
FIRESTORM GRIPPING
HOLLYWOOD.
MOVIE MOGUL HARVEY
WEINSTEIN TAKING A
LEAVE OF ABSENCE FROM
HIS OWN COMPANY AFTER
REPORTS OF MULTIPLE
SEXUAL HARASSMENT
COMPLAINTS AGAINST
HIM.
WEINSTEIN IS JUST THE
LATEST POWER PLAYER
ACCUSED OF MISCONDUCT
AGAINST WOMEN.
MORE FROM NBC'S ANNE
THOMPSON.
>> Reporter: DURING
AWARDS SEASON HARVEY
WEINSTEIN'S POWER IS
ON FULL DISPLAY.
>> I JUST WANT TO
THANK MY AGENT, KEVIN
UVANE AND GOD, HARVEY
WEINSTEIN.
>> Reporter: HIS FILMS
INCLUDING "THE KING'S
SPEECH" "PULP FICTION"
AND "SHAKESPEARE IN
LOVE" WINNING 75
OSCARS.
NOW IT IS SAID THAT HE
USED HIS POWER FOR
SORDID ENDS,
UNCOVERING SEXUAL
HARASSMENT SPANNING
ALMOST THREE DECADES,
FROM ACTRESSES ASHLEY
JUDD AND ROSE McGOWAN
TO YOUNG FEMALE
ASSISTANTS LOOKING TO
START CAREERS IN
HOLLYWOOD.
>> NOBODY WITH ANY
AMOUNT OF MONEY OR
GLAMOUR OR PROFILE
SHOULD BE HELD TO
DIFFERENT STANDARDS
THAN EVERY SINGLE MAN
RESPONSIBLE FOR AND
FRIENDS WITH WOMEN IN
THIS WORLD.
>> Reporter: THE STORY
STRIKING A NERVE.
WHEN DID YOU MEET YOUR
HARVEY WEINSTEIN
GETTING MORE THAN
2,400 RESPONSES ON
TWITTER FROM WOMEN IN
ALL WALKS OF LIFE.
THE MOVIE MOGUL, THE
LATEST POWERFUL MAN
ACCUSED OF PREYING ON
FEMALE EMPLOYEES.
FOX NEWS PAYING
MILLIONS FOR CLAIMS
AGAINST FORMER ANCHOR
BILL O'REILLY AND CEO
ROGER AILES.
RIDE-SHARING GIANT
UBER ACCUSED OF
FOSTERING A TOXIC
CULTURE OF SEXISM AND
HARASSMENT.
WHILE NOT ADMITTING TO
THE ALLEGATIONS, IN A
STATEMENT TO THE
"TIMES" WEINSTEIN SAID
I APPRECIATE THE WAY
I'VE BEHAVED WITH
COLLEAGUES IN THE PAST
HAS CAUSED A LOT OF
PAIN, AND I SINCERELY
APOLOGIZE FOR IT.
LISA BLOOM, WHO'S
REPRESENTED WOMEN IN
CLAIMS AGAINST BILL
COSBY, FOX NEWS AND
THEN-CANDIDATE DONALD
TRUMP IS ALSO
REPRESENTING
WEINSTEIN.
HE'S MAKING A
DOCUMENTARY OF ONE OF
HER BOOKS.
>> IT IS TIME FOR A
LOT OF OLD DINOSAURS
IN THE INDUSTRY AND
ALL INDUSTRIES TO
UPDATE THEIR THINKING
AND THEIR BEHAVIOR.
>> Reporter: A MAN
WITH THE POWER TO MAKE
OR BREAK CAREERS MAY
HAVE HARMED HIS OWN.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A
MOMENT
WITH THE BIG-NAME
STORE CHAIN LOOKING TO
SHAKE UP THE
GROCERY-DELIVERY WARS.
>>> A NEW SALVO
TONIGHT IN THE GROCERY
WARS AS BIG NAMES
BATTLE FOR YOUR MONEY.
TAKING AIM AT AMAZON,
COSTCO ANNOUNCED IT IS
GETTING IN THE
SAME-DAY GROCERY
DELIVERY GAME WHICH
THE COMPANY SAYS WILL
BE AVAILABLE IN MOST
METROPOLITAN AREAS AND
IT WILL OFFER TWO DAY
DELIVERIES FOR DRY
GOODS.
IT IS THE END OF AN
ERA ONLINE.
AOL INSTANT MESSENGER
KNOWN AS AIM IS
SIGNING OFF FOR GOOD.
BEFORE FACEBOOK AND
TWITTER IT WAS THE WAY
TO CHAT WITH FRIENDS
FOR SO MANY PEOPLE
THROUGHOUT THE LATE
'90s AND INTO THE
2000s WITH YOUR SCREEN
NAME AND BUDDY LISTS
AND CREATIVE AWAY
MESSAGES THAT MIGHT
NOW MAKE YOU CRINGE
>>> SCARY MOMENTS
CAUGHT ON CAMERA WHEN
AN AIRBUS JUMBO JET
CAME IN FOR A ROUGH
LANDING IN POWERFUL
CROSS WINDS.
TAKE A LOOK.
THE PLANE WOBBLED AS
IT TOUCHED DOWN,
APPEARING TO COME
CLOSE TO SLIDING OFF
THE RUNWAY IN GERMANY
YESTERDAY BEFORE THE
PILOT WAS ABLE TO
FINALLY STRAIGHTEN IT
OUT.
THE AIRBUS A-380 PLANE
IS THE LARGEST
COMMERCIAL AIRCRAFT IN
THE WORLD.
>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
THE CREATOR OF THE
SMASH HIT "HAMILTON,"
LIN-MANUEL MIRANDA ON
HIS STAR-STUDDED HIT
TO BENEFIT PUERTO
RICO.
THE BAY AREA GIVES HILLARY
CLINTON A HERO )S WELCOME!
NEXT AT 6: THE OUTCOME SHE )S
HOPING FOR... FROM THE RUSSIAN
HACKING INVESTIGATION.
PLUS, BART HAS BEEN FOUND
GUILTY! THE PUNISHMENT IT JUST
RECEIVED FOR THE DEATHS
OF TWO WORKERS...
NEXT.
RIGHT NOW AT 6:
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
MORE THAN TWO WEEKS
AFTER HURRICANE MARIA
SLAMMED PUERTO RICO
THAT U.S. TERRITORY
REMAINS IN DIRE NEED.
THAT'S WHY LYNN MANUEL
MIRANDA, TONY AND
GRAMMY AWARD WINNING
CREATOR OF THE SMASH
HIT "HAMILTON" GOT
SOME OF HIS FELLOW
MUSIC SUPERSTARS
TOGETHER FOR A SONG
BENEFITTING THE RELIEF
EFFORT.
TONIGHT OUR GABE
GUTIERREZ HAS AN
INSIDE LOOK ♪ >>
Reporter: IF THE SONG
WAS ONLY ABOUT A
STORM, IT WOULDN'T BE
SO PERSONAL.
♪ IT'S ALMOST LIKE
PRAYING ♪
>> Reporter: BUT FOR
LYNN MANUEL MIRANDA
HIS NEW SINGLE "ALMOST
LIKE PRAYING" INSPIRED
BY THE WEST SIDE STORY
SONG "MARIA" CUTS
DEEPER.
FEATURING JENNIFER
LOPEZ, GLORIA ESTEFAN
AND MARC ANTHONY, THE
MUSIC GIVES A VOICE TO
EACH OF PUERTO RICO'S
78 TOWNS.
♪ >> LIKE MANY PEOPLE
I HAVE FAMILY ON THE
ISLAND, AND WHAT WE
ALL EXPERIENCED IF WE
WEREN'T ON THE ISLAND
WAS THIS TERRIBLE
SILENCE IN THE WAKE OF
THE STORM.
AND OUR SOCIAL MEDIA
FEEDS WERE FULL OF THE
NAMES OF TOWNS.
>> Reporter: IT IS THE
LATEST VOICE IN THE
HURRICANE MARIA RELIEF
EFFORT, STEPHEN
COLBERT RAISING MORE
THAN AN MILLION
DOLLARS GETTING
CELEBRITIES TO POST
AWKWARD ADOLESCENT
PICTURES.
A GROUP RALLYING FOR
THE HARDEST HIT SOUTH
EASTERN COAST.
HOUSTON, STILL
RECOVERING ITSELF FROM
HURRICANE HARVEY.
>> AND WE GIVE BACK TO
ANY IN NEED AS THE
NATION HAS DONE SO FOR
US.
>> Reporter: TO ASBURY
PARK, NEW JERSEY TODAY
WHERE SUPPLIES WERE
RUSHED TO THE LOCAL
FOOD BANK EN ROUTE TO
SAN JUAN.
>> IT IS DEVASTATING.
>> Reporter: DEE DEE
MONTERO GREW UP IN
PUERTO RICO AND DIDN'T
HEAR FROM HER
75-YEAR-OLD MOTHER ON
THE ISLAND FOR DAYS
AFTER THE STORM.
>> THE PAIN IS SO DEEP
THAT YOU CAN'T EVEN
EXPRESS IT.
I HAVE CRIED SO MUCH
IN THE PAST COUPLE OF
WEEKS.
>> Reporter: BUT FOR
PUERTO RICANS, FROM
THAT PAIN HAS COME
PRIDE.
MIRANDA'S TRIBUTE
HELPING MAKE SURE 78
TOWNS ARE NOT
FORGOTTEN.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> WE APPRECIATE YOU
SPENDING PART OF YOUR
EVENING WITH US.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
♪ >> Announcer: MORE
AMERICANS WATCH NBC
NEWS THAN ANY OTHER
NEWS ORGANIZATION IN
THE WORLD.
>>> "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
IS ALWAYS AVAILABLE ON
DEMAND AND STREAMING
ON YOUR FAVORITE
SCREENS.
FOLLOW OUR LATEST
COVERAGE WITH THE NBC
NEWS APP.
RIGHT NOW AT 6:
HILLARY MANIA IN THE BAY AREA.
LONG LINES, AND LOUD CHEERS FOR
>>> WE LOVE YOU, HILLARY.
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, A LOT OF
LOVE FOR HILLARY CLINTON HERE IN
THE BAY AREA.
LONG LINES AND LOUD CHEERS FOR
MRS. CLINTON TODAY AND HER VISIT
CONTINUING THIS EVENING.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD EVENING AND THANKS FOR
BEING WITH US ON FRIDAY RAJ
MATHAI.
>> JESSICA AGUIRRE.
FROM A WINNEBAGO SIGNING TO A HE
NOTE ADDRESS.
THE FORMERLY PRESIDENTIAL CAN'T
IS BACK IN FRONT OF THE BASE.
MRS. CLINTON IS ON THE STANFORD
CAMPUS DISCUSS AGO WIDE RAINING
OF TOPICS.
LET'S GET A LOOK PROCESS.
THIS IS THE QUESTION AND ANSWER
PORTION.
EARLIER TODAY SHE DELIVERED THE
KE NOTE ADDRESS COVERING
DEMOCRATIC VALUES, DIPLOMACY,
TECHNOLOGY AND EVEN ELECTION
HACKING BY THE RUSSIANS.
>>> I CERTAINLY BELIEVE WE HAVE
WHAT IT TAKES TO UNDERSTAND WHAT
HAPPENED IN 2016.
AND DECISIVE TOLY TO MAKE SURE
IT NEVER HAPPENS AGAIN AND
CONFRONT THIS THREAT TO WESTERN
DEMOCRACY.
>> EARLIER IN THE DAY
MRS. CLINTON SIGNED BOOKS FOR
MORE THAN A THOUSAND PEOPLE IN
SAN FRANCISCO.
NBC BAY AREA KRISTI SMITH SHOWS
US THE EVENT.
AND A LINE THAT STRETCHED MORE
THAN A CITY BLOCK.
>> Reporter: SAN FRANCISCO IS
CERTAINLY FRIENDLY TERRITORY FOR
HILLARY CLINTON.
WE ARE TOLD THIS THIS BACK
SIGNING EVENT SOLD OUT IN LESS
THAN 18 HOURS.
MORE THAN 1,000 PEOPLE LINED UP
EARLY IN THE HOPES OF SAYING
HELLO AND THANK YOU TO THE
FORMER SECRETARY OF STATE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE LOVE YOU HILLARY.
>> Reporter: THE THE BOOK
SIGNING IN SAN FRANCISCO HILLARY
CLINTON ARRIVED TO