>> ALL RIGHT.
NBC NIGHTLY NEWS IS COMING UP
NEXT.
>> HOPE YOU CAN JOIN US TOMORROW
AT KW67.
>>> ON THIS SATURDAY
NIGHT, RISING TENSIONS
AFTER THE USAIR STRIKE
ON SYRIA, RUSSIA TAKES
A HARD LINE, SENDING A
WARSHIP TO THE
MEDITERRANEAN, VOICING
NEW SUPPORT FOR THE
ASSAD REGIME.
>>> MANHUNT.
THE SEARCH FOR A
SUSPECT WHO STOLE 16
HIGH-POWERED GUNS AND
SET AN ANTI-GOVERNMENT
MANIFESTO TO THE
PRESIDENT.
HIS MOVEMENTS CAPTURED
ON VIDEO.
>>> DEADLY TRUCK
ATTACK.
NEW INFORMATION FROM
SWEDEN SUGGESTING IT
COULD HAVE BEEN MUCH
WORSE AS EYEWITNESSES
DESCRIBE THE MOMENTS
OF TERROR.
>>> PREPARING FOR
BATTLE.
OUR INSIDE LOOK AT THE
SIMULATED ATTACK.
HOW ELITE MEDICAL
TEAMS ARE SAVING FOR
LIFE-SAVING MISSION.
>>> AND THE GUARDIAN.
THE WOMAN WHO FOUND
HER CALLING LOOKING
AFTER AMERICAN
CHILDREN LEFT BEHIND
AFTER THEIR
UNDOCUMENTED PARENTS
WERE DEPORTED.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
BEGINS NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN
NEW YORK, THIS IS "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS."
>>> GOOD EVENING.
REVERBERATIONS ON A
STRIKE ON AN SYRIAN
AIRFIELD ARE GETTING
LOUDER, NOT JUST IN
WORDS BUT IN ACTION.
RUSSIAN AND SYRIA
MILITARY JETS RESUMED
MISSIONS TODAY.
DASHING HOPES OF A NEW
FRIENDLIER
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN
VLADIMIR PUTIN AND
DONALD TRUMP.
ALL THIS JUST DAYS
BEFORE SECRETARY OF
STATE REX TILLERSON
HEADS TO MOSCOW FOR
MEETINGS WITH TOP
OFFICIALS.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH
RICHARD ENGEL IN
ISTANBUL.
>> Reporter: RUSSIAN
STATE TV BROADCASTING
FROM SYRIA AT THE AIR
BASE THAT IS
DESTROYED.
FOOTAGE SHOWS SOME
DAMAGE AND DEFIANTLY
FIGHTER JETS TAXIYING
AND TAKING OFF IN
BROAD DAYLIGHT.
LOCAL RESIDENTS
FILMING IT ON THEIR
CELL PHONES.
IT'S UNCLEAR IF THE
AIRCRAFT WERE FLOWN BY
SYRIAN OR RUSSIAN
PILOTS, BUT THE
MESSAGE IS CLEAR THE
U.S. STRIKE CHANGED
LITTLE.
NEW IMAGES SHOW THE
TOWN HIT BY A CHEMICAL
ATTACK WHICH THE U.S.
SAYS WAS HIT BY THAT
BASE IT IS A GHOST
TOWN NOW, BUT THERE
WERE MORE AIR STRIKES
TODAY.
JUST SO RUSSIA'S POINT
COULDN'T BE MISSED,
MOSCOW IS SENDING THIS
WAR SHIP, THE ADMIRAL,
ARMED WITH ITS OWN
CRUISE MISSILES TO THE
MEDITERRANEAN.
THE PRIME MINISTER
WARNED ON FACEBOOK
THAT WASHINGTON AND
MOSCOW WERE JUST ON
THE VERGE OF CONFLICT.
ALL OF IT IS A SHARP
WARNING TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP, DON'T ATTACK
RUSSIA'S ALLIES AGAIN.
>> THINGS THAT THE
RUSSIANS ARE SAYING
AND THE RUSSIANS ARE
DOING IS IN MANY
RESPECTS FOR THEIR
PUBLIC'S CONSUMPTION.
>> Reporter: WHILE THE
MISSILE STRIKES WERE
WELCOMED AROUND THE
WORLD, CRITICS ARE
INCREASINGLY ASKING IF
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION HAS A
THOUGHT OUT STRATEGY.
THE CURRENT POLICY
SEEMS FULL OF
CONTRADICTION
EXPRESSING CONCERN FOR
CIVILIAN SUFFERING IN
SYRIA.
>> BEAUTIFUL BABIES.
>> Reporter: WHILE
TRYING TO BAN ALL
SYRIAN REFUGEES FROM
ENTERING THE UNITED
STATES, BOMBING THE
SYRIAN REGIME AND
BOMBING GROUPS THE
REGIME IS FIGHTING
ATTACKING BOTH SIDES
IN A CIVIL WAR SOME
MIGHT SAY IS NO POLICY
AT ALL.
TODAY THE SECRETARY OF
STATE TILLERSON WHO
NEXT WEEK MEETS WITH
VLADIMIR PUTIN SPOKE
WITH HIS RUSSIAN
COUNTERPART WHO
INSISTED THERE WAS NO
CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACK IN SYRIA.
SO THERE IS STILL A
LINE OF COMMUNICATIONS
BETWEEN THE TWO SIDES.
BUT THEY SEEM TO BE
TALKING PAST EACH
OTHER.
JOSE.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP
DEFENDED THE SYRIAN
OPERATION TODAY AND
PRAISED THOSE WHO
CARRIED IT OUT, BUT
ANOTHER FIGHT WAS
GOING ON INSIDE THE
WHITE HOUSE.
KELLY O'DONNELL HAS
MORE FROM FLORIDA.
>> Reporter: TODAY AS
THE PRESIDENT SPENT
SEVERAL HOURS AT THE
TRUMP GOLF RESORT NEAR
HIS PALM BEACH HOME
PRAISE FROM HIS
TWITTER ACCOUNT
CONGRATULATIONS TO OUR
GREAT MILITARY MEN AND
WOMEN FROM THEIR ROLE
ON THE STRIKE ON
SYRIA.
ALSO TODAY THE
PRESIDENT IN
TRADITIONAL LETTER
FORM WROTE TO CONGRESS
WITH HIS OFFICIAL
LEGAL BASIS CLAIMING
HIS PURPOSE, TO
DEGRADE THE SYRIAN
MILITARY'S ABILITY TO
CONDUCT FURTHER
CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACKS AND HIS POWER
BY ACTING IN THE
FOREIGN POLICY
INTERESTS OF THE
UNITED STATES
REASONING THAT BOTH
CONFLICTS AND SUPPORTS
PAST CAMPAIGN
POSITIONS.
>> ON THE ONE HAND
HE'S ATTACKED THE
ASSAD REGIME AND HE'S
FOLLOWING THROUGH THE
COMMITMENT TO PUT MORE
FORCES ON THE GROUND
TO RID SYRIA OF ISIS.
>> Reporter:
INTERNATIONAL
HEADLINES FROM
FRIENDLY NATIONS,
SLASHED APPROVAL, BUT
INSIDE THE WHITE HOUSE
SPLINTERED POWER.
AMONG THE PRESIDENT'S
SENIOR TEAM.
CHIEF STRATEGIST STEVE
BANNON HAS DESCRIBED
TRUMP'S SON-IN-LAW
JARED KUSHNER AS WEST
WING DEMOCRAT DETACHED
FROM TRUMP'S
CONSERVATIVE BASE.
ADD TO THAT, CRITICISM
AIMED AT CHIEF OF
STAFF REINCE PRIEBUS
AFTER SOURCES SAY THE
PRESIDENT PEPPERED
ALLIES SEEKING TO
ASSIGN BLAME OVER THE
HEALTH CARE FAILURE,
RUMORS OF A
RESHUFFLING, BUT
TONIGHT THE POWER TRIO
HELD A LONG MEETING.
IT WAS DESCRIBED AS A
BURY THE HATCHET
SETTING.
IT HAS DRIVEN CRITICAL
STORIES OF THE WHITE
HOUSE OF WHO'S UP AND
WHO'S DOWN.
THE PRESIDENT WAS
AWARE OF THIS MEETING
AND IS PLEASED WITH
THE OUTCOME.
JOSE?
>> KELLY O'DONNELL,
THANK YOU.
AFTER THE STRIKE IN
SYRIA SOME OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S MOST
ARDENT SUPPORTERS ARE
ASKING WHAT HAPPENED
TO ONE OF THE CORE
PRINCIPLES, THE
CORNERSTONE TO HIS
CAMPAIGN AND HIS
ADMINISTRATION.
HALLIE JACKSON HAS
THAT STORY.
>> IT IS GOING TO BE
AMERICA FIRST.
REMEMBER THAT.
>> Reporter: FOR
PRESIDENT TRUMP A TWO
WORD WORLD VIEW.
>> AMERICA FIRST.
AMERICA FIRST, AMERICA
FIRST.
>> Reporter: CLEAR ON
THE CAMPAIGN TRAIL AS
HE RAILED AGAINST
INTERVENTION AND THEN
CAME HIS SYRIAN STRIKE
AND THE NEAR IMMEDIATE
BACKLASH FROM HIS
BASE.
>> THIS IS
UNBELIEVABLE.
THIS IS NOT WHAT WE
VOTED FOR.
>> Reporter: THAT IS A
CONSPIRACY THEORIST.
MAKING SURE THAT THE
AIR STRIKE SEEMS LIKE
A
BETRAYAL.
>> YOU ARE SEEING A
LOT OF DISTURBANCE IN
THE FORCE THAT REALLY
BELIEVED THAT DONALD
TRUMP REPRESENTED A
VERY VERY SHORT BREAK
WITH THE BUSH ERA
FOREIGN POLICY AND THE
REALITY IS THAT RIGHT
NOW HE'S NOT.
>> Reporter: THE
EDITOR OF ONE RIGHT
WING WEBSITE TWEETING
I'M OFFICIALLY OFF THE
TRUMP TRAIN.
ANN COULTER WRITING
THOSE WHO WANTED US
MEDDLING IN MIDDLE
EAST VOTED FOR OTHER
CANDIDATES AND AN
EDITOR QUESTIONED
ABOUT SIGNS OF UNREST
RESPONDING UNREST, I'M
APAPLEPTIC.
>> I KNOW TRUMP WAS
AMERICA FIRST, BUT
SOMETIMES THAT DOESN'T
ALWAYS WORK OUT.
>> Reporter: SOME
SUPPORTERS WATCHFUL.
>> I DO NOT THINK HE
SHOULD CONTINUE TO DO
AIR STRIKES, BUT IT
WAS A GOOD WARNING.
>> Reporter: AS THE
ADMINISTRATION FACES
QUESTIONS ABOUT ITS
FOREIGN POLICY
POSTURE, THE
PRESIDENT'S MOST
NATIONALISTIC
SUPPORTERS AREN'T
TOTALLY TURNING THEIR
BACKS.
REMEMBER THAT EDITOR
WHO SAID HE WAS OFF
THE TRUMP TRAIN?
HE WRITES I HAVE
TRUMP'S BACK.
>>> IN SWEDEN HUNDREDS
OF PEOPLE GATHERED
TODAY AT THE SITE OF
THAT TRUCK ATTACK
PAYING THEIR RESPECTS
TO THE FOUR PEOPLE
KILLED.
NBC KAOER KIER SIMMONS
IS THERE WITH NEW
DETAILS ON THE ATTACK
AND THE SUSPECT.
>> Reporter: DEBRIS
OUTSIDE THE DEPARTMENT
STORE TONIGHT, THE
TRUCK REMOVED, BUT
MANY QUESTIONS REMAIN,
COULD THIS HAVE BEEN
FAR WORSE.
POLICE CONFIRMING THE
VEHICLE CONTAINED A
DEVICE.
>> I CANNOT AT THIS
STAGE SAY THAT THIS IS
A BOMB OR SOME SORT OF
FLAMMABLE MATERIAL.
>> Reporter: UNDER
ARREST, A 39-YEAR-OLD,
FROM UZBEKISTAN KNOWN
TO AUTHORITIES BUT
REGARDED AS A MARGINAL
CHARACTER.
THE PRIME MINISTER
CALLING IT TERRORISM
SAYING THE AIM TO
UNDERMINE DEMOCRACY.
THE TRUCK HURDLED
ALONG A PEDESTRIAN
STRIKE FOR FIVE BLOCKS
BEFORE SMASHING INTO
THE DEPARTMENT STORE
FIVE BLOCKS AHEAD THE
SWEDISH PARLIAMENT
BUILDING.
FOUR MURDERED, 15
INJURED.
JOSHUA WITNESSING THE
HORROR.
>> YOU KNEW SOMETHING
WAS WRONG.
THERE WAS A TERRORIST
ATTACK.
>> Reporter: HE
ESCAPED INTO A STORE
AND THEN SECONDS LATER
THE TRUCK BARRELLING
INTO INNOCENT
SHOPPERS.
>> I SAW PEOPLE WERE
DYING AND THE
PARAMEDICS TRYING TO
REVIVE THEM.
>> Reporter: HE SHOWS
ME THE BAG HE HAD
DROPPED TO RUN FEET
FROM THE TRUCK'S PATH.
YOU WERE SECONDS AWAY
FROM BEING HIT BY THAT
TRUCK?
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
TEN OF THE INJURED ARE
STILL IN THE HOSPITAL,
INCLUDING A CHILD.
TWO IN INTENSIVE CARE.
TONIGHT, FLOWERS,
CANDLES AND MORE
QUESTIONS.
WERE OTHERS INVOLVED
AND HERE A
CONSTRUCTION SITE IN
THE TRUCK'S PATH.
IS THAT WHY IT STOPPED
OVER THERE?
WAS THE PLAN TO KEEP
GOING, KILL MORE
PEOPLE, EVEN REACH THE
SWEDISH PARLIAMENT.
JOSE?
>> KEIR SIMMONS, THANK
YOU VERY MUCH.
>>> IN THIS COUNTRY
THERE'S A MANHUNT FOR
A DANGEROUS SUSPECT
WHO AUTHORITIES SAY
STOLE MORE THAN ONE
DOZEN GUNS.
AND SENT A MANIFESTO
TO PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THIS IS GOING ON IN
WISCONSIN AND NBC HAS
THE DETAILS.
>> Reporter: POLICE
SAY THE MAN IS HEAVILY
ARMED AND DANGEROUS
AND HE COULD BE
ANYWHERE.
>> WE DON'T KNOW WHERE
HE IS.
>> Reporter: 150
OFFICERS FROM LOCAL,
STATE, AND FEDERAL
AGENCIES ARE SEARCHING
FOR THE 32-YEAR-OLD
MAN SUSPECTED OF
STEALING 16 GUNS IN
WISCONSIN.
POLICE SAY HE MADE
UNSPECIFIED THREATS TO
SEVERAL TARGETS.
INCLUDING SCHOOLS.
>> WE ASKED THE PUBLIC
HERE AND ACROSS THE
NATION IF THEY SEE
HIM, REPORT THAT
INFORMATION TO LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
>> Reporter: SCHOOLS
WERE CLOSED FRIDAY.
TODAY NEIGHBORS
DESCRIBED A MAN WHO
KEPT TO HIMSELF.
>> THE GUY IS LIKE A
REALLY DECENT, QUIET
GUY.
>> Reporter:
AUTHORITIES SAY THE
MAN HAD A PUBLIC
MESSAGE THIS WEEK
RELEASING THIS 15
MINUTE CELL PHONE
VIDEO OF HIM AT A POST
OFFICE TUESDAY MAILING
A 161 PAGE
ANTI-GOVERNMENT
MANIFESTO ADDRESSED TO
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
HE'S RECORDED BY
ANOTHER MAN WHO NEVER
REVEALS HIS FACE.
>> REVOLUTION, IT'S
TIME FOR CHANGE.
>> Reporter: AS HE
WALKS TOWARD THE
MAILBOX, THIS WARNING.
>> TODAY IS THE DAY.
SO REMEMBER THIS FACE.
>> GAME TIME.
>> Reporter: HOURS
LATER POLICE RESPOND
TO A BURGLARY AT A GUN
SHOP.
HE IS SEEN IN THESE
IMAGES.
30 MINUTES LATER A CAR
BURST INTO FLAMES
THAT'S REGISTERED TO
HIM.
>> THIS APPEARS TO BE
A MAN WHO HAS A
MESSAGE.
ALL OF THESE OTHER
ACTIONS THAT HE'S
TAKEN TO THIS DATE MAY
WELL JUST BE THE
GROUND WORK TO FINALLY
GET PEOPLE TO LISTEN
TO HIM.
>> Reporter: HE HAS A
HISTORY OF
MISDEMEANORS AND ONE
FELONY CONVICTION FOR
TRYING TO STEAL A GUN
FROM AN OFFICER.
TONIGHT, A CITY ON
EDGE AS THE MANHUNT
INTENSIFIES.
NBC NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> IT HAS BEEN A WEEK
OF SEVERE WEATHER ALL
AROUND THE COUNTRY,
INCLUDING A TORNADO
CAUGHT ON A HOME
SECURITY CAMERA THAT
BLEW INTO A HOUSE IN
ILLINOIS.
IT TORE OFF THE ROOF.
REPORTED WIND SPEED
150 MILES AN HOUR.
THAT AREA MAY GET HIT
BY MORE SEVERE
WEATHER, BUT TONIGHT
THE NORTHWEST IS
RECOVERING FROM DEADLY
WEATHER.
WINDS GUSTS UP TO 90
MILES AN HOUR LEFT
THOUSANDS WITHOUT
POWER.
>> Reporter: 90 MILE
AN HOUR GUSTS NEAR
PORTLAND, OREGON HAS
LEFT COMMUNITIES
UPROOTED.
>> IT WAS ALMOST LIKE
A VIDEO GAME.
IT WAS LIKE ONE TREE
AFTER ANOTHER.
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
>> Reporter: NOT
EVERYONE COULD.
A MAN WAS KILLED WHILE
OUT ON A WALK AND
ANOTHER DIED WHEN HIS
BOAT CAPSIZED DURING
THE STORM.
IN EUGENE, OREGON FOUR
DIED IN A SMALL PLANE
CRASH.
GOING DOWN DURING THE
GUSTY CONDITIONS.
THE WIND STORM CALLED
THE WORST IN MORE THAN
20 YEARS LEFT
THOUSANDS IN THE DARK.
EARLIER IN OAKLAND,
CALIFORNIA, HEAVY
RAINFALL CAUSED THIS
MUDSLIDE, WET EARTH
SLIDING INTO HOMES
BELOW.
>> MUD IS COMING
THROUGH THERE INTO THE
BATHROOM AND THROUGH
THE BEDROOM AND INTO
THE HALLWAY.
>> Reporter: AS MUDDY
WATERS RUN INTO BACK
YARDS, NEIGHBORS ARE
STUNNED.
>> I DON'T KNOW WHAT
TO EXPECT NEXT.
>> Reporter: DRIVING
HAIL IN SACRAMENTO, A
FOOT OF FALLING SNOW
IN THE SIERRA
MOUNTAINS, THIS SURGE
OF WET WEATHER ENDS A
FIVE-YEAR DROUGHT IN
CALIFORNIA.
AND WHILE TOUGH FOR
SOME.
>> THERE'S GOING TO BE
A LOT OF BENEFITS WITH
THIS ADDITIONAL RAIN
AND SNOW AND IT'S
LIKELY TO CONTINUE
RIGHT OVER THE NEXT
SEVERAL WEEKS.
>> Reporter: THE
PACIFIC NORTHWEST
CLEANING UP WHILE
BRACING FOR THE NEXT
ROUND.
NBC NEWS.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, TRAINING FOR
WAR.
WE'RE WITH THE MEDIC
WHO WILL BE CALLED ON
TO SAVE LIVES ON THE
BATTLEFIELD.
>>> HE SEARCHES THE
FIELDS FOR THOSE WHO
LABOR ON HIS COUNTRY
FARM AND TURNS THEIR
LIVES INTO ARTISTIC
VISIONS.
>>> SAD NEWS TONIGHT A
U.S. SOLDIER WAS
KILLED IN AFGHANISTAN.
DOCTORING AN OPERATION
AGAINST A BRANCH OF
ISIS IN THAT COUNTRY.
THIS LATEST LOSS
UNDERSCORES HOW U.S.
FORCES REMAIN IN
HARM'S WAY.
IN AFGHANISTAN AND
IRAQ AND SYRIA AND THE
NEED FOR A GROUP OF
SOLDIERS WHO DON'T GET
MUCH ATTENTION.
ELITE MILITARY MEDICS.
A MEDICAL
CORRESPONDENT SPENT
TIME AT A NATO
TRAINING CENTER FOR
THOSE WHO SAVE LIVES.
>> Reporter: A SCENE
STRAIGHT FROM THE
BATTLEFIELD, BUT THESE
MEDICS AREN'T IN A WAR
ZONE.
WE'RE IN A
STATE-OF-THE-ART
TRAINING CENTER IN
BELGIUM.
NBC NEWS WAS GRANTED
ACCESS TO THIS MEDICAL
TRAINING.
>> GIVE ME YOUR PIT
FALLS NOW.
>> Reporter: AS AN AIR
FORCE COLONEL, PILOT
AND ER DOCTOR I SERVED
IN IRAQ.
I TEACH THESE SOLDIERS
TO WORK AS A MEDICAL
TEAM.
SMOKE, GUN FIRE,
EXPLOSION, THIS IS HOW
WITH HE TRAIN MEDICS.
>> THEY KNOW HOW TO
REACT AND THEY'VE BEEN
IN THAT SITUATION WITH
THE HEART RATE UP.
>> Reporter: THEY KNOW
THEY CAN DO IT.
>> THEY KNOW THEY CAN
DO IT AND THEY HAVE
CONFIDENCE IN THEIR
SKILLS.
>> Reporter: EVERY
SECOND MATTERS WHEN
YOU NEED TO SAVE THE
LIFE OF SOMEONE
FIGHTING AT YOUR SIDE
WHO DOESN'T EVEN SPEAK
YOUR LANGUAGE.
>> THERE COULD BE AN
INJURY ON THE LITTLE
FIELD BY A DANISH
SOLDIER THAT'S GOING
TO GET TREATED BY A
GERMAN MEDIC AND
THAT'S THE REALITY OF
THE BATTLEFIELD.
>> Reporter: THESE
SPECIAL FORCES ARE
PART OF THE NATO ELITE
TEAM.
DEPLOYED FOR SOME ON
OF THE MOST SECRET AND
DANGEROUS MISSIONS.
>> IT'S LANGUAGE BODY.
WE WORK WITH THE EYES,
THE HANDS, SO IT'S
LIKE WE ARE ONE
NATION.
>> Reporter: THESE
MEDICS WILL RETURN TO
THEIR HOME COUNTRIES
TO PASS ON THAT ES
VITAL SKILLS TO THEIR
FELLOW WARRIORS
WORKING TOGETHER AS
ONE TO SAVE LIVES.
ARE THESE SOME OF THE
MEDICS THAT COULD BE
SENT INTO SYRIA.
>> YES.
THEY ARE PART OF THE
SPECIAL FORCES ELITE
TEAMS.
THEY WOULD BE THE
FIRST ONES ON THE
GROUND THERE.
WHEN THEY GO IN,
LIMITED SUPPORT,
LIMITED BACKUP.
THEY'RE CARRYING
EVERYTHING ON THEIR
BACK.
THEY TREAT THEIR
SOLDIERS AND THEY
TREAT CIVILIANS.
IN A SITUATION LIKE
THIS WITH THE NERVE
AGENT, THEY WOULD BE
TREATING THOSE
CIVILIANS AS WELL.
THAT'S WHAT THEY'RE
TRAINED FOR.
THAT'S WHY WE DO THIS.
>> DOES THAT TRAINING
AND EXPERIENCE
TRANSLATE INTO
CIVILIAN MEDICINE?
>> IT DOES.
THERE'S LESSONS WE
HAVE LEARNED.
TIGHT WRAPS THAT YOU
USE ON ARMS AND LEGS
TO SAVE LIVES TO
PEOPLE DON'T BLEED
OUT.
THEY'VE BEEN USING
THEM FOR 15 YEARS.
THEY'RE NOW STARTING
TO GET IN THE CIVILIAN
WORLD THAT IS LESSONS
WE LEARNED FROM THE
SPECIAL FORCES.
>> Reporter: THANK
YOU.
>>> ONE WOMAN'S
MISSION HELPING
CHILDREN, U.S.
CITIZENS, WHO MIGHT
GET CAUGHT UP IN THE
IMMIGRATION BACKLASH.
>>> WITH ALL THE
CHANGES BEING
DISCUSSED ON
IMMIGRATION POLICY,
THE CHILDREN OF
UNDOCUMENTED
IMMIGRANTS, MILLIONS
WHO ARE U.S. CITIZENS
FACE AN UNCERTAIN
FUTURE.
IF THE PARENTS GET
DEPORTED THE KIDS
COULD END UP IN FOSTER
CARE OR ADOPTED BY
STRANGER.
HERE IS THE STORY OF
ONE WOMAN TRYING TO
HELP THEM.
>> Reporter: SHE HEARD
A KNOCK ON HER DOOR 8
YEARS AGO SHE DIDN'T
KNOW SHE WOULD BE
OPENING THE DOOR ON
HER NEW LIFE'S
MEDICATION.
>> TWO KIDS CAME
ASKING FOR HELP.
>> Reporter: WHAT
STARTED WITH TWO LED
TO HUNDREDS AND
FINALLY MORE THAN
1,000 CHILDREN ALL
U.S. CITIZENS WITH
UNDOCUMENTED PARENTS.
WHAT WOULD HAPPEN TO
THEM IF BOTH PARENTS
ARE DEPORTED?
>> THEY WILL BECOME
ORPHANS.
>> Reporter: TO AVOID
THE CHILDREN BEING PUT
INTO FOSTER CARE OR UP
FOR ADOPTION, THESE
PARENTS GRANT NORA
POWER OF ATTORNEY OVER
THEIR KIDS.
SOME COME FOR A FEW
DAYS.
OTHERS STAY FOR
MONTHS.
>> SHE'S A MOTHER TO
ME.
SHE'S MY SAVIOR.
>> Reporter: LIKE THIS
15-YEAR-OLD BOY WHOSE
PARENTS WERE DEPORTED
TO INDIA.
>> SHE DOES EVERYTHING
FOR ME.
IT'S AMAZING HOW A
WOMAN I'VE NEVER MET
IN MY LIFE AT FIRST
CAN GIVE ME SO MUCH
LOVE AND WELCOME ME SO
MUCH AS HER OWN CHILD.
>> Reporter: THIS
10-YEAR-OLD GIRL KNOWS
WHAT TO DO IF SHE IS
SEPARATED FROM HER
MOTHER.
>> SHE TOLD ME TO OPEN
THE DOOR AND TO CALL
HER AND TO COME AND
PICK ME UP.
>> Reporter: NORA SAYS
THOSE PHONE CALLS HAVE
BECOME MORE COMMON
SINCE PRESIDENT TRUMP
TOOK OFFICE.
>> I'M AN AMERICAN
CITIZEN AND I'M AN
ORPHAN.
MY FATHER WAS
DEPORTED.
>> Reporter: SHE HAS
BEEN GIVING THESE
CHILDREN A VOICE AT
MEETINGS WITH LOCAL
LEADERS IN SOUTH
FLORIDA AND
WASHINGTON.
>> THIS IS SO SAD TO
BE AN AMERICAN CITIZEN
AND BUT AN AMERICAN
CITIZEN WITHOUT
RIGHTS.
NOBODY'S PAYING
ATTENTION.
>> Reporter: AN
IMMIGRANT HERSELF SHE
TAKES NO MONEY FROM
THE PARENTS SAYING
THEY'VE ALREADY GIVEN
HER SO MUCH.
>> THEY HAVE GIVEN ME
A PIECE OF THEIR
HEART.
>> Reporter: IN RETURN
SHE GIVES THESE
PARENTS WHAT THEY WANT
MOST, PEACE OF MIND.
NBC NEWS, MIAMI.
>>> WE'LL BE RIGHT
BACK.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT
THEY ARE OFTEN
FORGOTTEN, THE MEN AND
WOMEN WHO WORK ON
FARMS TENDING THE
FIELDS AND PICKING THE
FOODS THAT WIND UP OUR
TABLES.
MIGRANT WORKERS PLAY A
ROLE IN OUR ECONOMY.
HERE'S HARRY SMITH.
>> Reporter: IN A
STUDIO OUTSIDE
COLORADO IT'S
IMPOSSIBLE TO TELL
WHAT THIS ARTIST IS
WORKING ON.
HE PAINTS WITH AN AIR
BRUSH.
CATTLE GRAZING IN A
PASTURE, A FAMILIAR
SCENE TO HIS FANS AND
COLLECTORS.
HE GREW UP ON A FARM
ON THE HIGH PLAINS OF
EASTERN COLORADO.
HE'S BEEN DRAWING OR
PAINTING SINCE HE WAS
4.
>> WE HAD THIS WHITE
ENAMEL TABLE.
I WOULD GO IN THERE
AND SPEND HOURS
DRAWING ON THAT TABLE
WITH A PENCIL.
NEVER ONCE DID MY
MOTHER EVER SAY,
DONALD, DON'T DRAW ON
THE TABLE.
>> Reporter: PAINTING
WHERE HE COMES FROM
HAS BEEN HIS LIFE'S
WORK, BUT 20 YEARS AGO
HE CHANGED HIS FOCUS
AND HE STARTED
PAINTING GIANT
PORTRAITS OF WORKERS.
>> I WAS PHOTOGRAPHING
COWS.
I TURN AROUND AND SEE
THESE MIGRANTS SITTING
ON SACKS.
I THOUGHT THAT IS
BEAUTIFUL.
>> Reporter: SO BEGAN
AN ODYSSEY.
>> I PHOTOGRAPHED FOR
ABOUT NINE YEARS GOING
FROM TEXAS TO
WASHINGTON STATE TO
CALIFORNIA TO FLORIDA.
>> Reporter: ALL TO
FIND THE FACES THAT
WOULD END UP ON
CANVASS, FACES THAT
GIVE IDENTITY TO THE
INVISIBLE PEOPLE WHO
LABOR DAY AFTER DAY TO
PUT FOOD ON OUR
TABLES.
IS SOME OF THIS ABOUT
BRINGING DIGNITY TO --
>> ABSOLUTELY.
TO THE WORKERS.
>> Reporter: AN
EXHIBIT OF THE SERIES
RUNS AT THE COLORADO
SPRINGS FINE ARTS
CENTER THROUGH THE END
OF MAY.
HE SWEARS HIS WORK IS
APOLITICAL.
HE SAYS THE PAINTINGS
SHOULD BE VIEWED WITH
AN OPEN MIND.
>> I WANT PEOPLE TO
LOOK AT THESE
PAINTINGS AND
APPRECIATE THEM FOR
THE BEAUTY THAT THESE
PEOPLE ARE AND WHAT
THEY DO.
I'M AFRAID IF PEOPLE
GET INTO TRYING TO
MAKE A POLITICAL
STATEMENT, IT CLOUDS
THE ISSUE WHERE
THEY'RE NOT GOING TO
SEE THEM.
>> Reporter: DON HAS
SPENT ALMOST A QUARTER
OF HIS 81 YEARS ON THE
MIGRANT SERIES.
HE CRIES SOMETIMES
WHEN HE SPEAKS ABOUT
THEM AND WHY HE CRIES,
HE SAYS, HE DOESN'T
KNOW EXACTLY.
HARRY SMITH, NBC NEWS,
COLORADO SPRINGS.
>>> THAT'S "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS" FOR THIS
SATURDAY.
TOMORROW THE
REMARKABLE DISCOVERY
ABOUT CYCLING AND HOW
IT COULD HELP THOSE
WITH A DEBILITATING
ILLNESS.
THANK YOU AND GOOD
NIGHT.
THIS LATEST ROUND OF SEVERE
WEATHER DISRUPTING LIVES IN THE
EAST BAY.
HOW THE WEATHER TRIGGERED A
DANGEROUS DOMINO EFFECT IN ONE
NEIGHBORHOOD.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS NOW.
GOOD EVENING TO YOU.
>> OAKLAND HILLS RESPECTS HIT
HARD BY THIS RECENT RAIN.
A TREE TOPEING DOWN SMASHING
INTO A HOUSE.
TWO BLOCKS AWAY FOUR HOMES RED
TAGGED AFTER A MUDSLIDE.
>> RICK BOONE IS NEAR THAT
DAMAGE.
SOME PEOPLE HAVE TO FIND A PLACE
TO GO TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: THAT'S WHAT THEY
ARE TRYING TO FIGURE OUT.
THEY HAVE BEEN DOING THAT SINCE
LAST NIGHT.
NOW TONIGHT.
YEAH, COULD BE ANOTHER WEEK IF
NOT LONGER PEGGY AND TERRY.
AS THIS IS A BIG CLEAN UP FOR
THE RESIDENTS WHO ARE REALLY
CONCERNED THAT THE WORST IS YET
TO DAM.
>> THERE ARE A LOT OF TREES
AROUND HERE AND THERE IS A LOT
OF WATER THAT'S BEEN COMING
DOWN.
WE LOVE THE TREES BUT THIS IS
SCARY.
>> Reporter: CREWS TRY TO SAVE A
HOUSE AFTER A TREE FELL ON
THORNHILL DRIVE IN OAKLAND
SMASHING A HOME WITH A FAMILY
INSIDE A BLOCK AWAY.
>> THEY WERE PICKING UP
EVERYTHING.
THEY WERE LOADING UP A COUPLE OF
CARS.
THEY HAD A LITTLE BABY THEY WERE
HAPPY DIDN'T GET HIT.
>> Reporter: THE NEXT DOOR
NEIGHBOR SAY IT HAPPENED EARLY