BACKPACK.
THE OTHER MAN IS WEARING A BLACK
BASEBALL CAP WITH WHITE BANDS ON
THE BILL AND A WHITE LETTER ON
THE FRONT.
HE'S WEARING A WHITE V-NECK
T-SHIRT, BEIGE PANTS, A BLACK
HOODED COAT.
HE'S CARRYING A DARK BACKPACK.
THIS VIDEO SHOWS THE MEN WALKING
TOGETHER TOWARD THE FINISH LINE.
THE FBI SAYS THE MAN IN THE
WHITE BASEBALL CAP FIRST
ATTRACTED THEIR ATTENTION
BECAUSE HE APPEARED TO BE
PLACING ONE OF THE BOMBS.
>> THE ONLY ONE OBSERVED TO BE
PLANTING WHAT WE BELIEVE IS THE
DEVICE IS SUSPECT NUMBER TWO
WITH THE WHITE CAP.
>> WHAT TIME DID THEY PUT THE
DEVICES DOWN?
>> I DON'T HAVE THE PRECISE TIME
IN FRONT OF ME.
IT WAS SHORTLY BEFORE THE BOMB
BLASTS WENT OFF.
>> Reporter: INVESTIGATORS SAY
THEIR ATTENTION WAS FOCUSED ON
THE MAN WITH THE WHITE HAT.
AS THEY ANALYZED MORE PICTURES
THEY REALIZED THE TWO SPENT TIME
TOGETHER.
THEY SAY THEY DID NOT SEE THE
OTHER MAN ACTUALLY PLANTING A
BOMB.
>> SOMEBODY OUT THERE KNOWS
THESE INDIVIDUALS AS FRIENDS,
NEIGHBORS, CO-WORKERS OR FAMILY
MEMBERS OF THE SUSPECTS.
IT MAY BE DIFFICULT BUT THE
NATION IS COUNTING ON THOSE WITH
INFORMATION TO COME FORWARD AND
PROVIDE IT TO US.
>> Reporter: AS FOR THE BOMBS
THEMSELVES INVESTIGATORS BELIEVE
BOTH WERE LIKELY DETONATED BY
ELECTRONIC REMOTE CONTROLS.
FEDERAL AGENTS HAVE BEEN
CANVASSING HOBBY STORES IN THE
BOSTON AREA ASKING ABOUT RECENT
PURCHASES OF REMOTE-CONTROLLED
DEVICES.
THE FBI'S HOPE IS THAT PEOPLE
WILL SEARCH THEIR MEMORIES TO
SEE IF THEY CAN SHED LIGHT ON
WHAT'S NOW THE MOST IMPORTANT
QUESTION.
WHO ARE THESE TWO MEN?
BRIAN?
>> SO, PETE, THE VIDEO AND
STILLS HAVE ONLY BEEN IN OUR
HANDS FOR ABOUT AN HOUR NOW.
LOOKING AT IT, WHAT CAN WE GLEAN
FROM PHYSICAL EVIDENCE, POSSIBLE
RELATIONSHIP BETWEEN THE TWO
MEN?
I HAVE LOOKED AT THE WEB
TONIGHT.
THERE IS ALREADY A SLEW OF
THEORIES AS TO WHAT THE
ICONOGRAPHY IS ON BOTH HATS.
LEADING THEORY IS IT'S A
BRIDGESTONE GOLF LOGO ON THE
DARKER OF THE TWO.
WHAT CAN BE LEARNED?
>> Reporter: AS FOR THE
BRIDGESTONE LOGO, THAT'S WHAT WE
ARE TOLD BY FEDERAL
INVESTIGATORS WHO HAVE SEEN
THESE PICTURES FOR A WHILE BASED
ON THEIR OWN ANALYSIS.
ONE THING THE FBI SAID TONIGHT
IS THAT THIS IS IN ESSENCE A
STARTER SET OF PHOTOS.
THEY HOPE TO KEEP LOOKING
THROUGH THE PICTURES AND AS THEY
COME UP WITH PICTURES THAT SHOW
PERHAPS BETTER VIEWS AND BETTER
RESOLUTION, THEY WILL RELEASE
THOSE, TOO.
THIS ISN'T IT.
THEY HOPE TO HAVE MORE.
>> AFTER ALL THE TALK ABOUT ALL
THE GOOD DIGITAL IMAGES OF THE
FINISH LINE, THE VIDEO THAT'S
BEEN RELEASED IS SO FAR PRETTY
STANDARD SURVEILLANCE CAMERA,
BUILDING-MOUNTED.
>> Reporter: RIGHT.
HIGHEST QUALITY IN ONE SENSE AND
ALSO A BIRD'S EYE VIEW.
BECAUSE THE PEOPLE WHO ARE ON
THE GROUND, THEIR VISIBILITY IS
GOING TO BE LIMITED AS THE CROWD
IN FRONT OF THEM BLOCKS THEIR
VIEW.
SECONDLY, IT'S THE SURVEILLANCE
CAMERA THAT GIVES THEM THE
STRATEGIC LOOK AT WHAT THESE MEN
WERE DOING.
IT'S MOTION VIDEO SO THEY CAN
WATCH THEIR MOVEMENTS.
>> ALL RIGHT.
PETE WILLIAMS IN OUR WASHINGTON
NEWSROOM.
NO DOUBT A BIG STEP FORWARD IN
THIS INVESTIGATION.
LESTER HOLT WAS ON THE STREET IN
BOSTON WHEN THE PHOTOS WENT
PUBLIC AT THAT VERY MOMENT.
HE WITNESSED THE START OF WHAT
SOMEONE TODAY CALLED THE FIRST
NATIONWIDE ELECTRONIC
CROWD-SOURCED MANHUNT OF THE
DIGITAL ERA.
LESTER, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: BRIAN, GOOD
EVENING.
WHEN THE CROWD WATCHING US
GLOMMED ONTO THE FACT WE WERE
TALKING ABOUT PICTURES OF
SUSPECTS, THE SMARTPHONES
IMMEDIATELY CAME OUT.
PEOPLE STARTED WATCHING THAT
VIDEO.
ONE MAN SAID TO ME, I WISH I
KNEW THEM.
THE PRESIDENT WAS HERE JUST A
FEW HOURS BEFORE WE LEARNED OF
THE SUSPECT.
WHETHER HE KNEW ABOUT THEM OR
NOT IS UNCLEAR.
HE HAD A MESSAGE FOR WHOEVER DID
THIS.
WE WILL FIND YOU.
BOSTONIANS STOOD FOR HOURS IN A
LINE TEN BLOCKS LONG FOR A
CHANCE TO PUBLICALLY SHARE THEIR
SORROW AND EVEN THEIR FEARS.
>> I'M SICKENED BY THIS.
WE LIVE IN SUCH A FREE COUNTRY
AND TO HAVE A SENSE OF
INSECURITY.
♪
>> Reporter: INSIDE THE
CATHEDRAL, TEARS FLOWED OPENLY.
>> WE WILL RISE IN COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: IN WHAT HAS BECOME
A RITUAL OF LARGE SCALE AMERICAN
TRAGEDIES, FAMILIES AND FIRST
RESPONDERS ALONG WITH CIVIC
LEADERS AND THE GENERAL PUBLIC
TURN TO FAITH AND EACH OTHER TO
WORK THROUGH PAIN.
>> TOMORROW THE SUN WILL RISE
OVER BOSTON.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT OBAMA IN
AN ALL TOO FAMILIAR ROLE OF
COMFORTER-IN-CHIEF DREW LESSONS
FROM THE MARATHON ITSELF.
>> SCRIPTURE TELLS US TO RUN
WITH ENDURANCE THE RACE THAT IS
SET BEFORE US.
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT ALSO
PAID TRIBUTE TO THOSE WHO DIED.
>> WE COME TOGETHER TO PRAY AND
MOURN.
>> Reporter: IN REMARKS LACED
WITH RESOLVE IN THE FACE OF AN
UNKNOWN ENEMY THE PRESIDENT
RALLIED BOSTON AND AMERICA TO BE
UNDETERRED.
>> THE WORLD WILL RETURN TO THIS
GREAT AMERICAN CITY TO RUN
HARDER THAN EVER AND TO CHEER
EVEN LOUDER FOR THAT 118th
BOSTON MARATHON.
>> Reporter: AS THE CROWD
APPLAUDED AND CHEERED, THE
PRESIDENT WIPED AWAY TEARS.
LATER, HE MET WITH RACE
VOLUNTEERS TO THANK THEM.
AS BOSTON TENDS TO ITS EMOTIONAL
WOUNDS, SIX PEOPLE INJURED IN
THE BOMBINGS REMAIN IN CRITICAL
CONDITION.
THE NUMBER STILL HOSPITALIZED,
FEWER THAN 60.
>> IN GENERAL, PATIENTS ARE
GETTING BETTER.
WE ARE HAPPY WITH THEIR
PROGRESS.
>> Reporter: MEANTIME, THE
BEEFED-UP POLICE PRESENCE IN
BOSTON WAS RAMPED UP EVEN MORE
FOR TODAY'S PRESIDENTIAL VISIT.
A REMINDER THAT THIS ATTACK
REMAINS UNSOLVED.
FIRST LADY MICHELLE OBAMA
TRAVELED WITH THE PRESIDENT
TODAY AND VISITED PATIENTS AND
STAFF AT SOME OF THE HOSPITALS
THAT TREATED THE WOUNDED.
BRIAN?
>> LESTER HOLT IN BOSTON FOR US
TONIGHT.
LESTER, THANKS.
>>> WE SHIFT OUR ATTENTION NOW
OUT WEST TO THE HUGE CONCUSSION
AND FIRE THAT TORE THROUGH THE
TOWN OF WEST TEXAS LAST NIGHT.
A MASSIVE EXPLOSION AT A
FERTILIZER SUPPLY OUTLET.
WEST IS ABOUT 20 MILES NORTH OF
WACO.
IT ONLY COVERS A COUPLE DOZEN
BLOCKS BUT AFTER THE BLAST WHICH
ACTUALLY REGISTERED A 2.1 ON THE
RICHTER SCALE, A BIG PART OF THE
COMMUNITY IS SIMPLY GONE TODAY.
WHILE IT IS UNCLEAR AS OF NOW
HOW MANY PEOPLE HAVE BEEN KILLED
THE MAYOR SAYS 30 TO 40 PEOPLE
ARE MISSING.
A LOT OF THOSE FIRST RESPONDERS.
160 MORE ARE INJURED.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER IS AT THE
SCENE FOR US TONIGHT.
MIGUEL, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: BRIAN, GOOD
EVENING.
THAT EXPLOSION TOOK PLACE A MILE
AWAY FROM HERE.
WE HAVE BEEN ASKED TO KEEP OUR
DISTANCE AS RESCUE TEAMS SEARCH
FOR THE MISSING.
IT'S FEARED AT LEAST 15 ARE
DEAD.
AS YOU MENTIONED, 160 WOUNDED.
OFFICIALS WORRY BOTH THOSE
NUMBERS MAY CLIMB.
THE BLAST DECIMATED FOUR CITY
BLOCKS.
A WAR ZONE WHERE TONIGHT FIRST
RESPONDERS ARE SEARCHING FOR
SURVIVORS.
IN THE SMALL TOWN OF WEST --
>> FIREFIGHTERS DOWN.
AGAIN, THERE HAS BEEN AN
EXPLOSION.
THERE ARE FIREFIGHTERS DOWN.
>> Reporter: -- EMERGENCY CREWS
SCOURED DEBRIS FOR THEIR OWN.
WEST VOLUNTEER FIREFIGHTERS WHO
RUSHED IN, BUT NEVER MADE IT
OUT.
>> THIS TRAGEDY HAS MOST LIKELY
HIT EVERY FAMILY.
IT'S TOUCHED PRACTICALLY
EVERYONE IN THAT TOWN.
>> Reporter: THE FIRE AT THE
WEST FERTILIZER COMPANY BROKE
OUT WEDNESDAY EVENING.
MINUTES LATER, A DEADLY
EXPLOSION.
>> ARE YOU OKAY?
>> DAD?
I CAN'T HEAR.
>> COVER YOUR EARS.
>> I CAN'T HEAR.
>> Reporter: THE BLAST SO
POWERFUL IT WAS FELT 50 MILES
AWAY AND REGISTERED AS A 2.1
SEISMIC EVENT.
>> THE WINDOWS CAME IN ON ME.
THE ROOF CAME IN ON ME.
THE CEILING CAME IN.
I WORKED MY WAY OUT TO GO GET
SOME MORE HELP.
>> Reporter: OUTSIDE OF WACO,
THE WEST FERTILIZER COMPANY SITS
ADJACENT TO A NURSING HOME, TWO
SCHOOLS AND AN APARTMENT
COMPLEX.
TONIGHT THE AREA IS IN SHAMBLES.
ROOFS PEELED BACK, WALLS RIPPED
APART.
SOME 80 HOMES GONE.
FEARS OF A TOXIC CLOUD FORCED A
MAKESHIFT TRIAGE CENTER AT A
NEARBY FOOTBALL FIELD TO BE
MOVED WEDNESDAY.
TODAY, OFFICIALS DEEMED THE AIR
SAFE WHILE DEFENDING
FIREFIGHTERS WHO USED WATER TO
BATTLE THE AMMONIA-FUELLED
BLAZE.
>> I DON'T THINK WE SHOULD BE
SECOND GUESSING RIGHT NOW THE
ACTIONS OF THE FIRST RESPONDERS
AND WHETHER THEY WERE APPLYING
WATER AT THE APPROPRIATE PLACE
AT THE APPROPRIATE TIME.
>> Reporter: TEXAS HAS SEEN
DISASTER BEFORE.
IN 1947, NEARLY 600 WERE KILLED
WHEN A SHIP CARRYING AMMONIUM
NITRATE EXPLODED.
IT'S THE SAME MATERIAL USED BY
TIMOTHY McVEIGH IN THE 1995
OKLAHOMA CITY BOMBING.
>> WE NEED EVERY AMBULANCE WE
CAN GET.
WE GOT A LOT OF FIREMEN DOWN.
>> Reporter: IN WEST, POLICE SAY
SO FAR NO SIGNS OF FOUL PLAY.
BUT HEARTBREAK HERE IS
EVERYWHERE.
>> I'M KIND OF NUMB.
REALLY DON'T KNOW.
LIKE I SAID, IT WILL PROBABLY
HIT ME AT THE FUNERAL.
MY FAMILY IS TAKING IT REALLY
BAD.
REALLY BAD RIGHT NOW.
IT'S REALLY ROUGH.
>> Reporter: AS THE SEARCH FOR
THE MISSING PRESSES ON.
>> IT'S ONE OF THOSE THAT HELPS
EVERYBODY.
WANTS TO HELP EVERYBODY IN NEED.
>> Reporter: AS FEDERAL AND
LOCAL OFFICIALS INVESTIGATE WE
SHOULD NOTE THAT IN 2006 THE
WEST FERTILIZER FACILITY WAS
FINED FOR NOT OBTAINING OR
HAVING A PERMIT.
THEY HAVE SINCE RECTIFIED THE
PROBLEM.
TONIGHT IT IS BELIEVED 40 PEOPLE
ARE INJURED AND STILL IN THE
HOSPITAL.
BRIAN, WE HAVE LEARNED TONIGHT
THAT ONE OF THE MEN WHO WAS
KILLED WAS AN OFF-DUTY DALLAS
FIREFIGHTER WHO CAME HERE TO
HELP.
BRIAN?
>> MIGUEL ALMAGUER IN THE BADLY
SHAKEN TOWN OF WEST TEXAS
TONIGHT.
MIGUEL, THANKS.
>>> NBC NEWS HAS CONFIRMED IT
WAS INDEED RICIN THAT WAS IN
THOSE LETTERS MAILED TO SOME
OFFICIALS IN WASHINGTON.
IT'S BEEN CONFIRMED DUE TO A
SECOND ROUND OF TESTS.
TODAY, 45-YEAR-OLD PAUL KEVIN
CURTIS WAS IN A MISSISSIPPI
COURTROOM CHARGED WITH MAKING
THREATS AGAINST PRESIDENT OBAMA,
MISSISSIPPI SENATOR ROGER
WICKER, AND A LOCAL COUNTY
JUDGE.
CURTIS HAPPENS TO BE AN ELVIS
IMPERSONATOR.
SENATOR WICKER HIRED HIM A
DECADE AGO TO WORK AT AN EVENT.
A LAWYER FOR CURTIS SAID HE WAS
INNOCENT.
OFFICIALS SAY NONE OF THIS WAS
RELATED TO THE BOSTON BOMBINGS
THIS WEEK.
>>> STILL AHEAD FOR US ON THIS
THURSDAY NIGHT, CARS SWALLOWED
WHOLE DURING A MORNING COMMUTE.
FLOODING SO BAD THE GROUND IS
GIVING WAY IN SOME PLACES.
A LOT OF FOLKS ARE IN FOR A WILD
ONE AHEAD.
LATER THE WARNING TODAY FROM THE
F.A.A.
THE REASON FOR MAJOR FLIGHT
DELAYS STARTING THIS WEEKEND AT
A LOT OF THE BEST KNOWN AIRPORTS
ACROSS THIS COUNTRY.
>>> TAKE A LOOK AT THE NATIONAL
RADAR AND LOOK AT THE FRONT
CUTTING NORTH TO SOUTH AND
MOVING TO THE EAST.
IT'S A HUGE WEATHER SYSTEM
STRETCHING FROM THE MEXICAN
BORDER ALL THE WAY INTO CANADA,
DUMPING TORRENTS OF RAIN, SNOW,
HAIL, SPAWNING TORNADOES ALONG
THE WAY.
IT'S LEFT A LOT OF DAMAGE
BEHIND.
THE CHICAGO AREA PARTICULARLY
HARD-HIT.
NBC'S JOHN YANG IS IN LISLE,
ABOUT 25 MILES OUTSIDE OF
CHICAGO.
JOHN, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
BRIAN.
THE RADAR SAYS THERE IS MORE
RAIN ON THE WAY.
ACROSS THE REGION RIVERS ARE
STILL RISING AS FORECASTERS ARE
PREDICTING RECORD LEVELS AND
MASSIVE FLOODING.
CHICAGO STREETS TURNED INTO
RIVERS AND LANES OF MAJOR
EXPRESSWAYS SHUT DOWN AS HEAVY
RAIN FELL FASTER THAN STORM
SEWERS COULD CARRY IT AWAY.
NEIGHBORHOODS QUICKLY FLOODED.
IN LISLE, FIREFIGHTERS SET OUT
IN BOATS TO ANSWER CALLS FOR
HELP.
>> WE HAD TO BE PREPARED NOT
ONLY TODAY BUT OVER THE NEXT
SEVERAL DAYS FOR FLOODING IN
DIFFERENT PARTS OF OUR STATE.
>> Reporter: ON CHICAGO'S SOUTH
SIDE A CAR DROVE INTO A SINKHOLE
WHICH EVENTUALLY SWALLOWED TWO
PARKED CARS.
NORTH OF THE CITY IN GURNEY,
RESIDENTS HAVE PREPARED FOR
FLOODING FROM THE DES PLAINS
RIVER BY SANDBAGGING HOMES AND
BUSINESSES.
>> WE HAVE BEEN HERE ABOUT TEN
YEARS.
THIS IS ACTUALLY THE WORST IT'S
BEEN.
>> Reporter: THE RIVER IS
EXPECTED TO CREST TOMORROW
MORNING AT 11 1/2 FEET, A
RECORD.
OFFICIALS ARE ENCOURAGING
RESIDENTS ALONG THE RIVER TO
EVACUATE.
>> IT COULD BE A WEEK OR TWO
BEFORE FLOOD LEVELS
SIGNIFICANTLY DROP.
>> Reporter: PARTS OF IOWA AND
ILLINOIS HAVE GOTTEN MORE THAN
SEVEN INCHES OF RAIN AND TOTALS
APPROACHING SIX INCHES ARE NOT
UNCOMMON.
IN SOUTH DAKOTA THE STORM SYSTEM
BROUGHT SNOW AND TEMPERATURES IN
THE 20s.
WARMER WEATHER IN OKLAHOMA
SPAWNED AT LEAST FOUR TORNADOES
BUT NO ONE WAS SERIOUSLY
INJURED.
BACK IN CHICAGO, SUMP PUMPS ARE
HOT ITEMS.
>> WE'VE GOT THE LAST ONE HERE.
WE GOT ONE FROM THE FRONT OF THE
STORE.
THAT'S ABOUT IT.
EVERYONE WHO CAME IN BEHIND US,
I'M SURE THEY DIDN'T GET ONE.
>> Reporter: CYNTHIA GILL AND
HER FAMILY MOVED TO LISLE JUST
LAST WEEK.
NOW THEIR HOME IS AN ISLAND.
THEIR BASEMENT UNDER WATER.
>> MY DAUGHTER FLOATED ON A
MATTRESS TODAY TO TRY TO
RETRIEVE AS MUCH AS SHE SHOULD.
>> Reporter: WEATHER CHANNEL
METEOROLOGIST MIKE SEIDEL SAYS
THE DANGER HAS NOT PASSED.
>> ALTHOUGH THE RAIN AND STORMS
WILL END TONIGHT IN THE MIDWEST
ALL THE WATER HAS TO GO
SOMEWHERE.
IT IS GOING TO RUN INTO THE
RIVERS AND MANY OF THOSE WILL GO
OVER THEIR BANKS INTO FLOOD
STAGE AS WE HEAD TOWARDS THE
WEEKEND.
>> Reporter: OF COURSE
THUNDERSTORMS MEANS TROUBLE IN
THE AIR.
AT CHICAGO O'HARE AIRPORT, MORE
THAN 600 FLIGHTS CANCELLED
BECAUSE OF WEATHER.
BRIAN?
>> JOHN YANG REPORTING ON THE
WEATHER FOR US TONIGHT FROM
LISLE, ILLINOIS.
JOHN, THANKS.
>>> WE ARE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
WORD OF A HEALTH SCARE TONIGHT
FOR A HOLLYWOOD LEGEND AND HIS
PUBLIC REQUEST FOR HELP IN
FIGURING OUT WHAT IT IS.
>>> TALK ABOUT A SENTIMENTAL
JOURNEY.
THIS WILL WARM YOUR HEART AND WE
COULD USE SOME OF THAT RIGHT
ABOUT NOW.
OF THE 75 ORIGINAL DOOLITTLE
RAIDERS FROM WORLD WAR II ONLY
FOUR MEN SURVIVE TODAY.
NOW THREE OF THEM HAVE GATHERED
FOR WHAT WILL BE THEIR LAST
REUNION.
IT INCLUDED A FLIGHT IN A
BEAUTIFULLY RESTORED B-25.
DURING THE ORIGINAL OUTLANDISH
RAIDS 71 YEARS AGO TODAY 16
AIRCRAFT, ALL LOADED WITH
ONE-TON BOMBS TOOK OFF FROM THE
DECK OF A CARRIER FOUR MONTHS
AFTER PEARL HARBOR WITH ONLY
ENOUGH FUEL ON BOARD TO DROP
BOMBS ON TOKYO AND THEN LAND IN
CHINA WHERE THEY COULD ONLY HOPE
FOR SAFETY.
>>> REMARKABLE VIDEO OUT OF THE
UK.
IT IS ROUGH BUT THEN AGAIN IT
WAS A ROUGH DAY FOR LANDINGS AT
LEEDS BRADFORD AIRPORT.
IN THE MIDST OF A 70 MILES PER
HOUR GALE, BUT LAND THEY DID.
CRABBING INTO THE WIND ON FINAL
APPROACH.
NOT EVEN CLOSE TO LINING UP WITH
THE CENTER LINE OF THE RUNWAY,
BUT ALL OF THEM MANAGED TO
STRAIGHTEN OUT IN TIME.
SADLY IN-FLIGHT DRINK SERVICE
DIDN'T INCLUDE COMPLIMENTARY
COCKTAILS UPON ARRIVAL.
>>> ON THE SUBJECT OF AIR
TRAVEL, SOONER OR LATER THE
SO-CALLED SEQUESTER IN
WASHINGTON IS GOING TO AFFECT
ALL AMERICANS.
LIKE STARTING THIS SUNDAY WHEN
THE AIR TRAFFIC CONTROLLER
FURLOUGHS START.
OFFICIALS WARNED TODAY AT
AIRPORTS LIKE ATLANTA, CHICAGO,
O'HARE, NEWARK, JFK, LAGUARDIA,
DELAYS WILL START TO BE FELT.
UPWARDS OF 50 MINUTES ON SOME
FLIGHTS AT O'HARE.
>>> SOME UNSETTLING NEWS ABOUT
AN AMERICAN FAVORITE.
DICK VAN DYKE HAS BEEN FORCED TO
CANCEL AN APPEARANCE IN NEW YORK
BECAUSE OF AN UNDIAGNOSED
NEUROLOGICAL DISORDER.
HE'S ASKING FOR HELP WITH A
DIAGNOSIS.
ON HIS TWITTER ACCOUNT, DICK VAN
DYKE SOLICITED ASSISTANCE IN
FIGURING OUT WHAT HE'S GOT.
A THROBBING CONDITION IN HIS
HEAD WHEN HE TRIES TO LIE DOWN.
IT'S LED TO LACK OF SLEEP AND
FATIGUE.
IT HAS ELUDED TESTS AND SCANS SO
FAR.
DICK VAN DYKE IS 87 YEARS OLD.
>>> AND SOME GOOD NEWS TO REPORT
FROM THE WORLD OF PUBLIC HEALTH.
THE NATION'S INFANT MORTALITY
RATE FELL BY A FULL 12% IN THE
YEARS '05 TO 2011, HAVING BEEN
STATIC FOR YEARS.
THE BIGGEST CHANGE FOR THE
BETTER WAS IN THE SOUTH.
BUT THE U.S. STILL RANKS AN
EMBARRASSING 27th IN INFANT
MORTALITY AMONG THE WORLD'S 30
LEADING DEVELOPED NATIONS.
>>> ANOTHER PROBLEM FOR CARNIVAL
CRUISE LINE.
THIS TIME ON BOARD THE
"ECSTASY."
IT LOST POWER AT SEA WHILE
SAILING OFF THE COAST OF FLORIDA
WITH 2,000 PASSENGERS ON BOARD.
THE CRUISE LINE SAYS THERE WAS
NO FIRE, NO EMERGENCY.
POWER WAS EVENTUALLY RESTORED.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK HERE
TONIGHT, THE AMAZING MOMENT FROM
LAST NIGHT IN BOSTON.
>>> FINALLY HERE TONIGHT IN THE
WAKE OF THE MARATHON BOMBINGS,
BOSTON STRONG HAS EMERGED AS THE
PHRASE AND THE ICONOGRAPHY THAT
THE ENTIRE REGION HAS TAKEN ON.
IT WAS A TIGHT TOWN BEFORE THIS.
IT'S EVEN MORE SO NOW.
OUR OWN BAY STATE NATIVE ANNE
THOMPSON HAS OUR REPORT FROM
THERE TONIGHT.
♪ O SAY CAN YOU SEE
>> Reporter: THE FULL-THROATED
RENDITION OF THE NATIONAL ANTHEM
AT THE BRUINS GAME CAME AS NO
SURPRISE.
♪ OVER THE RAMPARTS
>> Reporter: BOSTONIANS HAVE
ALWAYS WORN THEIR PATRIOTISM ON
THEIR SLEEVE OR ON THEIR CHEST.
PETER RINIG PRINTS T-SHIRTS FOR
A LIVING.
WHAT'S THE IMPORTANCE OF THE
T-SHIRT?
>> TO SAY WHO YOU ARE.
>> Reporter: THIS SHIRT BEARS A
SIMPLE MESSAGE IN A CITY WHERE
TODAY THERE ARE NO DEGREES OF
SEPARATION.
>> EVERYBODY IN THE CITY KNOWS
EACH OTHER.
I THINK THAT'S WHAT MAKES BOSTON
BOSTON, YOU KNOW?
>> Reporter: HE KNEW CRYSTAL
CAMPBELL, ONE OF THE THREE
PEOPLE KILLED IN THE ATTACKS.
SOME OF THE MONEY FROM THE
T-SHIRTS WILL GO TO HER FAMILY
WHO TODAY MET WITH PRESIDENT
OBAMA.
>> YOUR DAUGHTER CRYSTAL WAS
ALWAYS SMILING.
♪
>> Reporter: AT THE INTERFAITH
SERVICE, MAYOR THOMAS MENINO,
RECOVERING FROM A BROKEN LEG,
PERSONIFIED HIS CITY AS HE STOOD
TO SPEAK -- WOUNDED BUT
DETERMINED.
>> BECAUSE THIS IS BOSTON.
A CITY WITH COURAGE, COMPASSION,
STRENGTH THAT KNOWS NO BOUNDS.
>> Reporter: YOU COULD SEE ITS
STRENGTH IN THE ARMS THAT
REACHED OUT TO RESCUE AND
COMFORT.
ONE MAN LITERALLY GIVING THE
SHIRT OFF HIS BACK DURING THOSE
FIRST CHAOTIC MOMENTS.
IN THE HANDS THAT GAVE OUT FOOD
AND WROTE CHECKS.
WHEN THOSE ARMS GREW WEARY --
♪ O, SAY DOES THAT STAR
SPANGLED ♪
>> Reporter: VOICES WERE RAISED
IN THE CITY WHERE THE AMERICAN
REVOLUTION BEGAN.
♪ THE LAND OF THE FREE
>> Reporter: THE HUB OF AMERICA
TODAY IS ITS HEART.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC NEWS, BOSTON.
♪ AND THE HOME OF THE BRAVE
>> ON THAT STRONG NOTE, THAT IS
OUR BROADCAST ON A THURSDAY
NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING HERE WITH
US.
I'M BRIAN WILLIAMS.
WE, OF COURSE, HOPE TO SEE YOU
RIGHT BACK HERE TOMORROW
EVENING.
>>> GOOD EVENING EVERYONE, I'M
IN FOR RAJ MATHAI.
>> WE'LL HAVE MORE ON THE FIRST
LADY'S VISIT WITH THE LOCAL
VICTIM ON THE ATTACK.
>>> AND WE BEGIN WITH THE
INVESTIGATION, FREE TIME OFF FOR
THE SELECTIVE EMPLOYEES IN THE
DISTRICT ATTORNEY'S OFFICE.
OUR INVESTIGATIVE UNIT FIRST
BROKE THE STORY THIS MONTH.
SANTA CLARA DISTRICT ATTORNEY
JEFF ROSEN GIVING TIME OFF TO
THE STAFF, TO MAKE UP FOR THE 5%
BONUS CUT.
>> WE HAVE JUST LEARNED COUNTY
COUNCIL HAS ISSUED ITS OPINION
ON THE LEGALITY OF THE DISTRICT
ATTORNEY GIVING FREE TIME OFF.
IT IS A CONFIDENTIAL DOCUMENT
DELIVERED TO THE BOARD OF
SUPERVISORS.
THE SOURCES CLOSE TO THE
COUNTY'S INVESTIGATION SAYS IT
DOES NOT LOOK GOOD FOR THE DA.
ONE PROBLEM IS HOW IT COULD OPEN
UP FOR OTHERS IN A BIG WAY.
OTHERS CALL IT THE ME-TOO
CLAUSE.
>> Reporter: LETTER AFTER
LETTER.
>> THERE IS A LOT OF ANIMOSITY
TOWARDS MR. ROSEN RIGHT NOW.
>> Reporter: DIFFERENT UNIONS,
SAME CONCERNS.
>> WE HAD AN UNDERSTANDING, A
TRUST, AN AGREEMENT.
A CONTRACT.
AND WE DID NOT EXPEC TO BE
SITTING HERE TODAY.
>> Reporter: IT COMES AFTER OUR
INVESTIGATION EXPOSES THE
DISTRICT ATTORNEY, JEFF ROSEN,
SUGGEST THAT TIME SHEETS BE
ALTER
ALTERED, ALLOWING EMPLOYEES TO
BANK VACATION AND SICK TIME
WHICH THEY CAN LATER USE.
HE MADE UP FOR A 5% BONUS CUT IN
THE MIDDLE OF THE BUDGET CRISIS.
>> SO YES, I BROUGHT IN
ADMINISTRATIVE LEAVE TO TRY TO
COMPENSATE THEM IN SOME WAY FOR
THAT.
>> Reporter: THAT ANSWER WOULD
BE A COSTLY ONE FOR THE COUNTY.
>> IT IS A PUBLIC GIFT THAT THE
PUBLIC DIDN'T KNOW THEY WERE
GIVING AWAY.
>> Reporter: THE SANTA CLARA
COUNTY PEACE OFFICER'S
ASSOCIATION HAD TO MAKE DRASTIC
CUTS TO HELP THE COUNTY.
>> FOR US IT IS A HUGE SLAP IN
THE CASE.
>> Reporter: UNIONS ARE NOW
POINTING TO THE ME-TOO CLAUSE IN
THEIR COUNTY CONTRACTS.
IT MEANS IF ONE COUNTY DIDN'T
TAKE THE CUTS PROMISED, OTHERS
DON'T HAVE TO EITHER.
>> ALL WE'RE ASKING FOR MYSELF
AND THE ASSOCIATION IS TO BE
TREATED FAIRLY.
THAT MEANS THAT THE COUNTY HAS
TO COME DOWN A LITTLE BIT ON
JEFF ROSEN AND WHAT HE IS DOING,
IS TO GET THINGS CORRECTED AND
THAT IT WHAT SHOULD HAPPEN.
>> BUT IF THE COUNTY IS NOT
GOING TO DO THAT BECAUSE HE IS
AN ELECTED OFFICIAL THEN THEY
HAVE NO OTHER MEANS OTHER THAN
TO MAKE EVERYBODY WHOLE.
WHICH MEANS FAIR SHARE FOR
EVERYBODY ELSE.
>> Reporter: SERGEANT DENNIS
MOSER IS THE PRESIDENT OF THE
ASSOCIATION.
>> BECAUSE YOU'RE AN ELECTED
OFFICIAL DOESN'T PUT YOU ABOVE
THE LAW.
>> Reporter: OTHER UNIONS ARE
ALSO DEMANDING ANSWERS.
THE REGISTERED NURSE'S UNION
SAYS THEY INTENTIONALLY VIOLATED
THE AGREEMENTS.
THE BUILDING AND CONSTRUCTION
TRADE WRITES IT IS WRONG
REGARDING THE ASSOCIATION.
OTHERS TALK ABOUT HOW IT COULD
IMPACT THE BUDGET.
>> IT IS VERY IMPORTANT HOW WE
GET THE CONTRACTS BUTTONED UP
AND THAT NOBODY DID SOMETHING
LIKE THAT.
>> Reporter: ROSEN STILL STANDS
BY HIS DECISION, CALLING THE 5%
BONUS CUT UNFAIR.
>> THAT IS NOT FAIR TO P