FOUND TODAY BY TWO FIREFIGHTERS
AT DYLAN BEACH.
>> NICE REUNION THERE.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US.
LESTER HOLT IS NEXT.
>> BYE.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT A
TRUMP ADMINISTRATION
PREPARING
OPTIONS FOR A MILITARY
STRIKE IN
SYRIA.
IS AMERICA ABOUT TO
WEIGH DEEPER INTO A
BLOODY CIVIL WAR AFTER
THAT HORRIFIC CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
ALL OF THAT AMID A
TENSE CONFRONTATION
OVER THE NORTH KOREA
NUCLEAR THREAT.
PRESIDENT TRUMP, THE
PRESIDENT
OF CHINA AND A
HIGH-STAKES
SHOWDOWN IN FLORIDA.
>>> PALACE INTRIGUE.
AFTER THE SUDDEN
DEMOTION OF TOP
TRUMP ADVISOR STEVE
BANNON,
TONIGHT WORD OF A
POWER STRUGGLE
WITH TRUMP'S
SON-IN-LAW JARED
KUSHNER.
>>> HOME GENETIC
TESTING
APPROVED BY THE FDA
FOR THE
FIRST TIME.
AT HOME TESTS FOR
EVERYTHING
FROM PARKINSON'S TO
LATE-STAGE
ALZHEIMER'S.
WOULD YOU WANT TO
KNOW?
>>> REMEMBERING DON
RICKLES, A
BELOVED COMEDY LEGEND
WHO
INVENTED A GENRE ALL
HIS OWN.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING FROM
LOS ANGELES, TO OUR
VIEWERS IN THE WEST,
AS WE COME ON THE AIR,
THE TRUMP WHITE HOUSE
MAY BE ON THE VERGE OF
LAUNCHING A MAJOR
MILITARY STRIKE
AGAINST SYRIA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP SPENT
PART OF THIS DAY
HUDDLED WITH HIS TOP
MILITARY ADVISERS,
REVIEWING OPTIONS THAT
MAY INCLUDE KEEPING
SYRIA'S AIR FORCE OUT
OF THE SKY OR EVEN
CRUISE MISSILE
ATTACKS.
AS A WAY OF PUNISHING
THE SYRIAN GOVERNMENT
FOR THAT HORRIFIC
CHEMICAL WEAPONS
ATTACK EARLIER THIS
WEEK.
AND IN A MAJOR POLICY
SHIFT, THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS
SPEAKING OPENLY ABOUT
REMOVING BASHAR AL
ASSAD FROM POWER.
WE HAVE TWO REPORTS,
WE BEGIN WITH HALLIE
JACKSON.
>> GOOD EVENING,
LESTER.
THIS IS THE ULTIMATE
TEST FOR A COMMANDER
IN CHIEF, WHETHER TO
TAKE MILITARY ACTION,
IN THIS CASE, AFTER A
HUMANITARIAN CRISIS
THAT HAS GRIPPED THE
COUNTRY WITH THE WORLD
WATCHING.
STEPPING OFF HIS PLANE
INTO THE CENTER OF AN
INTERNATIONAL CRISIS,
PRESIDENT TRUMP
HUDDLING TONIGHT WITH
HIS DEFENSE SECRETARY
FOR AN URGENT BRIEFING
ON MILITARY OPTIONS
AGAINST BASHAR AL
ASSAD.
>> I THINK WHAT
HAPPENED IN SYRIA IS A
DISGRACE TO HUMANITY.
AND HE'S THERE, AND I
GUESS HE'S RUNNING
THINGS, SO SOMETHING
SHOULD HAPPEN.
>> SOMETHING SHOULD
HAPPEN, HE SAYS.
NOT SPECIFIC BUT STILL
HIS STRONGEST SIGNAL
YET HE MAY MOVE TO
PUSH ASSAD OUT.
>> IT'S A SERIOUS
MATTER, IT REQUIRES A
SERIOUS RESPONSE.
>> Reporter: THE
SECRETARY OF STATE
SUGGESTING THERE'S NO
ROLE FOR ASSAD TO
GOVERN THE SYRIAN
PEOPLE.
CALLING ON OUR ALLIES
TO ACT THROUGH THE
POLITICAL PROCESS.
>> THOSE STEPS ARE
UNDERWAY.
>> TWO MILITARY
OFFICIALS TELL NBC
NEWS THE U.S. WATCHED
ON RADAR AS A SYRIAN
PLANE DROPPED BOMBS IN
THE NORTHERN PART OF
THE COUNTRY MONDAY.
HITTING A HOSPITAL,
THE FLASHES AND BOOMS
CLEARLY VISIBLE.
VICTIMS ON THE GROUND
REACTING LIKE THEY HAD
BEEN EXPOSED TO A
NERVE AGENT.
VICTIMS LIKE THE ONES
BURIED TODAY BY ABDEL
HAMEED EL-YOUSSEF.
CRYING OUT THE NAMES
OF HIS 2-YEAR-OLD
TWINS.
HIS CHILDREN AND WIFE
AMONG THE MORE THAN
HUNDREDS OF SYRIANS
KILLED.
IMAGES LIKE THESE HAVE
HORRIFIED THE
PRESIDENT.
TRIGGERING HIS
REVERSAL ON SYRIA.
NOW JUST 11 WEEKS INTO
HIS ADMINISTRATION,
THIS CRISIS BRINGING
HIM TO THE BRINK OF A
DECISION THAT WILL
DEFINE HIS LEGACY.
>> IF HE DOES NOTHING,
IT'S GOING TO BE OBAMA
ON STEROIDS IN TERMS
OF HIS PERCEPTION.
IF HE ACTS DECISIVELY
AND RESPONSIBLY, HE
CAN SET THE MIDEAST.
>> Reporter: A RUSSIAN
SPOKES PERSON TODAY
TELLS THE U.S. IT'S
SUPPORT FOR ASSAD IS
NOT CONDITIONAL.
HERE IN THE U.S., A
HIGH STAKES CRASH
COURSE, SYRIA NOW
OVERSHADOWING NORTH
KOREA.
THE COMPANY AT THE TOP
OF HIS AGENDA.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> AS LANGUAGE ABOUT
THE ASSAD REGIME
CANNOT LEAD AN
UNBIASSED
INVESTIGATION.
>> AS FAR AS I CAN
TELL, CONGRESSMAN
NUNES KILLED THAT.
>> THE INVESTIGATION
CAN HAVE A FRESH
START.
>> THE WORK HAS ALWAYS
CONTINUED BUT NOW I
THINK THE CLOUD THAT
HAD SETTLED OVER THE
COMMITTEE'S WORK HAS
BEEN LIFTED.
>> SCHIFF ALSO SAYS
HE'S OPTIMISTIC ABOUT
WORKING WITH THE
REPUBLICAN TAKING OVER
THE PROBE.
CONGRESSMAN MIKE KONYA
WAY OF TEXAS, TELLING
REPORTERS HERE AT THE
CAPITOL HE WILL FOLLOW
EVERY LEAD IN THIS
INVESTIGATION NO
MATTER HOW LONG IT
TAKES.
LESTER?
>> KASIE, THANK YOU.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
NOMINEE FOR THE
SUPREME COURT APPEARS
ALL BUT CERTAIN FOR
CONFIRMATION TOMORROW
AFTER HIGH DRAMA ON
THE SENATE FLOOR AND A
HISTORIC CHANGE BY
REPUBLICANS TO
OVERCOME A DEMOCRATIC
BLOCKADE.
AT 49 YEARS OLD, NEIL
GORSUCH COULD SIT ON
THE HIGH COURT FOR
DECADES.
OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: AS THE
SENATE PREPARED FOR
THE HISTORIC SHOWDOWN,
EMOTIONS WERE RAW OVER
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
NOMINEE, NEIL GORSUCH.
>> THE OPPOSITION TO
THIS PARTICULAR
NOMINEE IS MORE ABOUT
THE MAN THAT NOMINATED
HIM, AND THE PARTY HE
REPRESENTS.
THAN THE NOMINEE
HIMSELF.
>> DEMOCRATS WERE
STILL FUMING THAT
PRESIDENT OBAMA'S
NOMINEE MERRICK
GARLAND NEVER GOT A
HEARING.
>> THEY KEPT THAT
POSITION VACANT SO IT
COULD BE FILLED BY A
REPUBLICAN PRESIDENT.
THAT'S EXACTLY WHY
WE'RE HERE TODAY.
>> Reporter: AFTER
REPUBLICANS FAILED TO
MUSTER THE 60 VOTES
NEEDED TO END THE
FILIBUSTER ON GORSUCH,
THEY NEED TO ELIMINATE
FILIBUSTERS FOR
SUPREME COURT
NOMINEES.
THE NUCLEAR OPTION WAS
INVOKED WITH
REPUBLICANS ACTING OUT
OF PARTISAN DUTY
RATHER THAN PRINCIPLE.
>> I THINK IT'S A SAD
DAY FOR THE SENATE.
WE HAVE NOW DESTROYED
200 YEARS OF
TRADITION, REQUIRING
60 VOTES.
>> MANY LEGAL EXPERTS
SAY FROM NOW ON, WHEN
THE WHITE HOUSE AND
SENATE ARE CONTROLLED
BY THE SAME PARTY,
PRESIDENTS WILL BE
LESS LIKELY TO APPOINT
MODERATES.
>> IT WILL BECOME MUCH
MORE PARTISAN, AND
PRESIDENTS WILL NOT BE
ABLE TO NOMINATE
PEOPLE WHO ARE MORE
EXTREME.
THEY WON'T HAVE TO
CATER TO THE OTHER
PARTY.
>> Reporter: IT'S A
SAFE BET THAT NEIL
GORSUCH WILL BE
CONFIRMED TOMORROW IN
TIME TO TAKE HIS SEAT
AND HEAR THE FINAL 13
CASES OF THE TERM.
PETE WILLIAMS, NBC
NEWS AT THE SUPREME
COURT.
>>> LOTS OF SEVERE
WEATHER TONIGHT IN THE
EASTERN PART OF THE
COUNTRY WITH MILLIONS
FACING THE POSSIBILITY
OF DANGEROUS STORMS,
IN A WEEK THAT'S
ALREADY SEEN
WIDESPREAD DESTRUCTION
FROM DEVASTATING
TORNADOS.
WE GET THE LATEST FROM
NBC'S JACOB RASCON.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
STRONG WINDS, HEAVY
RAIN AND POSSIBLE
TORNADOS WREAKING
HAVOC ACROSS SEVERAL
STATES.
SIGNIFICANT DAMAGE
REPORTED IN PARTS OF
VIRGINIA, BRUTAL WINDS
TOSSING LARGE TREES
INTO HOMES.
KNOCKING OUT POWER TO
THOUSANDS.
>> SHE WAS SCREAMING,
I COULD NOT CONSOLE
HER, WE HUDDLED IN THE
LIVING ROOM.
>> PORTIONS OF THE
D.C. METRO AREA UNDER
A TORNADO WARNING AS
THE STORM PUSHED
THROUGH RIPPING THE
ROOF OFF THIS HIGH
SCHOOL BUILDING.
IN FLORIDA, AT LEAST A
DOZEN HOMES DESTROYED
BY A TORNADO TORNADO
IN OKEECHOBEE COUNTY,
AND THIS MASSIVE HOUSE
FIRE SPARKED BY
LIGHTNING.
IN THE MIDWEST, GUSTS
SO POWERFUL, THEY
SHATTERED HIGH RISE
WINDOWS IN CHICAGO.
OVER 15 MILLION
AMERICANS FACE SOME
SEVERE WEATHER THREAT
TODAY.
THE SAME SYSTEM THAT'S
RAVAGED THE SOUTH ALL
WEEK, FORCING MORE
THAN 1,000 FLIGHT
CANCELLATIONS IN
ATLANTA ALONE.
AND PRODUCING MORE
THAN 10 REPORTED
TORNADOS SO FAR,
INCLUDING IN
ELIZABETHTOWN,
KENTUCKY.
>> I FELT MY TRAILER
SHAKE, I SAW DEBRIS
FROM OVER THERE
HITTING MY TRAILER
MUCH.
>> Reporter: A LARGE
BARN LEVELED IN OHIO.
A MASSIVE CLEANUP
EFFORT FROM THE LATEST
TWISTER OUTBREAK.
AS THE LATEST SEVERE
WEATHER THREAT MOVES
NORTHEAST.
NO INJURIES WERE
REPORTED TODAY.
THE SEVERE WEATHER
THREAT MOVES ON
TONIGHT, AND INTO
TOMORROW MORNING,
INCLUDING FLOOD
WATCHES IN PARTS OF
THE NORTHEAST.
LESTER?
>> JACOB RASCON
TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, FINDING OUT
YOUR RISK FOR CERTAIN
DISEASES, THE FDA
APPROVES AT HOME
GENETIC TESTING.
ALSO REMEMBERING ONE
OF THE MOST FUNNY MEN
OF OUR TIME.
DON RICKELS.
>>> WE'RE BA
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH BIG HEALTH NEWS
TONIGHT FOR ANYONE
WHO'S EVER WORRIED
THEY MAY CARRIE A GENE
THAT PUTS THEM AT RISK
FOR LIFE THREATENING
DISEASES.
THE FDA IS GIVING A
GENETICS TESTING
COMPANY THE RIGHT TO
DIRECTLY MARKET TO THE
PUBLIC TO TEST FOR
SERIOUS MEDICAL ISSUES
IN YOUR OWN HOME.
THE QUESTION IS, WOULD
YOU WANT TO KNOW?
HERE'S TOM COSTELLO.
>> Reporter: AT A LAB
IN CALIFORNIA, A
SALIVA SAMPLE FROM
SOMEONE WHO WANTS TO
KNOW MORE ABOUT THEIR
DNA.
ARE THERE SIGNS OF A
DISEASE OR DISORDER IN
THEIR GENES.
TODAY FOR THE FIRST
TIME, THE FDA HAS
ALLOWED 23 AND ME TO
MARKET HOME DNA KITS
DIRECTLY TO CONSUMER
TO TEST FOR HEALTH
CONDITIONS.
IN MINNEAPOLIS,
CHRISTINE MARKS WITH
HER MOM CHARLOTTE IS
HOPING A DNA TEST WILL
GIVE HER PEACE OF
MIND.
AFTER HER FATHER DIED
OF ALZHEIMER'S
DISEASE.
>> I DON'T WANT MY
CHILDREN TO END UP
WITH IT, I DON'T WANT
THEM TO SEE ME WITH
THE DISEASE.
>> HERE'S HOW IT
WORKS.
CUSTOMERS ORDER THE
$200 KIT ONLINE.
THE SALIVA SAMPLE IS
TESTED FOR MORE THAN
HALF A MILLION MARKERS
WHICH COULD BE
ASSOCIATED WITH ONE OF
TEN DISEASES OR
CONDITIONS.
INCLUDING LATE ONSET
ALZHEIMER'S,
PARKINSON'S DISEASE,
CELIAC DISEASE AND
VARIOUS BLOOD
DISORDERS.
GENETIC RISK IS ONE
PIECE OF THE BIGGER
PUZZLE.
IT DOESN'T MEAN THEY
WILL OR WON'T
ULTIMATELY DEVELOP A
DISEASE.
WE TALKED TO DR.
ROBERT GREEN BY SKYPE.
>> WE'RE MOVING TOWARD
A SOCIETY OF
EMPOWERING PEOPLE WITH
HEALTH INFORMATION.
THIS IS A WELCOMED
STEP ALONG THAT
JOURNEY.
>> Reporter: STILL,
SOME DOCTORS WORRY
ABOUT GIVING PEOPLE
CONFUSING AND LIFE
CHANGING TEST RESULTS
WITHOUT HAVING A
PROFESSIONAL HELP THEM
INTERPRET WHAT THEY
MEAN.
BUT CHRISTINE MARKS
HAS DECIDED.
>> IT DOESN'T
NECESSARILY MEAN I'M
GOING TO GET
ALZHEIMER'S, BUT AT
LEAST I CAN BE
PROACTIVE.
>> Reporter: IT'S
BETTER TO KNOW.
TOM COSTELLO NBC NEWS,
WASHINGTON.
>>> THE NUMBER ONE
PLAYER AT GOLFING'S
MOST PRESTIGIOUS
EVENT.
TO REACH MY GOALS.
SO I LIKED WHEN
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
THAT I MAY REACH
MY BLOOD SUGAR
AND A1C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING
WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS
NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE
MY BODY TO DO WHAT
IT'S SUPPOSED TO DO
RELEASE ITS
OWN INSULIN.
TRULICITY RESPONDS WHEN
MY BLOOD SUGAR RISES.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN.
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE SYMPTOMS
SUCH AS ITCHING, RASH,
OR TROUBLE BREATHING;
A LUMP OR SWELLING IN YOUR NECK;
OR SEVERE PAIN IN
YOUR STOMACH AREA.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS,
WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE,
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS WORSE.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING YOUR
A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR NUMBERS
WITH A NON-INSULIN OPTION,
CLICK TO ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
CLICK TO ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
♪
Fifty years ago, humpback
whales were nearly extinct.
They rebounded because
a decision was made
to protect them.
Making the right decisions
today for your long-term
financial future can protect
you and your family,
and preserve your legacy.
Ask a financial advisor
how retirement
and life insurance solutions
from Pacific Life
can help you plan
for your future.
>>> A FINAL GOOD-BYE
TODAY TO AN AMERICAN
HERO.
JOHN GLENN THE FIRST
AMERICAN TO ORBIT THE
EARTH WAS LAID TO REST
IN ARLINGTON WITH FULL
MILITARY HONORS.
THE FLAG ON HIS COFFIN
WAS PRESENTED TO HIS
WIDOW, ANNIE GLEN.
THIS WOULD HAVE BEEN
THEIR 74th WEDDING
ANNIVERSARY.
THE FORMER MARINE
PILOT, ASTRONAUT AND
LONG-TILE SENATOR FROM
OHIO DIED IN DECEMBER
AT AGE 95.
>>> HEARTBREAK TONIGHT
IN ONE OF THE BIGGEST
STAGES  IN ALL OF
SPORTS.
THE TOP-RANKED GOLFER
IN THE WORLD AND
TOURNAMENT FAVORITE
DUSTIN JOHNSON
HAS SUDDENLY WITHDRAWN
AFTER SLIPPING AND
FALLING DOWN STAIRS
INJURING HIS BACK.
ON HIS WAY TO THE
FIRST TEE, JOHNSON
REALIZED THAT DESPITE
HIS INTENTION TO PLAY,
HIS BACK WOULDN'T LET
HIM.
>>> A SPECTACULAR VIEW
OF JUPITER IN ALL ITS
GLORY.
IT WAS TAKEN BY THE
HUBBELL TELESCOPE AND
SHOWS THE FAMOUS RED
SPOT AND BANDS OF
SWIRLING CLOUDS.
JUPITER IS AT ITS
CLOSEST DISTANCE FROM
EARTH THIS YEAR, 415
MILLION MILES.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
REMEMBERING A TRULY
FUNNY MAN WITH HIS
UNIQUE AND
UNFORGETTABLE SENSE OF
HUMOR.
er.
When a critical patient is far
from the hospital,
the hospital must come to the
patient.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
The AT&T network is helping
first responders
connect with medical teams in
near real time...
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
...Saving time when it matters
most.
Stay with me, Mrs. Parker.
That's the power of and.
For my constipation,
I switch laxatives.ed
Stimulant
laxatives
make your body
go by forcefully
stimulating the nerves
in your colon.
MiraLAX is
different.
It works with the
water in your body
to hydrate
and soften.
Unblocking your
system naturally.
MiraLAX.
with toothpaste
or plain water.an their dentures
And even though their
dentures look clean,
in reality
they're not.
If a denture were to be
put under a microscope,
we can see all the bacteria
that still exists
on the denture,
and that bacteria multiplies
very rapidly.
That's why dentists recommend
cleaning with Polident everyday.
Polident's unique
micro clean formula
works in just 3 minutes,
killing 99.99% of odor
causing bacteria.
For a cleaner, fresher,
brighter denture every day.
(de♪p breath)
(phone ringing)
They'll call back.
No one knows your Ford better
than Ford and Ford Service.
Right now, during
The Big Tire Event,
get a $140 rebate by mail,
on four select tires.
♪
the markets change...
at T. Rowe Price...
our disciplined
approach remains.
Global markets may be
uncertain...
but you can feel
confident
in our investment
experience
around the world.
Call us or your
advisor...
T. Rowe Price.
Invest With Confidence.
...so guys with ED....
...can take VIAGRA
when they need it.
Ask your doctor if your heart
is healthy enough for sex.
Do not take VIAGRA if you
take nitrates for chest pain
or Adempas® for
pulmonary hypertension.
Your blood pressure could
drop to an unsafe level.
To avoid long-term injury,
seek immediate medical help
for an erection lasting
more than four hours.
Stop taking VIAGRA
and call your doctor right
away if you experience
a sudden decrease or loss
in vision or hearing.
Ask your doctor about
VIAGRA Single Packs.
DICT T PVIOLY . IBRINGO
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
HE WAS ONE OF THE
FUNNIEST MEN OF HIS
TIME.
DON RICKLES WAS KNOWN
FOR HIS BIG MOUTH AND
VERBAL ASSAULTS,
QUALITIES THAT
ENDEARED HIM IN HIS
OWN WAY TO GENERATIONS
OF FANS.
RICKLES DIED AT HOME
HERE IN LOS ANGELES
TODAY AFTER A LONG
CAREER AND COUNTLESS
LAUGHS.
>> IT WAS QUITE A
NIGHT.
WOULD YOU WELCOME MR.
WARMTH, DON RICKLES.
>> THE ONLY THING
TRULY WARM ABOUT DON
RICKLES, SIZZLING
INSULTS, A MASTER AT
THE COMEDIC PUTDOWN.
>> WHAT IS YOUR
ANCESTRY?
>> HONDURAN.
>> I'VE BEEN IN THE
BUSINESS 25 YEARS AND
DON'T HAVE A JOKE FOR
A JERK THAT'S
HONDURIAN.
>> YEAH, HE WENT
THERE, BEFORE WENT
THERE WAS A THING.
>> DO YOU THINK INSULT
HUMOR IS EASY?
STANDING NEXT TO YOU
IT IS.
>> DON RICKLES DIDN'T
REALLY TELL JOKES.
>> I STARTED MAKING
FUN OF THE GUY THAT
YELLED AT ME MAKING
FUN OF THE ROOM,
MAKING FUN OF THE
PEOPLE AROUND ME AND
THEN IT BECAME A
LITTLE BIT OF PUTDOWN
THING.
>> HE CREDITED HIS
RISE TO ANOTHER MASTER
OF HUMOR, JOHNNY
CARSON AND MORE THAN
100 APPEARANCES ON HIS
SHOW.
>> WHEN I HIT JOHNNY'S
SHOW, THE WHOLE WORLD
KNEW ME.
>> GIVE ME A BREAK.
I'M SO LONELY.
>> EVEN BEFORE A
PRESIDENT, HE DIDN'T
HOLD BACK.
>> IT'S A BIG TREAT
FOR ME TO FLY ALL THE
WAY FROM CALIFORNIA TO
BE HERE FOR THIS KIND
OF MONEY.
>> RICKLES APPEARED ON
THE SILVER SCREEN AND
LATER THE ANIMATED
SCREEN IN "TOY STORY."
>> WHAT ARE YOU
LOOKING AT, YOU HOCKEY
PUCK?
>> RICKELS PERFECTED
THE SECRET SAUCE OF
MAKING PEOPLE LAUGH,
NOT JUST AT HIS HUMOR
BUT AT THEMSELVES.
>> HE IS WHAT WE ALL
ASPIRE TO BE.
>> NO MATTER WHAT HE
SAID, YOU ALWAYS KNEW
IT CAME WITH A WINK
BECAUSE HE KNEW THAT
WE KNEW IT WAS ALL IN
GOOD FUN.
>> I'D LIKE MY FAMILY
TO KNOW THAT I WAS A
GOOD FATHER AND A GOOD
HUSBAND AND I'D LIKE
THE PUBLIC TO KNOW
THAT I WAS LAUGHING
ALONG WITH THEM.
>> DON RICKLES LEAVES
BEHIND HIS WIFE
BARBARA.
AND A DAUGHTER.
HE WAS 90 YEARS OLD.
>>> THAT IS GOING TO
DO IT FOR US ON THIS
THURSDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
B THBIGR SRY NIG --
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, THE RAIN
IS BACK BUT THE BIGGER STORY
TONIGHT COULD BE THE STRONG
WINDS.
WE ARE IN A MICROCLIMATE WEATHER
ALERT.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD EVENING AND THANKS FOG BR
WITH US, I'M ROTH MATHAI.
>> AND I'M JANELLE WANG.
WE'LL SHOW YOU A LIVE PICTURE OF
THE GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE AND IN
PALO ALTO, YOU COULD SEE THE
BRIDGE IS WET RIGHT NOW.
AND WE WANT TO GIVE YOU A VIEW
OF THE LIVE DOPPLER RADAR.
COULD YOU SEE WHERE THE RAIN IS
COMING DOWN RIGHT NOW.
>> A LOT OF GREEN.
WE HAVE A TEAM OF REPORTERS
COVERING THE STORM AND THE
POTENTIAL DAMAGE.
LET'S BEGIN IN HOUSE WITH OUR
METEOROLOGIST ROB MAYEDA.
AND DO YOU EXPECT THE WIND TO
KNOCK DOWN POWER TONIGHT?
>> THAT IS THE REAL CONCERN.
THIS DOES STACK UP POSSIBLY AS
ONE OF THE WINDYER STORMS IN A
WHILE.
RIGHT NOW 66 DEGREES IN SAN
JOSE.
AND SEEING MAINLY LIGHTER RAIN
FALLING AROUND DOWNTOWN.
BUT YOU NOTICE HERE OFF TO THE
WEST AROUND SARATOGA, THE WEST
END OF THE SANTA CLARA VALLEY
SEEING HEAVIER RAIN.
IN PALO ALTO, THE COMMUTE ALONG
1010, LOOKS SOGGY.
AND 63 DEGREES.
AND FURTHER TO THE NORTH NOW
TOWARD SAN FRANCISCO AND THE
RAIN IS FALLING PRETTY GOOD FOR
THE LAST HOUR.
ACROSS THE GOLDEN GATE BRIDGE,
TEMPERATURE OF ABOUT 56 DEGREES
AND A STEADY RAIN INTO THE NORTH
BAY.
THIS SYSTEM POWERFUL LOOKING
WHEN YOU SEE IT ON THE
SATELLITE.
THE AREA OF LOW PRESSURE OFF THE
COAST AND A DEEP AREA OF LOW
PRESSURE AT 980 MILLIBARS AND
THE FRONT COMES THROUGH AND THEY
BOOST OUR WIND SPEEDS PROBABLY
UP TO 45 MILES PER HOUR AND EVEN
HIGHER JUST BEFORE 11:00 FROM
THE COAST INTO THE