THURSDAY.
I KNOW THAT WIND IS A LOT OUT TO
THERE BUT IT'S GOING TO CALM
DOWN FOR US.
>> HOLD ON TO YOUR CAP AND GOWN.
A VIEW WE HAVEN'T SEEN UNTIL NOW
OF THE OKLAHOMA NEIGHBORHOOD AND
SCHOOL THAT TOOK A DIRECT HIT.
ALSO HOW SO MANY PEOPLE SURVIVED
BY HIDING AND RIDING IT OUT IN
SOME UNUSUAL PLACES.
>>> A GRISLY ATTACK ON THE
STREETS OF LONDON.
A BRITISH SOLDIER AMBUSHED AND
KILLED BY MEN WITH KNIVES IN AN
APPARENT AND SHOCKING ACT OF
TERRORISM.
>>> TAKING THE 5th, THE IRS
OFFICIAL WHOSE ADMISSION STARTED
IT ALL GAVE RISE TO A SCANDAL.
WE'LL SHOW YOU THE DRAMATIC
MOMENT FROM TODAY WHEN SHE GOT
UP AND WALKED OUT AFTER REFUSING
TO TESTIFY BEFORE CONGRESS.
>>> AND FIGHTING BACK AGAINST
THE ALARMING RISE IN SEX
ASSAULTS IN THE U.S. MILITARY.
TONIGHT, MARIA SCHRIVER HAS A
SPECIAL REPORT FOR "NIGHTLY
NEWS" ON THE WOMEN LEADING THE
CHARGE.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
NBC-UNIVERSAL TELEVISION
>>> GOOD EVENING.
WE ARE JUST BACK FROM MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, WHERE LIFE WON'T BE
NORMAL FOR YEARS, WHERE THE
EARTH HAS BEEN WIPED CLEAN IN
SOME PLACES, AND WHERE THE DEATH
TOLL STANDS STILL AT 24, 324
PEOPLE INJURED, TEN CHILDREN
INCLUDING TWO INFANTS ARE AMONG
THE DEAD.
CONSIDERING THE FACT THAT THEY
HAVE COUNTED UP 13,000 HOMES IN
THE PATH OF THIS ONE STORM, SOME
PEOPLE ARE ALREADY EXPRESSING
BOTH THANKS AND SURPRISE THAT
THE TOLL WASN'T EVEN HIGHER.
FOLLOWING THE RAREST OF ALL
TORNADOES, THE EF5, THE MOST
POWERFUL ON EARTH.
TODAY WE LEARN HOW AND WHERE SO
MANY PEOPLE WERE ABLE TO HIDE,
RIDE IT OUT, AND SURVIVE THIS
ONE.
WE BEGIN OUR COVERAGE FROM
MOORE, OKLAHOMA, TONIGHT WITH
NBC'S LESTER HOLT.
LESTER, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: BRIAN, GOOD
EVENING.
THE FIGURE YOU MENTIONED, 13,000
HOMES IN THE PATH, THAT'S
DESTROYED OR BADLY DAMAGED.
THAT'S A HUGE IMPACT IN A TOWN
OF ONLY 56,000.
IMAGINE THAT.
$2 BILLION IN DAMAGE AND THIS
TOWN IS STILL BEGINNING TO
ACCEPT, UNDERSTAND, AND GRIEVE
THE LOSS OF SO MANY WHO LIVE
HERE AS WE LEARN MORE NAMES OF
THE DEAD.
AT THE SAME TIME, FOLKS CONTINUE
TO MARVEL THAT SO MANY PEOPLE
WALKED OUT OF WRECKAGE LIKE THIS
ALIVE.
>> I HOPE EVERYONE'S OKAY.
>> Reporter: EACH NEW VIEW OF
THE MASSIVE FUNNEL MAKES IT
HARDER TO COMPREHEND HOW SO MANY
PEOPLE SURVIVED.
IT'S A QUESTION MIKE SOTO HAS
WRESTLED WITH SINCE HE WAS
PULLED FROM UNDER HIS HOUSE ON
MONDAY.
>> THAT'S A MIRACLE.
>> Reporter: MIKE WAS IN A
CLOSET WHEN HIS HOUSE FELL IN
AROUND HIM.
TRAPPED HE SCRAPED A METAL WIRE
THROUGH AN OPENING TO ATTRACT
HIS NEIGHBORS' ATTENTION.
>> I COULD HEAR THE VOICES
SAYING, MAKE A NOISE, KEEP
MAKING NOISE BECAUSE THEY COULD
NOT FIND ME.
FINALLY THEY FOUND ME.
>> Reporter: MOST OF THE DEAD
HAVE BEEN IDENTIFIED.
AMONG THEM 65-YEAR-OLD HEMMET
BONDI.
SWEPT AWAY AS HE HUDDLED IN A
BATHROOM WITH HIS WIFE.
THEN THE CHILDREN KILLED AT
PLAZA TOWERS ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
LIKE BEST FRIENDS AN TONE I
CAN'T CANDELARIA AND EMILY
CONATZER.
THEY REPORTEDLY DIED HOLDING
ONTO EACH OTHER.
EMILY'S MOTHER POSTED ON
FACEBOOK, I KNOW SHE IS IN
HEAVEN SMILING DOWN.
THE FATHER OF JENAE HORNSBY
ANOTHER THIRD GRADER, SPOKE OF
THE SEARCH FOR HIS DAUGHTER.
>> I WAS JUST HOPING MAYBE SHE
MIGHT HAVE JUST BEEN
UNCONSCIOUS.
I HOPED SHE WAS ALIVE.
>> Reporter: MATT LAUER GOT A
FIRSTHAND LOOK AT THE
DEVASTATION INSIDE THE SCHOOL,
AND THE TOLL IT TOOK ON FIRST
RESPONDERS.
>> ONCE WE HAVE THE FIRST
RESPONDERS THAT COME IN CONTACT
WITH THE BODIES, ESPECIALLY
CHILDREN, THEY ARE OFFERED
DIFFERENT COUNSELING.
>> Reporter: THERE IS NO RHYME
OR REASON TO WHY SOME LIVED AND
OTHERS DIDN'T.
THE TINKER FEDERAL CREDIT UNION
BEFORE THE TORNADO AND AFTER.
THE HEAVILY REINFORCED VAULT IS
ALL THAT'S STANDING.
IT IS WHERE JAN DAVIS AND
THERESA PRICE TOOK COVER WITH 20
OTHERS.
>> EVEN THROUGH THE CLOSED DOOR
YOU COULD HEAR THE
DISINTEGRATION OF WHAT WE ARE
STANDING IN NOW.
THERE WAS NO DOUBT IN ANY OF OUR
MINDS THAT THE BUILDING WAS GONE
ON THE OUTSIDE.
>> TO ME THAT WAS THE ONLY
OPTION.
>> Reporter: THIS HOMEOWNER
HEARD AN INTERIOR ROOM WAS THE
FASTEST PLACE TO SHELTER IN A
PINCH.
HE AND HIS WIFE CHOSE THIS
CLOSET.
>> ALL I HEARD WAS A -- AND IT
WAS QUIET.
I SAT THERE -- WE SAT THERE FOR
A BIT.
>> Reporter: WHEN IT WAS OVER,
HALF HIS HOUSE AND MOST OF HIS
NEIGHBORHOOD WAS GONE.
FEW HOMES IN THIS CORNER OF
TORNADO ALLEY HAVE STORM CELLARS
OR SAFE ROOMS.
TODAY, TOWN OFFICIALS PROPOSED
THE IDEA OF MAKING THEM
MANDATORY FOR NEW HOMES.
>> IF YOU ASK MOST PEOPLE OUT
THERE, THEY ARE GOING TO REBUILD
AND PROBABLY GET A STORM
SHELTER.
>> Reporter: OF MORE IMMEDIATE
CONCERN HERE, CLEANING UP AS
HEAVY EQUIPMENT CREWS MOVED IN
TODAY, SO DID AN ARMY OF
VOLUNTEERS, LOADED WITH RAKES,
SHOVELS, AND BIG HEARTS.
>> THIS IS WHAT BEING OKLAHOMAN
IS ABOUT.
YOU HELP YOUR FRIENDS AND
FAMILY.
IT'S CALLED OKLAHOMA STRONG.
>> Reporter: TOMORROW IS THE
LAST DAY OF SCHOOL IN MOORE.
BRIAN, KIDS WHO ATTEND SCHOOLS
THAT HAVE BEEN DESTROYED HAVE
BEEN ENCOURAGED TO GO TO OTHER
SCHOOLS SO THEY CAN AT LEAST
CLOSE OUT THE SCHOOL YEAR WITH
THEIR CLASSMATES.
>> LESTER HOLT IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA.
THANK YOU.
>>> WE HAVE TO GO OVERSEAS TO A
TWISTED AND DISTURBING STORY OUT
OF LONDON TODAY.
FAIR WARNING, THIS IS TOUGH TO
LOOK AT, ESPECIALLY WHEN YOU
REALIZE WHAT IT IS WE ARE
LOOKING AT.
A BRITISH SOLDIER IN PLAIN
CLOTHES AMBUSHED AND KILLED ON A
CITY STREET WHILE HIS BARBARIC
ATTACKERS WAIT FOR POLICE TO
COME WHILE THEY TAKE -- ALLOW
PEOPLE TO TAKE VIDEO WHILE THEY
VENT THEIR MESSAGE ABOUT
RELIGION AND POLITICS.
FOR REASONS YOU WILL SEE, THIS
IS NOW BEING TREATED AS AN ACT
OF TERRORISM.
WE GET OUR REPORT TONIGHT FROM
NBC'S MICHELLE KOSINSKI IN
LONDON.
>> STEP BACK.
MOVE BACK.
>> Reporter: IN THE MIDDLE OF
THE DAY IN THE BUSY WORKING
CLASS NEIGHBORHOOD NEXT TO AN
ARMY BARRACKS, NEAR AN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL, A SCENE OF
SUCH RAW VIOLENCE, FEW COULD
BELIEVE IT.
>> LOOK AT THE GUY.
HE'S DEAD NOW.
>> Reporter: PEOPLE HERE SAY A
YOUNG MAN WHO NBC NEWS HAS
CONFIRMED WAS AN ACTIVE BRITISH
SOLDIER WEARING A CHARITY HELP
FOR HEROES T-SHIRT WAS WALKING
ALONG THIS SIDEWALK WHEN TWO MEN
IN A CAR APPARENTLY DROVE INTO
HIM, THEN GOT OUT AND STARTED
STABBING HIM WITH MULTIPLE LARGE
KNIVES.
>> THEY WERE HACKING AT THIS
POOR GUY, CHOPPING HIM, CUTTING
HIM.
>> Reporter: SOME EYEWITNESSES
SAY THE VICTIM WAS DECAPITATED
IN THE ATTACK AND THE TWO
SUSPECTS THEN APPROACHED PEOPLE
IN THE HORRIFIED CROWD.
>> THEY WERE TELLING PEOPLE TO
RECORD THEM DOING IT.
>> Reporter: ONE MADE A LONG
POLITICAL STATEMENT, WEAPONS
STILL IN HIS BLOOD-COVERED
HANDS.
>> WE SWEAR BY THE ALMIGHTY
ALLAH WE WILL NEVER STOP
FIGHTING YOU UNTIL YOU LEAVE US
ALONE.
>> Reporter: WHEN POLICE ARRIVED
WITNESSES SAY THE MEN CHARGED AT
OFFICERS WHO OPENED FIRE.
BOTH WERE HIT, NOW IN HOSPITAL.
>> SMALL GROUPS DECIDING TO
CARRY OUT THESE SORTS OF ATTACKS
IS A PART OF A BROADER TREND WE
HAVE SEEN RECENTLY.
THE BRUTALITY WE ARE SEEING IN
THIS ONE DOES SEEM TO BE A NEW
ELEMENT WE HAVE NOT SEEN BEFORE.
>> Reporter: PRIME MINISTER
DAVID CAMERON IS RUSHING HOME
FROM FRANCE FOR AN EMERGENCY
MEETING ON WHAT EXACTLY THIS
WAS, WHETHER OTHERS COULD BE
INVOLVED OR OTHER ATTACKS
PLANNED.
>> THERE ARE STRONG INDICATIONS
THAT IT IS A TERRORIST INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE TWO
SUSPECTS ARE FORMALLY UNDER
ARREST.
THE GOVERNMENT HERE IS
INCREASING SECURITY AT ARMY
BARRACKS ACROSS LONDON.
ONE OF THE MEN DID INDICATE THEY
TARGETED THE VICTIM BECAUSE HE
WAS A SOLDIER.
MICHELLE KOSINSKI, NBC NEWS,
LONDON.
>>> THERE HAS BEEN A NEW
DEVELOPMENT IN THE BOSTON
MARATHON BOMBING INVESTIGATION
WHICH LED TO A DEADLY
CONFRONTATION BETWEEN A MAN WHO
KNEW THE ALLEGED BOMBERS AND LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
OUR JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS COVERING THIS ALL DAY
HAS MORE FROM OUR D.C. NEWSROOM
TONIGHT.
PETE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: BRIAN,
INVESTIGATORS SAY THEIR SEARCH
FOR FRIENDS OF BOMBING SUSPECT
TAMERLAN TSARNAEV TOOK THEM TO
FLORIDA TO QUESTION IBRAGIM
TODASHEV, A NATIVE OF RUSSIA AND
A MIXED MARTIAL ARTS FIGHTER.
WHILE BEING INTERROGATED LAST
NIGHT AT A HOUSE IN ORLANDO,
OFFICIALS SAY HE ATTACKED AN FBI
AGENT AND WAS SHOT AND KILLED.
AUTHORITIES SAY BEFORE THAT
TODASHEV CONFESSED TO PLAYING A
ROLE IN A BRUTAL TRIPLE MURDER
IN WALTHAM, MASSACHUSETTS, IN
2011.
ONE OF THE VICTIMS WAS A FRIEND
OF TSARNAEV'S.
TODASHEV SAID TSARNAEV WAS
INVOLVED IN THE KILLING, TOO.
TODASHEV LIVED FOR A TIME IN THE
BOSTON SUBURB AND BECAME FRIENDS
WITH TSARNAEV WHO WAS A BOXER
THERE.
THEY SAY THE KILLINGS IN WALTHAM
STARTED AS AN ATTEMPT TO STEAL
DRUGS FROM THE THREE VICTIMS BUT
ENDED IN THEIR DEATHS TO KEEP
THEM FROM TALKING.
AUTHORITIES SAY THEY DO NOT
BELIEVE TODASHEV HAD ANY ROLE IN
THE BOSTON MARATHON BOMBINGS,
BRIAN.
>> PETE WILLIAMS IN OUR
WASHINGTON BUREAU TONIGHT.
THANKS.
>> NOW TO THE NEWS THAT BROKE
LATE TODAY.
THE U.S. GOVERNMENT ADMITTING
FOR THE FIRST TIME THAT THE U.S.
MILITARY HAS KILLED FOUR
AMERICANS IN DRONE STRIKES
OVERSEAS.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT/POLITICAL DIRECTOR
CHUCK TODD IS WITH US FROM THERE
WITH MORE THIS EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
BRIAN.
IT'S BEEN ONE OF THE MORE
SECRETIVE ASPECTS OF THE
GOVERNMENT'S WAR AGAINST AL
QAEDA AND OTHER EXTREMISTS.
NOW IT'S LESS SECRET.
FOR THE FIRST TIME THE OBAMA
ADMINISTRATION IS CONFIRMING
WHAT WE HAD ALREADY REPORTED FOR
SOME TIME -- THAT THE GOVERNMENT
TARGETED A U.S. CITIZEN, ANWAR
AL-AWLAKI FOR DEATH VIA DRONE
STRIKE IN YEMEN.
THE GOVERNMENT ALSO ACKNOWLEDGED
THREE OTHER AMERICAN B CITIZENS
INVOLVED IN TERRORISM HAVE BEEN
KILLED IN DRONE STRIKES.
IN THE LETTER TO CONGRESS,
ATTORNEY GENERAL ERIC HOLDER
DETAILED A LEGAL DEFENSE FOR
TARGETING AL-AWLAKI, WELL KNOWN
FOR JIHADIST WRITINGS.
HOLDER WROTE HIS TARGETING OF
AMERICANS INCLUDING THE
ATTEMPTED UNDERWEAR BOMBER
ATTACK AND THE PLOT TO HIDE
BOMBS ON CARGO PLANES MADE HIM A
LEGALLY JUSTIFIED TARGET BECAUSE
HE WAS AN IMMINENT THREAT, COULD
NOT BE CAPTURED AND WAS A
LEGITIMATE TARGET UNDER THE LAWS
OF WAR.
THIS COMES ON THE EVE OF A
SPEECH IN WHICH PRESIDENT OBAMA
PLANS TO LAY OUT A BROADER
COUNTER TERRORISM STRATEGY
INCLUING A LEGAL FRAMEWORK AND
MUCH MORE PUBLIC OVERSIGHT OF
DRONE STRIKES.
HE'S EXPECTED TO UNVEIL A NEW
PLAN TO TRY TO SHUT DOWN THE
PRISON CAMP ON GUANTANAMO BAY
CUBA.
>> CHUCK TODD FROM THE WHITE
HOUSE TONIGHT.
CHUCK, THANKS.
>>> THERE WAS PALPABLE ANGER ON
CAPITOL HILL TODAY AS SEVERAL
SENIOR OFFICIALS OF THE IRS WERE
CALLED TO TESTIFY IN THIS
GROWING SCANDAL OVER THE
TARGETING OF CONSERVATIVE GROUPS
FOR SPECIAL SCRUTINY.
IT IS CLEAR THIS IS JUST GETTING
UNDER WAY.
WE GET THE STORY TONIGHT FROM
NBC'S KELLY O'DONNELL.
>>> TODAY, CONFRONTATION AND
PUBLIC SPECTACLE AROUND A KEY
IRS OFFICIAL.
>> STEP BACK.
>> Reporter: FORCED TO APPEAR,
LOIS LERNER TOOK THE OATH AND
THEN TOOK THE 5th, HER
CONSTITUTIONAL RIGHT TO AVOID
SELF-INCRIMINATION.
>> I WILL NOT ANSWER ANY
QUESTIONS OR TESTIFY TODAY.
>> Reporter: LERNER'S REFUSAL TO
ANSWER CAME AFTER SHE STUNNED
THE HOUSE OVERSIGHT COMMITTEE BY
SPEAKING OUT, PROFESSING HER
INNOCENCE.
>> I HAVE NOT DONE ANYTHING
WRONG.
I HAVE NOT BROKEN ANY LAWS.
I HAVE NOT VIOLATED ANY IRS
RULES OR REGULATIONS.
>> Reporter: AN INSPECTOR
GENERAL FOUND BEFORE THE 2012
ELECTION THE IRS DIVISION RUN BY
LERNER INAPPROPRIATELY PICKED
OUT CONSERVATIVE AND TEA PARTY
GROUPS APPLYING FOR TAX-EXEMPT
STATUS FOR SPECIAL SCRUTINY.
>> SHE OUGHT TO STAND HERE AND
ANSWER OUR QUESTIONS.
>> Reporter: LERNER WAS EXCUSED
AND ATTENTION TURNED TO THE
FORMER IRS COMMISSIONER DOUGLAS
SHULMAN WHO SWORE LAST YEAR NO
TARGETING HAD HAPPENED, FOUND
OUT IT HAD, AND THEN FAILED TO
TELL CONGRESS.
HE FACED A BIPARTISAN FLOGGING.
>> YOU DID NOTHING.
YOU ABDICATED YOUR
RESPONSIBILITY.
>> IT WAS YOUR JOB TO MAKE SURE
PEOPLE WEREN'T ABUSED.
IT WAS YOUR JOB TO STOP ABUSE
AND ALSO TO REPORT IT.
>> Reporter: SHULMAN INSISTED HE
WAS NOT PERSONALLY RESPONSIBLE
BUT OFFERED HIS FIRST PUBLIC
APOLOGY.
>> I'M VERY SORRY THAT THIS
HAPPENED WHILE I WAS AT THE
INTERNAL REVENUE SERVICE.
>> Reporter: FRUSTRATED
LAWMAKERS SAID THE GOVERNMENT'S
CREDIBILITY IS AT STAKE.
>> TRUTH AND TRUST.
WE WANT TO BE ABLE TO TRUST THE
IRS.
BUT FOR THIS MOMENT ON THIS DAY
WE NEED TO BE ABLE TO TRUST YOUR
WORD.
>> Reporter: PART OF THE FURY
TODAY, LAWMAKERS TOLD US THEY
HAVE WRITTEN MORE THAN 130
LETTERS TO THE IRS IN THE LAST
COUPLE OF YEARS URGING THEM TO
LOOK INTO THIS.
THEY GOT NO INFORMATION OR WRONG
INFORMATION.
TODAY THE PRESIDENT'S PICK TO
TAKE OVER THE AGENCY BEGAN HIS
JOB AND PROMISES TO HAVE A
COMPREHENSIVE REVIEW ABOUT THE
IRS WITHIN 30 DAYS.
BRIAN?
>> KELLY O'DONNELL, A BUSY NEWS
DAY IN WASHINGTON.
KELLY, THANKS.
>>> LATE THIS AFTERNOON IN
CHICAGO AT A PACKED MEETING,
REPEATEDLY, LOUDLY INTERRUPTED
BY PROTESTERS, THE SCHOOL BOARD
VOTED TO CLOSE 49 ELEMENTARY
SCHOOLS AND ONE HIGH SCHOOL.
IT'S THE BIGGEST MASS PUBLIC
SCHOOL CLOSING IN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
30,000 CHILDREN WILL BE
AFFECTED.
NEARLY 90% OF THEM
AFRICAN-AMERICAN.
THE CITY SAYS THE SCHOOLS ARE
UNDERUSED.
MANY OTHERS UNDER PERFORM.
THERE IS OUTRAGE IN CHICAGO FOR
THE STUDENTS THIS WILL HAVE TO
UPROOT, INCLUDING CONCERNS FOR
STUDENT SAFETY IN BAD
NEIGHBORHOODS.
>>> STILL AHEAD FOR US TONIGHT,
A "NIGHTLY NEWS" EXCLUSIVE.
MARIA SCHRIVER REPORTS FOR US ON
THE POWERFUL WOMEN TRYING TO
STOP A POWERFUL AND DANGEROUS
SUBCULTURE WITHIN THE MODERN
MILITARY.
>>> LATER, WE WERE COVERING A
TORNADO IN JOPLIN, MISSOURI, TWO
YEARS AGO TONIGHT.
TONIGHT WHAT THEY HAVE LEARNED
THAT COULD HELP THE FOLKS IN
OKLAHOMA.
>>> WE ARE BACK NOW WITH AN NBC
NEWS EXCLUSIVE.
A SPECIAL REPORT ABOUT
THE ALARMING RISE IN THE NUMBER
OF SEXUAL ASSAULTS IN THE U.S.
MILITARY.
THERE HAVE BEEN SEVERAL HIGH
PROFILE INCIDENTS OF LATE.
TODAY A HOUSE COMMITTEE APPROVED
A SERIES OF PROVISIONS TO
MILITARY LAW INCLUDING STRIPPING
COMMANDING OFFICERS OF THE
AUTHORITY TO OVERTURN
COURT-MARTIAL SEX ASSAULT
CONVICTIONS.
TONIGHT IN A SPECIAL REPORT FOR
"NIGHTLY NEWS," MARIA SCHRIVER
TALKS WITH THREE POWERFUL WOMEN
IN CONGRESS WHO ARE LEADING THE
CHARGE FOR JUSTICE FOR A LOT OF
WOMEN IN THE MILITARY.
>> Reporter: IS THIS A MILITARY
CRISIS, A CULTURAL CRISIS, A
SEXUAL CRISIS, OR A LEGAL
CRISIS?
>> ALL OF THE ABOVE.
>> ALL OF IT.
>> WITHOUT A DOUBT.
WHEN YOU HAVE 26,000 VICTIMS A
YEAR AND LESS THAN 10% REPORT
THE CRIME?
>> THESE MEN AND WOMEN ARE GOING
THROUGH THE MOST HORRIBLE
CRIMES, YET THEY CANNOT FEEL
THEY CAN REPORT THESE CRIMES AND
THEY DO NOT FEEL THE EXISTING
SYSTEM WILL GIVE THEM JUSTICE.
>> THE PRESIDENT SAID THERE IS
NO SILVER BULLET.
IS THERE?
>> THERE ISN'T ONE SOLUTION.
WE HAVE TO DO NOT ONLY CHANGE
THE LAW, WE HAVE TO HAVE BETTER
TRAINING.
WE HAVE TO DISCHARGE INDIVIDUALS
WHO ARE CONVICTED OF THESE
CRIMES.
THAT WILL SEND SUCH A MESSAGE IF
THEY RECEIVE A DISHONORABLE
DISCHARGE.
>> ACCOUNTABILITY IS THE ANSWER.
WHEN THERE ARE MORE PROSECUTIONS
AND MORE CONVICTIONS AND MORE
MEN AND WOMEN FEEL COMFORTABLE
AS THEY COME FORWARD THAT THEY
AREN'T GOING TO BE MARGINALIZED,
LABELED WITH SOME DISORDER AND
KICKED OUT OF THE MILITARY, THEN
IT WOULD BE DIFFERENT.
>> Reporter: TALK A BIT ABOUT
THAT THAT THIS IS NOT JUST
WHAT'S GOING ON IN THE MILITARY
BUT THE RAMIFICATIONS OF THE SEX
ABUSE VIOLATIONS HAVE EFFECTS
FOR YEARS TO COME.
>> THE VICTIMS HAVE TOLD US THEY
CAN SURVIVE THE RAPE OR ASSAULT.
WHAT'S DIFFICULT TO SURVIVE IS
HOW THEY WERE TREATED
AFTERWARDS.
THEY SEE THE MILITARY AS THEIR
CALLING, AS THEIR FAMILY.
FOR A LOT OF THESE WOMEN WHEN
THEY SEPARATE FROM ACTIVE DUTY
THEY DO EXPERIENCE POST
TRAUMATIC STRESS DISORDER IN
HIGH NUMBERS.
>> THEY CARRY THIS WITH THEM FOR
THE REST OF THEIR LIVES.
WE HAVE GOT TO CLEAN THE SYSTEM
COMPLETELY.
>> Reporter: DO YOU FEEL THERE
IS A SIMILARITY BETWEEN WHAT WE
ARE SEEING IN THE MILITARY AND
WHAT'S HAPPENED IN THE CATHOLIC
CHURCH?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
WHENEVER YOU HAVE A CLOSED
SYSTEM AND YOU CAN CONTROL THE
ENVIRONMENT AND SWEEP THINGS
UNDER THE RUG, YOU CAN MOVE
PEOPLE AROUND WHICH IS WHAT
HAPPENED IN THE CATHOLIC CHURCH.
IT'S WHAT HAPPENED IN THE
MILITARY.
>> WHAT PARENT IS GOING TO WANT
TO HAVE THEIR DAUGHTER, IN
PARTICULAR, GO INTO THE MILITARY
IF THEY FEEL SHE'S NOT SAFE FROM
A SEXUAL ASSAULT FROM HER FELLOW
SERVICE MEMBERS?
>> Reporter: HOW CONFIDENT ARE
YOU THAT YOU WILL CHANGE THE
LAW?
>> OH, WE'RE GOING TO CHANGE THE
LAW.
>> VERY CONFIDENT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO CHANGE THE
LAW.
THERE IS NO TURNING BACK AT THIS
POINT.
>> THREE LEADING MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS WITH OUR SPECIAL
CORRESPONDENT MARIA SCHRIVER
TONIGHT.
>>> COMING UP FOR US THIS
EVENING, THE SPECIAL HONORS FOR
TWO EXTRAORDINARY AMERICAN
WOMEN.
For our families...
our neighbors...
and our communities...
America's beverage companies
have created...
a wide range of new choices.
Developing smaller portion sizes
and more..
low and no-calorie
beverages...
adding clear calorie labels so
you know...
exactly what you're choosing...
and in schools, replacing
full-calorie soft drinks...
with lower-calorie options.
With more choices and fewer
calories...
America's Beverage Companies are
delivering.
>>> THE NEXT MAYOR OF LOS
ANGELES WILL BE ERIC GARCETTI
TURNOUT IN THE ELECTION JUST
19.2%.
THAT'S A MODERN DAY RECORD LOW
GOING BACK TO 1938.
THE ERA BEFORE THE FREEWAYS CAME
TO SOUTHERN CALIFORNIA.
GARCETTI IS THE SON OF GIL
GARCETTI, FORMER D.A. WHO
PRESIDED DURING THE O.J. SIMPSON
DRAMA.
HE'S THE FIRST JEWISH MAYOR OF
THE NATION'S SECOND LARGEST CITY
AND TAKES OVER DURING A FRAUGHT
TIME FOR THE CITY'S FINANCES.
>>> WE LEARNED YESTERDAY WHILE
WE WERE IN OKLAHOMA THAT VERNON
McGARRITY HAS DIED.
HE RECEIVED THE MEDAL OF HONOR
FOR HIS ACTIONS IN WORLD WAR II.
BADLY WOUNDED IN A HEAVY FIRE
FIGHT IN BELGIUM IN '44 HE
RALLIED, RESCUED HIS MEN, SINGLE
HANDEDLY DISABLED A GERMAN TANK
AND TURNED BACK THE ASSAULT.
HE WAS 91.
HIS DEATH LEAVES 79 LIVING
RECIPIENTS OF THE MEDAL OF
HONOR.
>>> ALSO TONIGHT, TWO
FANTASTICALLY TALENTED WOMEN
NAMED CAROL ARE IN THE NEWS FOR
HONORS THEY ARE RECEIVING.
CAROL KING HAS RECEIVED THE
GERSHWIN PRIZE FROM THE LIBRARY
OF CONGRESS FOR POPULAR
SONGWRITING FROM HER
EXTRAORDINARY BODY OF WORK
STARTING WITH "UP ON THE ROOF,"
"YOU'VE GOT A FRIEND," "WILL YOU
STILL LOVE ME TOMORROW," A HUGE
LIST OF CONTRIBUTIONS.
AND THE GREAT CAROL BURNETT WILL
RECEIVE THE MARK TWAIN PRIZE FOR
AMERICAN HUMOR TO GO WITH HER 25
EMMYS AND EIGHT GOLDEN GLOBES.
THE PRIZE WILL BE HANDED OUT IN
OCTOBER AT THE KENNEDY CENTER IN
WASHINGTON.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, A MESSAGE
OF HOPE FROM THE PEOPLE WHO KNOW
WHAT THE PEOPLE IN MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, ARE IN FOR.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT I HAVE HERE
WITH ME ON THE DESK A BRICK FROM
JOPLIN HIGH SCHOOL.
THEY WERE KIND ENOUGH TO GIVE A
FEW OF THESE OUT TO VARIOUS
FOLKS WITH TIES TO THAT
COMMUNITY.
THE BRICKS ARE A CHERISHED
SYMBOL OF ALL THAT WAS LOST TWO
YEARS AGO TODAY WHEN AN EF5
TWISTER TORE UP JOPLIN INCLUDING
THE HIGH SCHOOL.
A THIRD OF THE TOWN WAS
DESTROYED.
162 PEOPLE LOST THEIR LIVES.
NOW SOME OF JOPLIN'S FIRST
RESPONDERS HAVE GONE TO MOORE,
OKLAHOMA, TO HELP OUT.
BACK IN JOPLIN, THE FOLKS ARE
TALKING ABOUT WHAT THEY HAVE
LEARNED THESE PAST TWO YEARS.
NBC'S ERICA HILL HAS OUR REPORT
TONIGHT FROM JOPLIN.
>> Reporter: A NEW LANDSCAPE IS
EMERGING IN JOPLIN, ONE THAT
LOOKS ALMOST NOTHING LIKE THIS
22-MILE PATH OF DESTRUCTION.
>> DEVASTATION IS A SHORT WHILE,
BUT DETERMINATION LASTS ALL THE
TIME.
>> Reporter: DETERMINED TO COME
BACK STRONGER.
BETHANY FIRST SHARED HER STORY
OF SURVIVAL WITH BRIAN AFTER SHE
AND HER HUSBAND DON RODE OUT THE
TORNADO IN THIS BATHTUB.
>> HE GOT ON TOP OF ME TO TAKE
THE BRUNT OF MOST OF IT.
AND, YOU KNOW, HE'S MY HERO.
>> Reporter: DON SAVED BETHANY,
BUT HE DIDN'T SURVIVE.
TWO YEARS LATER, THE VOID
REMAINS, BUT BETHANY IS GRATEFUL
FOR A SECOND CHANCE.
>> I GET TO SAY THANK YOU FOR --
LETTING ME HAVE THIS LIFE.
BUT I GET TO LIVE IT FOR HIM,
TOO.
>> Reporter: A LIFE THAT NOW
INCLUDES A 4-MONTH-OLD DAUGHTER
WHO BETHANY CALLS HER
INSPIRATION.
THERE IS PLENTY OF INSPIRATION
TO BE FOUND HERE.
NEARLY 90% OF AFFECTED
BUSINESSES ARE NOW OPEN.
75% OF HOMES HAVE BEEN REBUILT,
AND 80% OF NEW HOMES NOW INCLUDE
A SAFE ROOM.
MERCY HOSPITAL, A NEW FACILITY
WILL OPEN IN 2015 WITH WALLS AND
WINDOWS BUILT TO WITHSTAND 250
MILE AN HOUR WINDS.
ITS ELECTRICAL SYSTEMS SECURELY
BURIED UNDER GROUND.
>> JOPLIN IS A CITY OF HOPE.
WE KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE TO
SUFFER, BUT WE ALSO KNOW WHAT
IT'S LIKE TO GET BACK UP.
>> TRY TO SAY THE RIGHT THINGS
THAT CAN COME EVEN WHENEVER IT
DOESN'T SEEM THERE COULD BE
ANOTHER BRIGHT DAY.
>> Reporter: THERE IS MUCH TO
CELEBRATE AS THIS TOWN REBUILDS,
BUT IT IS THE STRENGTH OF ITS
PEOPLE THAT IS THE TRUE MEASURE
OF SUCCESS.
ERICA HILL, NBC NEWS, JOPLIN,
MISSOURI.
>>> AND THAT IS OUR BROADCAST ON
A WEDNESDAY NIGHT.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M BRIAN WILLIAMS.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
>>> GOOD EVENING, AND THANK YOU
FOR JOINING US.
I'M JESSICA AGEAR.
>> I'M RAJ MATHAI.
A BATTLE IS BREWING IN THE SOUTH
BAY OVER FIRST AMENDMENT RIGHTS.
AND ACCUSATIONS THAT A WELL
KNOWN WEEKLY NEWSPAPER ALSO
SERVED AS AN ONLINE BROTHEL.
THE METRO NEWSPAPER HAS A LINK
ON ITS OWN WEBSITE FOR ADULT
ESCORT SERVICES AND CRITICS ARE
DEMANDING THE NEWSPAPER REMOVE
IT.
THE METRO SAYS THE CRITICISM IS
THE RESULT OF RUFFLED FURTHERS
OVER ITS REPORTING OF LOCAL
POLITICS.
DAVID TRUJILLO JOINS US NOW.
THE PAPER SAYS THEY'RE BEING
UNFAIRLY TARGETED.
ARE THEY BREAKING ANY LAWS WITH
THE WEBSITE LINK?
>> Reporter: DOESN'T SEEM TO AT
THIS POINT, RAJ.
THE METRO HAS BEEN DOING SOME
GOOD AND EXTENSIVE INVESTIGATIVE
REPORTING ON LOCAL POLITICIANS
AND CANDIDATES.
THE EDITOR AND CEO TELLS ME
THAT'S THE REASON THESE
ACCUSATIONS ARE COMING OUT.
BUT CRITICS SAY THIS IS ABOUT
ADVERTISEMENT THAT EXPLOITS
WOMEN AND CHILDREN.
LO
LOGON TO THE METRO WEBSITE AND
YOU'LL FIND A SECTION FOR ADULT
ESCORT SERVICES.
SOME IMAGES ARE TOO GRAPHIC TO
BROADCAST.
SOME CALL IT ONLINE