5:00.
SEE YOU AT 6:00.
>> BYE-BYE!
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT --
PLAN OF ATTACK?
THE U.S. NOW SAYS IT IS
UNDENIABLE THAT SYRIA USED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON ITS OWN
PEOPLE.
THE SECRETARY OF STATE CALLING
IT A MORAL OBSCENITY.
IS AMERICA ABOUT TO STRIKE?
>>> THE BURN ZONE, NOW THE SIZE
OF CHICAGO.
ONE OF THE BIGGEST FIRES EVER IN
CALIFORNIA.
AND IS SAN FRANCISCO'S
THREATENED WATER AND POWER
SUPPLY OUT OF THE WOODS?
>> EARLY DETECTION OF OVARIAN
CANCER, ONE WITH OF THE
DEADLIEST AND HARDEST TO
DIAGNOSIS.
TONIGHT A SIMPLE BLOOD TEST THAT
COULD SAVE THOUSANDS OF LIVES.
>> AND, ABOUT LAST NIGHT.
THE PERFORMANCE THAT LEFT NO
DOUBT SHE IS NOT HANNAH MONTANA
ANYMORE.
DID SHE GO TOO FAR?
OR WAS THAT EXACTLY THE POINT?
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
THE WHITE HOUSE TONIGHT SAYS
THERE IS NO QUESTION THEY DID
IT.
CALLING OUT THE SYRIAN
GOVERNMENT OVER A CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ATTACK LAST WEEK THAT
KILLED HUNDREDS OF SYRIAN
CIVILIANS.
THE LANGUAGE FROM WASHINGTON
TODAY WAS EXCEEDINGLY BLUNT.
SECRETARY OF STATE JOHN KERRY
THIS AFTERNOON LAYING OUT THE
CASE FOR A LIKELY U.S. MILITARY
RESPONSE.
>> THE KILLING OF WOMEN AND
CHILDREN AND INNOCENT BYSTANDERS
BY CHEMICAL WEAPONS IS A MORAL
OBSCENITY.
BY ANY STANDARD IT IS
INEXCUSABLE AND DESPITE THE
EXCUSES AND EQUIVOCATIONS THAT
SOME HAVE MANUFACTURED, IT IS
UNDENIABLE.
>> TONIGHT THE WHITE HOUSE IS
GATHERING INTERNATIONAL BACKING
FOR POSSIBLE AIR STRIKES AGAINST
SYRIA WHILE U.N.
CHEMICAL WEAPONS INSPECTORS HAVE
FINALLY BEEN ALLOWED IN TO
GROUND ZERO OF LAST WEEK'S
ATTACK.
NBC'S RICHARD ENGEL MADE IT INTO
SYRIA TODAY.
HE IS NOW SAFELY BACK ON THE
TURKISH SIDE OF THE BORDER WITH
A LOT MORE ON TODAY'S
FAST-MOVING DEVELOPMENTS.
RICHARD, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING,
LESTER.
SOME WESTERN OFFICIALS BELIEVE
THAT PRESIDENT BASHAR AL ASSAD
PERSONALLY ORDERED THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
TONIGHT, THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS NO
FINAL DECISION HAS BEEN MADE
ABOUT ANY U.S. MILITARY ACTION.
>> Reporter: U.N. INSPECTORS
TODAY IN DAMASCUS.
ONE OF THEIR VEHICLES SHOT BY A
SNIPER, BUT AFTER A BRIEF DELAY
THEY FINALLY BEGAN THEIR WORK
INTERVIEWING SURVIVORS, DOCTORS
AND TAKING SAMPLES.
BUT THIS MAY ALREADY BE A SIDE
SHOW.
THE U.S. AND OTHERS ALREADY
BELIEVE THE ASSAD REGIME USED
CHEMICAL WEAPONS LAST WEEK ON A
SCALE NOT SEEN ANYWHERE IN
DECADES.
SO AMERICA IS ONCE AGAIN
BUILDING A CASE FOR MILITARY
ACTION.
>> THERE MUST BE ACCOUNTABILITY
FOR THOSE WHO WOULD USE THE
WORLD'S MOST HEINOUS WEAPONS.
>> Reporter: THE LIKELY ACTION
CRUISE MISSILE STRIKES FROM FOUR
U.S. NAVY DESTROYERS AND TWO
SUBMARINES ALREADY IN THE
MEDITERRANEAN.
POSSIBLE TARGETS, SYRIAN
MILITARY FACILITIES AND WEAPONS
SYSTEMS, PLANES AND AIRFIELDS,
COMMAND AND CONTROL BUNKERS, BUT
NOT U.S. OFFICIALS SAY PRESIDENT
ASSAD HIMSELF.
AND NOT CHEMICAL WEAPONS STOCK
PILES.
TOO RISKY.
WOULD IT BE LEGAL?
U.N. BACKING IS UNLIKELY WITHOUT
RUSSIAN SUPPORT.
BUT A COALITION OF ARAB AND
EUROPEAN STATES ALONG WITH THE
U.S. COULD BE USED TO JUSTIFY A
STRIKE.
WE TRAVELED TO NORTHERN SYRIA
TODAY WITH U.S.-BACKED REBELS.
SYRIANS TELL US THE UNITED
STATES HAS AN ENORMOUS
RESPONSIBILITY NOW.
YES, THIS ISN'T AMERICA'S WAR.
AND NO, THESE PEOPLE HERE DON'T
WANT AMERICAN TROOPS AND FOR
THIS TO BECOME ANOTHER IRAQ.
BUT THEY SAY, IF THE UNITED
STATES DOESN'T INTERVENE NOW,
BASHAR AL ASSAD'S REGIME WILL BE
ENCOURAGED TO GO FURTHER AND
THEY BELIEVE USE CHEMICAL
WEAPONS AGAIN.
OSAMA MOAS ARRIVED AT A CAMP
WITH HIS WIFE AND 11 CHILDREN
TODAY.
HE TOLD US HE CAME TO HIDE FROM
THE POISON GAS.
AND DIDN'T KNOW WHERE ELSE TO
GO.
>> Translator: IT IS A DIRTY
REGIME HE SAID.
>> Reporter: BUT THE MOST
POWERFUL WORDS CAME FROM THIS
10-YEAR-OLD A MESSAGE SHE SAID
SHE HAD FOR PRESIDENT OBAMA.
>> Translator: DOES HE WANT HIS
KIDS TO BE LIKE US?
AREN'T WE JUST LIKE THEM?
WHEN WE GET BIGGER, WE ARE GOING
TO WRITE, "OBAMA DIDN'T HELP US"
SHE SAID.
SECRETARY KERRY MADE IT CLEAR
TODAY THE U.S. WANTS TO HELP.
AND IS PREPARING TO ACT.
>> THE IMAGES OF ENTIRE FAMILIES
DEAD IN THEIR BEDS, HUMAN
SUFFERING THAT WE CAN NEVER
IGNORE OR FORGET.
ANYONE WHO COULD CLAIM THAT AN
ATTACK OF THIS STAGGERING SCALE
COULD BE CONTRIVED OR FABRICATED
NEEDS TO CHECK THEIR CONSCIENCE
AND THEIR OWN MORAL COMPASS.
>> Reporter: THE SYRIAN REGIME
DENIES IT EVER USED CHEMICAL
WEAPONS.
SYRIAN REBELS TELL US THAT ASSAD
HAS USED THEM AT LEAST 30 TIMES
SINCE THIS WAR BEGAN AND THIS
LATEST CASE WAS JUST THE MOST
FLAGRANT.
LESTER?
>> RICHARD ENGEL IN TURKEY
TONIGHT, THANKS.
>>> THERE IS SOME LATE
DEVELOPMENTS OUT OF WASHINGTON
REGARDING POSSIBLE U.S. ACTION
AGAINST SYRIA.
ANDREA MITCHELL OUR CHIEF
FOREIGN AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT.
ANDREA, WHAT ARE YOU HEARING
TONIGHT?
>> Reporter: OFFICIALS ARE
TELLING ME, LESTER, THEY'RE
GOING TO PROVIDE INTELLIGENCE TO
BACK UP THEIR CONCLUSION IN
COMING DAYS PERHAPS AS EARLY AS
TOMORROW.
ONE REASON JOHN KERRY WAS SO
PASSIONATE TODAY, THE SCALE OF
THIS ATTACK AND ITS BRAZEN
QUALITY.
WITH THOSE INSPECTORS ON THE
GROUND THEY SAY A MILITARY
OPTION WAS NOT AUTOMATIC.
IF RUSSIA HAD CHANGED ITS POLICY
OR SYRIA ACKNOWLEDGED WHAT IT
HAD DONE, THEY MIGHT NOT NEED TO
PUNISH THE REGIME.
SO FAR, THEY HAVE BRITISH,
FRENCH, TURKEY ON BOARD.
THEY HOPE THE ARAB LEAGUE WILL
ENDORSE A LIMITED ATTACK NOT
AIMED AT TOPPLING ASSAD BUT
MAKING IT CLEAR THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ON THIS SCALE
IS JUST NOT ACCEPTABLE.
THEY HAVE PENTAGON PLANS ON THE
SHELF FOR A WHILE.
I'M TOLD THIS IS NOT IMMINENT.
THEY'RE GOING TO TRY TO ORGANIZE
THE ALLIES, NOTIFY CONGRESS AND
LIKELY NOT ATTACK WHILE THOSE
U.N. INSPECTORS ARE STILL ON THE
GROUND.
THEY'RE SCHEDULED TO LEAVE
SUNDAY.
LEATHER?
>> ALL RIGHT, ANDREA.
THANKS.
NEARLY TWO MILLION PEOPLE HAVE
BECOME REFUGEES FLEEING THE WAR
IN SYRIA.
AS WE HAVE BEEN REPORTING THERE
IS A GRIM MILESTONE REACHED AS
WELL.
NEARLY ONE MILLION OF THOSE
REFUGEES ARE CHILDREN, MOST
UNDER THE AGE OF 11.
NBC'S ANN CURRY MADE HER WAY
TODAY TO ONE OF THE REFUGEE
CAMPS, THE BIGGEST IN FACT.
IT'S ON SYRIA'S BOARD WITH
JORDAN.
IT'S BURSTING AT THE SEAMS WITH
130,000 PEOPLE.
ANN JOINS US FROM AMMAN.
ANN?
>> Reporter: LESTER, GOOD
EVENING.
WITH THE MASSIVE NUMBERS AND THE
SHOCKING IMAGES OF CHILDREN
SUFFERING IN AN APPARENT
CHEMICAL ATTACK, THE WAR IN
SYRIA APPEARS TO BE TURNING AN
EMOTIONAL CORNER, CAPTURING THE
ATTENTION OF THE WORLD.
TODAY WE FOUND ONE SMALL SYRIAN
BOY, ONE OF THE ONE MILLION.
IN A CLINIC INSIDE JORDAN'S
ZAATARI REFUGEE CAMP, WE FOUND
JALAL, WHO BARELY ESCAPED THE
WAR BACK HOME.
[ SPEAKING FOREIGN LANGUAGE ]
>> Translator: AT LEAST 7 YEARS
OLD HE LOOKS BACK ON WHAT WAS
ONCE A HAPPY CHILDHOOD IN SYRIA.
>> Translator: WE USED TO PLAY
BALL WITH OUR FATHER AND GO ON
SWINGS AND SHOOT MARBLES AND
RIDE BICYCLES HE SAYS.
[ BOMB BLASTS ]
BUT WAR CAME TO HIS HOMETOWN.
[ GUNFIRE ]
HE TELLS US "WE WERE NOT ALLOWED
TO LEAVE THE HOUSE BECAUSE
SNIPERS WOULD START SHOOTING AT
US.
THEY WOULD SLAUGHTER THE MEN AND
CUT OFF THEIR FINGERS OR ARMS
AND THROW THEIR BODIES INTO THE
SCHOOLS."
SIX WEEKS AGO PLAYING OUTSIDE
WITH HIS 10-YEAR-OLD BROTHER AND
FRIENDS, SOMETHING EXPLODED.
JALAL WAS HIT BY SHRAPNEL AND
WATCHED CLOSE FRIENDS DIE.
>> Translator: ONE HAD HIS
STOMACH CUT OPEN, HE SAYS, THE
FIGHTING WAS AS CLOSE AS YOU ARE
FROM US.
WE CRAWLED ON OUR BELLIES OR
RAN.
WE FELL AND SCRAPED OUR KNEES.
SOMETIMES WE WOULD START
SHAKING.
EVEN OUR MOTHERS STARTED CRYING.
>> Reporter: JALAL'S MOTHER,
NIMAD DESCRIBES THEIR ESCAPE.
>> Translator: WHEN WE HEARD A
SNIPER WAS CLOSE, WE TOLD THE
CHILDREN TO CRAWL ALONG.
THE ROAD.
THANK GOD THEY LISTENED TO US
AND THEY ARE SAFE.
>> Reporter: THEY WALKED THREE
DAYS LEAVING JALAL'S FATHER A
COOK TO FIGHT AS A REBEL.
THEY HEARD FROM HIM JUST ONCE
SINCE THEY LEFT HOME.
NOW JALAL'S MOTHER WEEPS FOR ALL
THEIR LOST LOVED ONES.
TODAY, SAFE IN THE CAMP, JALAL
GETS A CHANCE TO BE A KID AGAIN.
BUT AT NIGHT HE SAYS IT'S HARD
TO SLEEP.
HE DREAMS OF HIS FATHER AND
CRIES.
JALAL'S STORY IS ONE GLIMPSE
INTO THIS WAR'S TRAGEDY FOR
SYRIA'S CHILDREN.
MEANTIME, THE CRISIS HAS
OUTPACED THE WORLD'S RESPONSE
MAKING FOR VERY TOUGH CONDITIONS
INSIDE THOSE REFUGEE CAMPS.
TODAY WE WITNESS SEVERAL HUNDRED
SYRIAN REFUGEES LEAVING THE
ZAATARI REFUGEE CAMP TO GO BACK
TO SYRIA.
ONE SAYING, "I WOULD RATHER DIE
UNDER SHELL FIRE THAN LIVE IN
THIS CAMP."
LEATHER?
>> ALL RIGHT.
ANN CURRY TONIGHT IN AMMAN.
THANK YOU.
>>> BACK IN THIS COUNTRY NOW TO
ANOTHER BIG STORY WE ARE
FOLLOWING TONIGHT, THAT
OUT-OF-CONTROL WILDFIRE IN
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK, NOW ONE
OF THE BIGGEST IN CALIFORNIA
HISTORY.
IT IS ROUGHLY THE SIZE OF
CHICAGO.
SO BIG THEY CAN SEE IT ON THE
INTERNATIONAL SPACE STATION, THE
IMAGE NASA PROVIDED US.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO JOINS US WITH
THE LATEST.
TOM, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: HI, LESTER.
THAT'S THE SMOKE BEHIND ME OFF
THE TOP OF THE TREES AND ALSO
THE BUILDING THERE.
THE FIRE SERVICE FIRE CHIEF
TELLS ME THIS IS THE TOUGHEST
FIRE HE HAS FOUGHT IN HIS
30-YEAR CAREER.
SUNRISE THIS MORNING IN
TUOLUMNE, CALIFORNIA, BROUGHT
RELIEF.
THE TOWN WAS STILL STANDING.
THE FIRE OVER THE RIDGE AND IN
THE RIVER CANYONS BELOW
STRETCHES SOME 200 SQUARE MILES
INCLUDING YOSEMITE NATIONAL
PARK.
COMMANDERS THINK THEY'RE
STARTING TO GET THE UPPER HAND,
BUT IT IS ONLY 15% CONTAINED.
WE ARE FACING RECORD FUEL, DRY
CONDITIONS ACROSS THIS STATE.
>> THE FIRE SHOT OVER HERE.
>> Reporter: TUCKED BETWEEN THE
TREES ON ROBIN HOOD WAY WE FOUND
STRIKE TEAM 2276 ALPHA, FROM SAN
MATEO COUNTY.
IF THE FIRE COMES OVER THE HILL
IT WILL BE ON TOP OF THEM AND
THE HOMES THEY'RE PREPARED TO
DEFEND WITHIN MINUTES.
>> THIS IS REALLY DANGEROUS.
IT IS DANGEROUS.
WE HAVE HAD 19 FIREFIGHTERS, HOT
SHOT CREW, DIE JUST RECENTLY IN
ARIZONA.
FIRE IS UNPREDICTABLE.
WHEN IT GETS IN THE TREE TOPS IT
MOVES DIFFERENT THAN IT DOES ON
THE GROUND.
>> Reporter: THE CHALLENGE --
FIRES THIS BIG CREATE THEIR OWN
WIND PATTERNS AND VACUUMS.
IN YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK THE
FIRE REMAINS CONTAINED IN A
REMOTE WILDERNESS AREA.
IT HAS GOT WILDLIFE, LIKE THIS
MOTHER AND CUB ON THE MOVE.
BUT FOR THE CITY OF SAN
FRANCISCO, SOME 150 MILES AWAY,
THE CONCERN IS THE WATER SUPPLY.
MOST OF WHICH COMES FROM THE
HETCH HETCHY RESERVOIR IN THE
FIRE ZONE.
>> WHEN YOU BURN DOWN EVERYTHING
YOU HAVE A MOONSCAPE OUT THERE
THAT WITH FLOODS CAN CONTAMINATE
THE WATERS.
>> OH, MAN.
>> Reporter: JUST OUTSIDE OF
YOSEMITE NATIONAL PARK TODAY,
80-YEAR-OLD LOUIS PEYTON
RETURNED TO THE FAMILY CABIN HIS
FATHER BUILT.
>> THIS WAS THE MAIN CABIN HERE.
>> Reporter: ALL OF IT GONE.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DO OUR BEST TO
GET IT BACK, YOU KNOW?
FOR OUR GRANDKIDS AND THEIR
GRANDKIDS CAN ENJOY IT.
>> Reporter: MEANWHILE ACROSS
THIS REGION, WHOLE TOWNS HAVE
TURNED OUT TO THANK THE THOUSAND
OF FIREFIGHTERS WHO HAVE COME
FROM AS FAR AWAY AS SAN DIEGO
AND THE OREGON STATE LINE.
THE FIGHT CONTINUES.
>> SOMEBODY HAS GOT TO PUT THIS
FIRE OUT.
UNLESS IT STARTS TO RAIN WE HAVE
TO FIGHT THIS THING
AGGRESSIVELY.
>> Reporter: FIRE COMMANDERS
THINK THEY'RE MAKING GOOD
PROGRESS ON THIS FIRE.
BUT THE AFTERNOON WINDS, BIG --
THAT'S THE BIG VARIABLE, AND
THEY'RE KICKING UP YET AGAIN.
LESTER?
>> A LOT MORE AHEAD ON A MONDAY
NIGHT.
FIGHTING OVARIAN CANCER ONE OF
THE DEADLIEST FORMS.
BECAUSE BY THE TIME IT IS FOUND
IT IS OFTEN TOO LATE.
NOW THERE IS A PROMISING NEW WAY
THAT COULD CATCH IT EARLY.
WE'LL TELL YOU ABOUT IT.
>>> LATER, HIGH EMOTION, AND ONE
OF THIS NATION'S HIGHEST HONORS
TODAY FOR A GENUINE AMERICAN
HERO.
>>> THERE IS ENCOURAGING NEWS
TONIGHT TO SHARE ABOUT A SILENT
KILLER OF WOMEN -- OVARIAN
CANCER.
IT KILLS 14,000 WOMEN EVERY YEAR
AND MOST ARE DIAGNOSED TOO LATE
FOR TREATMENT TO BE EFFECTIVE.
TONIGHT THE LATEST RESULTS ON A
STUDY OF A BLOOD TEST THAT COULD
POTENTIALLY SAVE A LOT OF LIVES
BY DETECTING THIS DISEASE MUCH
EARLIER.
HERE IS CHIEF MEDICAL EDITOR DR.
NANCY SNYDERMAN.
>> Reporter: WHEN LIZ DEGALLE
MET LINDA NELSON TAYLOR THEIR
FIRST YEAR IN COLLEGE, THE TWO
QUICKLY BECAME BEST FRIENDS.
>> SHE WAS ALWAYS A TRUE FRIEND
AND A LOT OF FUN TO BE WITH.
WE WERE LIKE SISTERS.
AND IT WAS AN INSTANT
FRIENDSHIP.
>> Reporter: THAT BOND LASTED
MORE THAN 20 YEARS UNTIL LINDA
DIED OF OVARIAN CANCER AT THE
AGE OF 43.
IT IS A DISEASE NOTORIOUSLY
DIFFICULT TO DIAGNOSE AT AN
EARLY STAGE.
SO IN LINDA'S MEMORY, LIZ JOINED
A STUDY AT M.D. ANDERSON CANCER
CENTER FOLLOWING MORE THAN 4,000
LOW-RISK, POST-MENOPAUSAL WOMEN
OVER 11 YEARS USING A SIMPLE
BLOOD TEST CALLED CA-120, A
COMMON MARKER FOR OVARIAN
CANCER.
BY GIVING THIS BLOOD TEST YEARLY
AND ROUTINELY TRACKING THE
RESULTS, DOCTORS COULD PICK UP
EARLY STAGES OF THE DISEASE WITH
ALMOST 100% ACCURACY.
>> IT IS ONLY WHEN YOU LOOK AT
IT OVER TIME THAT IT STARTS TO
BECOME MUCH MORE EFFECTIVE AT
PICKING UP EARLY STAGE DISEASE.
>> Reporter: BASED ON THOSE
RESULTS, SOME WOMEN HAD
ULTRASOUNDS TO LOOK FOR A
CANCEROUS MASS, AND IF
NECESSARY, SURGERY.
ABOUT HALFWAY THROUGH THE STUDY,
LIZ DEGALLE'S CA-125 NUMBERS
WERE UP, AND SHE WAS DIAGNOSED
WITH EARLY STAGE OVARIAN CANCER.
>> I JUST THOUGHT I WAS TIRED.
I HAD SOME PAIN, DIFFERENT
PLACES, BUT NOTHING ON A REGULAR
BASIS.
>> Reporter: THAT IS COMMON.
THE REASON SO MANY WOMEN AREN'T
DIAGNOSED UNTIL THE CANCER HAS
SPREAD.
THE PROBLEM, SYMPTOMS ARE OFTEN
VAGUE AND CAN MIMIC OTHER
AILMENTS.
THEY MAY INCLUDE ABDOMINAL
DISCOMFORT, INCLUDING BLOATING,
CRAMPS, CHANGES IN BOWEL HABITS,
BACK PAIN AND ABNORMAL BLEEDING.
DOCTORS SAY THERE MAY BE CAUSE
FOR CONCERN IF ANY OF THESE LAST
FOR MORE THAN A FEW WEEKS.
WE HAVE BEEN TRACKING LIZ'S
PROGRESS THE PAST FEW YEARS.
SHE HAS HAD SURGERY AND
CHEMOTHERAPY AND NOW IS CANCER
FREE.
IF YOU ARE WONDERING IF THIS
TEST SHOULD BECOME PART OF YOUR
ROUTINE CHECKUP, THE ANSWER FOR
RIGHT NOW IS NO.
BUT THERE IS AN EVEN BIGGER
STUDY UNDER WAY IN THE U.K., IN
TWO YEARS WHEN THOSE RESULTS ARE
DUE THEN WE WILL BE ABLE TO SAY
IS CA-125 SPECIFIC ENOUGH FOR
WOMEN TO BE USED AS A ROUTINE
SCREENING TEST.
BUT WE ARE NOT THERE YET.
AND I THINK OVER AND OVER AGAIN
AS YOU AND I HAVE TALKED, IT'S
THE HUMAN GENOME THAT WILL CRACK
THIS OPEN NOT JUST SCREENING
TESTS.
THAT'S WHY WE DO THE BIG
STUDIES.
>> ENCOURAGING NONETHELESS.
DR. SNYDERMAN, THANKS.
>> YOU BET.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
A BIG WEATHER PREDICTION TONIGHT
FROM A FORECASTER KNOWN FOR
GETTING IT RIGHT.
>>> PRESIDENT OBAMA TODAY
PRESENTED THE NATION'S HIGHEST
MILITARY HONOR, THE MEDAL OF
HONOR, TO AN ARMY STAFF SERGEANT
WHO DISPLAYED EXTRAORDINARY
COURAGE DURING A FIREFIGHT WITH
THE TALIBAN IN AFGHANISTAN.
IT'S THE FIRST TIME SINCE THE
VIETNAM WAR THAT TWO LIVING
SOLDIERS FROM THE SAME BATTLE
HAVE BEEN PRESENTED WITH THE
MEDAL.
HERE'S NBC'S PENTAGON
CORRESPONDENT JIM MIKLASZEWSKI.
>> Reporter: SURROUNDED BY
SOARING CLIFFS, COMBAT OUTPOSTS
KEATING IN EASTERN AFGHANISTAN
WAS UNDER CONSTANT ATTACK.
BUT IN OCTOBER 2009, THE TALIBAN
LAUNCHED THE FIERCEST ASSAULT
YET.
ARMY SPECIALIST TY CARTER WAS
JOLTED FROM HIS SLEEP.
>> THERE WAS SOMETHING VERY
DIFFERENT.
THE SOUND OF THE GUNFIRE WAS
NONSTOP.
>> Reporter: MORE THAN 400
TALIBAN UNLEASHED AN AVALANCHE
OF ROCKET, MORTAR AND MACHINE
GUNFIRE ON THE 52 AMERICANS
BELOW.
>> THE HILLS LOOKED LIKE SOME
BODY JUST KICKED OVER AN ANT
HILL.
YOU COULD SEE THEM MOVING.
>> Reporter: CARTER RAN 100
METERS ACROSS THE OPEN
BATTLEFIELD WITH AMMO FOR FELLOW
SOLDIERS NOT ONCE BUT THREE
TIMES, DODGING A TORRENT OF
BULLETS ON THE WAY.
>> THE QUICKER YOU ARE MOVING
THE LESS CHANCE A SNIPER OR
BULLET WILL HIT YOU.
>> Reporter: CARTER AND HIS
SERGEANT WERE WOUNDED AND
TRAPPED IN A HUMVEE.
>> WE WERE VERY LOW ON AMMO.
EVERYBODY AROUND US WHO WAS
FRIENDLY WAS US EITHER WOUNDED
OR DEAD.
>> Reporter: SPECIALIST STEFAN
MACE WAS ON THE GROUND SERIOUSLY
WOUNDED CRAWLING TOWARDS THE
HUMVEE PLEADING FOR HELP.
>> THAT'S THE FIRST TIME THAT I
ASKED CAN I GET TO MACE?
I SEE HIM.
HE IS RIGHT THERE.
HE SAID NO, YOU'RE NO GOOD TO
HIM DEAD.
>> Reporter: WERE YOU ANGRY?
FRUSTRATED?
>> I WAS INSANE.
THERE IS NO TRUE PAIN UNTIL YOU
HAVE SEEN YOUR FAMILY MEMBERS
SUFFER IN FRONT OF YOU.
THAT IS REAL HELL.
>> Reporter: EIGHT AMERICANS
WERE KILLED.
25 WOUNDED.
UNDER HEAVY FIRE, CARTER
EVENTUALLY CARRIED MACE TO
SAFETY.
BUT HE LATER DIED OF HIS WOUNDS.
>> WHEN I FOUND OUT THAT HE HAD
DIED, I BELIEVE THAT I WAS A
COMPLETE FAILURE.
NOT JUST IN COMBAT, OR IN THE
ARMY, BUT IN LIFE.
>> Reporter: EVEN NOW STAFF
SERGEANT CARTER STILL SUFFERS
POST-TRAUMATIC STRESS.
AT TODAY'S MEDAL OF HONOR
CEREMONY, PRESIDENT OBAMA HAILED
CARTER FOR HIS EFFORTS TO HELP
OTHERS STRUGGLING WITH PTSD.
>> LOOK AT THIS MAN.
LOOK AT THIS SOLDIER.
LOOK AT THIS WARRIOR.
HE IS AS TOUGH AS THEY COME.
>> Reporter: AND A TRUE AMERICAN
HERO, ON AND OFF THE
BATTLEFIELD.
JIM MIKLASZEWSKI, NBC NEWS, THE
PENTAGON.
>>> IN OTHER NEWS TONIGHT, SOME
WEATHER NEWS AND A BIG SUPER
BOWL PREDICTION.
THAT'S GOT A LOT OF PEOPLE
TALKING TONIGHT.
IT HAS NOTHING HOWEVER TO DO
WITH THE TEAMS IN NEXT
FEBRUARY'S GAME IN NEW JERSEY.
THE NEW EDITION OF THE "FARMERS'
ALMANAC" SAYS THE COMING WINTER
IS GOING TO BE COLDER THAN
NORMAL AND A BIG SNOWSTORM WILL
HIT THE NORTHEAST AROUND THE
TIME OF THE BIG GAME AND RIGHT
OVER THE STADIUM WHERE THE
GIANTS AND JETS PLAY, WHICH HAS
NO ROOF.
THE ALMANAC SAYS ITS FORECASTS
ARE RIGHT ABOUT 80% OF THE TIME.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
PERFORMANCE THAT STUNNED THE
CROWD AND LEFT THE VIEWERS
WONDERING WHAT EXACTLY IT WAS
THAT THEY JUST WITNESSED.
>>> OUR FINAL STORY TONIGHT IS A
LONG WAY FROM A TIME WHEN WALT
DISNEY REPORTEDLY ASKED ANNETTE
FUNICELLO NOT TO SHOW HER NAVEL
IN ALL THOSE 1960s BEACH MOVIES.
WHEN FORMER DISNEY STAR MILEY
CYRUS STEPPED ON STAGE AT LAST
NIGHT'S MTV VIDEO MUSIC AWARDS,
IT LEFT MANY OF THE 10 MILLION
VIEWERS WONDERING WHAT EXACTLY
IT WAS THEY WERE WATCHING.
WE GET THE STORY FROM NBC'S ANNE
THOMPSON.
>> Reporter: IF MILEY CYRUS
WANTED TO PROVOKE A REACTION AT
LAST NIGHT'S VIDEO MUSIC AWARDS
SHE GOT IT.
IN AN OUTFIT AND PERFORMANCE
THAT LEFT LITTLE TO THE
IMAGINATION.
THE FORMER DISNEY STAR GYRATED
ON STAGE WITH ROBIN THICKE
SINGING HIS HIT SONG, "BLURRED
LINES."
>> I WILL TELL YOU MILEY CYRUS
IS NO LONGER HANNAH MONTANA.
>> Reporter: HANNAH MONTANA, THE
ROLE THAT MADE CYRUS FAMOUS, WAS
AN INNOCENT, ALL-AMERICAN
TEENAGER WHO LED A SECRET DOUBLE
LIFE AS A POP STAR.
BROOKE SHIELDS PLAYED MONTANA'S
MOM IN THE SERIES.
>> I WANT TO KNOW WHO IS
ADVISING HER AND WHY IT IS
NECESSARY.
>> Reporter: THE PERFORMANCE LIT
UP TWITTER, SETTING A RECORD OF
306,000 TWEETS WERE MINUTE.
C.J. FARLEY, BLOGGED FOR THE
"WALL STREET JOURNAL" AS HE
WATCHED WITH HIS KIDS.
WHAT KID YOUR 8-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER THINK?
>> SHE WAS HORRIFIED BY IT.
SHE WANTED ME TO TELL ANY ONE
WHO WOULD LISTEN THAT SHE WAS
HORRIFIED BY THIS.
>> Reporter: SYDNEY IDOLIZED
CYRUS AS HANNAH MONTANA, BUT
LAST NIGHT'S PERFORMANCE MADE
HER SAD.
MADE HER SAD.
>> WE LOOKED UP TO HER AND SHE
KIND OF LET US DOWN I GUESS.
>> Reporter: MEMBERS OF THE
TELEVISION COUNCIL BLASTED MTV
FOR SUBSTITUTING TALENT WITH
SEX.
"HOW IS THIS IMAGE OF FORMER
CHILD STAR MILEY CYRUS
APPROPRIATE FOR 14-YEAR-OLDS?"
IT ASKED IN A STATEMENT TODAY.
THIS AWARDS SHOW IS FAMOUS FOR
OUTRAGEOUS BEHAVIOR, MUCH
INVOLVING ANOTHER EX-DISNEY
STAR, BRITNEY SPEARS.
CYRUS IS NOW MANAGED BY SPEARS'
MANAGER, AND THE SIMILARITIES
MAY NOT END THERE.
SHE COMMANDED $15 MILLION TO
JUDGE "X FACTOR."
SHE HAD A SUCCESSFUL WORLD TOUR.
I THINK MILEY CYRUS WOULD JUST
BE LIKE THANKING THE HEAVENS
ABOVE IF IN TEN YEARS HER CAREER
WAS STILL AS VIBRANT AS BRITNEY
SPEARS' IS.
>> Reporter: CALCULATING WHAT
SOME CALL CRINGE-WORTHY MOMENTS
TO SELL SONGS.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>> AND THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR
THIS MONDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NBC BAY AREA NEWS STARTS
NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING, AND THANKS FOR
JOINING US.
>> WE BEGIN WITH THE DEVELOPING
STORY, THE RIM FIRE STILL
RAGING.
THIS FIREFIGHT NEAR YOSEMITE NOW
THE 13th LARGEST FIRE IN STATE
HISTORY.
WANT TO SHOW YOU WHAT IT LOOKS
LIKE FROM THE AIR WHERE YOU CAN
SEE ALL THE SMOKE THAT IT'S
CREATING.
WE'RE NOW TALKING ABOUT A FIRE
THAT'S BEEN BURNING SINCE AUGUST
17th.
RUGGED TERRAIN, HIGH
TEMPERATURES MAKING IT
DIFFICULT.
IT'S BURNED THROUGH 230 SQUARE
MILES, AN AREA AS BIG AS
CHICAGO.
THE RIM FIRE, JUST 15%
CONTAINED.
ALTHOUGH THAT'S BETTER THAN WHAT
IT WAS YESTERDAY WHEN IT WAS
JUST 7%.
PUTTING MORE THAN 3,000
FIREFIGHTERS ON THE FRONT LINE.
JODI HERNANDEZ IS LIVE WITH THE
LATEST DETAILS FOR US.
>> Reporter: JESSICA,
FIREFIGHTERS TELL ME THIS HAS
BEEN A RELATIVELY GOOD DAY.
THE RIM FIRE, AS YOU MENTIONED,
IS NOW 15% CONTAINED.
AND THOUGH THOUSANDS AND
THOUSANDS OF ACRES OF WILD LAND
HAVE BURNED, THINGS FINALLY SEEM
TO BE MOVING IN THE RIGHT
DIRECTION.
FIREFIGHTERS ARE POURING ALL
THEY HAVE ON THE RIM FIRE.
NOW IN ITS SECOND WEEK, THE
FIRE'S TORCHED 150,000 ACRES,
DESTROYED MORE THAN 20
STRUCTURE, INCLUDING 11 HOMES.
4500 HOUSES REMAINED THREATENED.
>> I COULD SEE FROM MY HOUSE,
AND JUST HARD BEING ABLE TO GET
YOUR STUFF TOGET W