LOW HUMIDITY.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
WE'LL BE BACK AT 6:00.
>> LOESTER HOLT IS NEXT.
>>> TONIGHT, INTO THE
GUNFIRE.
HARROWING NEW VIDEO
FROM THE FIRST MOMENTS
OF CHAOS AND CARNAGE.
OFFICERS RUNNING
TOWARD THE DANGER.
AND TONIGHT, SOME OF
THE MOST POWERFUL
STORIES OF HEROISM
WE'VE HEARD.
A FATHER AND SON WHO
BOTH TOOK BULLETS
WHILE WORKING
FRANTICALLY TO SAVE
OTHERS.
>> HE KEPT TELLING ME
THAT HE LOVED
EVERYBODY AND JUST
WANTED EVERYBODY TO
KNOW THAT HE LOVED
EVERYBODY.
>>> PLUS, NEW DETAILS
ON THE INVESTIGATION.
THE GUNMAN'S
GIRLFRIEND BACK IN THE
U.S. NOW BEING
QUESTIONED BY THE FBI.
>>> ALSO, FALLOUT FROM
THE NBC NEWS EXCLUSIVE
THAT HAS ROCKETED
ACROSS WASHINGTON.
REX TILLERSON'S
BOILING POINT.
SOURCES SAY THE
SECRETARY OF STATE WAS
ON THE VERGE OF
RESIGNING.
SO FRUSTRATED HE EVEN
REFERRED TO PRESIDENT
TRUMP AS A MORON.
>>> AND A NEW TROPICAL
THREAT.
A POTENTIAL HURRICANE
TAKING AIM AT THE
GULF.
>>> "NIGHTLY NEWS"
BEGINS RIGHT NOW.
>>> LAS VEGAS MASS
SHOOTING.
THIS IS NBC "NIGHTLY
NEWS" WITH LESTER
HOLT, REPORTING
TONIGHT FROM LAS
VEGAS.
>>> GOOD EVENING,
EVERYONE.
THANK YOU FOR BEING
WITH US ON THIS
WEDNESDAY EVENING.
BEHIND ME THOSE
BLOWN-OUT WINDOWS HIGH
UP IN THE MANDALAY BAY
HOTEL ARE HARD TO MISS
ON THIS END OF THE
VEGAS STRIP.
A THANKFULLY TEMPORARY
REMINDER OF THE 11
MINUTES OF
COLD-BLOODED VIOLENCE
HERE JUST THREE NIGHTS
AGO.
TONIGHT, A NEW PIECE
OF VIDEO TAKEN JUST
BELOW THE HOTEL AS THE
GUNFIRE ERUPTED.
IT WAS CAPTURED BY A
CAB DRIVER IN THE TAXI
QUEUE AT THE MANDALAY
BAY AS THE SHOTS RANG
OUT, CAPTURING AN
EERIE CALM AMONG
CONFUSED HOTEL GUESTS,
AND THEN THE PANIC OF
FLEEING CONCERTGOERS.
11 MINUTES IN WHICH
LIVES WERE ABRUPTLY
ENDED OR FOREVER
ALTERED.
>> I SAID, LET'S GET
DOWN, AND HE SAID, NO,
WE'LL GET TRAMPLED.
LET'S GO.
AND HE WRAPPED HIS
ARMS AROUND MY BACK.
AND AS WE STARTED TO
RUN, I FELT HIM GET
SHOT IN THE BACK, AND
WE FELL TO THE GROUND.
>> AND TONIGHT, AS THE
PRESIDENT AND FIRST
LADY VISITED WITH
SURVIVORS AND FIRST
RESPONDERS HERE, WE'RE
GETTING A TERRIFYING
NEW GLIMPSE OF THAT
NIGHT THROUGH THE EYES
OF POLICE RESPONDING
TO THE SHOTS.
THERE WERE MOMENTS OF
TERROR AND SOME OF
REMARKABLE BRAVERY.
OUR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MIGUEL
ALMAGUER BEGINS OUR
COVERAGE TONIGHT.
>> GO THAT WAY!
GET OUT OF HERE!
THERE'S GUNSHOTS
COMING FROM OVER
THERE.
GO THAT WAY!
>> Reporter: POLICE
SAY THEY RAN INTO 11
MINUTES OF HELL.
>> GET BACK!
>> Reporter: THE LAS
VEGAS POLICE
DEPARTMENT RELEASING A
SAMPLING OF BODY CAM
FOOTAGE CAPTURING THE
INTENSE HORROR, VOLLEY
AFTER VOLLEY OF
RELENTLESS GUNFIRE.
>> GET DOWN, GET DOWN,
GET DOWN!
>> Reporter: BULLETS
TEARING THROUGH THE
AIR MUFFLED ONLY BY
SCREAMS.
>> THEY KNEW WHAT THEY
WERE DOING, BUT IT'S
ALSO NOT JUST A FLY BY
THE SEAT OF YOUR PANTS
TYPE OF RISK.
IT'S A CALCULATED
RISK.
>> Reporter: WITH
OFFICERS SWEEPING ON
TO THE KILLING FIELD,
THIS CAMERA BURIED
UNDER A VEST, SHOWS
ONE OFFICER USING HIS
BODY TO SHIELD A
VICTIM LYING ON THE
GROUND.
ALONGSIDE POLICE,
PARAMEDICS KNOWING
THEY, TOO, COULD BE
KILLED.
>> IT'S VERY INTENSE.
>> Reporter: JEFF
BUCHANAN'S TEAM
SCRAMBLED TO PUT ON
KEVLAR.
>> THEY'RE FOCUSED ON
THE PATIENTS AND
THEY'RE ALSO FOCUSED
ON MAKING SURE THAT
THEY SAVE AS MANY
PEOPLE AS POSSIBLE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
NEW VIDEO CAPTURED BY
A CAB DRIVER.
IN THE CHAOS, POLICE
WOULD EVENTUALLY SPOT
THE SHOOTER.
>> MUZZLE BLASTS FROM
THE MANDALAY BAY.
>> NORTH OF THE
MANDALAY BAY, IT'S
COMING OUT OF A
WINDOW.
>> Reporter: FEAR AND
PANIC WERE EVERYWHERE.
VICTIMS PILING INTO
THIS TAXI.
>> JUST GO!
JUST GO.
>> OKAY.
I'M GOING.
>> EVERYBODY'S DYING.
COME ON.
>> Reporter: AMONG
THOSE PULLED TO
SAFETY, 24-YEAR-OLD
KRISTIN BABIK.
>> OUT OF EVERYONE WHO
WAS RUNNING AWAY AND
SCREAMING, THERE WERE
A LOT OF PEOPLE GOING
TOWARD IT TO HELP.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
BABIK IS RECOVERING.
SHE'S STILL WEARING
HER CONCERT WRISTBAND.
>> I'M FORTUNATE I
DIDN'T PASS AWAY, BUT
I'M ALSO UNFORTUNATE
THAT I AM NOW STUCK
WITH THIS BULLET WOUND
IN MY BACK FOR THE
REST OF MY LIFE.
>> GO, GO, GO, GO.
>> Reporter: AN URBAN
BATTLEFIELD NO ONE
WILL EVER FORGET.
DURING THE GUNFIRE
FROM THIS HOTEL ROOM,
POLICE SAY MANY OF
THEIR OFFICERS WERE
WEARING BODY CAMERAS,
ADDING MUCH OF THE
VIDEO IS STILL BEING
REVIEWED.
SOME IS TOO GRAPHIC TO
SHOW.
IT IS A REAL LIFE
ACCOUNT OF THE TERROR
THAT RAINED DOWN ON SO
MANY.
LESTER?
>> SO TERRIFYING JUST
TO WATCH IT, I CAN'T
IMAGINE LIVING THROUGH
IT.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER, THANK
YOU.
>>> TONIGHT, THE WOMAN
WHO LIVED WITH THE LAS
VEGAS ATTACKER IS BACK
IN THE U.S., ARRIVING
IN LOS ANGELES, WHERE
SHE SPENT MOST OF THE
DAY ANSWERING
QUESTIONS FROM THE FBI
AND LAS VEGAS
AUTHORITIES.
INVESTIGATORS ARE
HOPING SHE CAN PROVIDE
SOME ANSWERS THAT HAVE
SO FAR BEEN ELUSIVE.
WE GET ALL THE LATEST
NOW FROM OUR JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS.
>> Reporter: UNDER
POLICE ESCORT, MARILOU
DANLEY ARRIVED LATE
LAST NIGHT IN LOS
ANGELES FROM A FAMILY
VISIT IN THE
PHILIPPINES AND WAS
QUESTIONED FOR HOURS
TODAY AT THE FBI'S
L.A. OFFICE.
INVESTIGATORS WANT TO
KNOW IF SHE HAD ANY
HINT THAT STEPHEN
PADDOCK WAS PLANNING A
VIOLENT ATTACK OR IF
SHE KNEW OF ANY REASON
WHY HE WOULD COMMIT
SUCH A HORRIBLE CRIME.
SO FAR THEY SAY NO
OBVIOUS ANSWERS.
LATE TODAY HER LAWYER
READ A STATEMENT FROM
HER.
>> HE NEVER SAID
ANYTHING TO ME OR TOOK
ANY ACTION THAT I WAS
AWARE OF THAT I
UNDERSTOOD IN ANY WAY
TO BE A WARNING THAT
SOMETHING HORRIBLE
LIKE THIS WAS GOING TO
HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: IN
AUSTRALIA, WHERE SHE'S
FROM, HER SISTER SAID
IN AN INTERVIEW THAT
STEPHEN PADDOCK GAVE
HER THE AIRLINE TICKET
TO GET HER OUT OF THE
COUNTRY SO THAT HE
COULD FREELY CARRY OUT
HIS SHOOTING RAMPAGE.
>> SHE WAS SENT AWAY.
SHE WAS SENT AWAY SO
THAT SHE WILL BE NOT
THERE TO INTERFERE
WITH WHAT HE IS
PLANNING.
SO IN MY -- IN MY
HEART AND IN MY
UNDERSTANDING, HE DONE
THIS SOLELY HIMSELF.
>> Reporter: IN HER
STATEMENT, DANLEY SAID
SHE FEARED THE PLANE
TICKET AND THE MONEY
HE WIRED TO HER MEANT
HE WANTED TO BREAK UP
WITH HER.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS SAY
12 OF THE 23 RIFLES
FOUND IN PADDOCK'S
HOTEL ROOM WERE
EQUIPPED WITH BUMP
STOCKS TO MAKE THEM
FIRE LIKE MACHINE GUNS
AND CLIPS TO HOLD 60
TO 100 ROUNDS OF
AMMUNITION.
AS INVESTIGATORS BUILD
A TIMELINE OF WHAT LED
UP TO THE ATTACK,
THEY'RE TRYING TO
TRACK DOWN A WOMAN WHO
WAS SEEN WITH PADDOCK
IN THE DAYS BEFORE THE
SHOOTING.
THEY DON'T KNOW WHAT
CONNECTION, IF ANY,
SHE HAD TO THE ATTACK,
BUT THEYANT TO KNOW
WHO SHE WAS SO THEY
CAN TALK TO HER.
THEY'RE ALSO SCOURING
PADDOCK'S HEALTH
RECORDS.
HE TOOK VALIUM, BUT
FEDERAL OFFICIALS SAY
TONIGHT THEY FOUND NO
SERIOUS MENTAL HEALTH
PROBLEMS.
SO FAR THE FBI SAYS NO
IDEA OF WHAT DROVE HIM
TO COMMIT MASS MURDER.
>> WE LOOK FOR ACTUAL
INDICATORS OF
AFFILIATION, OF
MOTIVE, OF INTENT, AND
SO FAR WE'RE NOT
THERE.
WE DON'T HAVE THOSE
SORT OF INDICATORS.
>> Reporter: A SENIOR
LAW ENFORCEMENT
OFFICIAL SAYS TONIGHT
THAT MARILOU DANLEY'S
BEEN COOPERATIVE AND
THAT THERE'S NO SIGN
SHE HAD ANYTHING TO DO
WITH STEPHEN PADDOCK'S
MASS SHOOTING.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT, PETE
WILLIAMS TONIGHT,
THANK YOU.
>>> AND AS THE
INVESTIGATION MOVES
FORWARD, WE ARE
HEARING MORE DRAMATIC
ACCOUNTS OF A STRUGGLE
TO GET OUT ALIVE ONCE
THE CHAOS AND
CONFUSION BEGAN.
STRANGERS HELPING
STRANGERS UNDER THAT
HAIL OF GUNFIRE.
AT ONE HOSPITAL, WE
WERE THERE FOR AN
EMOTIONAL REUNION
BETWEEN A SURVIVOR AND
A GOOD SAMARITAN WHO
SAVED HER LIFE.
HERE'S NBC'S CATIE
BECK.
>> Reporter: AS
BULLETS STARTED
RAINING DOWN SUNDAY,
THOUSANDS BEGAN THEIR
DESPERATE ATTEMPTS TO
ESCAPE.
BUT KAREN SMERBER
COULDN'T.
SHOT IN THE STOMACH,
SHE WAS DOUBLED OVER
IN PAIN.
INSTEAD OF RUNNING,
SHE CALLED HER
HUSBAND.
>> I WAS GOING TO DIE.
IF THIS IS IT, HAD TO
SAY GOOD-BYE.
>> Reporter: BUT THE
CALL HOME WAS
INTERRUPTED BY A GOOD
SAMARITAN.
THE MAN WITH A MOTIVE
TO KILL STILL FIRING
FROM HIS 32nd FLOOR
SNIPER'S NEST.
NOW ANOTHER MAN WITH A
MISSION TO SAVE
CARRIED THE MOTHER OF
FOUR AWAY FROM HARM.
>> YEP.
MY GUARDIAN ANGEL
SHOWED UP.
HIS NAME'S SHAUN.
AND HE PICKED ME UP.
HE PICKED ME UP AND
CARRIED ME OUT OF
THERE.
>> Reporter: SHAUN
TOPPER FLAGGING DOWN A
CAR, RIDING WITH HER
TO THE HOSPITAL.
INCREDIBLY THE BULLET
HAD PASSED THROUGH HER
WITHOUT HITTING ANY
VITAL ORGANS.
WHEN YOU THINK ABOUT
THE FACT, KAREN, THAT
YOU WERE IN THIS
SITUATION.
YOU WERE PROBABLY
BLEEDING
SIGNIFICANTLY.
>> I WAS BLEEDING TO
DEATH.
IF HE DIDN'T GET ME
HERE, I WOULD HAVE
DIED.
>> Reporter: TODAY WE
WERE THERE WHEN SHAUN
STOPPED BY.
ON HIS 24th BIRTHDAY,
HE'S AT THE BEDSIDE
AND SAYS THERE'S NO
BETTER GIFT THAN
SEEING HER RECOVER.
>> WHETHER WE LIKE IT
OR NOT, OUR LIVES ARE
INTERTWINED FOREVER.
>> YEAH.
>> Reporter: SHAUN
WON'T ACCEPT A HERO
TITLE FOR WHAT HE DID
THAT NIGHT.
HE SAW HER AND
REACTED.
BUT SMERBER'S HUSBAND
MATT SAYS HE DESERVES
THAT AND MORE.
>> I'M STILL MARRIED
TODAY AND MY KIDS HAVE
THEIR MOM AND STEP-MOM
AND BECAUSE OF ONE
HEROIC PERSON.
>> Reporter: NOW
MAKING A STRONG
RECOVERY, THE MOMENTS
OF TERROR HAUNT
SMERBER'S DREAMS, BUT
WHEN SHE AWAKES SHE
HOLDS ON TO ANOTHER
MEMORY, THE MOMENT A
STRANGER PICKED HER UP
AND SAVED HER LIFE.
CATIE BECK, NBC NEWS,
LAS VEGAS.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP
AND THE FIRST LADY, AS
WE SAID EARLIER, MADE
THEIR WAY HERE TO LAS
VEGAS TODAY MEETING
WITH VICTIMS AND THEIR
FAMILIES, THANKING
FIRST RESPONDERS AND
MEDICAL STAFF OF THEIR
HEROIC EFFORTS AND
DELIVERING A MESSAGE
FROM THE NATION TO
THIS HEARTBROKEN CITY.
>> WE KNOW THAT YOUR
SORROW FEELS ENDLESS.
WE STAND TOGETHER TO
HELP YOU CARRY YOUR
PAIN.
YOU'RE NOT ALONE.
WE WILL NEVER LEAVE
YOUR SIDE.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP
TODAY HERE IN LAS
VEGAS.
MUCH MORE FROM LAS
VEGAS AS WE CONTINUE
IN A MOMENT.
>>> BUT BACK IN
WASHINGTON, PRESIDENT
TRUMP IS RETURNING TO
NEW FALLOUT FROM OUR
NBC NEWS EXCLUSIVE
REPORT REVEALING HIGH
TENSIONS BETWEEN HIM
AND HIS SECRETARY OF
STATE REX TILLERSON.
TONIGHT, TILLERSON IS
FIRING BACK AFTER
MULTIPLE OFFICIAL
SOURCES TOLD NBC NEWS
HE CAME TO THE BRINK
OF RESIGNING OVER THE
SUMMER AND THE
SECRETARY RESPONDING
TO ANOTHER EXPLOSIVE
DETAIL IN OUR
REPORTING, THAT HE
INSULTED THE PRESIDENT
IN FRONT OF OTHER
OFFICIALS.
LET'S GET MORE FROM
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
SECRETARY OF STATE REX
TILLERSON COMING OUT
TO RESPOND TO AN NBC
NEWS REPORT ABOUT
FRICTION WITH THE
PRESIDENT AND THAT HE
WAS ON THE VERGE OF
RESIGNING THIS SUMMER.
>> THERE ARE SOME NEWS
REPORTS THIS MORNING
THAT I WANT TO
ADDRESS.
>> Reporter: BUT
STOPPING SHORT OF A
FULL DENIAL.
>> THERE'S NEVER BEEN
A CONSIDERATION IN MY
MIND TO LEAVE.
>> Reporter: BUT
SENIOR ADMINISTRATION
OFFICIALS CONFIRM TO
NBC NEWS TILLERSON
THREATENED TO RESIGN
IN JULY.
THE BOILING POINT, THE
PRESIDENT'S HIGHLY
POLITICAL SPEECH TO
THE BOY SCOUTS, A
GROUP TILLERSON ONCE
LED.
>> WE WON FLORIDA, WE
WON SOUTH CAROLINA, WE
WON NORTH CAROLINA, WE
WON PENNSYLVANIA.
>> Reporter: JUST DAYS
EARLIER TILLERSON EVEN
CALLED THE PRESIDENT A
MORON AFTER A PENTAGON
MEETING, ACCORDING TO
THREE SENIOR
OFFICIALS.
TILLERSON TODAY NOT
DENYING THAT.
>> I'M NOT GOING TO
DEAL WITH PETTY STUFF
LIKE THAT.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT IN LAS VEGAS
TODAY LABELING THE NBC
REPORT FAKE NEWS.
>> IT WAS A TOTALLY
PHONY STORY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH.
IT WAS MADE UP.
IT WAS MADE UP BY NBC.
TOTAL CONFIDENCE IN
REX.
I HAVE TOTAL
CONFIDENCE.
>> Reporter: BUT
MULTIPLE SOURCES TELL
NBC TILLERSON DID
DISPARAGE THE
PRESIDENT AND ALSO
TALKED ABOUT QUITTING
REPORTS NBC'S CAROL
LEE.
>> KELLY AND MATTIS
MOVED IN TO TRY TO
CONVINCE HIM TO STICK
AROUND.
AND THEN VICE
PRESIDENT PENCE
FOLLOWED UP WITH WHAT
ONE SOURCE DESCRIBED
TO US AS A PEP TALK.
>> Reporter: IN FACT,
TILLERSON AND THE
PRESIDENT HAVE CLASHED
FOR MONTHS OVER IRAN,
OVER A DISPUTE BETWEEN
U.S. ALLIES IN THE
PERSIAN GULF AND
NORTH KOREA.
COMING TO A HEAD THIS
WEEKEND WHEN THE
PRESIDENT ATTACKED
TILLERSON'S OUTREACH
TO NORTH KOREA
TWEETING SUNDAY, SAVE
YOUR ENERGY, REX,
WE'LL DO WHAT HAS TO
BE DONE.
THE PRESIDENT'S
DIPLOMATIC BOMBSHELL
COMING JUST HOURS
AFTER TILLERSON
RETURNED FROM CHINA
WHERE HE TOLD
REPORTERS THE U.S. HAS
A BACKCHANNEL TO TALK
WITH NORTH KOREA.
LEADING TO A CHORUS OF
HEADLINES THAT
TILLERSON SHOULD QUIT.
>> I THINK SECRETARY
TILLERSON REALLY DOES
HAVE TO ASK HIMSELF
THE QUESTION WHETHER
HE SHOULD BE STAYING
IN THIS POSITION.
>> Reporter: AND THE
VICE PRESIDENT SAYING
THAT HE NEVER
DISCUSSED RESIGNING
WITH TILLERSON.
SENATE FOREIGN
RELATIONS CHAIRMAN
CORKER SAYING
TILLERSON, KELLY AND
MATTIS ARE, QUOTE,
HELPING SEPARATE OUR
COUNTRY FROM CHAOS.
LESTER?
>> ANDREA MITCHELL,
THANK YOU.
>>> AS THE WHITE HOUSE
DEALS WITH THAT
FALLOUT IN CONGRESS,
THERE ARE GROWING
CALLS FOR A BAN ON
BUMP STOCKS, THE
DEVICES THE LAS VEGAS
GUNMAN USED TO TURN
HIS SEMIAUTOMATIC
WEAPONS ESSENTIALLY
INTO AUTOMATIC MACHINE
GUNS.
AND AS OUR CHIEF WHITE
HOUSE CORRESPONDENT
HALLIE JACKSON
REPORTS, SOME
PROMINENT REPUBLICANS
TONIGHT ARE SIGNALING
THAT THEY ARE OPEN TO
A BAN.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP TODAY ARGUES NOW
IS NOT THE TIME TO
TALK GUN CONTROL.
>> WE'RE NOT GOING TO
TALK ABOUT THAT TODAY.
WE WON'T TALK ABOUT
THAT.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT VISITING
VEGAS WHERE SOME
22,000 PEOPLE
EXPERIENCED THE
DEADLIEST SHOOTING IN
MODERN U.S. HISTORY.
DIANNE FEINSTEIN'S
DAUGHTER WAS ALMOST
ONE OF THEM.
>> THEY WERE GOING TO
STAY AT THAT HOTEL.
THAT'S HOW CLOSE IT
CAME TO ME.
>> Reporter: IN
WASHINGTON, THE
SENATOR, WHOSE
DAUGHTER NEVER ENDED
UP AT THE COUNTRY
CONCERT, IS
INTRODUCING A NEW BAN
ON BUMP STOCKS.
THE NEVADA SHOOTER HAD
12 OF THE DEVICES
WHICH LEGALLY ALLOW A
SEMIAUTOMATIC GUN TO
SHOOT FASTER LIKE AN
AUTOMATIC.
DEMOCRATIC SENATOR
RICHARD BLUMENTHAL
CO-SPONSORS THE BILL.
HAVE YOU HAD
DISCUSSIONS ON THE
OTHER SIDE OF THE
AISLE?
>> THERE IS
RECEPTIVENESS THAT I
THINK IS VERY, VERY
SIGNIFICANT.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST
TWO REPUBLICANS SAY
THEY WOULD BACK A BUMP
STOCK BAN.
ONE TEXAS LAWMAKER, A
GUN OWNER, SAYS
THERE'S NO REASON FOR
THE DEVICES, WHICH
SENATOR BILL CASSIDY
WASN'T FAMILIAR WITH
UNTIL NOW.
>> WHO WANTS TO SEE
ANOTHER LAS VEGAS?
ON THE OTHER HAND,
THERE'S NOT GOING TO
BE A SINGLE LAW WHICH
STOPS SOMEBODY
DETERMINED TO DO
SOMETHING BAD.
>> Reporter: GOP
LEADERS SAY THEY WANT
TO LEARN MORE, BUT NO
HEARING'S BEEN
SCHEDULED YET.
FOR DEMOCRATS AN
UPHILL BATTLE.
FOR SOME REPUBLICANS,
A SLIPPERY SLOPE.
>> IT'S NOT JUST ABOUT
BUMP STOCKS.
IT'S ABOUT ULTIMATELY
GETTING RID OF THE
SECOND AMENDMENT.
>> Reporter: THAT'S
ECHOED AT THE CLARK
COUNTY SHOOTING
COMPLEX A HALF HOUR
FROM THE VEGAS STRIP.
>> THERE SHOULD NOT BE
ANY RESTRICTIONS
WHATSOEVER ON GUN
RIGHTS.
>> Reporter: BUT IN
WASHINGTON THEY ARE
TALKING.
THE QUESTION NOW
WHETHER THAT TALK WILL
TURN TO ACTION.
HALLIE JACKSON,
NBC NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, HOTELS ON
HIGH ALERT.
THE ENHANCED SECURITY
YOU MAY FIND NEXT TIME
YOU CHECK IN AFTER THE
MASS SHOOTING HERE.
HOPE YOU CAN STAY WITH
US.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
FROM LAS VEGAS WHERE
TONIGHT RESORTS HAVE
STEPPED UP SECURITY AS
OFFICIALS TRY TO ADD
EXTRA LAYERS OF SAFETY
WHILE TRYING TO FIND
THE RIGHT BALANCE
BETWEEN THE EASE OF
ENJOYING THE HOTELS
AND CASINOS UP AND
DOWN THE STRIP AND THE
NEED TO PROTECT WHAT
COULD BE SEEN AS SOFT
TARGETS.
HERE'S NBC'S JO LING
KENT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
MAJOR NEW SECURITY
MEASURES DEPLOYED IN
LAS VEGAS, THREE DAYS
AFTER SUNDAY'S MASS
SHOOTING FROM A HOTEL
ROOM WINDOW.
LAW ENFORCEMENT
STEPPING UP SECURITY
OUTSIDE OF HOTELS AND
INSIDE AT THE WYNN AND
ENCORE, BEYOND THE
SECURITY CAMERAS, NEW
BAG CHECKS AND
HANDHELD METAL
DETECTORS FOR GUESTS
AND STAFF.
PLUS, K-9 UNITS
SCOURING THE STRIP AND
SEARCHING HOTEL ROOMS
FOR POSSIBLE THREATS.
JEFF AND PENNY
CHITTENDON HAVE
VISITED VEGAS TEN
TIMES.
THIS TRIP IS
DIFFERENT.
>> LAST NIGHT WE HAD
TO GO THROUGH METAL
DETECTORS, WHICH WAS
THE FIRST TIME WE'VE
EVER HAD TO DO THAT.
>> Reporter: THE
CHALLENGE KEEPING
PEOPLE SAFE WHILE
MAINTAINING AMBIENCE
FOR 43 MILLION ANNUAL
VISITORS.
>> WE'RE OBSERVING
EVERYONE WHO COMES ON
TO OUR PROPERTY.
WE'RE DOING BAG
CHECKS.
WE DON'T WANT TO PUSH
BUSINESS AWAY BUT WE
WANT TO MAKE SURE THAT
EVERYBODY IS SAFE.
>> Reporter: SECURITY
OFFICIALS SAY IT'S
IMPOSSIBLE TO FULLY
GUARANTEE THE SAFETY
OF LAS VEGAS OR ANY
CITY WITH THOUSANDS OF
ROOMS AND BALCONIES
OVERLOOKING POPULAR
PUBLIC SPACES.
>> DO WE WANT TO TIE
DOWN EVERYBODY'S
FREEDOM BECAUSE WE
HAVE A NUT AND PIECE
OF GARBAGE LIKE THIS
THING?
I DON'T THINK SO.
>> Reporter: BUT
HOTELS AND CITIES CAN
DO MORE.
>> POSSIBLY PUT
SENSORS IN THE
WINDOWS.
THAT WAY WINDOWS, ONCE
IT'S BROKEN OUT, YOU
OBVIOUSLY KNOW THERE'S
AN EVENT GOING ON.
>> Reporter: GUESTS
CAN BE MORE VIGILANT,
TOO.
>> EVERYBODY HAS A
ROLE IN SECURITY.
EVERYBODY KNOWS THE
SAYING, SEE SOMETHING,
SAY SOMETHING.
YOU CAN GO TO A VALET
ATTENDANT, YOU CAN GO
TO THE FRONT DESK.
THEY ALL HAVE A DIRECT
LINE TO SECURITY.
>> Reporter: NEW
EFFORTS TO MAKE SURE
WHAT HAPPENS IN VEGAS
IS SAFE.
JO LING KENT, NBC
NEWS, LAS VEGAS.
>>> COMING UP, THE NEW
TROPICAL THREAT EYEING
THE U.S. THAT COULD
DEVELOP INTO A
HURRICANE.
AL ROKER IS TRACKING
THE DANGER.
IS
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>>> BACK NOW FROM LAS
VEGAS, WE'LL HAVE MORE
FROM HERE IN A MOMENT,
BUT THERE IS A
GATHERING STORM WE
NEED TO TELL YOU
ABOUT, A NEW TROPICAL
THREAT TAKING AIM AT
THE GULF COAST
POTENTIALLY AS A
HURRICANE.
AL ROKER JOINS US WITH
THE FORECAST.
AL, WHERE'S THIS ONE
GOING?
>> WELL, AS YOU SAY,
LESTER, WE'RE LOOKING
AT THE GULF AND
PROBABLY VERY CLOSE TO
THE FLORIDA PENINSULA.
RIGHT NOW, IT'S A
TROPICAL DEPRESSION 55
MILES WEST OF THE SAN
ANDRES ISLAND.
WE LOOK AT THIS
NOW SATURDAY MORNING.
YOU'VE GOT THE
AMERICAN MODEL, THE
EUROPEAN MODEL AND THE
NATIONAL HURRICANE
CENTER TRACK, AND IT
BRINGS IT SATURDAY
RIGHT MAKING ITS WAY
AS A CATEGORY 1 STORM
INTENSIFYING RAPIDLY,
MAKING ITS WAY TOWARD
THE FLORIDA PENINSULA
BY EARLY SUNDAY
MORNING.
THE EURO A LITTLE
SLOWER.
THE AMERICAN MODEL OFF
TO THE WEST.
WE'LL JUST, LESTER,
HAVE TO WAIT AND SEE,
BUT WE ARE LOOKING AT
WHAT COULD BE
POTENTIALLY A CATEGORY
1 STORM MAKING
LANDFALL SUNDAY
MORNING EARLY
AFTERNOON.
>> THIS BUSY STORM
SEASON CONTINUES, AL,
THANK YOU.
>>> AS WE MONITOR THAT
THREAT, MILLIONS ARE
STILL REELING FROM
HURRICANES HARVEY,
IRMA AND MARIA.
AND THAT'S WHY ALL
FIVE LIVING FORMER
PRESIDENTS ARE TEAMING
UP TO HEADLINE A
CONCERT BENEFITING
RECOVERY EFFORTS.
THE DEEP FROM THE
HEART CONCERT WILL BE
HELD IN TEXAS OCTOBER
21st.
>>> UP NEXT TONIGHT,
NEVER OFF DUTY.
FIRST RESPONDERS IN
THE CROWD WHO JUMPED
INTO ACTION WHEN
BULLETS STARTED FLYING
HERE IN VEGAS.
A NEW TIMELINE OF THE LAS VEGAS
MASSACRE...
IN JUST THE PAST HOUR -
INVESTIGATORS TOOK US MINUTE BY
MINUTE INTO THE SHOOTING ...
PLUS: LAPTOPS SNATCHED FROM
CUSTOMERS. WHAT POLICE ARE DOING
AFTER SEVERAL BOLD THEFTS AT
LOCAL COFFEE SHOPS.
NEXT.
>>> FINALLY, WE CAN
NEVER SAY ENOUGH ABOUT
THE BRAVE FIRST
RESPONDERS WHO RISKED
THEIR LIVES TO SAVE
OTHERS IN THE TRAGEDY
HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
MANY WERE OFF DUTY AND
HAD COME FROM ALL OVER
TO ENJOY SOME GOOD
MUSIC WHEN SUDDENLY
THE SHOOTING BEGAN.
OUR JOE FRYER HAS
MORE.
>> Reporter: THEY
WEREN'T WEARING
UNIFORMS, BUT THAT
MASSIVE COUNTRY MUSIC
CROWD WAS FILLED WITH
POLICE OFFICERS,
FIREFIGHTERS AND
PARAMEDICS.
OFF DUTY IS HOW WE
DESCRIBE THEM, BUT
THIS MOMENT PROVED
THEY'RE NEVER TRULY
OFF.
>> I STARTED CRAWLING
TOWARDS PEOPLE WHO
WERE WOUNDED.
>> Reporter: TRAVIS
PHIPPEN, WAS AT THE
CONCERT WITH HIS
FATHER JOHN.
BOTH JUMPED INTO
ACTION.
>> HE WAS COVERING
THIS GIRL, AND HE GOT
SHOT.
I GOT OVER THERE AS
FAST AS I COULD, AND I
PUT MY ARM AROUND HIM.
AND THAT'S WHEN I GOT
SHOT.
>> Reporter: TRAVIS
SURVIVED.
HIS DAD DID NOT.
>> HE WANTED EVERYBODY
TO KNOW HOW MUCH HE
LOVED THEM, AND HE
WANTED ME TO TELL
THEM.
THAT WAS THE LAST
THING HE SAID TO ME.
>> Reporter: JONATHAN
SMITH WAS ALSO SHOT,
HIT IN THE NECK.
>> I STARTED LOOKING
AROUND LIKE I REALLY
DON'T WANT TO DIE.
I DON'T WANT TO DIE.
>> Reporter: THAT'S
WHEN TOM McGRAPH
APPEARED, ONE OF ABOUT
18 OFF-DUTY SAN DIEGO
POLICE OFFICERS AT THE
FESTIVAL.
>> I REMEMBER JUST
HOLDING HIS HAND
TELLING HIM THAT HE
JUST NEEDED TO FIGHT.
HE MADE IT THIS FAR.
>> Reporter: DOZENS OF
OFF-DUTY FIREFIGHTERS
FROM THE VEGAS AREA
WERE ALSO ON THE SCENE
INCLUDING JESSE GOMEZ
WHO GOT HIS FAMILY TO
SAFETY, THEN TOLD HIS
WIFE HE WAS GOING BACK
TO HELP.
>> IT'S PROBABLY ONE
OF THE HARDEST
DECISIONS I'VE EVER
MADE, BUT SHE KNEW I
HAD TO GO.
>> Reporter: WHEN
TRAGEDY HIT, THE PLACE
KNOWN AS SIN CITY HAD
NO SHORTAGE OF ANGELS.
JOE FRYER, NBC NEWS,
LAS VEGAS.
>>> AND THAT IS
"NIGHTLY NEWS" FOR
THIS WEDNESDAY NIGHT
FROM LAS VEGAS.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HERE IN LAS
VEGAS CONSOLING THE SURVIVORS
AND THE NATION.
>> WE'LL OVERCOME TOGETHER AS
AMERICANS.
>> WHILE AMERICA HEALS.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF I WOULD BE
HERE TODAY.
>> THE FBI QUESTIONS THE
GIRLFRIEND OF THE GUNMAN
SEARCHING FOR A MOTIVE.
>>> THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US.
CONTINUING TO ANCHOR OR COVERAGE
FROM THE CRIME SCENE.
>> WE'RE HERE IN OUR NBC BAY
AREA STUDIO.
INVESTIGATORS RELEASED NEW
INFORMATION INCLUDING WHAT IS
THE OFFICIAL TIMELINE OF EVENTS.
THIS IS WHAT WE HAVE LEARNED.
IT STARTED AT EXACTLY 10:05 WHEN
THE FIRST SHOTS FIRED.
SEVEN MINUTES LATER THE FIRST
OFFICERS ARRIVED ON THE SCENE.
AT 10:15, THE LAST SHOT HEARD
FROM THE GUNMAN.
TWO MINUTES LATER OFFICERS
REACHED THE 32nd FLOOR.
THEY SEARCHED ROOMS FOR VICTIMS
AND CLEARED THE FLOOR.
AT 11:20, OFFICERS ENTERED THE
ROOM TO FIND PADDOCK DEAD FROM A
SELF-INFLICTED GUNSHOT WOUND.
>> WITHIN THE PAST 60 MINUTES
PRESIDENT TRUMP LANDED AT JOINT
BASE.
HE SPENT TIME TOURING A
HOSPITAL.
>> WE HAVE A TEAM OF REPORT ERTS
TO BRING YOU THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: GOOD EVENING.
SO DIFFICULT AS WE GET ALL THIS
NEW INFORMATION ABOUT THE