>> Reporter: STEPS AWAY FROM
THEIR ULTIMATE GOAL, THE
UNTHINKABLE.
MARATHON RUNNERS AND SPECTATORS
VIOLENTLY INJURED.
THE TWO EXPLOSIONS
GOING OFF WITHIN SECONDS OF EACH
OTHER AT BOSTON'S COPLEY SQUARE.
>> AT FIRST IT SOUNDED LIKE A
CANNON BLAST.
IT FELT SO STRONG IT ALMOST BLEW
MY HAT OFF.
EVERYBODY STARTED RUNNING THE
OTHER WAY.
THERE WERE PEOPLE RUNNING OVER
TOWARDS THEM TO HELP THE
INJURED.
THERE WERE REALLY BAD, BAD
INJURIES.
SOME PEOPLE WERE VERY, VERY
BADLY HURT.
>> Reporter: THE CLOCK AT THE
FINISH LINE READ 4:09:43 WHEN
THE FIRST EXPLOSION WENT OFF ON
BOYLSTON STREET.
THE SECOND A BLOCK AWAY.
A PLACE OF CELEBRATION INSTANTLY
TRANSFORMED INTO A SCENE OF
CHAOS.
>> EVERYTHING WAS NORMAL.
EVERYONE WAS RELAXED AND HAPPY.
THEN THE EXPLOSION RIGHT NEXT TO
THE FINISH LINE.
AND THEN WITHIN ANOTHER MAYBE 30
SECONDS, ANOTHER EXPLOSION.
AND THEN PANDEMONIUM STRUCK.
>> Reporter: NOW THERE WAS A
RACE OF A DIFFERENT KIND -- TO
RESCUE PEOPLE AND SAVE THEM.
>> I WAS CARRYING SOMEBODY WHO
LOST BOTH OF THEIR LEGS IN THE
EXPLOSION.
IT WAS A LOT OF THEM WITH LOST
LIMBS.
CATASTROPHIC.
>> IT WAS LOUD.
IT WAS REALLY, REALLY LOUD.
THEN CHAOS EVERYWHERE.
>> Reporter: THE SMOKE COULD BE
SEEN FROM ACROSS THE CHARLES
RIVER.
BOSTON POLICE CALLED IN ALL OFF
DUTY OFFICERS TO HELP.
AMBULANCES TOOK 19 VICTIMS
TO MASSACHUSETTS GENERAL
HOSPITAL.
>> THIS IS LIKE A BOMB EXPLOSION
THAT WE HEAR B ABOUT ABOUT ON T
IN BAGHDAD OR ISRAEL OR
SOME OTHER TRAGIC PLACE IN THE
WORLD.
>> IT WAS CARNAGE.
I SAW A MAN WHO LOST PART OF HIS
LEG.
AND ALL OF THE FOLKS FROM THE
MARATHON WERE TREATING THE
RUNNERS AND HAD TO BE CALLED
INTO ACTION.
>> Reporter: 27,000 RUNNERS
FROM 96 COUNTRIES SIGNED UP FOR
THE 26.2-MILE RACE.
THOSE STILL ON THE COURSE WERE
DIVERTED AWAY FROM THE FINISH
LINE.
AUTHORITIES WOULD NOT SPECULATE
ON WHETHER IT WAS TERRORISM.
>> WE ARE NOT BEING DEFINITIVE
ON THIS RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN REACH YOUR OWN
CONCLUSIONS BASED UPON WHAT
HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: THE RACE FAMOUS FOR
HEARTBREAK HILL TODAY THE SITE
OF JUST HEARTBREAK.
TONIGHT EVERY POLICE AGENCY IN
THE STATE OF MASSACHUSETTS IS
SENDING HELP TO BOSTON AS IS THE
FEDERAL GOVERNMENT.
BOSTONIANS ARE TOLD TO STAY
INDOORS.
IF THEY HAVE TO GO OUT TO AVOID
LARGE CROWDS.
WHILE AUTHORITIES TRY TO FIGURE
OUT WHO BROUGHT TO SUCH A
VIOLENT DEADLY END THE DAY THAT
PEOPLE IN BOSTON, BRIAN, HAVE
ALWAYS CALLED THE VERY BEST DAY.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THANK YOU VERY MUCH FOR THAT.
LET'S GO TO KATY TUR WHO MADE
HER WAY UP THERE.
AS I UNDERSTAND IT THERE ARE 15
BLOCKS THAT ARE VIRTUALLY
FROZEN.
PEOPLE HAVE BEEN TOLD TO
SHELTER IN PLACE AND ONCE THEY
GO OUT, AVOID CROWDS WHICH IS
TRICKY ON THIS DAY WHICH IS A
HOLIDAY EVERY YEAR.
>> Reporter: IT'S PRETTY TRICKY
IN THIS AREA, BRIAN.
THIS IS THE BACK BAY OF BOSTON.
IT IS A POPULAR AREA.
IT IS A BUSY AREA ON A NORMAL
DAY.
IT IS CHAOTIC HERE DURING THE
MARATHON IN A GOOD WAY.
IT'S CELEBRATORY.
THE BARS ARE OPEN.
PEOPLE ARE OUT.
RIGHT NOW THERE ARE PEOPLE HERE.
THEY WANT TO SEE WHAT'S GOING
ON.
I GUESS THEY ARE TRYING NOT TO
CONGREGATE.
FOR THE MOST PART IT'S QUIET FOR
THIS AREA.
AFTER THE EXPLOSION THERE WERE
STREAMS OF PEOPLE WALKING THE
STREETS.
THE SUBWAYS WERE SHUT DOWN AND
BECAUSE OF THAT, PEOPLE HAD TO
WALK FOR MILES IN SOME CASES TO
THEIR DESTINATION.
IN FACT, WE ARE TWO BLOCKS FROM
THE FINISH LINE.
TWO BLOCKS FROM WHERE THE
EXPLOSIONS HAPPENED.
WE SAW A WOMAN RIGHT OVER HERE,
WITNESSES SAW HER STUMBLING TO
THIS BLOCK WITH SHRAPNEL WOUNDS.
NBC HAS CONFIRMED SHRAPNEL WAS
PART OF THEEGS -- THESE
EXPLOSIONS.
THAT'S WHY THERE WERE LOWER LIMB
INJURIES.
PEOPLE REPORTED SEEING
TOURNIQUETS APPLIED ON THE
RACEWAY.
BACK BAY IS NORMALLY A BUSY
AREA.
THE STREETS ARE CLOSED RIGHT
NOW.
THERE ARE A NUMBER OF
ROADBLOCKS THROUGHOUT THE AREA.
THERE WAS A GROUND STOP AT LOGAN
AIRPORT.
WE HAD TO CIRCLE OVER PROVIDENCE
FOR QUITE A WHILE BEFORE THEY
ALLOWED US TO LAND.
AS YOU WOULD IMAGINE, A VERY
HEAVY POLICE PRESENCE HERE.
THE NATIONAL GUARD IS HERE AND
PEOPLE ARE ON ALERT.
THEY WANT TO KNOW WHAT'S GOING
ON.
THE POLICE COMMISSIONER ASKED
EVERYBODY TO STAY INSIDE,
EVERYBODY TO GO HOME IF THEY
CAN.
FROM WHAT YOU CAN TELL ALTHOUGH
THERE ARE PEOPLE OUT HERE, MOST
OF THEM HAVE HEEDED THAT ORDER,
AT LEAST AROUND HERE.
BRIAN?
>> WE CAN SEE LOOKING AT TAPE OF
THE FINISH LINE THE DIGITAL
SEEMS TO SAY THIS WAS THE 4:09,
FOUR HOUR, NINE MINUTE FINISHING
MARK.
IF YOU ARE CROSSING THE FINISH
LINE AT THAT POINT IN THIS RACE
YOU HAVE DONE VERY WELL.
TO FINISH AT ALL YOU HAVE DONE
VERY WELL.
BUT PEOPLE THOUGHT, AND YOU
CAN'T BLAME THEM, THAT THIS WAS
SOME KIND OF CANNON, A PLANNED
THING.
I HAD ONE EYEWITNESS DESCRIBE IT
IN TERMS OF WORLD TRADE.
THAT ONCE THE SECOND BUILDING
WAS HIT THAT DAY WE KNEW IT WAS
SOMETHING DIFFERENT.
WELL ONCE THE SECONDARY
EXPLOSION WENT OFF, THEY KNEW IT
WAS NOT AN ACCIDENT OF THE
CONSTRUCTION OF THE CITY LIKE A
GAS MAIN.
>> Reporter: CERTAINLY WHEN
YOU'RE AT A MARATHON, ESPECIALLY
IN BOSTON WHERE THEY HAVEN'T HAD
ISSUES LIKE THEY HAVE HAD IN NEW
YORK, NOBODY WAS EXPECTING
SOMETHING LIKE THIS TO HAPPEN.
INITIALLY NOBODY THOUGHT -- THEY
WEREN'T SURE IF IT WAS EVEN AN
ACCIDENT, A GAS MAIN BREAK.
PEOPLE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT WAS
GOING ON.
WHEN THE SECOND EXPLOSION
HAPPENED 15 SECONDS LATER PEOPLE
STARTED TO BELIEVE THERE WAS
SOMETHING FISHY, SOMETHING BAD.
THAT'S WHEN PEOPLE STARTED TO
GET SCARED, RUN AWAY.
A BIT OF A CHAOTIC SCENE OUT
HERE.
BRIAN?
>> KATY TUR ON THE STREETS OF
BOSTON TONIGHT.
FOR A 15-BLOCK AREA PEOPLE
AREN'T ALLOWED.
WE DON'T KNOW WHEN PEOPLE WILL
BE ALLOWED BACK IN.
>>> TO WASHINGTON WE GO.
OUR JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS HAS BEEN WORKING THIS
STORY ALL DAY.
PETE, WHAT CAN YOU TELL US
TONIGHT?
>> TONIGHT AUTHORITIES CONFIRM
THAT THERE WERE TWO BOMBS.
WE KNOW THAT MUCH.
BUT IT'S UNCLEAR HOW MANY OTHERS
WERE PLANTED.
THEY SAY THERE WERE OTHER
SUSPICIOUS PACKAGES.
AND THE WORD, OF COURSE, OF
ANOTHER BOMB ELSEWHERE PLACED AT
THE JFK LIBRARY IS APPARENTLY
TURNING OUT NOT TO BE TRUE.
AT LEAST FIVE OTHER PACKAGES
HAVE BEEN FOUND ON THE STREET,
HAVE BEEN DEEMED SUSPICIOUS AND
ARE BEING DESTROYED.
BUT THERE IS NO FIRM
CONFIRMATION OF WHETHER THEY
WERE ACTUALLY EXPLOSIVE DEVICES
ALTHOUGH SOME OFFICIALS TONIGHT
SAY THERE IS REASON TO THINK
THAT SOME OF THEM WERE.
WE ARE TOLD, BY THE WAY, THAT
ONE OF THE TWO VICTIMS KILLED IN
THE EXPLOSION WAS 8 YEARS OLD.
BOSTON POLICE SAY THERE WAS NO
SPECIFIC INTELLIGENCE WARNING OF
ANY KIND OF ATTACK.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS TONIGHT SAY
THERE IS NO REASON TO THINK THAT
THIS IS PART OF ANY LARGER
THREAT.
AT THIS POINT THEY BELIEVE IT IS
CONFINED TO BOSTON.
BUT A MEETING TONIGHT WILL
DECIDE WHETHER ANY KIND OF
NATIONAL ALERT WILL BE SENT OUT.
THERE IS NO SUSPECT IN CUSTODY,
AUTHORITIES SAY.
BUT SOME PEOPLE ARE BEING
QUESTIONED INCLUDING SOME WITH
INJURIES WHO WERE TAKEN TO
BOSTON HOSPITALS.
ONE OF THOSE, A PERSON IN WHOM
THERE IS SOME INTEREST IS A
YOUNG PERSON WHO WAS HERE ON A
STUDENT VISA.
BRIAN?
>> PETE WILLIAMS IN OUR
WASHINGTON NEWSROOM.
WE'LL LOOK FOR FURTHER DETAILS
FROM THERE.
PETE, THANKS.
>>> MICHAEL LEITER IS OUR
NATIONAL SECURITY ANALYST AT NBC
NEWS, FORMER DIRECTOR OF THE
NATIONAL COUNTERTERRORISM CENTER
IN WASHINGTON.
MICHAEL, TWO THINGS.
OVERSEAS VETERANS OF THE WARS
THE PAST TEN YEARS AND THOSE OF
US WHO SPENT TIME THERE, NUMBER
ONE, THE PRIMARY EXPLOSION, THEN
THE SECONDARY EXPLOSION AS
PEOPLE ARE RUNNING TO THE FIRST.
AND NUMBER TWO, THE NATURE OF
THESE INJURIES.
AN EXPLOSIVE DEVICE APPARENTLY
WITH ADDED SHRAPNEL.
THAT HAUNTS EVERYBODY
INVOLVED.
>> YES, BRIAN.
THE IDEA OF USING TWO EXPLOSIVE
DEVICES, THE FIRST CHARGE WHICH
ATTRACTS TO SOME EXTENT THE
FIRST RESPONDERS -- POLICE,
FIRE, MEDICAL -- AND THEN HAVE A
SECOND CHARGE GO OFF THAT'S
TARGETING THOSE RESPONDERS
POTENTIALLY IS THE SIGN OF A
MORE SOPHISTICATED ATTACK.
AS YOU NOTED, THE SHRAPNEL, THE
IDEA THERE COULD HAVE BEEN BALL
BEARINGS OR SOMETHING ELSE IN
THESE EXPLOSIVES SPECIFICALLY
TRYING TO KILL OR MAIM, NOT JUST
TRYING TO HAVE A SMALL EXPLOSION
AND GET SOME ATTRACTION.
THE SIGN OF A TERRORIST
ORGANIZATION THAT'S TRYING TO
KILL PEOPLE.
>> HERE WE ARE IN THE POST 9/11
ERA.
WHILE IT'S FAMILIAR NOW TO US IN
A KIND OF HIDEOUS WAY, IT ALSO
ISN'T.
WE SHOULD EMPHASIZE THAT WHILE
PEOPLE, ESPECIALLY IN BIG CITIES
AND ESPECIALLY ON THE EAST
COAST, ARE GOING TO SEE
PRECAUTIONS AT TRAIN STATIONS
AND AIRPORTS AND PERHAPS BIG
OBVIOUS MOVEMENT OF LAW
ENFORCEMENT, THERE IS NO REASON
TO FEAR THAT THIS IS ANY, AT
THIS HOUR, PART OF ANY WIDER
PLAN.
CORRECT?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
PEOPLE SHOULD VIEW THE
PRECAUTIONS IN WASHINGTON, NEW
YORK, SAN FRANCISCO, LOS ANGELES
MERELY AS PRECAUTIONS.
THIS IS EXACTLY WHAT THE FEDERAL
GOVERNMENT AND STATES AND CITIES
PREPARE FOR IN THE EVENT OF AN
ATTACK.
HEIGHTENING BASIC PREPAREDNESS,
PUTTING MORE POLICE ON THE
SCENE.
THAT IS NOT BECAUSE THEY KNOW
SOMETHING SPECIFIC.
IT IS BECAUSE EVERYONE WANTS TO
MAKE SURE THAT THERE IS A SHOW
OF FORCE AND SHOULD SOMETHING
ELSE ARISE THAT THEY ARE IN A
GOOD POSITION TO RESPOND.
BUT IT IS NOT THE SIGN OF A
SPECIFIC THREAT NECESSARILY.
>> MICHAEL LEITER IN OUR
WASHINGTON BUREAU.
MICHAEL, THANK YOU AS ALWAYS.
>>> ACROSS TOWN WE GO TO THE
WHITE HOUSE.
CHUCK TODD WAS STANDING IN THE
BRIEFING ROOM WHEN THE PRESIDENT
ENTERED AT ABOUT 6:10 TONIGHT TO
GIVE HIS REMARKS ON WHAT THE
WHITE HOUSE WAS SAYING SO FAR.
CHUCK?
>> I CAN TELL YOU THIS.
ONE OF THE THINGS THE PRESIDENT
DID NOT SAY IS HE DID NOT CALL
THIS TERRORISM.
I CAN TELL YOU FROM TALKING TO
SOURCES THIS WAS DISCUSSED AND
THE DECISION WAS MADE NOT TO
HAVE THE PRESIDENT USE THAT
SPECIFIC WORD.
A NATIONAL SECURITY OFFICIAL
E-MAILS AND SAYS THIS.
ANY EVENT WITH MULTIPLE
EXPLOSIVE DEVICES AS THIS
APPEARS TO BE IS CLEARLY AN ACT
OF TERROR AND WILL BE APPROACHED
AS AN ACT OF TERROR.
HOWEVER WE DO NOT KNOW WHO
CARRIED OUT THIS ATTACK.
A THOROUGH INVESTIGATION WILL
DETERMINE WHETHER IT WAS PLANNED
AND CARRIED OUT BY A TERRORIST
GROUP, FOREIGN OR DOMESTIC.
THEY ARE CAREFUL WITH THEIR
LANGUAGE.
WE KNOW THE PRESIDENT HAS BEEN
BRIEFED ALL DAY FROM THE FBI
DIRECTOR, HOMELAND SECURITY
DIRECTOR, CHIEF TERRORISM
ADVISER.
HE HIMSELF HAS BEEN GIVING
BRIEFINGS TO THE LEADERSHIP IN
CONGRESS.
BUT I CAN TELL YOU IN TALKING TO
OFFICIALS AROUND HERE, BRIAN,
THERE IS A LITTLE BIT OF
FRUSTRATION OF HOW LITTLE THEY
DO KNOW AT THIS POINT IN TIME
WHICH IS WHY THE PRESIDENT WAS
CLEARLY BEING VERY CAREFUL WITH
THE LANGUAGE HE CHOSE TO USE.
>> CHUCK TODD AT THE WHITE
HOUSE, THANKS.
WE'LL TAKE A QUICK BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK, WE'LL TALK
ABOUT THE NATION'S NEED TO
SECURE LARGE PUBLIC EVENTS AND
HOW THAT JOB MIGHT HAVE GOTTEN
TOUGHER TODAY.
JOB MIGHT HAVE G
See life in the best light.
Outdoors, or in.
Transitions® lenses
automatically filter
just the right amount of light.
So you see everything
the way it's meant to be seen.
Maybe even a little better.
Visit your Eyecare
professional today
to ask about
our newest lenses,
Transitions Vantage and
Transitions XTRActive lenses.
Experience life well lit.
Ask which Transitions
adaptive lens is best for you.
CONSTIPATED?
YEAH.
MM.
SOME LAXATIVES LIKE Dulcolax
CAN CAUSE CRAMPS.
BUT Phillips' Caplets
DON'T.
THEY HAVE MAGNESIUM.
FOR EFFECTIVE RELIEF
OF OCCASIONAL CONSTIPATION.
THANKS.
[ Phillips' Lady ]
LIVE THE REGULAR LIFE.
Phillips'.
I'M ON EXPERT ON SOFTBALL.
AND TEA PARTIES.
I'LL HAVE
MORE AWKWARD CONVERSATIONS
THAN I'M EQUIPPED FOR,
BECAUSE I'M RAISING TWO GIRLS
ON MY OWN.
I'LL WORRY ABOUT THE ECONOMY
MORE THAN A FEW TIMES
BEFORE THEY'RE GROWN.
BUT IT'S FOR THEM,
SO I'VE FOUND A WAY.
WHO MATTERS MOST TO YOU
SAYS THE MOST ABOUT YOU.
AT MassMutual WE'RE OWNED
BY OUR POLICYOWNERS,
AND THEY MATTER MOST TO US.
READY TO PLAN FOR YOUR FUTURE?
WE'LL HELP YOU GET THERE.
[ Male Announcer ]
YOU'VE REACHED THE AGE
WHERE YOU DON'T BACK DOWN
FROM A CHALLENGE.
THIS IS THE AGE OF KNOWING
HOW TO MAKE THINGS HAPPEN.
SO, WHY LET
ERECTILE DYSFUNCTION
GET IN YOUR WAY?
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT VIAGRA.
20 MILLION MEN ALREADY HAVE.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR IF YOUR HEART
IS HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE VIAGRA IF YOU TAKE
NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN;
IT MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE DROP
IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
HEADACHE, FLUSHING,
UPSET STOMACH,
AND ABNORMAL VISION.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
SEEK IMMEDIATE MEDICAL HELP
FOR AN ERECTION
LASTING MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
STOP TAKING VIAGRA
AND CALL YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU EXPERIENCE
A SUDDEN DECREASE OR LOSS
IN VISION OR HEARING.
THIS IS THE AGE
OF TAKING ACTION.
VIAGRA.
TALK TO YOUR DOCTOR.
>>> WE ARE BACK TONIGHT.
THIS IS THE SCENE AS IT
HAPPENED.
2:50 P.M. THIS AFTERNOON IN
BOSTON DURING THE MARATHON.
THERE IS THE EXPLOSION.
ONE RUNNER HIT BY SHRAPNEL GOES
DOWN.
THIS IS AN IMPORTANT POINT HERE.
BETWEEN THE POINT OF THE
EXPLOSION AND THE CROWD POLICE,
BOSTON EMS, RACE VOLUNTEERS WERE
CAUGHT UP IN IT.
THEY WERE AMONG THE TARGETS.
SO HAVING SEEN THIS, HAVING
WITNESSED THIS, THE QUESTION
BECOMES HOW CAN WE EVER KEEP OUR
PUBLIC EVENTS SAFE IF SOMEONE
WAS ALLOWED TO GET TWO DEVICES
THIS CLOSE TO THIS CLASSIC A DAY
IN BOSTON, MASSACHUSETTS?
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO HAS BEEN
LOOKING AT THIS CONUNDRUM FOR
SECURITY PERSONNEL ALL DAY.
TOM, EVENING.
>> Reporter: HI, BRIAN.
WE TALK ABOUT HOW SECURITY
CHANGED AFTER 9/11.
AND IT DID.
BUT SECURITY EXPERTS HAVE BEEN
DEALING WITH TERRORIST THREATS
AT BIG GATHERINGS SINCE THE
MUNICH GAMES IN 1972.
TRYING TO ENSURE EVERYONE'S
SAFETY IS A HERCULEAN CHALLENGE.
FOR ANY POLICE AGENCY PLANNING
FOR BIG CROWDS MEANS MONTHS OF
NIGHTMARES.
SECURES AND STEALING A COURSE
LIKE THE BOSTON MARATHON WITH
20,000 RUNNERS AND HALF A
MILLION SPECTATORS IS ALMOST AN
IMPOSSIBLE CHALLENGE.
BILL BRATTON WAS THE BOSTON
POLICE COMMISSIONER BEFORE
LEADING THE NYPD AND THE LAPD.
>> IT IS EXTRAORDINARILY
DIFFICULT, AS YOU MIGHT IMAGINE,
THAT 26-MILE ROUTE.
DOUBLE IT, 52 THE MILES BECAUSE
YOU HAVE TWO SIDES OF THE
STREET.
MOST OF THE SECURITY WOULD BE
FOCUSED ON THE FINISH LINE AREA
WHERE THE ACTUAL BOMBING
OCCURRED.
>> Reporter: ATLANTA, 1996.
A BACKPACK HOLDING PIPE BOMBS
PACKED WITH NAILS EXPLODED IN
OLYMPIC PARK.
TWO DIED.
MORE THAN A HUNDRED WOUNDED.
IT WASN'T UNTIL 2003 THAT POLICE
TRACKED DOWN DOMESTIC TERRORIST
ERIC ROBERT RUDOLPH.
>> GET BACK, PLEASE!
>> Reporter: LONDON, 2005.
A SERIES OF COORDINATED SUICIDE
ATTACKS ON THE SUBWAY AND BUS
SYSTEM LEFT 52 PEOPLE DEAD, 700
INJURED.
THE ATTACKERS USED HOME MADE
EXPLOSIVES PACKED INTO
BACKPACKS.
THOSE ATTACKS ON FINDS OF THE
SECRET SERVICE WHEN PRESIDENT
OBAMA WAS SWORN IN FOR THE FIRST
TIME IN 2009.
DAN BONNGENO WAS THE LEAD SECRET
SERVICE AGENT AS PEOPLE PACKED
THE NATIONAL MALL IN DOWNTOWN
D.C.
A POTENTIAL TERRORIST COULD HAVE
BEEN HIDING IN PLAIN SIGHT.
>> YOU CAN'T GUARANTEE ANYTHING.
YOU REDUCE THE PROBABILITY TO
HOPEFULLY SOMETHING MINUSCULE SO
IF SOMETHING HAPPENS YOUR
RESPONSE IS ENOUGH TO KEEP
CASUALTIES TO A MINIMUM N TIMES
SQUARE 2010.
A CAR BOMB FAILED TO EXPLODE AND
WAS DISARMED BEFORE IT COULD
HURT ANYONE.
TWO DAYS LATER A
PAKISTANI-AMERICAN WAS CAUGHT
TRYING TO BOARD A FLIGHT TO THE
MIDDLE EAST.
BIG SPORTING EVENTS LIKE THE
BOSTON MARATHON HAD BEEN VIEWED
AS INVITING TARGETS SINCE 9/11.
THE MARINE CORPS MARATHON
ATTRACTS 30,000 RUNNERS EACH
YEAR.
SUPER BOWL ORGANIZE OHHERS ARE
OFTEN CRITICIZED FOR TOO MUCH
SECURITY AT THE BIG GAME.
AND SECURING EVERY POSSIBLE
PUBLIC EVENT THAT COULD INVITE
AN ATTACK IS RESPOND REASONABLE.
MICHAELLE LEITER WAS THE COUNTER
TERRORISM DIRECTOR UNDER
PRESIDENT GEORGE W. BUSH.
>> YOU CAN'T PROTECT ALL OF THE
PEOPLE AT ALL OF THE LARGE
SPORTING EVENTS OR ANY PUBLIC
GATHERING.
THAT'S THE ADVANTAGE TERRORISTS
HAVE.
THEY CAN LOOK FOR THE SOFTEST,
LEAST DEFENDED AREA.
>> IT IS NOT UNUSUAL TO SEE
TRASH BINS REMOVED, MAILBOXES
REMOVED, EVEN THE MANHOLE COVERS
SCREWED DOWN.
THAT'S THE KIND OF EXTRAORDINARY
SECURITY YOU GET IN A
PRESIDENTIAL ZONE.
PUTTING IN PLACE THAT KIND OF
SECURITY AT AN OUTDOOR MARATHON,
BRIAN, WOULD BE A DIFFERENT
MATTER.
>> AGAIN, HOW IRONIC THIS
HAPPENED AT WHAT WAS PERHAPS THE
MOST SECURE ZONE IN ALL OF
BOSTON ALONG THOSE 26 MILES
TODAY.
TOM COSTELLO FROM WASHINGTON
TONIGHT.
TOM, THANKS.
>>> WE'LL TAKE ANOTHER BREAK.
WHEN WE COME BACK, AN EYEWITNESS
TO TODAY'S BOMBING.
[ Male Announcer ]
THIS IS KEVIN.
TO PROVE TO YOU THAT Aleve
IS THE BETTER CHOICE FOR HIM,
HE'S AGREED TO GIVE IT UP.
THAT'S TODAY?
[ Male Announcer ]
WE'LL BE WITH HIM ALL DAY
AS HE GOES BACK
TO TAKING TYLENOL.
I WAS OKAY, BUT AFTER LUNCH
MY KNEE STARTED TO HURT AGAIN.
AND NOW I'VE GOT TO
TAKE MORE PILLS.
♪
YUP. ANOTHER PILL STOP.
CAN I GET MY Aleve BACK YET?
♪
FOR MY PAIN, I WANT MY Aleve.
[ Male Announcer ] LOOK FOR THE
EASY-OPEN RED ARTHRITIS CAP.
FROM Capital One...
BORIS EARNS UNLIMITED REWARDS
FOR HIS SMALL BUSINESS.
CAN I GET THE SMITH CONTRACT,
PLEASE?
THANK YOU.
THAT'S
THREE NEW PAPER SHREDDERS.
[ Boris ]
PUT 'EM ON MY Spark Card.
[ Garth ] BORIS' SMALL BUSINESS
EARNS 2% CASH BACK
ON EVERY PURCHASE EVERY DAY.
GREAT BUSINESSES
DESERVE UNLIMITED REWARDS.
READ BACK THE CHICKEN'S
TESTIMONY, PLEASE.
"BUK, BUK, BUKKA!"
[ Male Announcer ]
GET THE Spark Business Card
FROM Capital One
AND EARN UNLIMITED REWARDS.
CHOOSE 2% CASH BACK
OR DOUBLE MILES
ON EVERY PURCHASE EVERY DAY.
TOLD YOU I'D GET HALF.
WHAT'S IN
YOUR WALLET?
YOU KNOW WHO YOU ARE.
YOU CAN PART A CROWD,
WITHOUT SAYING A WORD...
IF YOU HAVE YET TO MASTER
THE QUIET SNEEZE...
YOU STASH TISSUES
LIKE A SQUIRREL STASHES NUTS...
WELL MUDDLERS, MUDDLE NO MORE.
TRY ZYRTEC®. IT GIVES YOU
POWERFUL ALLERGY RELIEF.
AND ZYRTEC® IS DIFFERENT
THAN CLARITIN®
BECAUSE ZYRTEC® STARTS WORKING
AT HOUR ONE
ON THE FIRST DAY YOU TAKE IT.
CLARITIN® DOESN'T START WORKING
UNTIL HOUR THREE.
ZYRTEC®. LOVE THE AIR.
CLARITIN® DOESN'T START WORKING
UNTIL HOUR THREE.
AN INTENSE BURNING SENSATION
I WOKE UP WITH THIS HORRIBLE
RASH ON MY RIGHT SIDE.
LIKE SOMEBODY HAD
SET IT ON FIRE.
AND THE DOCTOR SAID, CINDIE,
YOU HAVE SHINGLES.
HE SAID, YOU HAD CHICKENPOX
WHEN YOU WERE A LITTLE GIRL...
I SAID, YES, I DID.
I DON'T THINK
ANYBODY EVER THINKS
THEY'RE GOING
TO GET SHINGLES.
BUT IT HAPPENED TO ME.
FOR MORE OF THE INSIDE STORY,
VISIT SHINGLESINFO.COM
WHEN I TAKE A PICTURE
OF THIS CHECK,
IT GOES STRAIGHT TO THE BANK.
OH.
OH LOOK THE LION IS OUT!
NO MOMMY NO!
DON'T WORRY HONEY,
IT ONLY WORKS ON CHECKS.
DEPOSIT CHECKS FROM
YOUR SMARTPHONE
WITH CHASE QUICKDEPOSIT.
JUST SNAP A PICTURE,
HIT SEND AND DONE.
TAKE A STEP FORWARD
AND CHASE WHAT MATTERS.
>>> WE ARE BACK TONIGHT THIS DAY
OF THE TWIN BOMBINGS AT THE END
OF THE BOSTON MARATHON.
WE WANT TO TALK NOW TO AN
EYEWITNESS, SOMEONE WE SPOKE TO
EARLIER DURING OUR DEVELOPING
LIVE COVERAGE.
HE WAS VERY CLOSE TO THE SITE OF
THE INITIAL AND THEN THE
SECONDARY BOMB.
TELL US HOW FAR YOU WERE AWAY,
WHAT YOU REMEMBER, WHAT YOU SAW
AND FELT.
>> I WAS ABOUT A HALF BLOCK AWAY
FROM THE SCENE.
INITIALLY I FELT THE FIRST ONE
AND I FELT IT GO THROUGH THINK
LEG INTO MY CHEST.
I WAS SITTING DOWN.
E EVERYONE IN THE ROOM, EVERYONE
OUTSIDE JUST STOPS MOVING AND
INSTANTLY HAD NO IDEA WHAT WAS
HAPPENING UNTIL THAT SECOND BOMB
WENT OFF.
THAT SECOND BOMB YOU FELT JUST
AS MUCH, YOU HEARD JUST AS LOUD
AND EVERYONE INSTANTLY KNEW THAT
IT WAS NOT WHAT WE THOUGHT AND
IT WAS A BOMB.
AT THAT VERY MOMENT I WALKED
OUTSIDE.
I LOOKED DOWN THE STREET AND YOU
COULD SEE SMOKE COMING.
PEOPLE'S FACES INSTANTLY CHANGED
FROM SMILES TO TEARS AND FEAR
AND WERE BASICALLY RUNNING FOR
THEIR LIVES.
YOU COULD LOOK AT ANY DIRECTION
AT ANY MOMENT AT THE
INTERSECTION AND THERE WERE
THOUSANDS AND THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE THAT YOU COULD SEE IN ANY
DIRECTION SHUTTING DOWN THE
STREETS.
>> IF THERE WAS A BLESSING IT
WAS THAT THE MEDICAL TENT WAS
RIGHT THERE AT THE CONCLUSION OF
THE RACE.
YOU HAD MEDICAL PROFESSIONALS
AND A LOT OF BOSTON P.D. ALREADY
ON THE SCENE.
>> YEAH.
I'M STAYING AT THE FAIRMONT AND
THE MEDICAL TENT IS OUTSIDE OUR
FRONT DOOR.
IT WAS ONE OF THE CRAZIEST
SCENES I HAVE SEEN.
EVERYBODY WAS RUSHING.
NO ONE KNEW WHAT TO DO.
EMS WAS RUNNING TOWARD THE
SCENE.
EVERYONE WAS IN FEAR.
>> ALSO THE DEFINITION OF
TERRORISM.
IT'S THE LAST THING YOU EXPECT
AT THE FINISH LINE OF THE BOSTON
MARATHON ON PATRIOTS DAY IN
BOSTON.
SERDAR OZTURK, THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
ANOTHER BREAK AND WE ARE BACK
WITH MORE AFTER THIS.
THE BATTLE OF BATAAN,
1942.
[ all ]
FORT BENNING, GEORGIA, IN 1999.
[ Male Announcer ]
USAA AUTO INSURANCE
IS OFTEN HANDED DOWN FROM
GENERATION TO GENERATION
BECAUSE IT OFFERS
A SUPERIOR LEVEL OF PROTECTION
AND BECAUSE USAA'S COMMITMENT
TO SERVE THE MILITARY,
VETERANS, AND THEIR FAMILIES
IS WITHOUT EQUAL.
BEGIN YOUR LEGACY.
GET AN AUTO-INSURANCE QUOTE.
USAA.
WE KNOW WHAT IT MEANS TO SERVE.
BUT WITH ADVAIR,
I'M BREATHING BETTER.
SO NOW I CAN HELP MAKE THIS
A GREAT BLOCK PARTY.
♪
[ Male Announcer ]
ADVAIR IS CLINICALLY PROVEN
TO HELP SIGNIFICANTLY IMPROVE
LUNG FUNCTION.
UNLIKE MOST COPD MEDICATIONS,
ADVAIR CONTAINS
BOTH AN ANTI-INFLAMMATORY
AND A LONG-ACTING
BRONCHODILATOR
WORKING TOGETHER
TO HELP IMPROVE
YOUR LUNG FUNCTION ALL DAY.
ADVAIR WON'T REPLACE
FAST-ACTING INHALERS
FOR SUDDEN SYMPTOMS
AND SHOULD NOT BE USED
MORE THAN TWICE A DAY.
PEOPLE WITH COPD TAKING ADVAIR
MAY HAVE
A HIGHER CHANCE OF PNEUMONIA.
ADVAIR MAY INCREASE
YOUR RISK OF OSTEOPOROSIS
AND SOME EYE PROBLEMS.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
IF YOU HAVE A HEART CONDITION
OR HIGH BLOOD PRESSURE
BEFORE TAKING ADVAIR.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR
IF INCLUDING ADVAIR COULD HELP
IMPROVE YOUR LUNG FUNCTION.
[ Male Announcer ]
ADVAIR DISKUS
FLUTICASONE PROPIONATE AND
SALMETEROL INHALATION POWDER.
GET YOUR FIRST PRESCRIPTION
FREE
AND SAVE ON REFILLS
AT ADVAIRCOPD.COM.
[ Agent Smith ]
I'VE FOUND SOFTWARE
THAT INTRIGUES ME.
IT APPEARS
IT'S AN AGENT OF GOOD.
GE HAS WIRED
THEIR MEDICAL HARDWARE
WITH INNOVATIVE SOFTWARE
TO BE IN MANY PLACES
AT THE SAME TIME.
USING DATA TO CONNECT PATIENTS
TO SOFTWARE, TO NURSES
TO THE RIGHT PEOPLE
AND MACHINES.
♪
HELPING HOSPITALS
TREAT PEOPLE EVEN BETTER,
WHILE DRAMATICALLY
REDUCING WAITING TIME.
NOW A WAITING ROOM
IS JUST A ROOM.
[ telephone ringing ]
[ static warbles ]
[ beeping ]
RED OR BLUE?
♪
>>> MARATHON DAY, PATRIOTS DAY
IS SUPPOSED TO BE A GREAT DAY
EVERY DAY IN BOSTON.
INSTEAD THIS YEAR IT TURNED INTO
A HORRIBLE DAY.
NBC'S KATY TUR IS ON THE STREETS
OF BOSTON TONIGHT.
WHAT CAN YOU TELL US THERE?
>> Reporter: BRIAN, THE SUN IS
SETTING HERE AND THE RUNNERERS
ARE MAKING THEIR WAY BACK HOME,
BACK TO YOUR HOTELS.
FAMILIES ARE REUNITING WITH
LOVED ONES, TRYING TO SEE IF
EVERYONE IS SAFE.
BEING GLAD SO MANY ARE SAFE
TONIGHT AND TRYING TO GET THEIR
HEAD AROUND JUST WHAT HAPPENED
IN ALL OF THE TRAGEDY THAT
UNFOLDED.
AGAIN, WE ARE IN THE BACK BAY OF
BOSTON.
H THIS IS A VERY POPULAR AREA.
AFTER THE MARATHON RIGHT ABOUT
NOW THIS AREA WOULD BE CROWDED.
IT IS RIGHT NOW PRETTY DEAD.
IT IS VERY FAR FROM NORMAL,
BRIAN.
IT WILL BE VERY FAR FROM NORMAL
FOR QUITE SOME TIME.
>> KATY, THANKS.
THAT'S GOING TO CONCLUDE OUR
REGULAR HALF HOUR OF NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" FOR TONIGHT.
IF YOUR STATION IS CARRYING IT,
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK ON THE AIR
WITH A SPECIAL HOUR-LONG
EDITION, A SECOND HALF HOUR OF
THE BROADCAST.
IF NOT, IT WILL BE AVAILABLE ON
OUR WEBSITE.
AND AN EARLY HEADS-UP, WE ARE
BACK ON THE AIR TONIGHT AT 10:00
P.M. EASTERN, 7:00 ON THE WEST
COAST WITH A PRIMETIME SPECIAL
ON WHAT'S HAPPENED IN BOSTON
TODAY.
-- Captions by VITAC --
www.vitac.com
>> Announcer: TERROR IN BOSTON.
THIS IS NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
BRIAN WILLIAMS.
>> Announcer: TERROR IN BOSTON.
THIS IS NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
CAPTIONS PAID FOR BY
NBC-UNIVERSAL TELEVISION
>>> THAT IS WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE
AT GROUND LEVEL.
THE FINISH LINE AT THE BOSTON
MARATHON.
IT WAS AFTER THE FIRST, THE TOP
TIER OF FINISHERS.
IT WAS AT THE FOUR UR, NINE
MINUTE MARK, EXACTLY 2:50 THIS
AFTERNOON WHEN FIRST ONE
EXPLOSION AND THEN A SECONDARY
EXPLOSION WENT OFF.
PEOPLE COULDN'T IMAGINE WHAT THE
FIRST ONE WAS, BUT WITH THE
SECOND THEY KNEW, THEY SUSPECTED
IT WAS SOME SORT OF ATTACK.
IT APPEARS TONIGHT WE ARE COMING
ON THE AIR YET AGAIN IN THIS
POST 9/11 ERA WITH WORD OF AN
APPARENT TERRORIST ATTACK WITHIN
OUR SHORES.
A TERRIBLE DAY IN BOSTON ON WHAT
IS A HOLIDAY IN THAT CITY.
IT IS PATRIOTS DAY.
THEY MARK THE LEXINGTON AND
CONCORD BATTLES.
THE RED SOX PLAY BASEBALL AND
THEY RUN THE BOSTON MARATHON.
TONIGHT THE DEATH TOLL STANDS AT
TWO.
OVER 100 INJURED.
WE WANT TO GO TO JONATHAN HALL
WHO REPORTS FROM WHGH TV.
WE HAVE BEEN WATCHING THEIR LIVE
COVERAGE AND AIRING IT TO A
NATIONAL AUDIENCE.
JONATHAN, YOU ARE AT BRIG HAM
WOMEN'S HOSPITAL WHERE THEY TOOK
SOME OF THE INJURED, CORRECT?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
BOSTON-AREA HOSPITALS HAVE BEEN
COMPLETELY INUNDATED WITH
PATIENTS.
THEY DRILL FOR THIS.
THEY SAY THEY ARE UP TO THE TASK
AND THEY ARE READY, TREATING
SERIOUSLY INJURED PEOPLE.
THIS KNOWS NO BOUNDS.
IT DIDN'T DISCRIMINATE ON AGE OR
GENDER.
WE UNDERSTAND HERE PATIENTS
RANGED IN AGE FROM 3 TO 62, BOTH
MEN AND WOMEN.
DOZENS PEA BEING TREATED HERE.
WE SAW FBI AGENTS, ATF AGENTS
GOING IN AND OUT.
MASSACHUSETTS STATE POLICE, THE
BOSTON S.W.A.T. TEAM IS GUARDING
THE ENTRANCE OF THE HOSPITAL.
IT IS ON LOCK DOWN.
NOBODY IN, NOBODY OUT UNLESS
THEY HAVE THE PROPER
IDENTIFICATION.
OF COURSE, RELATIVES OF THOSE
INJURED ARE ALLOWED ACCESS TO
THE HOSPITAL.
ONCE AGAIN, A LOT OF PEOPLE HERE
COMING IN, COMING OUT.
WE HAVE SEEN PEOPLE CRYING.
WE HAVE HEARD THE STORIES AS