>> THAT'S HOT LIKE A 25 DEGREE
DIFFERENCE.
>> BIG.
>> NIGHTLY NEWS IS NEXT.
>> SEE YOU AT 6:00.
BYE.
>>> TONIGHT, HAND THEM
OVER.
GROWING BIPARTISAN
CALLS FOR PRESIDENT
TRUMP TO GIVE CONGRESS
THE TAPES, IF HE
SECRETLY RECORDED
COMEY.
AS NEW QUESTIONS ARISE
ABOUT THE TIME LINE
AND WHAT WAS DISCUSSED
AT THAT DINNER.
A MASSIVE CYBER ATTACK
SPREADS, CRIPPLING
COMPANIES AROUND THE
WORLD.
NEW FEARS IN THE U.S.,
IS YOUR FAMIL
PROTECTED.
>>> A DEADLY PLANE
CRASH OUTSIDE NO.
A JET GOES DOWN, MULT
I WILL BUILDINGS AND
CARS IN FLAMES.
>>> THE PARENTS OF A
BEN STATE STUDENT WHO
DIED DURING HAZING
SPEAKING OUT.
SAYING THEIR SON WAS
TREATED LIKE ROADKILL
BY FRAT MEMBERS WHO
WAITED 12 HOURS TO
EQUAL FOR HELP.
>>> HOW MUCH CAFFEINE
IS TOO MUCH FOR KIDS?
A STARTLING NEW
WARNING.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING TO
OUR VIEWERS IN THE
WEST.
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH
MULTIPLE REPORTS
SAYING PRESIDENT TRUMP
DISCLOSED CLOSELY
GUARDED CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION ABOUT ISIS
TO RUSSIA'S FOREIGN
MINISTER DURING A
MEETING LAST WEEK.
POTENTIALLY
JEOPARDIZING A
VALUABLE SOURCE OF
INTEL ABOUT ISIS.
THE WASHINGTON POST
BROKE THE STORY.
THE PRESIDENT WENT OFF
SCRIPT DURING HIS
MEETING WITH THE
RUSSIANS, SHARING
CLASS 1235IFIED DETAILS
ABOUT ISIS
CAPABILITIES THAT ARE
SO CLOSELY HELD THEY
ARE NOT SHARED WITH
EVEN THE CLOSEST
ALLIES.
HALLIE JACKSON HAS THE
DEVELOPING DETAILS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
NEW PUSH BACK FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE ON A
BOMBSHELL WASHINGTON
POST REPORT, ALSO
CONFIRMED BY OTHER
OUTLLTS.
IT SAYS PRESIDENT
TRUMP SHARED HIGHLY
CLASSIFIED INFORMATION
WITH THE RUSSIAN
FOREIGN MINISTER AND
AMBASSADOR IN A
MEETING LAST WEEK,
CITING CURRENT AND
FORMER U.S. OFFICIALS.
IT'S INFORMATION THAT
CAME FROM AN ALLY THAT
PROVIDED IT UNDER AN
INTELLIGENCE SHARING
AGREEMENT.
THE PRESIDENT REVEALED
MORE INFORMATION TO
THE RUSSIAN AMBASSADOR
THAN WE HAVE SHARED
WITH OUR OWN ALLIES.
>> THIS COUNTRY,
WHATEVER IT IS, WILL
HAVE SECOND THOUGHTS
IN THE FUTURE BEFORE
SHARING THREAT
INFORMATION OF THIS
KIND.
>> THE WHITE HOUSE
FLATLEY INSISTING THIS
STORY IS FALSE.
>> AT NO TIME WERE
INTELLIGENCE SOURCES
OR METHODS DISCUSSED.
AND THE PRESIDENT DID
NOT DISCLOSE ANY
MILITARY OPERATIONS
THAT WERE NOT ALREADY
PUBLICLY KNOWN.
TWO OTHER SENIOR
OFFICIALS WHO WERE
PRESENT, INCLUDING THE
SECRETARY OF STATE,
REMEMBER THE MEETING
THE SAME WAY AND HAVE
SAID SO.
THEY'RE ON THE RECORD
ACCOUNTS SHOULD
OUTWEIGH THOSE OF
ANONYMOUS SOURCES.
I WAS IN THE ROOM, IT
DIDN'T HAPPEN.
>> THE DISCUSSION THAT
HE MIGHT HAVE SHARED
HIGHLY CLASSIFIED
INFORMATION
INAPPROPRIATELY WITH
THE RUSSIAN FOREIGN
MINISTER IS DEEPLY
TROUBLING.
>> IT'S DISTURBING AND
LET'S FIND OUT WHAT
THE DETAILS ARE,
WHETHER IT ACTUALLY
HAPPENED OR NOT.
WE JUST HAVE AN
INITIAL REPORT, SO
IT'S VERY DIFFICULT TO
COMMENTS UNTIL WE GET
ALL THE FACTS HERE.
>> I DON'T KNOW IF
IT'S ACCURATE.
IT WOULD BE TROUBLING.
I HAVE NO IDEA.
>> Reporter: IT'S
WORTH NOTING SOME ARE
DENYING SOMETHING THAT
WAS NEVER REPORTED.
THAT THE PRESIDENT
DIDN'T REVEAL SOURCES
AND METHODS, DESPITE
NO INDICATION FROM THE
POST THAT ACTUALLY
OCCURRED.
IT'S UNCLEAR WHETHER
KEY MEMBERS OF
CONGRESS WERE BRIEFED
ON ANY OF THIS PRIOR
TO THE NEWS BREAKING
LATE TONIGHT.
MEANING ALL BUT
CERTAIN FALLOUT
TOMORROW ON CAPITOL
HILL.
LESTER?
>> HALLIE JACKSON AT
THE WHITE HOUSE, THANK
YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE MASSIVE
CYBER ATTACK SPREADING
AROUND THE WORLD.
NOW 150 COUNTRIES
AFFECTED, 300,000
COMPUTERS AS MORE
COMPANIES WERE LOCKED
OUT OF THEIR SYSTEMS
TODAY, PROMPTING NEW
FEARS HERE IN THE U.S.
PERHAPS THE MOST
STARTLING PART IS THAT
THIS RANSOMWARE ATTACK
IS HARDLY UNIQUE.
IN 2016 THERE WERE
MORE THAN 4,000
ATTACKS EVERY DAY.
LEAVING COMPANIES AND
PRIVATE CITIZENS WITH
A PERMANENT LOSS OF
PRIVATE, FINANCIAL OR
FAMILY RECORDS.
>> Reporter: IT
DOESN'T TAKE MUCH
EXPERTISE TO LAUNCH A
RANSOMWARE ATTACK.
>> HOW TO AVOID
SUSPICION.
>> Reporter: AS JAMES
LINE SHOWED US,
HACKERS ADVERTISE DO
IT YOURSELF RANSOMWARE
KITS ON THE DARK WEB.
>> IT ALLOWS YOU TO
CUSTOMIZE AVENUE
ASPECT OF THE
RANSOMWARE WITHOUT
HAVING TO WRITE ANY
CODE YOURSELF.
>> THERE'S NO WAY TO
KNOW WHO THIS PERSON
IS OR WHERE THEY ARE?
>> THAT'S CORRECT
ABOUT.
>> IT'S IMPOSSIBLE TO
TRACE.
THE PROBLEM IS GROWING
BY THE DAY.
LOSSES TOTALED A
BILLION IN 2015.
FAST FORWARD TO 2016
AN IBM SECURITY STUDY
FOUND
RANSOMWARE E-MAILS
SPIKED 6,000%.
MICROSOFT IS PUSHING
AN URGENT PATCH.
>> THE MOST IMPORTANT
THING IS TO
IMMEDIATELY DOWNLOAD
THE SECURITY PATCH AND
MAKE SURE YOUR SYSTEM
IS SECURE.
>> TO PROTECT YOURSELF
FROM AN ATTACK, KEEP
YOUR OPERATING SYSTEM
AND SECURITY SOFTWARE
UP TO DATE.
BACK UP YOUR DATA ON
THE CLOUD ORRIN
EXTERNAL HARD DRIVE.
NEVER CLICK ON A
SUSPICIOUS E-MAIL OR
LINK.
AND LIMIT THE NUMBER
OF EMPLOYEES WHO HAVE
USER CONTROL ACCESS.
IF YOUR COMPUTER IS
HELD HOSTAGE, SHOULD
YOU PAY THE RANSOM?
>> SOME SOME CASES,
PEOPLE HAVE DECIDED
THEY HAVE TO PAY THE
RANSOM.
THE COST OF LOSING
THAT DATA FOREVER OR
NOT HAVING ACCESS TO
THAT DATA IS TOO
GREAT.
>> IT'S A GAMBLE, BUT
PERHAPS THE ONLY WAY
TO RECLAIM YOUR
DIGITAL LIFE.
ANOTHER MAJOR
DEVELOPMENT.
DISNEY CEO BOB IGER
HAS REPORTEDLY TOLD
EMPLOYEES THAT HACKERS
MAY HAVE STOLEN A YET
TO BE RELEASED DISNEY
MOVIE AND ARE
DEMANDING MONEY OR
THEY WILL START
RELEASING CHUNKS OF
THE MOVIE.
DISNEY IS NOT
RELEASING THE NAME OF
THE MOVIE, BUT SAYS SO
FAR IT'S NOT PAYING.
LESTER?
>> TOM COSTELLO, THANK
YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE THREAT
FROM NORTH KOREA AFTER
ANOTHER PROVOCATIVE
ACTION CONDEMNED BY
THE U.N. SECURITY
COUNCIL LATE TODAY.
A MISSILE LAUNCH
UNLIKE ANY THEY'VE
TRIED BEFORE.
THERE ARE FEARS IT
COULD REACH A U.S.
TERRITORY.
WE GET LATE DETAILS
FROM OUR CHIEF FOREIGN
CORRESPONDENT RICHARD
ENGEL.
>> Reporter: FOR THE
NORTH KOREAN REGIME,
IT WAS A BIG SUCCESS.
THE LEADER, KIM
JONG-UN SHOWN ON STATE
TV SUPERVISING THE
MISSILE LAUNCH.
AND CELEBRATING WHEN
THIS ONE UNLIKE THE
LAST TWO THEY TESTED,
FLEW 1200 MILES IN THE
AIR AND DIDN'T BLOW
UP.
NORTH KOREA CLAIMED
THE MISSILE CAN CARRY
A NUCLEAR WARHEAD.
NO PROOF THAT IT CAN,
BUT IT COULD
POTENTIALLY PUT U.S.
TERRITORY IN RANGE,
GUAM HOME TO A U.S.
MILITARY BASE AND
AMERICAN BOMBERS.
>> KIM JONG-UN IS
AGGRESSIVE, HE'S
UNPREDICTABLE.
I THINK THE ANSWER IS,
WE HAVE TO ENGAGE.
THERE HAS TO BE SOME
DIPLOMACY.
CHINA HAS TO HELP US
MORE THAN THEY HAVE.
>> VLADIMIR PUTIN
CALLED THE MISSILE
TEST DANGEROUS.
BUT ADVISED AGAINST
INTIMIDATING
PYONGYANG.
AT THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY, NO TALK OF
SENDING ARMADA'S THIS
TIME, INSTEAD ABOUT
SOUTH KOREA'S NEW
PRESIDENT WHO FAVORS
TALKS WITH NORTH
KOREA.
ZBLAT PRESIDENT LOOKS
FORWARD TO HAVING A
CONVERSATION WITH THE
NEW PRESIDENT AND
DISCUSSING THE WAY
FORWARD, BUT I'M NOT
GOING TO GET AHEAD OF
THAT DISCUSSION.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP IN HIS INTERVIEW
WITH LESTER HOLT,
SEEMED TO BE DIALING
DOWN HIS RHETORIC.
>> YOU'VE WARNED NORTH
KOREA THAT ALL OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE MANY.
>> SURE, ALL OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE.
>> THAT'S WHAT I'M
GETTING AT, IN THAT
SENSE --
>> YES, ALL OPTIONS
ARE ON THE TABLE.
THAT I CAN SAY.
>> Reporter: THIS
MISSILE FLEW VERY
HIGH, OVER 1,000 MILES
HIGH, AND OFFICIALS
ARE CONCERNED ABOUT
THIS NEW CAPABILITY,
AND SPECIFICALLY
THEY'RE TRYING TO
FIGURE OUT ABOUT ITS
REENTRY, WAS IT A
CONTROLLED REENTRY, OR
DID IT CRASH TO THE
GROUND.
IF IT WAS A CONTROLLED
REENTRY, THAT WOULD BE
A SIGNIFICANT STEP.
>> VERY WORRYING.
>> YES.
>>> THE FIERY CRASH OF
A PLANE ON APPROACH TO
ONE OF THE NEW YORK
AREA'S BUSIEST
AIRPORTS LATE TODAY
KILLED TWO PEOPLE
AFTER THE PLANE
PLUMMETED INTO A
BUILDING.
THE PRIVATE LEARJET
CAME DOWN IN CLEAR BUT
WINDY WEATHER JUST A
QUARTER MILE FROM THE
RUNWAY AT TETERBORO
AIRPORT THIS
AFTERNOON, AS
HORRIFIED WITNESSES
WATCHED IN BELIEF.
KRISTEN DAHLGREN
REPORTS FROM THE
SCENE.
>> THE THICK BLACK
SMOKE COULD BE SEEN
FOR MILES.
>> AIRPORT'S CLOSED
PP.
>> PIECES OF THE
LEARJET IN FLAMES,
SCATTERED THROUGH THE
STREETS.
>> SURROUNDING TOWNS
RESPONDING.
LET ME KNOW WHAT
ADDITIONAL YOU'LL
NEED.
>> THE PLANE APPEARED
TO MISS ITS LANDING.
CRASHING INTO AT LEAST
TWO BUILDINGS,
INCLUDING THE
DEPARTMENT OF PUBLIC
WORKS.
>> EVERYTHING BACK
THERE IS JUST A
DISASTER, THERE'S LIKE
A DOZEN CARS THAT ARE
JUST -- GOT INTO FIRE,
THE BUILDING GOT INTO
FIRE, AND IT'S JUST
SHOCKING.
IT'S REALLY SHOCKING.
>> TWO CREW MEMBERS
WERE KILLED.
THERE WERE NO
PASSENGERS ON BOARD,
AND THEY DON'T BELIEVE
ANYONE ON THE GROUND
WAS INJURED.
>> USUALLY ALL THIS
RIGHT HERE IS ALL
INDUSTRY, FACTORIES
AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
IT'S JUST REALLY
SHOCKING, ONCE I HEARD
THE BIG BOOM, I DIDN'T
KNOW WHAT WAS GOING
ON.
>> THE PLANE WAS
REGISTERED TO A
MONTANA AVIATION
COMPANY.
THERE WERE STRONG
WINDS IN THE AREA AS
IT MADE ITS WAY FROM
PHILADELPHIA TO TIG
TETERBORO.
JUST HOURS AFTER
PERFORMING ON THE
"TODAY" SHOW, NEW KIDS
ON THE BLOCK, JONATHAN
KNIGHT WROTE, OUR
PLANE IS GROUNDED
UNTIL THE SCENE IS
CLEARED.
SCARY.
AS YOU CAN SEE, IT IS
WINDY OUT HERE
TONIGHT, AT THIS HOUR,
THEY BELIEVE EVERYBODY
IN THE BUILDINGS HAVE
BEEN ACCOUNTED FOR.
SINCE SOME CARS WERE
HIT, THEY'RE MAKING
SURE THERE ARE NO
ADDITIONAL CASUALTIES.
THE NTSB AND FAA ARE
ENROUTE TO
INVESTIGATE.
>> KRISTEN DAHLGREN
TONIGHT, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO NEW
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE
DEADLY FRATERNITY
SCANDAL AT PENN STATE.
A FAMILY OF THE PLEDGE
SPEAKING OUT TO NBC'S
MATT LAUER ABOUT HIS
FINAL HOURS, THEIR
PAIN AND THE BLAME
THEY PLACE ON THOSE
WHO ALLEGEDLY WAITED
FAR TOO LONG TO GET
HIM HELP.
>> IT WAS HORRIFIC.
THIS WASN'T BOYS BEING
BOYS, MATT.
THIS WAS MEN WHO
INTENDED TO FORCE FEED
LETHAL AMOUNTS OF
ALCOHOL INTO OTHER
YOUNG MEN.
>> Reporter: JIM AND
EVELYN SAY THEIR SON
TIM WAS NOT A BIG
DRINKER, BUT HE WAS
PLEDGING A FRATERNITY,
AND PART OF THAT MEANT
PARTICIPATING IN WHAT
WAS KNOWN AS THE
GAUNTLET.
SURVEILLANCE VIDEO
SHOWS PLEDGES
SHOTGUNING BEERS AND
DRINKING FROM VODKA
BOTTLES.
AFTER MORE THAN AN
HOUR, HE'S SEEN
SEVERELY STAGGERING,
DRUNKENLY TOWARD THE
BASEMENT STEPS.
THE BROTHERS HEAR HIM
FALL AND CARRY HIM
BACK TO THE COUCH.
>> BECAUSE OF HOW
INEASTBOUND REATED TIM
WAS.
HE FELL A NUMBER OF
TIMES.
>> HE WAS SEVERELY
INJURED.
AND FOR 12 HOURS.
>> THEY SLAPPED HIM,
THEY THREW WATER IN
HIS FACE, THEY SAT ON
HIM.
>> THEY DID A STERNUM
RUB.
>> SOMEBODY KNEW WHAT
A STERNUM RUB WAS, AND
KNEW IF HE DIDN'T
REACT TO IT, THERE'S A
SIGNIFICANT ISSUE.
THEY DID NOTHING ABOUT
IT.
>> NEARLY 12 HOURS
AFTER TIMOTHY PIAZZA
FELL, SOMEONE FINALLY
DID CALL 911.
TIMOTHY'S OLDER
BROTHER MICHAEL WAS
THE FIRST TO LEARN
THAT SOMETHING WAS
WRONG.
>> ONE OF HIS
ROOMMATES CALLED ME TO
SEE IF I KNEW WHERE HE
WAS, BECAUSE HE HADN'T
COME HOME.
SO I CALLED THE
HOSPITAL JUST TO SEE.
AND THE WOMAN ON THE
PHONE TOLD ME HE WAS
IN THE EMERGENCY ROOM,
AND WHEN I GOT THERE,
I FOUND OUT PRETTY
QUICKLY HOW SERIOUS IT
WAS.
>> DID YOU ASK ANY OF
THE SURGEONS OR THE
DOCTORS HAD HE BEEN
BROUGHT TO YOU --
>> YES.
>> AN HOUR, TWO HOURS,
FOUR HOURS, SIX HOURS,
WOULD THE OUTCOME HAVE
BEEN DIFFERENT?
>> I SAID THOSE EXACT
WORDS?
AND THE DOCTOR SAID
YEAH.
>> SO THOSE 12 HOURS,
THAT IS WHAT MADE THE
DIFFERENCE?
>> YES.
>> YEAH.
>> THEY KILLED HIM.
>> IN A STATEMENT, THE
UNIVERSITY SAID THIS
IS HEART WRENCHING FOR
THE FAMILY, AND OUR
COMMUNITY.
>> 18 YOUNG MEN ARE
FACING CHARGES TO
DATE.
DO YOU SEE THEM ALL AS
BEING EQUALLY
CULPABLE?
>> I THINK IT'S UP TO
THE JURY TO DECIDE.
>> WHAT ABOUT IN YOUR
HEART?
>> IN MY HEART THEY'RE
ALL MORALLY CULPABLE.
>> THAT'S MATT LAUER
WITH THAT POWERFUL
INTERVIEW.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, A 16-YEAR-OLD
COLLAPSES IN CLASS,
AND LATER DIES AFTER
OFFICIALS SAY HE HAD
TOO MANY OF THE
BEVERAGES MILLIONS
CONSUME EVERY DAY.
HOW MUCH CAFFEINE IS
TOO MUCH FOR YOUR
CHILD?
>>> ALSO SOMETHING NEW
AT THE AIRPORT THAT
COULD MAKE CHECKING
YOUR BAG SO MUCH
FASTER.
STAY WITH US.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH A JARRING WARNING
FROM A SOUTH CAROLINA
CORONER AFTER THE
DEATH OF A TEENAGER
BEING BLAMED ON AN
OVERDOSE OF CAFFEINE.
TOO MUCH CONSUMED IN
WAY TOO SHORT A TIME
HAVING AN ESPECT ON
HIS HEART.
A MESSAGE FROM HIS
GRIEVING PARENTS TO
OTHERS.
WE GET THE DETAILS
FROM NBC'S KERRY
SANDERS.
>> Reporter: WHEN
16-YEAR-OLD DAVIS
COLLAPSED AND DIED
LAST MONTH, MEDICAL
TEAMS WERE PERPLEXED.
WHY WOULD AN OTHERWISE
HEALTHY TEENAGER DROP
DEAD OF A HEART
ATTACK.
A LARGE DIET MOUNTAIN
DUE, A CAFE LATTE FROM
McDONALDS AND SOME
TYPE OF ENERGY DRINK.
>> IT WAS SO MUCH
CAFFEINE AT THE TIME
OF HIS DEATH THAT IT
CAUSED HIS ARRHYTHMIA.
>> THE TEENAGER'S
PARENTS DEVASTATED.
THAT SOMETHING SO
READILY AVAILABLE LIKE
CAFFEINE, COULD HAVE
CAUSED HIS DEATH.
HIS FATHER SAID DAVIS
ROUTINELY AVOIDED
ALCOHOL AND DRUGS.
>> IT WASN'T A CAR
CRASH THAT TOOK HIS
LIFE, INSTEAD IT WAS
AN ENERGY DRINK.
>> ACCORDING TO THE
MAYO CLINIC, AN
AVERAGE 8 OUNCE COFFEE
CON SANS UP TO 165
MILLIGRAMS OF
CAFFEINE.
A NATURAL STIMULANT
FOUND IN COFFEE BEANS,
TEA AND COCOA.
AN AMERICAN ACADEMY OF
PEDIATRICS RECOMMENDS
ADD LESS ANTS NOT
CONSUME MORE THAN 100
MILLIGRAMS OF CAFFEINE
PER DAY.
CAFFEINE CAN TRIGGER
AN UNDERLYING
UNDETECTED HEART
PROBLEM.
>> IT'S THAT
DANGEROUS?
>> IT'S VERY
DANGEROUS.
SINCE THE CAFFEINATED
DRINKS HAVE EMERGED ON
THE MARKET SEVERAL
YEARS AGO, THERE'S
BEEN AN INCREASE OF
INCIDENCE OF SUDDEN
CARDIAC DEATH.
>> TONIGHT THE FAMILY
IS SHATTERED.
>> I STAND BEFORE YOU
AS A BROKEN HEARTED
FATHER AND HOPE THAT
SOMETHING GOOD CAN
COME FROM THIS.
>> A SENSELESS DEATH
FROM A SEEMINGLY
HARMLESS PRODUCT.
KERRY SANDERS, NBC
NEWS TAMPA.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A
MOMENT WITH THE NEW
BATTLE BREAKING OUT
OVER A CONTROVERSIAL
SYMBOL OF THE PAST.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH A FIERCE BATTLE
ERUPTING IN VIRGINIA
OVER ONE CITY'S PLAN
TO REMOVE A
CONFEDERATE STATUE.
IT'S PART OF A FIGHT
ACROSS THE SOUTH THAT
SOME SAY IS ABOUT
ELIMINATING SYMBOLS OF
RACISM, WHILE OTHERS
SEE IT AS PRESERVING
HISTORY.
GABE GUTIERREZ HAS THE
STORY.
>>> CARRYING TORCHES,
DEMONSTRATORS IN
VIRGINIA RALLIED
AGAINST PLANS TO
REMOVE THIS STATUE OF
ROBERT E. LEE.
>> WE ARE SIMPLY JUST
WHITE PEOPLE WHO LOVE
OUR HERITAGE, OUR
CULTURE.
>> Reporter: THE
FOUNDER OF THE
SO-CALLED ALT RIGHT
MOVEMENT.
>> I'M HERE TO TAKE
PART IN THIS GREAT
CELEBRATION.
>> SLAVERY IS DEAD,
AND WE NEED EVERYONE
TO REALIZE AND
RECOGNIZE THAT VERY
FACT.
>> IT'S THE LATEST
BATTLE ACROSS THE
SOUTH TO REMOVE
CONFEDERATE SYMBOLS
FOLLOWING THE 2015
MASSACRE OF NINE BLACK
CHURCH GOERS IN SOUTH
CAROLINA.
WORKERS IN NEW ORLEANS
HAVE TAKEN DOWN
SEVERAL MONUMENTS.
IN VIRGINIA, THE ISSUE
IS CREEPING INTO THE
RACE FOR GOVERNOR, AND
HAS BECOME A RALLYING
CRY AGAINST POLITICAL
CORRECTNESS FOR
REPUBLICAN CANDIDATE
CORY STEWART.
>> WES BELLAMY IS
CHARLOTTEVILLE'S
MAYOR.
>> WHAT I SAW WAS
REMINISCENT OF THE
1940s AND 1930s AS A
KKK COMMUNITY.
HOW CAN WE SAY WE ARE
A WELCOMING CITY FOR
ALL, WITH ONE OF THE
MOST DIVISIVE AND
IGNORE AN THE STATUES
YOU WILL FIND IN THE
COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT A
COURT INJUNCTION
BLOCKING THE STATUE'S
REMOVAL FOR SIX
MONTHS.
AS THE TENSION BETWEEN
THE COUNTRY'S PAST AND
PRESENT BECOMES A
MONUMENTAL FIGHT.
GABE GUTIERREZ NBC
NEWS, CHARLOTTESVILLE.
>>> DELTA PLANS TO
TEST NEW TECHNOLOGY AT
MINNEAPOLIS/ST. PAUL,
THAT WOULD ALLOW
PEOPLE TO CHECK THEIR
BAGS BY SCANNING THEIR
FACES.
NO AGENT NECESSARY.
IF THE PILOT PROGRAM
GOES WELL, THE AIRLINE
PLANS TO ROLL IT OUT
ACROSS THE COUNTRY.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK,
HE ROSE FROM POVERTY
TO PLAY COLLEGE
FOOTBALL.
PERHAPS HIS MOST
AMAZING ACHIEVEMENT
HAPPENED OFF THE
FIELD.
INSPIRING AMERICA IS
NEXT.
THE REASON BAY AREA LAWYERS SAY
LOW INCOME DRIVERS ARE
UNFAIRLY PUNISHED.
===JESS/TAKE VO===
PLUS:
A FAMILIAR FACE AT PRACTICE.
BUT WHEN CAN WE EXPECT STEVE
KERR BACK ON THE BENCH FOR THE
WARRIORS?
===NEXT CLOSE===
THE NEWS IS NEXT.
==JESS/TAKE VO==
RIGHT NOW AT 6:
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, A
REMARKABLE STORY OF
PERSEVERANCE.
THE YOUNG MAN YOU'RE
ABOUT TO MEET
CONCURRED EVERY
OBSTACLE IN HIS PATH
TO ACHIEVE THE DREAM
OF PLAYING COLLEGE
FOOTBALL.
NBC'S RON MOTT HAS
MORE IN OUR INSPIRING
AMERICA REPORT.
>> KYLAN LEWIS MOORE.
>> Reporter: THE WAY
HE READS IT, HIS LIFE
DOESN'T MAKE MUCH
SENSE ON PAPER, BUT
IT'S UNFOLDING AS
PLANNED.
>> I LIKE TO DREAM
DREAMS SO BIG, SO
UNFATHOMABLE, THAT
WITHOUT DIVINE
INTERVENTION FROM GOD,
THEY'RE DESTINED TO
FAIL.
>> GROWING UP IN THE
COMPTON CARSON
CALIFORNIA AREA, NO
HOT WATER, HARDLY ANY
FOOD SOME DAYS, FOR
ALL HE LACKED, HE
LITERALLY PUSHED THAT
MUCH HARDER, AND
FOOTBALL CHANGED
EVERYTHING.
>> THE ONLY
ALTERNATIVE TO GET A
SHOT IS TO GET A JUMP,
NO, I DON'T GANG BANG,
I JUST PLAY FOOTBALL.
>> FOOTBALL GAVE US
LIFE.
>> HIS MOM HELPED
POINT THE WAY.
>> WE MAY LIVE IN THE
'HOOD, BUT THE 'HOOD
DOESN'T LIVE IN US.
I ENVISION THE
UNLIMITED PLACES THAT
MY CHILDREN CAN GO.
>> Reporter: INJURIES
LIMITED PLAYING TIME,
SO HE TACKLED THE
BOOKS BIG TIME.
A STUDENT, FULLING
BRIGHT SCHOLARSHIP,
MOTIVATIONAL SPEAKER.
NOW FRESHLY GRADUATED
FROM TCU.
>> THAT'S MY SON.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER
GREAT ADVENTURE
AWAITS.
OXFORD UNIVERSITY IN
ENGLAND.
ROAD SCHOLAR.
>> THIS IS A LONG WAY
FROM EAST COMPTON.
>> FOR REAL, IT REALLY
IS.
>> HIS FUTURE UNLIKE
HIS PAST, RICH WITH
POSSIBILITIES.
>> I WANT TO MAKE
SOMETHING OUT OF
MYSELF, I'M STARTING
TOWARD THAT.
>> PERFECT SENSE
REALLY, EVEN ON PAPER.
>> RON MOTT, FT. WORTH
TEXAS.
>>> THAT'S GOING TO DO
IT ON A MONDAY NIGHT,
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING.
AND GOOD NIGHT.
RUN THE RED LIGHT -- PAY THE
PRICE.
AND IN SOME CASES --- GO TO
JAIL.
THE BAY AREA LAWYERS WHO ACCUSE
THE SYSTEM OF BEING
UNFAIR TO SOME DRIVERS.
==JESS/2-SHOT==
THE NEWS AT 6 STARTS NOW.
THANKS FOR JOINING US.
I )M JESSICA AGUIRRE.
==JAN/2-SHOT==
AND I )M JANELLE WANG -- IN FOR
RAJ MATHAI.
DOES THE PUNISHMENT FIT THE
CRIME?
==JAN/RAIL==
A NEWREPORT FINDS THE HIGH PRICE
FOR SPEEDING AND
RUNNING RED LIGHTS ... TOO STEEP
FOR MANY IN THE BAY AREA,
AND NOW THERE )S A FIGHT TO
CHANGE IT.
N-B-C BAY AREA )S MICHELLE
ROBERTS JOINS US LIVE FROM SAN
JOSE WITH MORE.
MICHELLE, IT COULD EVEN LEAD TO
JAIL TIME.
JESS/HSET
DENIALS TONIGHT FROM THE TRUMP
WHITE HOUSE--WHICH IS