>>> THE FIRE CONTINUES TO SPREAD
THROUGH THE NEIGHBORHOOD NEAR
FAIRFIELD HIGH SCHOOL.
WE'LL FOLLOW THE STORY AND THE
OTHER HEADLINES AT 6:00.
THANKS FOR JOINING US AT 5:0037
>>> ON THE BROADCAST TONIGHT,
READY TO GO.
THE MILITARY SIGNALS ITS FORCES
ARE IN PLACE AND ABLE TO STRIKE
SYRIA AT A MOMENT'S NOTICE
SHOULD THE PRESIDENT ISSUE THE
ORDER.
.>> THE MEASLES OUTBREAK LINKED
>>> HOUSING SURGE, PRICES ARE
RISING FAST.
WE'LL TELL YOU HOW MUCH MORE IT
WILL COST YOU TODAY THAN IF YOU
HAD BOUGHT JUST WEEKS AGO.
IS NOW THE TIME TO MAKE YOUR
MOVE?
>>> AND THE DOLPHIN MYSTERY.
ALONG THE EAST COAST.
WHY ARE SO MANY OF THE BELOVED
CREATURES TURNING UP SICK?
TONIGHT THERE'S FINALLY AN
ANSWER.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING, I'M LESTER
HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
THERE ARE A NUMBER OF
INDICATIONS TONIGHT THAT A
U.S.-LED MILITARY STRIKE AGAINST
SYRIA COULD BE LAUNCHED BEFORE
THE END OF THE WEEK.
MOMENTUM FOR PUNISHING ACTION
AGAINST THE ASSAD GOVERNMENT HAS
BEEN BUILDING THROUGHOUT THE
DAY, AND AS WE BEGIN HERE
TONIGHT, THERE ARE SEVERAL NEW
DEVELOPMENTS TO REPORT.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS IT WILL
RELEASE SOLID EVIDENCE THAT THE
SYRIAN GOVERNMENT ORDERED A MASS
CHEMICAL WEAPONS ATTACK ON ITS
OWN PEOPLE LAST WEEK.
ON THE DIPLOMATIC SIDE,
INTERNATIONAL SUPPORT FOR AN
ATTACK IS GROWING.
AND FROM THE PENTAGON, WORD THAT
U.S. WAR SHIPS ARE IN PLACE AND
READY TO LAUNCH WHEN THE ORDER
IS GIVEN.
THIS FAST MOVING CHAIN OF EVENTS
ALL TOUCHED OFF BY THOSE
HORRIFIC IMAGES OF DEAD AND
DYING CIVILIANS THAT SHOCKED THE
WORLD.
NBC'S ANDREA MITCHELL BEGINS OUR
COVERAGE TONIGHT FROM
WASHINGTON.
ANDREA, GOOD EVENING.
>> GOOD EVENING, LESTER.
BRUSHING ASIDE ASSAD'S DENIAL,
THE ADMINISTRATION'S GOAL IS TO
PUNISH HIM AND STOP HIM FROM
ORDERING ANOTHER CHEMICAL
ATTACK.
HOPING TO PREVENT MORE DEATHS
FROM DEVASTATING WEAPONS NOT
SEEN IN DECADES.
AND LESTER, FAIR WARNING, THESE
LATEST PICTURES ARE VERY HARD TO
WATCH.
THIS IS A DIFFERENT KIND OF WAR.
A WAR THAT KILLS BABIES
SILENTLY, SUDDENLY, BATHING THEM
NOT IN BLOOD, BUT IN THE TEARS
OF A DOCTOR.
GHASTLY IMAGES OF LAST WEEK'S
ATTACK.
MOST TOO HORRIFYING TO SHOW ON
TELEVISION.
EMERGING ONLY TODAY.
THIS INFANT APPARENTLY BARELY A
MONTH OLD.
AND A NEW HORROR NEAR ALEPPO,
THE OPPOSITION CLAIMS
PHOSPHOROUS BOMBS AND NAPALM
DROPPED ON CIVILIANS MONDAY,
KILLING AT LEAST TEN, WOUNDING
DOZENS.
A REPORT THAT HAS NOT BEEN
INDEPENDENTLY VERIFIED.
IN TEXAS TODAY, SPEAKING TO
VETERANS, THE VICE PRESIDENT
CONTINUED THE DRUM BEAT TO
PUNISH BASHAR AL ASSAD.
>> THERE'S NO DOUBT WHO IS
RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS HEINOUS USE
OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS IN SYRIA.
THE SYRIAN REGIME.
>> Reporter: THE WHITE HOUSE IS
NOT WAITING FOR A REPORT FROM
THE U.N. CHEMICAL WEAPONS TEAM
THAT FINALLY GOT TO THE ATTACK
SITE MONDAY.
OFFICIALS TELL NBC NEWS THEY
HAVE INTELLIGENCE INTERCEPTS,
TYING THE ATTACK TO THE REGIME.
PLUS PHYSICAL EVIDENCE.
>> WE KNOW THAT THE REGIME
MAINTAINS CUSTODY OF THE
CHEMICAL WEAPONS IN SYRIA, AND
USES THE TYPES OF ROCKETS THAT
WERE USED TO DELIVER CHEMICAL
WEAPONS ON AUGUST 21st.
THE OPPOSITION DOES NOT.
>> Reporter: BRITISH PRIME
MINISTER DAVID CAMERON CUT SHORT
HIS HOLIDAY TO CALL A SPECIAL
SESSION OF PARLIAMENT THURSDAY.
>> WHAT WE'VE SEEN IN SYRIA ARE
APPALLING SCENES OF DEATH AND
SUFFERING BECAUSE OF THE USE OF
CHEMICAL WEAPONS BY THE ASSAD
REGIME.
I DON'T BELIEVE WE CAN LET THAT
STAND.
>> Reporter: RUSSIA'S VLADIMIR
PUTIN INTERRUPTED A MEETING TO
TAKE A CALL FROM THE BRITISH
PRIME MINISTER.
PUTIN IS STILL BLOCKING U.N.
ACTION.
BUT TODAY THE ARAB LEAGUE, LED
BY THE SAUDIS DENOUNCED THE
ASSAD GOVERNMENT FOR THE
CHEMICAL ATTACK.
WHEN THE ORDER COMES, THE
PENTAGON HAS FOUR DESTROYERS,
SUBMARINES, PLUS THE NATO BASE
IN TURKEY.
>> WE ARE READY TO GO LIKE THAT.
>> Reporter: MILITARY
INTELLIGENCE IS UPDATING TARGETS
TO TEACH ASSAD A LESSON.
>> HE VALUES HIS MILITARY
COMMAND AND CONTROL NODES, HIS
COMMUNICATIONS NODES, HIS
MILITARY AIR FIELD.
WE'LL PROBABLY CRATER RUNWAYS SO
PLANES CAN'T TAKE OFF.
WE'LL TRY TO HIT PLANES ON THE
TARMAC.
>> Reporter: WHAT ABOUT
UNINTENDED CONSEQUENCES?
THE U.S. MILITARY PLAN IS NOT TO
GET IN THE MIDDLE OF THE CIVIL
WAR AND TRY TO TOPPLE ASSAD.
BUT OPPOSITION LEADER GENERAL
LEE JUST TOLD RICHARD ENGEL THEY
WILL SEIZE THE CHANCE TO TRY TO
DEFEAT ASSAD.
>> I THINK THERE IS A VERY GOOD
CHANCE TO FALL THE ASSAD REGIME.
>> Reporter: AND WILL ONE OF
SYRIA'S ALLIES, IRAN OR
HEZBOLLAH RETALIATE AGAINST
ISRAEL?
ISRAEL SAYS IT'S READY FOR
ANYTHING.
THE ADMINISTRATION WILL GIVE A
CLASSIFIED INTELLIGENCE
ASSESSMENT TO CONGRESS THIS WEEK
AND MAKE A DECLASSIFIED VERSION
PUBLIC.
OFFICIALS HAVE DELAYED THE
ANTICIPATED RELEASE FOR A DAY OR
SO, TO MAKE SURE THERE ARE NO
MISTAKES.
FULLY CONSCIOUS OF THE FALSE
CLAIMS ABOUT IRAQ'S WMD A DECADE
AGO.
LESTER?
>> ANDREA MITCHELL TONIGHT,
THANKS.
>>> AS THE OBAMA ADMINISTRATION
AMPS UP THE RHETORIC FOR
POSSIBLE MILITARY ACTION AGAINST
SYRIA, A LOT OF AMERICANS ARE
FOCUSED ON OTHER THINGS, LIKE
THE DWINDLING DAYS OF SUMMER.
BUT IS THERE SUPPORT FOR A
MILITARY STRIKE?
NBC'S KEVIN TIBBLES WENT TO THE
MINNESOTA STATE FAIR TODAY TO
SEE HOW ALL THIS IS PLAYING FAR
FROM WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: AS THE LATE SUMMER
HEAT WAVE BEATS DOWN, FOLKS HEAD
FOR THE MIDWAY, THE COTTON
CANDY, CORN DOGS, CORN ON THE
COB, ICE CREAM, EVEN PICKLES ON
A STICK.
BUT TODAY IS ALSO MILITARY
APPRECIATION DAY, AND MANY VETS
AND THEIR FAMILIES NOW WORRY
ABOUT ALLEGED CHEMICAL ATTACKS
IN SYRIA.
>> NOW, WHAT TO DO WITH SYRIA,
THAT'S THE QUESTION NOBODY HAS
THE ANSWER.
>> CHEMICAL WEAPONS?
>> THAT'S AWFUL.
NOBODY SHOULD USE THAT.
>> Reporter: SHOULD THE UNITED
STATES DO ANYTHING ABOUT THIS?
>> I WOULD LIKE TO SEE THEM DO
SOMETHING, BECAUSE I THINK IF WE
DON'T DO SOMETHING, IT'S GOING
TO CONTINUE.
>> SOMEBODY'S GOT TO DO
SOMETHING ABOUT IT.
>> TO ME IT SHOULD BE WITH THE
ALLIES, OTHERWISE WE'RE GOING TO
GET INVOLVED WITH SOMETHING WE
DON'T WANT TO GET INVOLVED IN.
>> Reporter: MANY FAIR GOERS SAY
THEY'RE TORN ABOUT WHAT AMERICA
SHOULD DO.
>> WE GET INVOLVED IN SO MANY
PLACES WE REALLY DON'T BELONG.
>> Reporter: OTHERS ARE DEAD SET
AGAINST ANY INVOLVEMENT.
>> WE HAVE PLENTY OF OUR OWN
BATTLES TO BE FOUGHT.
WE SHOULDN'T BE GETTING INTO A
MIDDLE EASTERN CONFLICT RIGHT
NOW.
>> I THINK WE'RE INVOLVED IN
ENOUGH STUFF OVERSEAS, YOU KNOW?
TRYING TO BRING THE TROOPS HOME
AND LET SOMEONE ELSE DEAL WITH
IT.
>> Reporter: AS MINNESOTANS
CELEBRATE THE TROOPS, MANY WORRY
ABOUT WHAT MIGHT LIE AHEAD.
>> I PRAY FOR THOSE GUYS EVERY
NIGHT.
THEY'RE IN MY PRAYERS.
>> MANY HERE HAVE EITHER SERVED
OR HAVE LOVED ONES SERVING
OVERSEAS.
THEY ARE PATRIOTIC, BUT THEY ARE
ALSO CONCERNED ABOUT ANY FUTURE
MILITARY CONFLICT.
LESTER?
>> KEVIN TIBBLES, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO THE MASSIVE AIR AND
GROUND WAR IN THE WEST AGAINST
ONE OF THE LARGEST WILDFIRES IN
THE HISTORY OF CALIFORNIA,
CONTINUING TO EXPLODE OUT OF
CONTROL TONIGHT.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER SPENT MUCH
OF THE DAY IN A HELICOPTER HIGH
ABOVE THAT BATTLE GAINING A
UNIQUE PERSPECTIVE IN JUST HOW
HIGHLY COORDINATED THIS
FIREFIGHT IS.
>> Reporter: SO WE'RE ABOUT 15
MILES AWAY FROM THE HEART OF THE
FIRE.
WE'RE DOWN WIND, SO THE SMOKE
HERE IS SOCKING IN THE AIRPORT,
WE'RE NOT ABLE TO LEAVE THE
AIRPORT IT'S TOO DANGEROUS TO
FLY.
AS SOON AS WE FIND A POCKET OF
STRONG WINDS THAT CLEARS OUT
SOME OF THIS SMOKE, WE'LL TAKE
OFF.
SO IT LOOKS LIKE WE HAVE A
WINDOW HERE, AND WE'RE GOING TO
TAKE OFF.
HOPEFULLY WE CAN MAKE IT UP
BEFORE THE SMOKE COMES BACK INTO
THE AIRPORT.
>> LOOKS GOOD TO GO, WE'RE SAFE.
WE'RE GOOD TO GO.
>> Reporter: THIS FIRE IS
ROUGHLY 230 SQUARE MILES BIGGER
THAN THE SIZE OF THE CITY OF
CHICAGO.
AND ALL ALONG THESE RIDGES WE
CAN SEE FIRES.
THERE'S NO DOUBT THIS FIRE IS
GROWING, IT'S CERTAINLY QUICKLY
ON THE MOVE.
YOU CAN SEE FROM THE FUEL LOAD
DOWN HERE, THERE'S JUST HUNDREDS
OF THOUSANDS OF ACRES THAT CAN
STILL BURN.
>> WE'RE GOING TO MAKE OUR WAY
DOWN TO THE SOUTH SIDE.
FOR BETTER VISIBILITY.
IT LOOKS LIKE EVERYTHING IS
BLOWN UP TO THE NORTH.
>> Reporter: THIS FIRE HAS BEEN
BURNING FOR A WEEK AND A HALF.
AND THERE'S NO DOUBT THIS FIRE
COULD BURN FOR WEEKS LONGER.
CREWS MAY NOT BE ABLE TO ACCEPT
ACCESS SO MUCH OF THIS TERRAIN
DOWN THERE.
IT IS VERY RUGGED, IT IS VERY
ROCKY BELOW.
FROM THE AIR HERE, YOU GET THAT
UNIQUE PERSPECTIVE.
YOU CAN UNDERSTAND WHY THEY
CAN'T DROP FIREFIGHTERS INTO THE
BURN ZONE.
IF THEY PUT CREWS DOWN ON THE
GROUND DOWN THERE, THERE'S
NOWHERE THEY WOULD BE ABLE TO
RUN.
THERE ARE NO ESCAPE ROUTES.
SO ON THIS FLANK OF THE FIRE,
THEY SIMPLY HAVE TO ATTACK IT
FROM THE AIR.
THE DC-10 IS ONE OF THE BIGGEST
ASSETS CREWS HAVE ON THE GROUND.
THIS PLANE CAN DROP NEARLY
12,000 GALLONS OF FIRE
RETARDANT.
IT CAN STOP FLAMES DEAD IN ITS
TRACKS.
YOU CAN SEE JUST HOW HOT THIS
FIRE IS BURNING.
BEHIND ALL OF THIS SMOKE AND ASH
IN THE AIR, YOU CAN SEE THERE
ARE HOTSPOTS, THERE ARE FLAMES
TOWERING HUNDREDS OF FEET INTO
THE AIR.
THE BLAZE IS STILL VERY ACTIVE.
STILL BURNING VERY QUICKLY, AND,
OF COURSE, VERY, VERY DANGEROUSi
FROM 10,000 FEET ABOVE THE RIM
FIRE, I'M MIGUEL ALMAGUER, NBC
NEWS.
>> AMAZING PERSPECTIVE OF WHAT
THEY'RE UP AGAINST THERE.
>>> ALSO, ALONG THE EASTERN
SEABOARD TONIGHT THERE'S BEEN A
TROUBLING MYSTERY, WHAT'S BEEN
KILLING SO MANY DOLPHINS?
TONIGHT, SCIENTISTS BELIEVE THEY
HAVE FIGURED IT OUT.
OUR CHIEF ENVIRONMENTAL AFFAIRS
CORRESPONDENT ANNE THOMPSON
REPORTS.
>> Reporter: THEY ARE SOME OF
NATURE'S MOST BEAUTIFUL AND
GRACEFUL CREATURES.
BUT THE BOTTLE NOSE DOLPHINS
ALONG THE EASTERN SEABOARD ARE ñ
IN TROUBLE.Ko
FROM NEW YORK TO NORTH CAROLINA,
FEDERAL SCIENTISTS REPORT 357
DOLPHINS DIED BETWEEN JULY 1st
OF THIS YEAR, AND AUGUST 26th.
A SUDDEN AND DRAMATIC INCREASE
DURING A PERIOD THAT TYPICALLY
SEES 36 DEATHS.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS SAY THE CAUSE
IS THE MORBILLIVIRUS.
THE HUMAN STRAIN OF THE DISEASE
CAUSES THE MEASLES.
UNLIKE PEOPLE, THERE'S NO WAY TO
VACCINATE WILD DOLPHINS.
>> WE'RE EXPECTING, BECAUSE OF
THE MIGRATION OF THE DOLPHINS,
THAT THE VIRUS AND THE IMPACT OF
THE VIRUS IS GOING TO SPREAD
SOUTHWARD.
>> Reporter: HOWEVER, SCIENTISTS
SAY THE STRAIN KILLING THE
DOLPHINS, CANNOT BE PASSED TO
BEACH GOERS AND SWIMMERS.
IN DOLPHINS, THE MORBILLIVIRUS
WEAKENS THEIR IMMUNE SYSTEMS,
CAUSING THE MAMMALS TO LOSE
WEIGHT, AND MAKING THEM
SUSCEPTIBLE TO OTHER DISEASES.
THIS IS THE BIGGEST DIE-OFF OF
EAST COAST DOLPHINS IN 25 YEARS,
WHEN THE VIRUS KILLED AT LEAST
740 DOLPHINS.
TODAY, THE SOURCE OF THE VIRUS
REMAINS A MYSTERY.
SCIENTISTS WILL LOOK TO SEE IF
CONTRIBUTING FACTORS, SUCH AS
MAN-MADE POLLUTION, MAKE THE
DOLPHINS MORE VULNERABLE TO THIS
FAST-MOVING DISEASE.
ANNE THOMPSON NBC NEWS, NEW
YORK.
>>> IF YOU'VE BEEN SHOPPING FOR
A NEW HOME OR THINKING ABOUT
SELLING ONE, YOU HAVE PROBABLY
NOTICED THE PRICES HAVE BEEN
GOING UP.
IN SOME CASES WE LEARNED WAY UP
FROM JUST A YEAR AGO.
19% IN ATLANTA.
NEARLY 25% IN SAN FRANCISCO.
AND SIMILAR PICTURES IN MANY
MAJOR CITIES.
SO IS THIS THE TIME TO GET INTO
THE MARKET?
CNBC'S CARL QUINTANILLA IS HERE
WITH MORE FOR US.
CARL?
>> LESTER, THOSE ARE EYE POPPING
NUMBERS IN SOME VERY BIG CITIES.
EVEN IN THE HEARTLAND WE'RE
SEEING PRICES ON THE RISE.
THAT MEANS FAMILIES WHO ARE
THINKING OF BUYING ARE UNDER
MORE PRESSURE TO MAKE THEIR
MOVE.
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING TODAY, SIR?
>> GOOD.
>> Reporter: IN A HOUSING MARKET
PICKING UP STEAM.
MINNESOTA REALTOR RYAN NESS GOES
DOOR TO DOOR EVERY WEEK, TRYING
TO CONVINCE ANYONE TO SELL.
>> IT'S A FAST MOVING MARKET,
THERE'S A LOT OF BUYERS OUT
THERE WAITING FOR THE RIGHT HOME
TO COME ON.
YOU HAVE A GIANT FRIDGE HERE.
>> Reporter: BUYERS LIKE ELLEN
AND GEORGE WHO HAVE BEEN LOOKING
FOR A HOME SINCE MARCH,
UNSUCCESSFULLY BECAUSE THERE'S
NOT MUCH FOR SALE.
EVEN IN THEIR SUBURB OF
WOODBURY, WHERE PRICES ARE UP
13% IN A YEAR.
>> MY HUSBAND CONSTANTLY REMINDS
ME THE INTEREST RATES ARE GOING
UP, FIND A HOUSE.
>> Reporter: THOSE MORTGAGE
RATES HAVE BEEN CLIMBING SINCE
MAY, AND ARE NOW AT A TWO-YEAR
HIGH.
>> THIS IS THE MASTER.
>> Reporter: THREATENING SOME
BUYERS RIGHT OUT OF THEIR PRICE
RANGE.
IF THEY BOUGHT THIS $420,000
HOME TODAY, WITH 20% DOWN, THEIR
MORTGAGE PAYMENT WOULD BE $200
MORE THAN IT WOULD HAVE BEEN
JUST THREE MONTHS AGO.
>> THERE REALLY IS AN IMPETUS TO
FIND AS MUCH HOUSE AS YOU CAN
GET FOR AS LITTLE MONEY AS YOU
CAN AND CASH IN ON THE DEAL THAT
EXISTS RIGHT NOW.
>> Reporter: SOME HOUSING
EXPERTS SAY THE RISE IN RATES
AND PRICES HAS HAPPENED TOO
QUICKLY, PUTTING SOME MARKETS
BACK IN BUBBLE TERRITORY, JUST
FIVE YEARS AFTER THE HOUSING
CRISIS BEGAN.
>> THE CONFIDENCE THAT'S DRIVING
THE CURRENT BOOM COULD
EVAPORATE, AND MORE SUDDENLY
THAN MANY PEOPLE EXPECT.
>> Reporter: ADDING STRESS TO
THE SINGLE BIGGEST FINANCIAL
DECISION MOST OF US EVER MAKE.
>> MAKING MY WIFE HAPPY.
CERTAINLY THE MOST STRESSFUL
THING ABOUT THE WHOLE THING.
>> Reporter: ONE AREA WHERE
RISING RATES HAVE ALREADY TAKEN
A BITE, REFINANCING.
THEY'RE DOWN 16% FROM MAY, AS
SOME HOMEOWNERS, LESTER, DECIDE
THEY MAY HAVE ALREADY MISSED OUT
ON A BARGAIN.
>> YOU HEAR ABOUT LOCATION,
LOCATION, LOCATION.
THERE'S TIMING, TIMING, TIMING.
>> TRUE.
>> CARL, THANKS.
GOOD TO HAVE YOU HERE.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT, THE
OUTBREAK RAISING A LOT OF
QUESTIONS AND CONCERNS AT A
TEXAS MEGA CHURCH.
WHAT IS BEHIND THE RESURGENCE OF
A DISEASE THAT WAS ONCE
VIRTUALLY ERADICATED.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW WITH NEWS
ABOUT MEASLES, A VIRUS DECLARED
ALL BUT WIPED OUT MORE THAN A
DECADE AGO IN THIS COUNTRY BUT
MAKING A TROUBLING COMEBACK.
THE LATEST OUTBREAK IS CENTERED
ON A MEGA CHURCH NEAR FT. WORTH
TEXAS, AT LEAST 21 CASES HAVE
ORIGINATED THERE, INCLUDING 14
CHILDREN, THE YOUNGEST JUST 4
MONTHS OLD.
WHY IS THIS HAPPENING NOW, AND
WHAT DO PARENTS NEED TO KNOW?
HERE'S CHIEF MEDICAL EDITOR DR.
NANCY SNYDERMAN.
>> Reporter: IN FT. WORTH TEXAS,
TODAY, 4-YEAR-OLD JULIAN
AGUILERA IS GETTING HIS MEASLES
SHOT.
A QUICK PINCH TO THE ARM AND A
LOLLIPOP LATER, HE'S ALL SMILES.
IT'S A RELIEF TO HIS MOM TOO.
>> YOU DON'T WANT YOUR KIDS TO
GET SICK.
>> Reporter: THE LARGELY
PREVENTIBLE INFECTION IS MAKING
A COMEBACK, AND THE LATEST
OUTBREAK IN NORTH TEXAS.
OF THE 21 CASES ORIGINATING AT
THIS MEGA CHURCH, AT LEAST 16 OF
THOSE WERE NOT FULLY VACCINATED.
WHICH MEANS TWO SHOTS AS A CHILD
AND FOR MOST ADULTS A BOOSTER.
>> SOMEONE WHO ACTUALLY HAD THE
DISEASE IN JULY, HAD COME BACK
FROM A COUNTRY WHERE MEASLES IS
MORE COMMON, INCUBATING THE
DISEASE, BECAME SICK HERE AND
THENTHER PEOPLE GOT IT.
>> Reporter: ACROSS THE COUNTRY
THERE HAVE BEEN 161 CASES OF
MEASLES IN 16 STATES SO FAR THIS
YEAR.
THAT'S NEARLY TRIPLE THE NUMBER
IN 2012.
WHILE NINE OUT OF THE TEN
CHILDREN OLD ENOUGH TO RECEIVE
VACCINATIONS GET THEM.
PEDIATRICIAN DR. LAURA POPPER IS
CONCERNED ABOUT THE GROWING
NUMBER OF FAMILIES WHO ARE
OPTING OUT FOR NONMEDICAL
REASONS.
>> IT'S MORE MIDDLE CLASS, UPPER
MIDDLE CLASS, PEOPLE ARE
DECIDING THEY'RE AFRAID OF
VACCINES.
THEY BOUGHT THE IDEA THAT AUTISM
IS CONNECTED WITH MMR, AND
THAT'S A LIE.
>> Reporter: HEALTH OFFICIALS
SAY WELL INTENTIONED PARENTS WHO
CHOOSE NOT TO VACCINATE ARE
NEEDLESSLY PUTTING THEIR
CHILDREN AND COMMUNITIES AT
RISK.
MEASLES IS SO CONTAGIOUS THAT
IF ONE PERSON HAS IT, THE CDC
SAYS 90% OF THE PEOPLE WHO ARE
NOT FULLY IMMUNIZED AND COME IN
CLOSE CONTACT TO THAT PERSON
WILL ALSO GET THE INFECTION.
>> MAYBE IF THEY LIVED REMOTELY
ON AN ISLAND SOMEWHERE, THAT
WOULD WORK, BUT WE DON'T.
>> VACCINATIONS HAVE BEEN SO
SUCCESSFUL OVER THE LAST FEW
DECADES.
FOR A LOT OF YOUNG COUPLES WHO
FORGET THAT THESE ILLNESSES CAN
HAVE A RESURGENCE AND THEY CAN
KILL.
A REMINDER THAT VACCINATIONS CAN
PROTECT NOT ONLY YOUR CHILD, BUT
THEY TAKE CARE OF YOUR COMMUNITY
TOO.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT.
DR. NANCY, THANKS.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A MOMENT WITH
A FATHER, A DAUGHTER AND A
DREAM.
>>> WE'RE SEEING RARE FOOTAGE
TONIGHT OF FORMER PRESIDENT
GERALD FORD CALMLY AND CAREFULLY
REMEMBERING THE ATTEMPT ON HIS
LIFE IN SEPTEMBER OF 1975 IN A
PARK IN SACRAMENTO.
IT'S LARGELY UNSEEN FOOTAGE FROM
THE TRIAL OF CHARLES MANSON
FOLLOWER LYNNETTE "SQUEAKY"
FROOME.
FORD REMEMBERS SEEING FROOME
PUSHING HER WAY THROUGH THE
CROWD.
>> AS I STOPPED, I SAW A HAND
COME THROUGH THE CROWD IN THE
FIRST ROW.
AND THAT WAS THE ONLY ACTIVE
GESTURE THAT I SAW.
BUT IN THE HAND WAS A WEAPON.
>> THE GUN, YOU'LL RECALL, WAS
NEVER FIRED AND FORD WAS NOT
HURT.
FROOME WAS RELEASED FROM PRISON
IN 2009.
>>> TOMORROW MARKS THE 50th
ANNIVERSARY OF THE MARCH ON
WASHINGTON AND MARTIN LUTHER
KING'S LANDMARK "I HAVE A DREAM"
SPEECH.
DR. KING'S YOUNGEST DAUGHTER
BERNICE WAS JUST 5 MONTHS OLD
THAT DAY IN 1963.
WE SAT DOWN WITH HER RECENTLY AT
HISTORIC EBENEZER BAPTIST CHURCH
IN ATLANTA WHERE HER FATHER WAS
PASTOR.
SHE TALKED ABOUT THE SPEECH AND
MEMORIES OF HER FATHER.
HERE'S BERNICE KING IN HER OWN
WORDS.
>> HIM LIFTING ME UP IS EXACTLY
WHAT I REMEMBER GROWING UP WITH
MY FATHER.
YOU KNOW, AS I GREW UP, I HAD A
RANGE OF EMOTIONS.
I BECAME, YOU KNOW, ANGRY.
ANGRY THAT HE LEFT, ANGRY AT GOD
FOR NOT PROTECTING HIM.
ANGRY AT WHITES AT THE TIME,
BECAUSE I FELT THEY WERE
RESPONSIBLE FOR HIS DEATH.
ANGRY AT BLACKS BECAUSE I FELT
WE WEREN'T DOING ENOUGH TO
CONTINUE HIS WORK.
AND SO I THINK AT THAT MOMENT, I
REALIZED THE IMPORTANCE OF HIS
CONTRIBUTION, BUT AT THE SAME
TIME, I REALIZED THE MAGNITUDE
OF MY OWN LOSS.
IN THE SENSE THAT, YOU KNOW, WHY
MY DAD?
>> BECAUSE I HAVE A DREAM --
>> EVERY TIME HE SPEAKS, YOU
KNOW, HE'S CHALLENGING US TO BE
BETTER, TO DO MORE.
>> -- THAT MY FOUR LITTLE
CHILDREN WILL ONE DAY LIVE IN A
NATION WHERE THEY WILL NOT BE
JUDGED BY THE COLOR OF THEIR
SKIN, BUT BY THE CONTENT OF
THEIR CHARACTER.
I HAVE A DREAM.
>> THE WHOLE PURPOSE OF
REMEMBERING AND COMMEMORATING IS
NOT TO BE SATISFIED WITH JUST
THE ACCOMPLISHMENTS THAT WE'VE
MADE, BUT IT'S ALSO TO FURTHER
INSPIRE US.
BECAUSE MY MOTHER SAYS TROUBLE
IS A NEVER ENDING PROCESS.
FREEDOM IS NEVER REALLY WON, YOU
EARN IT AND WIN IT IN EVERY
GENERATION.
>> FREE AT LAST.
FREE AT LAST.
THANK GOD ALL MIGHTY, WE ARE
>> IT DOESN'T MATTER HOW MANY
TIMES I LISTEN TO IT, IT'S
ALWAYS, WOW!
I WISH HE WERE HERE.
>> BERNICE KING IN HER OWN WORDS
TONIGHT.
WE'LL BE BROADCASTING FROM
WASHINGTON TOMORROW.
YOU CAN JOIN THE NBC NEWS DREAM
DAY PROJECT USING THE #DREAMDAY.
WE'LL BE RIGHT BACK.
>>> OUR FINAL STORY TONIGHT IS
ABOUT A SMALL BUT EXTRAORDINARY
RAY OF HOPE IN A PLACE WHERE
THERE'S FAR TOO LITTLE HOPE.
THAT SYRIAN REFUGEE CAMP IN
JORDAN.
NBC'S ANN CURRY HAS THE STORY OF
ONE YOUNG BOY IN DESPERATE NEED
OF MEDICAL ATTENTION, AND A
DOCTOR WHO'S MAKING A DIFFERENCE
TO HELP HIM.
>> Reporter: ON THE MOVE THROUGH
ZAATARI CAMP, A DOCTOR LEADS US
TO ONE OF THE MOST VULNERABLE
HERE.
SULEMAN, A REFUGEE HIMSELF, WAS
DETERMINED TO GET HELP FOR A BOY
WHO DESPERATELY NEEDED IT.
>> WHEN I SAW HIM, THE LIFE IN
MY EYES DIED.
>> Reporter: THE LIFE IN YOUR
EYES DIED WHEN YOU SAW HIM?
>> WHEN I SAW HIM.
>> Reporter: SULEMAN TOOK US TO
THE BOY'S MOTHER.
MAY WE SEE YOUR SON?
SHE LED US DOWN UNMARKED ROADS
TO A PLACE WE COULD NOT HAVE
FOUND BY OURSELVES, INTO HER
SMALL SHELTER.
AND THERE HE WAS, HIS FACE
GAUNT, HIS ARMS LIKE TWIGS.
HIS NAME IS IBRAHIM.
HE IS 10 YEARS OLD, BORN IN
SYRIA WITH A CONDITION THAT
CAUSES HIS MUSCLES TO ATROPHY.
PHYSICAL THERAPY HAD HELPED HIM
WALK, HIS MOTHER SAYS, BUT
SYRIA'S WAR HAS CHANGED THAT.
IN THE PAST SIX MONTHS, HE'S
LOST MORE THAN 20% OF HIS BODY
WEIGHT, CAN NO LONGER STAND, AND
WON'T EAT.
WHY CAN'T YOU EAT?
HE SAYS "MY STOMACH FEELS
FUNNY."
HIS MOTHER FEARS FOR HIS LIFE.
SHE SAYS, I'M VERY SAD ABOUT MY
SON.
HIS FATHER WAS KILLED.
SINCE THEY FLED HERE, SHE'S
TRYING TO GET HELP AS HER SON'S
CONDITION WORSENS.
BUT SHE SAYS LOCAL CLINICS
TURNED HER AWAY.
WE SUGGESTED A CLINIC SHE DIDN'T
KNOW ABOUT, IN THIS SPRAWLING
CAMP AND OFFERED HER AND IBRAHIM
A RIDE THERE.
15 MINUTES LATER, AT THE GATES
OF DOCTORS WITHOUT BORDERS, A
YOUNG PHYSICIAN ADMITTED
IBRAHIM, AND SOON DOCTORS WERE
GIVING HIM A CHECKUP.
THEY SAY THEY'LL REFER HIM TO A
SPECIALIST WHO MIGHT ONE DAY
HELP HIM WALK AGAIN.
IN THE MEANTIME, THEY OFFER
NUTRITIONAL SUPPLEMENTS AND
WEEKLY CHECKUPS TO HELP HIM GAIN
WEIGHT AND GET STRONGER.
TODAY, THAT'S ENOUGH TO GIVE A
WORRIED MOTHER AND HER SON HOPE
FAR FROM HOME.
ANN CURRY, NBC NEWS JORDAN.
>>> THAT'S OUR BROADCAST FOR
THIS TUESDAY NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR BEING WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT IN FOR BRIAN.
WE HOPE TO SEE YOU RIGHT BACK
HERE TOMORROW EVENING.
GOOD NIGHT.
>>> NBC BAY AREA NAHS BEGINS
WITH BREAKING NEWS.
>>> THAT BREAKING NEWS RIGHT NOW
OVER FAIRFIELD, A NEIGHBORHOOD
RAVAGED BY FIRE.
THE PD TELLS US AT LEAST FIVE
HOMES HAVE BURNED, AND AT ONE
POINT AT LEAST TEN OTHERS WERE
THREATENED, INCLUDING AN
APARTMENT COMPLEX.
AS MANY AS 50 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
EVACUATED.
THIS IS WHAT IT LOOKED LIKE JUST
AFTER IT BROKE OUT AROUND 3:30
THIS AFTERNOON.
ROOFS ON FIRE, INTENSE FLAMES
SHOOTING OUT, AND THICK, BLACK
SMOKE.
NOW CREWS AT THIS MOMENT ARE
STILL WORKING TO CONTAIN THE
FIRE, BUT IT LOOKS AS IF THEY'VE
GOTTEN A HANDLE ON IT.
WANT TO SHOW YOU EXACTLY WHERE
THAT FIRE WAS BURNING.
IT'S IN FAIRFIELD, NOT FAR FROM
THE FAIRFIELD HIGH SCHOOL ON
MARIGOLD DROVE.
IT'S EAST OF I-80.
>>> NOW A LIVE LOOK FROM OUR NBC
CHOPPER WHICH HAS BEEN ON THE
SCENE SINCE THIS FIRE BROKE OUT
AROUND 3:30 OR 3:45 THIS
AFTERNOON
>>> THAT'S EASTBOUND 80 AT THE
BOTTOM OF YOUR SCREEN, AND THE
SMALL A GOOD NEWS HERE IS THAT
80 HAS BEEN OPEN THROUGHOUT THIS
ORDEAL.
SMOKE HAS BEEN GOING THE OTHER
WAY INTO THE COMMUNITY AND AWAY
FROM 80.
SO THE COMMUTE, THOUGH IT'S
SLUGGISH, 80 REMAINS OPEN.
WE WANT TO BRING IN GAIL SPEARS,
A SPOKESPERSON FROM THE CITY OF
FAIRFIELD.
ARE YOU WITH US?
>> CALLER: I AM.
>> AT THIS POINT, IT'S 6:00.
CAN YOU TELL US THE VERY LATEST?
>> Caller: WE'VE OPENED AN
EVACUATION CENTER OVER AT
FAIRFIELD HIGH