FOR US AT 5:00.
LESTER HOLT JOINS US FROM PUERTO
RICO IN NIGHTLY NEWS.
>>> SEVERAL DEVELOPING
STORIES TONIGHT.
HERE IN PUERTO RICO
APOCALYPTIC SCENES.
OUR FIRST LOOK AT
GROUND ZERO WHERE
HURRICANE MARIA MADE
LANDFALL, AND WE'RE
WITH THE MILITARY AMID
A MASSIVE HUMANITARIAN
CRISIS LIKE FEW WE'VE
EVER SEEN BEFORE.
>>> NORTH KOREA CALLS
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
THREATENING RHETORIC A
DECLARATION OF WAR AND
WARNS IT HAS THE RIGHT
TO SHOOT DOWN AMERICAN
BOMBERS IN
INTERNATIONAL AIR
SPACE.
A DANGEROUS NEW
ESCALATION WITH A
NUCLEAR-ARMED NATION.
>>> CRITICAL
CONDITION.
PROTESTERS IN
WHEELCHAIRS ARE
DRAGGED FROM A HEARING
AT THE CAPITOL.
A DRAMATIC
CLIFF-HANGER WITH THE
CLOCK TICKING DOWN.
REPUBLICANS MOUNT A
LAST GASP PUSH TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE.
>>> THE WHITE HOUSE
TODAY PLAYING DEFENSE
OVER PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
NFL TIRADE.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> THIS IS NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT REPORTING
TONIGHT FROM SAN JUAN,
PUERTO RICO.
>>> AND GOOD EVENING
FROM SAN JUAN.
WE MADE OUR WAY TO
PUERTO RICO TODAY.
A DAY-LONG JOURNEY
ABOARD A MILITARY
TRANSPORT.
AIR NATIONAL GUARD HAS
AN AIR BRIDGE GOING
NOW.
A MASSIVE RELIEF
OPERATION.
THERE IS DEVASTATION
EVERYWHERE.
IT IS LIKE A CURTAIN
IS SLOWLY BEING LIFTED
ON THIS DISASTER
REVEALING MORE AND
MORE OF THE SUFFERING
AND THE DIRE STRAITS
ON THIS ISLAND.
POWER IS STILL LARGELY
OUT.
THAT MEANS BANKS AND
HOSPITALS AND THE
THINGS THAT PEOPLE
DEPEND ON, THEY CAN'T
GET TO UNLESS THERE
ARE GENERATORS
WORKING.
AND IN THOSE CASES
THERE ARE LONG LINES.
GAS STATIONS.
GETTING WATER IS
EXTRAORDINARILY
DIFFICULT.
WE'RE GETTING OUR
FIRST LOOK AT THE
GROUND ZERO WHERE
HURRICANE MARIA MADE
ITS LANDFALL ALMOST A
WEEK AGO.
OUR GABE GUTIERREZ IS
THERE TONIGHT AND HAS
MORE.
GABE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER,
THE MASSIVE CLEANUP
EFFORT IS UNDER WAY.
THIS IS THE AREA WHERE
THE EYE OF THE STORM
HIT.
ROOFS BLOWN OFF, LIVES
TORN APART.
THERE IS STILL A
DESPERATE NEED TO
COMMUNICATE.
NO POWER AND NO END IN
SIGHT.
WHEN MARIA ROARED ON
SHORE, PUERTO RICO'S
SOUTHEAST CORNER
ENDURED THE FIRST
IMPACT.
>> THIS IS THE TOWN,
YES.
>> Reporter: IN THE
COASTAL TOWN OF
MAUNABO, NORMA ROSADO
LOST THE ROOF OFF HER
HOME AND HER SMALL
BUSINESS BLEW AWAY
ENTIRELY.
>> MANY OF US, WE
DON'T HAVE A LOT OF
MONEY.
THAT WILL TAKE US A
LONG TIME TO RECOVER
FROM THE THINGS THAT
WE LOST.
>> Reporter: NOW THE
HUNT IS ON HERE FOR
THE BASICS.
THIS WOMAN SNAGGING
WATER FROM THE SIDE OF
A MOUNTAIN.
EVERYTHING IS
DESTROYED, SHE SAYS.
WITH MANGLED POWER
LINES EVERYWHERE AND
EYE-POPPING LINES AT
GAS STATIONS, PEOPLE
HERE FEEL PARALYZED
AND DISCONNECTED.
SATELLITE IMAGES SHOW
THE ISLAND BEFORE
MARIA HIT AND AFTER,
NOW ALMOST TOTALLY IN
THE DARK.
NO CELL SERVICE
EITHER.
AND THIS WOMAN HASN'T
BEEN ABLE TO REACH HER
FAMILY IN
INDIANAPOLIS.
WHEN OFFERED A
SATELLITE PHONE, SHE
TELLS THEM SHE'S ALL
RIGHT, BUT HER
95-YEAR-OLD
GRANDFATHER PASSED
AWAY DURING THE STORM.
TODAY SAN JUAN'S
AIRPORT PACKED AS
TRAVELERS RUSHED TO
ESCAPE ON THE FEW
COMMERCIAL FLIGHTS.
THE U.S. MILITARY
DELIVERING
HUMANITARIAN AID,
LAUNCHING RELIEF
MISSIONS FROM THE "USS
KEARSARGE" BY AIR AND
SEA.
>> THE MARINES ARE
HERE, THE MARINES ARE
LANDING.
>> Reporter: RUSHING
TO HELP CLEAR ROADS.
>> THIS WILL NOT
HAPPEN OVERNIGHT.
THIS IS GOING TO BE A
MARATHON.
>> Reporter: IN
NORTHWEST PUERTO RICO
ENGINEERS ARE
INSPECTING A MAJOR DAM
AFTER FINDING A CRACK.
THANKFULLY SO FAR IT'S
HOLDING.
>> IT IS SAD TO SEE.
>> Reporter: OUTSIDE
SAN JUAN PASTOR
ANTONIO FONT RUNS THIS
MASSIVE CHURCH THAT
HIS FATHER BUILT AND
MARIA RIPPED APART.
>> AND TO SEE IT JUST
DESTROYED IN JUST A
FEW HOURS IS REALLY
SAD, BUT WE ARE A
CHURCH OF HOPE.
SO WE ARE GOING TO
REBUILD.
>> Reporter:
REBUILDING WILL TAKE
TIME FOR AN ISLAND IN
CRISIS AND IN NEED.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS MAUNABO, PUERTO
RICO.
>>> AS WE NOTED, WE
ARRIVED HERE TODAY
ABOARD AN AIR NATIONAL
GUARD C-130.
AN OPERATION IS BEING
STAGED, ESSENTIALLY A
HUB AND SPOKE
OPERATION, OUT OF
GEORGIA BRINGING
PLANES WITH NEEDED
RELIEF MATERIALS.
AND THEY'RE REALIZING
NOW THIS IS A MISSION
THAT'S GOING TO LAST A
LONG TIME.
THIS SMALL PIECE OF
AMERICA ALMOST A
THOUSAND MILES FROM
THE U.S. MAINLAND HAS
NEVER FELT MORE
REMOTE, BUT IT IS NOT
FORGOTTEN.
WITH THE SUN BARELY
UP, THIS CORNER OF THE
SAVANNAH INTERNATIONAL
AIRPORT IN GEORGIA WAS
ALIVE WITH THE SOUNDS
OF VITAL PROVISIONS
BEING LOADED ABOARD
NATIONAL GUARD
TRANSPORTS.
A HUB OF AN AERIAL
LIFELINE PROVIDING
HUMANITARIAN AID THAT
TAKES ON ADDED MEANING
FOR THESE CREWS.
>> WE SPEND MOST OF
THE TIME TRYING TO DO
THIS OVERSEAS, OVER IN
A WAR ZONE.
TO BE ABLE TO DO IT
BACK HOME AND HELP OUT
OUR FELLOW AMERICAN
CITIZENS HERE AFTER
SOME OF THESE
HURRICANES, IT'S
PRETTY REWARDING.
>> Reporter: FOR THIS
CREW OF THIS PUERTO
RICO NATIONAL GUARD
C-130, THEIR MISSION
THIS WEEKEND WAS
PERSONAL.
>> IT'S BEEN A
SACRIFICE NOT TO BE
WITH MY FAMILY, BUT
MISSION COMES FIRST.
SO WE ARE READY TO
JUST GO BACK, SEE OUR
FAMILIES, THEN HEAD
BACK TO THE STATES OR
WHATEVER TO GET THE
SUPPLIES.
>> Reporter: YOU CAN
SEE THE RAMP IS LINED
WITH PLANES FROM
NATIONAL GUARD UNITS
ACROSS THE COUNTRY,
KENTUCKY AND TEXAS AND
MISSOURI.
THIS C-130 BELONGS TO
THE RHODE ISLAND
NATIONAL GUARD.
WE'LL BE TRAVELING ON
THIS ONE TO SAN JUAN
AFTER A BRIEF STOP IN
ST. CROIX.
THEY'RE LOADING WATER
AND MEALS
READY-TO-EAT.
ONCE AIRBORNE, THE
URGENCY OF THIS
HUMANITARIAN MISSION
IS APPARENT ON THEIR
FACES.
WHAT'S IT LIKE FLYING
INTO THE HURRICANE
ZONES IN TERMS OF WHAT
YOU'RE SEEING OUT THE
WINDOW WHEN YOU'RE
DESCENDING?
>> IT'S A LITTLE
DISTRACTING, TO BE
HONEST WITH YOU.
I HAVE A LOT TO DO UP
HERE IN THE RIGHT
SEAT, BUT WHEN I SEE
SOME OF THE
DEVASTATION DOWN THERE
ON THE GROUND, IT'S
PRETTY BAD.
I'VE NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT.
>> Reporter: GETTING
INTO SAN JUAN HAS NOT
BEEN EASY, THE AIRPORT
HAS BEEN STRUGGLING TO
GET UP TO FULL
OPERATIONS.
>> A LOT OF THE
FACILITIES THAT WE USE
TO NAVIGATE AREN'T UP.
IT'S KINDS OF LIKE THE
WILD WEST A LITTLE
BIT.
BUT WE'RE TRAINED TO
DO IT, AND WE DO IT
PRETTY WELL, I THINK.
>> Reporter: FINALLY
ON THE GROUND YOU
DON'T HAVE TO GO FAR
FROM THE AIRPORT TO
APPRECIATE JUST HOW
GREAT THE NEED IS.
THE MILITARY HAS PUT
THEIR OWN RADAR SYSTEM
IN PLACE TEMPORARILY
HERE.
THEY'RE TRYING TO GET
IT LINKED INTO THE FAA
SYSTEM.
THAT WILL ALLOW THEM
TO BRING MORE FLIGHTS
IN AS THE DAYS GO ON.
EVEN AS WE LOOK AT
WHAT HURRICANE MARIA
DID TO PUERTO RICO,
BELIEVE IT OR NOT
TONIGHT, IT IS STILL A
HURRICANE, A CATEGORY
1.
WHILE IT'S NOT A
THREAT TO MAKE
LANDFALL IN THE U.S.,
TROPICAL STORM FORCE
WINDS ARE EXPECTED ON
THE OUTER BANKS OF
NORTH CAROLINA.
ALSO A 2 TO 4-FOOT
STORM SURGE AND
DANGEROUS SURF BEFORE
THIS STORM TURNS
FURTHER OUT TO SEA.
WE'LL HAVE MORE FROM
PUERTO RICO IN JUST A
MOMENT, BUT FIRST,
LET'S SEND IT UP TO
NEW YORK WITH SAVANNAH
GUTHRIE WHO HAS SOME
OF THE OTHER BIG
STORIES OF THE DAY.
HI, SAVANNAH.
>> HI, LESTER.
THERE IS BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT OUT OF
WASHINGTON WHERE A
THIRD REPUBLICAN
SENATOR HAS NOW COME
OUT AGAINST THE LATEST
GOP BILL TO REPEAL AND
REPLACE OBAMACARE.
THAT'S ENOUGH NO VOTES
TO DOOM THAT BILL.
THIS COMES HOURS AFTER
PROTESTS ERUPTED
INSIDE THE CAPITOL,
SOME DEMONSTRATORS IN
WHEELCHAIRS DRAGGED
FROM THE HEARING.
OUR CAPITOL HILL
CORRESPONDENT KASIE
HUNT WAS THERE FOR THE
DRAMATIC MOMENTS AND
HAS ALL THE LATE
DETAILS.
>> Reporter: AFTER AN
EMOTIONAL DAY OF
PROTESTS AND DOZENS OF
ARRESTS, THE
LAST-DITCH REPUBLICAN
EFFORT TO REPEAL
OBAMACARE APPARENTLY
DEAD TONIGHT WITH
SENATOR SUSAN COLLINS
OF MAINE ANNOUNCING
SHE'S A NO AFTER THE
NONPARTISAN
CONGRESSIONAL BUDGET
OFFICE SAID LATE
TONIGHT THAT MILLIONS
MORE WOULD LOSE
COVERAGE.
THIS BILL WILL HAVE A
SUBSTANTIALLY NEGATIVE
IMPACT ON THE NUMBER
OF PEOPLE COVERED BY
INSURANCE, COLLINS
WROTE IN A LENGTHY
STATEMENT.
WITH ONLY 52
REPUBLICANS IN THE
SENATE AND RAND PAUL
AND JOHN McCAIN ALSO
VOTING NO, THERE'S NO
PATH FORWARD.
EARLIER TODAY THE
BILL'S CO-AUTHOR --
>> SOMEBODY BETTER
COME UP WITH A WAY TO
GET MEDICAID IN A
SUSTAINABLE FASHION OR
ELSE IT'S GOING TO
BREAK THE BANK.
>> Reporter: THE
BILL'S ONLY HEARING
HELD TODAY WAS DELAYED
BY PROTESTERS WHO
SHOWED UP BEFORE DAWN.
>> WE LEFT OUR HOTEL
AT 4:30 IN THE
MORNING.
>> Reporter: SCREAMING
AT ITS CO-AUTHOR
LINDSEY GRAHAM.
>> SHAME, SHAME,
SHAME.
>> Reporter: ONCE
INSIDE, YELLING.
CAPITOL POLICE
DRAGGING PROTESTERS IN
WHEELCHAIRS FROM THE
ROOM.
THE HEARING DELAYED.
>> IF YOU WANT A
HEARING, YOU BETTER
SHUT UP.
>> Reporter: GRAHAM
WAITING TO TESTIFY,
AND THE BILL'S OTHER
AUTHOR DR. BILL
CASSIDY.
THE PUBLIC SPECTACLE
PLAYING OUT ACROSS
CAPITOL HILL.
THE CBO ESTIMATED THAT
MILLIONS OF PEOPLE
WITH EXPENSIVE
PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS WOULD NOT
HAVE COMPREHENSIVE
COVERAGE UNDER THE
PLAN BUT THAT IT'S
HARD TO KNOW THE EXACT
NUMBER BECAUSE IT
COULD VARY WIDELY BY
STATE.
THAT'S WHAT WORRIES
SHAELYNN WHO DROVE
FROM PENNSYLVANIA WITH
HER SISTER BRITTANY
WHO HAS CEREBRAL
PALSY.
>> SHE WAS BORN WITH
THIS DISABILITY.
SHE IS WHAT'S
CONSIDERED A
PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION.
UNFORTUNATELY FOR HER,
HER SERVICES WOULD GET
CUT TREMENDOUSLY.
>> Reporter: AFTER A
FEW MINUTES INSIDE
SHAELYNN WAS DRAGGED
OUT AND ARRESTED.
A FEW HOURS LATER THE
GOP EFFORT HAD FAILED
AGAIN.
THIS IS ANOTHER
EMBARRASSMENT FOR
REPUBLICANS WHO HAVE
BEEN TRYING TO REPEAL
AND REPLACE OBAMACARE
FOR SEVEN YEARS.
THE QUESTION NOW
WHETHER REPUBLICAN
LEADERS WILL EVEN PUT
THIS ON THE FLOOR FOR
A VOTE, AND TONIGHT
THAT SEEMS UNLIKELY.
SAVANNAH?
>> ALL RIGHT, KASIE
HUNT, THANK YOU SO
MUCH.
>>> NOW TO THE
SITUATION BETWEEN THE
U.S. AND NORTH KOREA.
IT HAS BEEN A WAR OF
WORDS, BUT NOW THE
FOREIGN MINISTER OF
NORTH KOREA IS SAYING
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
RECENT THREATS ARE, IN
FACT, A DECLARATION OF
WAR.
ARE WE HEADED TOWARD A
MILITARY
CONFRONTATION?
NBC'S RICHARD ENGEL
NOW ON THE NEW WORRIES
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: ON THE
SAME DAY NORTH KOREA
SAID THE U.S. HAS
DECLARED WAR, IT
RELEASED A COMPUTER
SIMULATION SHOWING HOW
IT WOULD DESTROY
AMERICAN AIRCRAFT AND
SET A CARRIER ABLAZE.
IT'S PROPAGANDA BUT
EXPERTS SAY THERE IS
NOW A REAL RISK OF AN
EXCHANGE OF FIRE WITH
NUCLEAR-ARMED NORTH
KOREA OR WORSE.
THE GROWING CONCERN
COMES AFTER PRESIDENT
TRUMP STEPPED UP HIS
PERSONAL INSULTS
AGAINST KIM JONG-UN
LABELING HIM LITTLE
ROCKET MAN AND
TWEETING, HE WON'T BE
AROUND MUCH LONGER.
BEYOND RHETORIC, THE
U.S. THIS WEEKEND FLEW
TWO ADVANCED BOMBERS
NEAR NORTH KOREA'S
BORDER.
NORTH KOREA'S FOREIGN
MINISTER REPLIED
TODAY.
"SINCE THE UNITED
STATES DECLARED WAR ON
OUR COUNTRY," HE SAID,
"WE WILL HAVE THE
RIGHT TO MAKE
COUNTERMEASURES
INCLUDING SHOOTING
DOWN U.S. BOMBERS EVEN
OUTSIDE NORTH KOREAN
AIR SPACE."
>> WE'VE NOT DECLARED
WAR ON NORTH KOREA,
AND FRANKLY, THE
SUGGESTION OF THAT IS
ABSURD.
>> Reporter: FORMER
NATO SUPREME ALLIED
COMMANDER ADMIRAL
JAMES STAVRIDIS, AN
NBC NEWS CONTRIBUTOR,
SAYS THIS MAY GO
BEYOND THE WAR OF
WORDS.
>> I WOULD SAY THE
CHANCES OF AN EXCHANGE
OF ORDNANCE ARE NOW
APPROACHING 50/50.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS
NORTH KOREA COULD FIRE
AT AN AMERICAN JET OR
SHIP.
THE U.S. COULD FIRE
BACK.
>> WE ARE AT SUCH A
HIGH LEVEL OF
POTENTIAL ESCALATION
TO FULL-BLOWN WAR
BECAUSE OF THE
RELATIVE INEXPERIENCE
OF THE LEADER IN
PYONGYANG AND THE
LEADER IN WASHINGTON.
>> Reporter: THE
SPOKESMAN FOR THE
UNITED NATIONS TODAY
SEEMED TO AGREE.
>> FIERY TALK CAN LEAD
TO FATAL
MISUNDERSTANDINGS.
>> Reporter: CONCERN
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
KIM JONG-UN'S GAME OF
BRINKMANSHIP COULD
BECOME A CONFLICT.
THE BIG WORRY AMONG
EXPERTS IS THAT THERE
IS SOME EXCHANGE OF
FIRE PERHAPS FUELED BY
THE RHETORIC AND THAT
IT SNOWBALLS.
THE NATIONAL SECURITY
ADVISER, H.R.
McMASTER, SAID THE
U.S. DOESN'T WANT WAR
BUT CAN'T DISCOUNT THE
POSSIBILITY.
SAVANNAH, BACK TO YOU.
>> RICHARD, THANK YOU.
>>> TONIGHT THE WHITE
HOUSE IS PLAYING
DEFENSE, CAUGHT IN A
FIRESTORM OVER
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
TARGETING OF NFL
PLAYERS FOR KNEELING
DURING THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM.
IN THE MEANTIME, THE
PRESIDENT TODAY IS
CONTINUING TO FAN THE
FLAMES.
NBC'S PETER ALEXANDER
HAS THE HEATED BACK
AND FORTH.
>> Reporter: AFTER A
WAVE OF DEFIANCE, THE
SPORTS WORLD STANDING
UP TO THE PRESIDENT BY
KNEELING DOWN, TONIGHT
SOME OF THE GREATEST
ATHLETES ARE CALLING
OUT PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> WE HAVE TO FIGURE
OUT A WAY TO COME
TOGETHER AND BE AS
GREAT AS WE CAN BE AS
A PEOPLE.
BECAUSE THE PEOPLE RUN
THIS COUNTRY, NOT ONE
INDIVIDUAL.
AND DAMN SURE NOT HIM.
>> Reporter: BUT THE
PRESIDENT'S NOT
BACKING DOWN.
TODAY TWEETING STAND
FOR OUR ANTHEM,
INSISTING THE ISSUE OF
KNEELING HAS NOTHING
TO DO WITH RACE.
DESPITE HIS POLARIZING
COMMENTS ATTACKING
COLIN KAEPERNICK,
AMONG OTHERS, WHO
BEGAN TAKING A KNEE
DURING THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM LAST YEAR TO
HIGHLIGHT POLICE
BRUTALITY AND RACIAL
INJUSTICE.
>> WOULDN'T YOU LOVE
TO SEE ONE OF THESE
NFL OWNERS WHEN
SOMEBODY DISRESPECTS
OUR FLAG, TO SAY, GET
THAT SON OF A BITCH
OFF THE FIELD RIGHT
NOW?
OUT!
HE'S FIRED!
>> Reporter: THE
ROSTER OF CRITICS
GROWING INCLUDING
PATRIOTS QUARTERBACK
AND TRUMP FRIEND TOM
BRADY.
>> I CERTAINLY
DISAGREE WITH WHAT HE
SAID AND, YOU KNOW,
THOUGHT IT WAS JUST
DIVISIVE.
>> THIS ISN'T ABOUT
THE PRESIDENT BEING
AGAINST ANYONE, BUT
THIS IS ABOUT THE
PRESIDENT AND MILLIONS
OF AMERICANS BEING FOR
SOMETHING, BEING FOR
HONORING OUR FLAG,
HONORING OUR NATIONAL
ANTHEM.
>> Reporter: THE
INTERSECTION OF SPORTS
AND POLITICS DATES
BACK DECADES, FROM
MUHAMMAD ALI TO MEXICO
CITY, BUT NOW FRESH
BATTLE LINES ARE BEING
DRAWN.
SEVERAL NASCAR OWNERS
WARNING THEY'LL BOOT
TEAMMATES WHO
DEMONSTRATE.
WHILE ONE OF THE
SPORT'S BIGGEST NAMES,
DALE EARNHARDT JR., IS
VOICING HIS SUPPORT
FOR PEACEFUL PROTESTS.
TONIGHT THE NFL
SPOKESMAN WHO SAYS
THIS FEUD HAS UNIFIED
THE LEAGUE AND ITS
PLAYERS IS DELIVERING
A MESSAGE TO THE
PRESIDENT INSISTING IF
HE WANTS TO ENGAGE IN
A POSITIVE,
CONSTRUCTIVE
CONVERSATION, HE HAS
THEIR NUMBER.
SAVANNAH.
>> PETER, THANK YOU
VERY MUCH.
>>> ALSO FROM THE
WHITE HOUSE, NEWS
ABOUT THE NEW TRAVEL
BAN THE ADMINISTRATION
IS HOPING WILL PASS
MUSTER WITH THE
SUPREME COURT WHICH
WEIGHED IN ON THE
ISSUE TODAY AS THE
PRESIDENT'S SENIOR
ADVISER AND SON-IN-LAW
WAS SWEPT UP IN A
CONTROVERSY ALL TOO
FAMILIAR OVER HIS
E-MAIL.
CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HALLIE
JACKSON NOW WITH THE
STORY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE PRESIDENT'S
ORIGINAL TRAVEL BAN
LONG IN LEGAL LIMBO IS
CATCHING A BREAK FROM
THE SUPREME COURT.
THE JUSTICES SET TO
HEAR ARGUMENTS IN TWO
WEEKS ARE INSTEAD
POSTPONING THAT, A
SIGN THE COURT THINKS
THE LEGAL BATTLE OVER
THE OLD BAN IS MOOT
BECAUSE OF THE NEW
VERSION JUST UNVEILED.
>> THE TOUGHER, THE
BETTER.
>> Reporter: THE
PRESIDENT'S NEW
TOUGHER BAN PUTS
INDEFINITE
RESTRICTIONS ON
VISITORS AND
IMMIGRANTS FROM EIGHT
NATIONS INCLUDING FIVE
MUSLIM COUNTRIES ON
THE ORIGINAL LIST.
THE LATEST VERSION
REMOVES SUDAN AND ADDS
CHAD, VENEZUELA AND
NORTH KOREA.
WITH CRITICS ARGUING
IT STILL SEEMS LIKE
RELIGIOUS PROFILING TO
THEM.
>> IT REEKS OF THE
FIRST TWO TRAVEL BANS
WHERE THEY WERE
TARGETING MUSLIMS IN
FIRST TWO AND EVEN
WITH THE ADDITION OF
NORTH KOREA AND
VENEZUELA, AT ITS
CORE, IT'S STILL A
MUSLIM BAN.
>> Reporter: THE NEW
TRAVEL BAN JUST ONE OF
THE HEADLINES OUT OF
THE WHITE HOUSE TODAY
INCLUDING THIS ONE.
JARED KUSHNER, THE
PRESIDENT'S
SON-IN-LAW, USING
PRIVATE E-MAIL AS A
GOVERNMENT EMPLOYEE.
HIS LAWYER TELLS NBC
THOSE MESSAGES WERE
MOSTLY NEWS ARTICLES
OR COMMENTARY
FORWARDED TO KUSHNER'S
OFFICIAL ADDRESS AND
PRESERVED.
WILL THE WHITE HOUSE
COMMIT TO RELEASING
JARED KUSHNER'S
PRIVATE E-MAILS
RELATED TO GOVERNMENT
BUSINESS?
>> I'D HAVE TO ASK.
I'M NOT AWARE OF THAT
CONVERSATION.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS
NOW DEMANDING TO SEE
THOSE E-MAILS.
IT'S DIFFERENT FROM
WHAT HILLARY CLINTON
DID, USE A PRIVATE
SERVER REPEATEDLY AS
SECRETARY OF STATE.
STILL, AFTER CAMPAIGN
MOMENTS LIKE THESE --
>> I MADE A MISTAKE
USING A PRIVATE
E-MAIL.
>> THAT'S FOR SURE.
>> Reporter: A
POLITICAL IRONY TO
SOME IS INESCAPABLE.
CLINTON WITH MSNBC'S
CHRIS HAYES.
>> I'M WAITING TO SEE
THE OUTRAGE ON THE
PART OF REPUBLICAN
MEMBERS OF CONGRESS
ABOUT THIS.
AND YOU WILL NOT SEE
IT.
>> Reporter: HALLIE
JACKSON, NBC NEWS, THE
WHITE HOUSE.
>>> FORMER CONGRESSMAN
ANTHONY WEINER IS
HEADED TO PRISON.
HE WAS SENTENCED TODAY
TO 21 MONTHS FOR
SEXTING WITH A
15-YEAR-OLD GIRL.
WEINER IS THE
ESTRANGED HUSBAND OF
ONE OF HILLARY
CLINTON'S MOST SENIOR
AIDES, HUMA ABEDIN.
HE WAS FINED $10,000
AND ORDERED TO REPORT
TO PRISON BY NOVEMBER
6.
HE ALSO MUST ENTER
INTO A SEX OFFENDER
TREATMENT PROGRAM
AFTER HIS RELEASE.
>>> STILL AHEAD, MORE
FROM LESTER IN PUERTO
RICO.
>>> AND THE TERRIFYING
MOMENTS WHEN A GUNMAN
OPENED FIRE AT A
CHURCH IN TENNESSEE.
SURVIVORS DESCRIBE
WHAT IT WAS LIKE, AS
WE LEARN NEW DETAILS
ABOUT THE SUSPECT.
STAY WITH US.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH A
BIG UNANSWERED
QUESTION ONE DAY AFTER
A GUNMAN OPENED FIRE
AT A CHURCH IN
TENNESSEE KILLING A
WOMAN AND INJURING
HALF A DOZEN OTHER
PEOPLE.
JUST WHAT WAS THE
ALLEGED SHOOTER'S
MOTIVATION?
WE GET THE LATEST NOW
FROM NBC'S KERRY
SANDERS.
>> Reporter: PRAYERS
TODAY FOR THE VICTIMS
SHOT BY A MASKED
GUNMAN MOMENTS AFTER
CHURCH SERVICES
CONCLUDED ON SUNDAY.
>> DISPATCH, THIS IS A
LEVEL ONE MASS
CASUALTY INCIDENT.
>> Reporter: SIX
PEOPLE INJURED.
A SEVENTH, 39-YEAR-OLD
MELANIE SMITH, KILLED
IN THE PARKING LOT.
HER 19-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER, BRIANNA.
>> THERE'S NO
UNDERSTANDING IT.
>> Reporter: THE
SUSPECT, 25-YEAR-OLD
EMANUEL KIDEGA SAMSON
ACCIDENTALLY SHOT
HIMSELF WHEN AN USHER
WRESTLED HIM TO THE
GROUND.
22-YEAR-OLD CALEB
ENGEL HELD THE ALLEGED
GUNMAN AT BAY WITH
HIS OWN PISTOL.
>> HE'S MY HERO.
>> Reporter: MINERVA
WAS FEET FROM THE
GUNMAN WHEN HE BEGAN
SHOOTING.
HER 6-YEAR-OLD SON AND
SEVEN OTHER KIDS IN A
BIBLE STUDY CLASS
BARRICADING THEMSELVES
BEHIND A CLOSED DOOR.
WHAT ABOUT YOUR OWN
SAFETY?
>> YOU KNOW, YOU'RE A
MOTHER.
YOU DON'T EVEN THINK
ABOUT YOU.
>> Reporter: ACCORDING
TO AN AFFIDAVIT,
SAMSON ADMITTED HE WAS
ARMED WITH A HANDGUN
AND HE FIRED UPON THE
CHURCH BUILDING.
SAMSON, AN AMATEUR
BODY BUILDER STUDYING
TO BECOME A SECURITY
GUARD, EMIGRATED TO
THIS COUNTRY FROM
SUDAN AS A CHILD.
POLICE RECORDS SHOW HE
WAS INVOLVED IN TWO
DOMESTIC DISTURBANCES
EARLIER THIS YEAR.
NO CHARGES WERE EVER
FILED.
IN ANOTHER REPORT
POLICE SAY SAMSON
TEXTED HIS FATHER IN
JUNE THAT HE HAD PUT A
GUN TO HIS HEAD
THREATENING SUICIDE.
TONIGHT THE FBI HAS
LAUNCHED A CIVIL
RIGHTS INVESTIGATION
HOPING TO FIND A
MOTIVE FOR HIS ALLEGED
ATTACK AT A CHURCH
WHERE PARISHIONERS SAY
HE HAD OCCASIONALLY
VISITED.
>> I JUST WANT TO KNOW
WHY, WHY HE CAME TO
THE CHURCH, WHY HE DID
WHAT HE DID.
>> Reporter: KERRY
SANDERS, NBC NEWS,
ANTIOCH, TENNESSEE.
>>> IN A MOMENT, BACK
TO LESTER IN PUERTO
RICO, AND WE'LL HAVE
AN UPDATE ON THE
MEXICO EARTHQUAKE.
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
FROM PUERTO RICO, BUT
WE WANT TO TURN TO THE
OTHER MAJOR NATURAL
DISASTER WE'VE BEEN
FOLLOWING, THAT HUGE
EARTHQUAKE IN MEXICO
WHICH HAS LEFT MORE
THAN 300 PEOPLE DEAD
NEARLY A WEEK AFTER
THAT 7.1 EARTHQUAKE.
THE SEARCH CONTINUES
FOR ANYONE WHO MAY
SOMEHOW STILL BE ALIVE
UNDERNEATH THE RUBBLE.
MANY REMAIN HOMELESS.
IN FACT, TENS OF
THOUSANDS REMAIN
HOMELESS.
AND FUNERALS ARE UNDER
WAY IN A COUNTRY
SHAKEN BY TWO
SIGNIFICANT
AFTER-SHOCKS OVER THE
WEEKEND.
MORE NOW FROM NBC'S
MIGUEL ALMAGUER.
>> Reporter: SIX DAYS
AFTER THE DEADLY
EARTHQUAKE HERE, SIGNS
OF LIFE ARE STILL
COMING FROM BENEATH
THE RUBBLE.
SIX PEOPLE MAY BE
ALIVE BURIED IN THIS
BUILDING.
DOZENS OF FAMILY
MEMBERS ANXIOUSLY
WAIT.
ADRIAN MORENO, 26, IS
NOT ON THE LIST OF
SURVIVORS, SO HIS
BROTHER DANIEL PRAYS.
"WE KNOW THEY ARE
WORKING VERY HARD," HE
SAYS.
"WE HAVE HOPE THAT
WON'T DIE."
WITH MORE THAN A
HUNDRED RESCUES,
INCLUDING THIS DOG
OVER THE WEEKEND,
CHANCES FOR MIRACLES
ARE FADING.
WHEN THIS SEVEN-FLOOR
APARTMENT COMPLEX CAME
CRASHING DOWN, THERE
WERE 15 PEOPLE INSIDE.
12 WERE KILLED, 3
SURVIVED.
IN THIS RATTLED
COUNTRY, FEAR IS
EVIDENT IN EVERYDAY
LIFE, BUT TONIGHT IT'S
LIVES THEY ARE TRYING
TO SAVE.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER, NBC
NEWS, MEXICO CITY.
>>> I'LL BE BACK IN
JUST A MOMENT WITH
SOME FINAL THOUGHTS
FROM SAN JUAN.
===JESS VO===
THE BOLD STATEMENT A BAY AREA
HIGH SCHOOL BAND IS PLANNING
WITHIN THE NEXT HOUR.
===RAJ VO===
ALSO, ATM ROBBERY SPREE. HOW
MANY CASH MACHINES THIS
COUPLE IS ACCUSED OF HITTING IN
ONE DAY.
===NEXT CLOSE===
NEXT.
>>> FINALLY FROM
PUERTO RICO, THIS IS
AN ISLAND WITH A LONG
WAY TO GO ON ITS ROAD
TO RECOVERY.
LEAVING THE AIRPORT
THE SIGNS OF DESPAIR
WERE APPARENT
EVERYWHERE.
EVEN PEOPLE JUST
PARKING AROUND A LONE
WORKING CELL TOWER TO
TRY TO GET A MESSAGE
OUT.
OR PEOPLE JUST A SHORT
DISTANCE FROM US
GATHERED IN A LONG
LINE FOR A RESTAURANT
ABLE TO SERVE FOOD.
WE WILL CONTINUE TO
COVER THIS STORY AND
UPDATE YOU AS PUERTO
RICO RECOVERS, AS WE
SAID, HOME TO ALMOST
3.5 MILLION AMERICANS.
IF YOU'D LIKE TO HELP,
WE'VE PUT A LIST OF
ORGANIZATIONS ON OUR
WEBSITE.
THANK YOU FOR SPENDING
PART OF YOUR EVENING
WITH US.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, GOOD NIGHT FROM
PUERTO RICO.
PROTESTS -- ARE PR
OF VOCAL REACTIONS. THIS
>>> RIGHT NOW AT 6:00, THE
SILENT PROTEST PROMPTING A LOT
OF VOCAL REACTION.
THIS EVENING THE DALLAS COWBOYS
KNEELING DURING THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM.
WILL BE THE END OF AN EMOTIONAL
48 HOURS?
THE NEWS AT 6:00 STARTS RIGHT
NOW.
GOOD EVENING AND THANKS FOR
BEING WITH US ON THIS MONDAY.
RAJ MATHAI.
>> JESSICA AGUIRRE.
IT'S NOT OEM THE COWBOYS KNOWN
AS AMERICA'S TEAM.
A BAY AREA HIGH SCHOOL BAND IS
JOINING THE NATIONAL DEBATE WHEN
IT PLAYS THE NATIONAL ANTHEM AT
THE A's GAME WITHIN THE HOUR.
AS WE SAID THE COWBOYS AND
CARDINALS ARE THE LATEST TEAMS
TO JOIN THE PROTEST.
HAPPENED 30 MINUTES AGO.
BUT OVER THE WEEKEND NFL TEAMS
LINKED ARMED DURING THE ANTHEM,
BLASTING ATHLETES WHO TAKE A
KNEE DURING THE ANTHEM.
>> THE PRESIDENT WAS AT IT AGAIN
LATE THIS AFTERNOON.
TREMENDOUS BACKLASH AGAINST THE
NFL AND ITS PLAYERS FOR
DISRESPECT OF OUR COUNTRY.
ON FRIDAY MR. TRUMP SAID NFL
OWNERS SHOULD FIRE PLAYERS WHO
KNEEL IN FRONT OF THE FLAG.
NOW THE A's ARE ALSO
INSTRUMENTAL IN REIGNITING THIS
DEBATE.
STUDENTS IN OAKLAND ARE SOUNDING
DISPLEASURE WITH EQUAL RIGHTS.
MARIANNE FAVRO JOINS US FROM THE
COLISEUM WHERE THE STUDENTS ARE
ABOUT TO PERFORM.
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT AT 6:5
A TONIGHT MEMBERS OF THE OAKLAND
UNIFIED SCHOOL DISTRICT HONOR
BAND WILL PERFORM THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM AT THE OAKLAND A's "A"
GAME.
I TALKED WITH STUDENTS THIS
AFTERNOON WHO TOLD ME THEY PLAN
TO PERFORM ON BENDED KNEE AND IT
WON'T BE THE TIERS TIME.
LAST YEAR INPO