LATE WEEK IS STILL MILD AND THEN
WE GET INTO THE HUMID AIR FOR
THE HOLIDAY WEEKEND.
UNFORTUNATELY, A LITTLE
UNSETTLED.
>> PETE, THANKS.
LESTER HOLT IS LIVE IN LAS
VEGAS.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" STARTS RIGHT
NOW.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT.
THE DEADLIEST MASS
SHOOTING IN MODERN
AMERICAN HISTORY.
AT LEAST 59 DEAD, OVER
500 WOUNDED AS A
SNIPER OPENS FIRE FROM
A SMASHED-OUT HOTEL
WINDOW HIGH ABOVE A
COUNTRY MUSIC
FESTIVAL, UNLEASHING A
MASSACRE ON THE VEGAS
STRIP.
>>> FIRST RESPONDERS
ON A FRANTIC MISSION
TO FIND THE GUNMAN.
SURVIVORS DESCRIBING
SCENES OF SHEER
TERROR.
>> BULLETS FLYING
EVERYWHERE.
EVERYBODY RUNNING.
IT WAS REALLY, REALLY
BAD.
>> TONIGHT A BAFFLING
MYSTERY.
WHY DID HE DO IT?
WHAT WE'VE LEARNED
ABOUT THE GUNMAN AND
HIS MASSIVE ARSENAL.
WE HAVE IT ALL COVERED
INCLUDING
EXTRAORDINARY ACTS OF
HEROISM IN A FIELD OF
HORROR.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> LAS VEGAS MASS
SHOOTING.
THIS IS NBC "NIGHTLY
NEWS" WITH LESTER HOLT
REPORTING TONIGHT FROM
LAS VEGAS.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THE HEARTS OF OUR
NATION ACHE TONIGHT
WITH A SICKENING
FAMILIARITY.
ANOTHER MASS MURDER,
ANOTHER TAKING OF
INNOCENT LIVES ON AN
UJ IMAGINABLE SCALE.
LAST NIGHT'S ATTACK
HERE ALONG THE VEGAS
STRIP IS THE WORST
U.S. SHOOTING IN
MODERN HISTORY.
AS OF RIGHT NOW AT
LEAST 59 DEAD,
HUNDREDS INJURED
ABOUT.
AS WE COME ON THE AIR
A BROKEN-OUT WINDOW ON
THE UPPER FLOOR OF THE
MANDALAY BAY HOTEL
BEHIND ME POINTS TO
WHERE HELL WAS
UNLEASHED.
A GUEST ROOM TURNED
SNIPER'S NEST FOR A
64-YEAR-OLD MAN ARMED
WITH MORE THAN A DOZEN
WEAPONS LAUNCHED HIS
WITHERING RAPID-FIRE
GUN ATTACK, TURNING AN
OPEN-AIR EVENING
CONCERT ON THE GROUNDS
JUST OVER MY SHOULDER
INTO AN YOU ARE BAB
-- URBAN KILLING
FIELD.
WE HAVE A TEAM
ASSEMBLED TO COVER ALL
ANGLES OF THIS
DEVELOPING STORY.
WE START WITH NBC'S
JOE FRYER.
>> Reporter: IN A
MATTER OF SECONDS, A
COUNTRY MUSIC FESTIVAL
TURNED TRAGIC AS A
STRM OF GUNFIRE
RAINING DOWN UPON AN
INNOCENT CROWD.
>> HE WAS SHOOTING
EVERYBODY.
AND THERE WAS DEAD
PEOPLE EVERYWHERE.
AND I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT WAS HAPPENING.
THERE WAS JUST -- IT
WAS JUST SHOOTING
RANDOMLY.
>> Reporter: IT
STARTED AT 10:08 P.M.
FIRST REPORTS OF SHOTS
FIRED AS SINGER JASON
ALDEAN PERFORMED.
INITIALLY THERE WAS
CONFUSION.
MANY WONDERING IF THE
SOUNDS WERE PART OF
THE SHOW.
>> IT'S FIREWORKS.
STOP.
IT'S FIREWORKS.
>> Reporter: BUT THEY
QUICKLY REALIZED WHAT
WAS HAPPENING.
>> WE HAVE AN ACTIVE
SHOOTER!
PE HAVE AN ACTIVE
SHOOTER INSIDE THE
FAIRGROUNDS!
>> Reporter: A GUNMAN
PERCHED ON THE 32nd
FLOOR OF THE MANDALAY
BAY RESORT HAD OPENED
FIRE ON 22,000 CONCERT
GOERS.
>> WE GOT ABOUT 40 TO
50 PEOPLE WERE PINNED
AGAINST THIS WALL.
>> Reporter: ALL OF
THEM SCRAMBLING TO
FIND SHELTER WHEREVER
THEY COULD.
>> AND THEN ONE AFTER
THE OTHER.
WE WERE LAYING DOWN ON
THE FLOOR.
I DIDN'T KNOW TO GET
UP, TO RUN, JUST TO
STAY, TO DUCK.
>> Reporter: AT 11:20,
1 HOUR AND 12 MINUTES
AFTER THE SHOOTING
GAN, THE S.W.A.T. TEAM
BUSTED INTO THE
SHOOTER'S HOTEL ROOM.
>> ALL UNITS ON THE
32nd FLOOR, S.W.A.T.
IS THERE.
MOVE BACK.
>> BREACH, BREACH,
BREACH.
>> Reporter: INSIDE
THEY FOUND STEPHEN
PADDOCK DEAD.
AUTHORITIES SAY HE
KILLED HIMSELF.
THEY LOOKED FOR
MARILOU DANLEY BUT SHE
WAS OUT OF THE
COUNTRY.
>> RIGHT NOW WE
BELIEVE HE'S THE SOLE
AGGRESSOR AT THIS
POINT AND THE SCENE IS
STATIC.
>> Reporter: LAW
ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS
BELIEVE PADDOCK FIRED
OUT OF TWO ADJOINING
ROOMS USING A DEVICE
SIMILAR TO A HAMMER TO
SMASH THE WINDOWS.
AUTHORITIES SAY THEY
FOUND MORE THAN A
DOZEN WEAPONS INSIDE
THOSE ROOMS.
AS THE CHAOS UNFOLDED
OUR TEAM WAS ACTUALLY
STAYING IN THE
MANDALAY BAY TOWER
UNDER LOCKDOWN.
>> THERE ARE FLASHING
RED AND BLUE LIGHTS
EVERYWHERE AS THIS
AREA HAS BEEN FLOODED
BY POLICE AND
EMERGENCY RESPONDERS.
>> Reporter: WE WERE
SIX FLOORS ABOVE THE
GUNMAN WHO WAS ON THE
32nd FLOOR OF THE
HOTEL FIRING ACROSS
LAS VEGAS BOULEVARD
TOWARD THE CONCERT.
THE STAGE 400 YARDS
FROM THE HOTEL WITH
THE CROWD GATHERED IN
FRONT.
MANY THEN FLEEING TO
THE FESTIVAL'S MAIN
ENTRANCE.
>> IT WAS VERY SCARY
AT THE TIME.
AND I GOT MY WIFE UP.
AS I GOT HER UP, TWO
GUYS CAME RUNNING BY
THAT WERE CARRYING A
GIRL OR SOMEBODY THAT
WAS ALL BLOODY, AND IT
LOOKED LIKE THEY'D
BEEN SHOT.
>> Reporter: IN THE
END, A MASSIVE LOSS OF
LIFE AND HUNDREDS
INJURED IN THE WORST
MASS SHOOTING IN
MODERN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
DURING THAT LOCKDOWN,
OUR TEAM WAS TOLD TO
STAY INSIDE OF OUR
ROOMS FOR A TOTAL OF
TEN HOURS BEFORE WE
GOT THE ALL-CLEAR.
IN THAT TIME ON TWO
OCCASIONS LOOKING
THROUGH THE PEEPHOLE,
WE COULD SEE POLICE
GOING DOWN THE HALLWAY
ONE OF THOSE TIMES
WITH GUNS DRAWN.
THEN LESTER, ON A
THIRD OCCASION POLICE
RETURNED KNOCKING ON
ALL THE DOORS CHECKING
TO MAKE SURE ALL THE
GUESTS WERE OKAY.
>> JOE, THANK YOU.
MEANTIME, POLICE AND
FEDERAL AGENTS ARE
DIGGING INTO THE
GUNMAN'S RECENT PAST
TRYING TO FIGURE OUT
WHAT SET HIM OFF, WHAT
COULD POSSIBLY HAVE
LED HIM TO CARRY OUT
SUCH AN ATROCITY.
THE MORE DETAILS WE
LEARN THE DEEPER THIS
MYSTERY GETS.
NBC NEWS JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS HAS THE
LATEST.
>> THIS WE UNDERSTAND
IS THE HOUSE THAT WAS
OWNED BY PADDOCK.
>> Reporter: LESS THAN
AN HOUR AFTER THE
SHOOTING STOPPED --
>> THEY DO HAVE A
LARGE CREW OUT HERE.
>> Reporter: POLICE
AND FEDERAL AGENTS
DESCENDED ON THE HOME
OF STEPHEN PADDOCK IN
MESQUITE, NEVADA.
A SEARCH TURNED UP 19
MORE GUNS, AMMUNITION
AND EXPLOSIVES BUT NO
CLUES ABOUT WHAT DROVE
HIM TO COMMIT MASS
MURDER.
HE LIVED THERE WITH
HIS GIRLFRIEND MARILOU
DANLEY.
>> WE HAVE NOT HAD ANY
CONTACTS WITH THESE
PEOPLE IN THE PAST.
WE HAVEN'T HAD ANY
TRAFFIC STOPS, WE
HAVEN'T HAD ANY LAW
ENFORCEMENT CONTACTS,
NO ARRESTS OR NOTHING.
>> Reporter: A YOUNGER
BROTHER ERIC PADDOCK
SAYS THE FAMILY NEVER
SAW IT COMES.
>> JUST LIKE AN
ASTEROID FELL OUT OF
THE SKY.
THERE'S NO -- THERE
WAS NOTHING THAT WOULD
SAY HE WOULD DO THIS
KIND OF THING.
THERE'S NO
AFFILIATIONS.
THERE'S NO CHURCH,
THERE'S NO RELIGION,
THERE'S NO POLITICS,
THERE'S NO ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: HE SAYS
PADDOCK RECENTLY
TEXTED TO ASK HOW HIS
90-YEAR-OLD MOTHER WAS
DOING AFTER HURRICANE
IRMA AND TEXTED AGAIN
ABOUT ATTENDING A
FAMILY WEDDING.
THEIR FATHER, BENJAMIN
HOSKINS PADDOCK, WAS
ONCE ON THE FBI'S TEN
MOST WANTED LIST AFTER
ESCAPING FROM PRISON
IN 1968 WHILE SERVING
TIME FOR BANK ROBBERY.
THE FBI DESCRIBED THE
FATHER AS PSYCHOPATHIC
WITH SUICIDAL
TENDENCIES.
BUT THE SON, STEPHEN
PADDOCK, HAD NO
BRUSHES WITH THE LAW.
HE WAS A RETIRED
ACCOUNTANT AFTER
LIVING FOR A TIME IN
TEXAS AND FLORIDA, A
MULTIMILLIONAIRE REAL
ESTATE DEVELOPER, HIS
BROTHER SAYS.
INVESTIGATORS SAY IN
THE PAST FEW WEEKS HE
GAMBLED HEAVILY AT LAS
VEGAS HOTELS AND
CASINOS, PLACING TENS
OF THOUSANDS OF
DOLLARS IN BETS.
FEDERAL OFFICIALS AND
GUN STORE OWNERS SAY
HE HAS LEGALLY
PURCHASED RIFLES AND
HANDGUNS OVER THE PAST
SEVERAL MONTHS IN
NEVADA.
MORE THAN A DOZEN
ASSAULT-TYPE RIFLES
LIKE THIS WERE FOUND
IN HIS HOTEL ROOM,
FEDERAL OFFICIALS SAY,
ALONG WITH SOME SNIPER
RIFLES WITH SCOPES AND
TRIPODS.
BUT THEY HAVEN'T YET
DETERMINED WHAT MADE
THEM AUTOMATIC,
CAPABLE OF SHOOTING
CONTINUOUSLY AND
RAPIDLY, WHETHER THEY
WERE BOUGHT ILLEGALLY
THAT WAY OR LATER
MODIFIED.
POLICE SAY HE CHECKED
INTO THE MANDALAY BAY
HOTEL LAST THURSDAY
AND BROUGHT IN ALL THE
GUNS AND AMMUNITION
HIMSELF ALONG WITH HIS
LUGGAGE, KEEPING IT
HIDDEN FROM THE
HOUSEKEEPING STAFF.
BUT INVESTIGATORS SAY
THEY DON'T KNOW WHY
PADDOCK CAME TO THE
HOTEL TO KILL AND WHY
HE TARGETED A COUNTRY
MUSIC CONCERT.
SO FAR THEY SAY THEY
FOUND NO NOTES, NO
E-MAILS, NO SOCIAL
MEDIA POSTINGS
INDICATING HOW LONG
AGO HE DEVELOPED THIS
PLAN, BUT THEY SAY
THEY DO NOT BELIEVE
THAT HE HAD ANY HELP.
LESTER?
>> PETE WILLIAMS,
THANK YOU.
>>> IT IS HARD TO
WATCH THAT SMARTPHONE
VIDEO OF THE ATTACK
WITHOUT IMAGINING
YOURSELF IN SUCH A
SITUATION.
WHAT WOULD I DO?
HOW WOULD I REACT?
THOSE VIDEOS MADE US
ALL WITNESSES TO THE
SHOOTING.
ONLY THOSE WHO LIVED
THROUGH IT CAN SPEAK
TO THE HARD CHOICE OF
SURVIVAL IN A PLACE
WHERE IT APPEARED
THERE WERE NO GOOD
CHOICES.
THE IMAGES ARE HARD TO
SHAKE.
A NIGHT OUT TURNING
INTO A NIGHTMARE.
SPLIT SECOND
DECISIONS.
DO YOU RUN OR DO YOU
TAKE COVER?
MIKE CROFT WAS TEN
FEET FROM THE STAGE
WHEN THE SHOTS BEGAN.
>> I KNEW THEY CAME
FROM THE HOTEL.
I'M LIKE WE'RE
SCREAMING AT PEOPLE TO
GET DOWN ON THE GROUND
SO YOU'RE NOT A
TARGET.
>> Reporter: HIS
FRIEND ROB McINTOSH
HAD BEEN SHOT.
YOUR INSTINCT WAS GET
DOWN, NOT RUN.
>> YES.
OH, YEAH, MY BUDDY WAS
HIT.
I'M NOT LEAVING HIM.
>> Reporter: WHERE WAS
HE HIT?
>> THREE TIMES IN THE
CHEST.
>> Reporter: DID HE
REMAIN CONSCIOUS?
>> YES, THE WHOLE
TIME.
HE HAD HIS FINGER IN
THE BULLET HOLE.
LEAVE YOUR FINGER IN.
>> Reporter: A THAT
MOMENT BACKSTAGE MORE
CRITICAL DECISIONS.
BUZZ BRAINARD WORKING
WITH SIRIUS/XM THERE
WITH HIS 19-YEAR-OLD
SON HANK.
>> JUST EVERYBODY I
SAW DOVE UNDERNEATH
THE TOUR BUSES.
MY SON WAS THERE.
I WAS ON TOP OF HIM.
WE'RE ON THE GROUND
UNDERNEATH.
BULLETS WERE HITTING
THE DIRT, SO YOU COULD
FEEL THE DIRT --
>> Reporter: YOU'RE
FEELING THEN KO
CUSHION OF THE
BULLETS.
>> HITTING YOUR FACE,
THE DIRT IS.
>> Reporter: BELIEVING
THE ONLY WAY TO GET
OUT WAS TO RUN ACROSS
THE STAGE THAT JASON
ALDEAN JUST FLED.
>> I GRABBED MY SON BY
THE HAND.
HE'S 19 YEARS OLD, BUT
HE WAS MY LITTLE BOY
THERE.
>> Reporter: YEAH,
YEAH.
>> AND WE SPRINTED
ACROSS THE STAGE.
BY THE TIME WE MERGED
WITH THE CROWD THAT
WAS HERE, SO THEN IT
JUST -- IT BECAME
CHAOS.
>> Reporter: A BIT OF
A STAMPEDE.
>> IT WAS EXACTLY A
STAMPEDE.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
I MEAN, THERE WAS
REALLY NOWHERE TO
HIDE.
>> Reporter:
MEANWHILE, MIKE CROCK
HAD BEEN TRYING TO GET
HIS FRIEND HELP.
>> WE ACTUALLY LOADED
FOUR WOUNDED PEOPLE UP
IN THE BACK OF A
PICKUP TRUCK AND TRIED
TO GET TO THE
HOSPITAL.
FINALLY WE RAN INTO AN
AMBULANCE.
AND SO YOU KNOW, THEY
STARTED TRIAGING AND
WE GOT MY BUD NE THE
AMBULANCE.
AND ONE OF THE YOUNG
MEN THAT WAS IN THE
BACK OF THE TRUCK AS I
WAS CARRYING HIM, HE
PASSED AWAY.
SO THAT YOUNG MAN,
SOMEBODY'S SON, YOU
KNOW, PASSED AWAY
RIGHT THERE.
IT WAS NOT BY HIMSELF.
HE WAS ALWAYS WITH
SOMEBODY.
>> Reporter: BUT LATE
TODAY, THE MOMENT MIKE
HAD BEEN WAITING FOR.
>> YOU'RE ONE OF THE
LUCKY ONES.
>> Reporter: REUNITED
IN THE HOSPITAL WITH A
FRIEND HE HAD HELPED
SAVE.
>> YOU DID GOOD.
THANKS FOR STAYING
WITH ME.
>> Reporter: ONE
GLIMMER OF HOPE
TONIGHT.
SO MANY DESPERATE FOR
MORE.
MIKE CROCK'S FRIEND
ROB IS FACING MORE
SURGERY BUT IS
EXPECTED TO RECOVER.
AND MIKE TOLD US HE'S
PLANNING TO DONATE
BLOOD FOR THE INJURED.
>>> NOW TO THOSE WHO
DIDN'T MAKE IT OUT.
THE COUNTRY MUSIC
FESTIVAL THAT CAME
UNDER ATTACK HERE HAD
BROUGHT IN TENS OF
THOUSANDS OF FANS FROM
FAR AND WIDE.
AMONG THOSE KILLED, A
NEWLYWED PROTECTING
HIS WIFE.
A SPECIAL EDUCATION
TEACHER.
A SINGLE MOM.
POLICE OFFICERS.
AND SO MANY MORE.
NBC'S STEPHANIE GOSK
WITH MORE NOW ON THE
VICTIMS.
>> Reporter: AS
BULLETS STARTED
RAINING DOWN ON
SUNDAY, SONNY'S
INSTINCT WAS TO
PROTECT HIS WIFE OF
JUST OVER A YEAR,
HEATHER.
HE GRABBED HER AND
STARTED RUNNING WHEN
HE WAS SHOT IN THE
BACK.
HEATHER SAYS HE SAVED
MY LIFE AND LOST HIS.
AT THIS POINT I CAN
BARELY BREATHE.
MELTON WAS A
REGISTERED NURSE IN
TENNESSEE.
HIS WIFE IS A SURGEON.
THEY MET AT THE
HOSPITAL AND FELL IN
LOVE.
>> HE WAS A VERY KIND,
LOVING PERSON THAT
EVERYBODY LIKED A LOT.
>> Reporter: BRYCE
JORDAN LINED UP TO
DONATE BLOOD JUST
HOURS AFTER LEARNING
HIS COUSIN QUINTON
ROBINS WAS KILLED.
ROBINS ATTENDED THE
UNIVERSITY OF NEVADA
LAS VEGAS.
IN HIS FREE TIME HE
COACHED HIS LITTLE
BROTHER'S FLAG
FOOTBALL TEAM.
>> I LOVED QUINTON.
HE WAS A VERY POPULAR
KID AROUND SCHOOL AND
AROUND TOWN.
>> Reporter: AT LEAST
TWO MANHATTAN BEACH,
CALIFORNIA, RESIDENTS
DIED.
INCLUDING RACHEL
PARKER.
AND SPECIAL EDUCATION
TEACHER SANDY CASEY.
HER PARTNER
CHRISTOPHER SAID SHE
LIVED LIFE TO THE
FULLEST AND MADE ME
THE HAPPIEST MAN IN
THE WORLD.
SECRETARY LISA ROMERO
AND OFFICE MANAGER
SUSAN SMITH ALSO AMONG
THE VICTIMS.
28-YEAR-OLD SINGLE
MOTHER JESSICA
CLEMCHUCK WAS VISITING
LAS VEGAS WITH HER
FIANCE.
YOU ARE HEAVEN SENT.
YOU ARE MY ONE AND
ONLY SHE WROTE TO HIM
LAST WEEK.
SHE LEAVES BEHIND
CHILDREN.
LAS VEGAS OFFICER
CHARLESTON HART FD.
>> ONE OF MY OFFICERS
WA WAS OFF DUTY
ATTENDING THE CONCERT
AND LOST HIS LIFE.
>> Reporter: ONE
WITNESS SAID OFF-DUTY
OFFICERS IN THE CROWD
WERE INJURED WHEN THEY
ACTED AS HUMAN
SHIELDS.
>> THEY LAID OVER TOP
OF US EVERY TIME A
ROUND WAS FIRED.
>> Reporter: MECHANIC
JORDAN McKILLEDEN WAS
A BIG FAN OF LAS
VEGAS.
HE CROSSED PATHS WITH
HEATHER GOOZE.
I'M WITH A YOUNG MAN
WHO DIED IN MY ARMS,
SHE WROTE ON FACEBOOK.
SO MANY STILL
SEARCHING FOR LOVED
ONES AND ANSWERS.
FAMILIES ARE BEING
DIRECTED HERE TO THIS
CONVENTION CENTER.
WITH SO MANY
CASUALTIES, THE
IDENTIFICATION PROCESS
WILL BE COMPLICATED.
THEY MAY GO DAYS
WITHOUT KNOWING FOR
SURE WHAT HAPPENED TO
THEIR LOVED ONES.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT,
STEPHANIE GOSK, THANK
YOU.
>>> THE EMERGENCY
RESPONSE IN THE CITY
WAS OVERWHELMING.
VICTIMS POURING INTO
HOSPITALS ANY WAY THEY
COULD FOR HOURS.
SOME CLINGING TO LIFE,
OTHERS WALKING
WOUNDED.
OUR NATIONAL
CORRESPONDENT MIGUEL
ALMAGUER HAS MORE ON
THE MEN AND WOMEN ON
THE FRONTLINES IN THE
RUSH TO SAVE LIVES.
>> Reporter: AS CHAOS
TURNED TO CARNAGE,
THOUSANDS RAN FOR
EXITS WHILE THOSE IN
UNIFORM POURED IN TO
HELP.
>> WE'RE GETTING SHOT
AT.
WE'RE GETTING SHOT AT.
>> Reporter: FIRST
RESPONDERS RISKING
THEIR OWN LIVES TO
SAVE OTHERS.
>> WE'RE TAKING
GUNFIRE.
IT'S GOING RIGHT OVER
OUR HEADS.
>> Reporter: WEARING
KEVLAR HELMETS AND
VESTS, THEY TENDED TO
THE WOUNDED ANY WAY
THEY COULD.
>> WE'RE MAKING
TOURNIQUETS OUT OF
BLANKETS, BUT I'M
RUNNING OUT OF
BLANKETS HERE.
>> Reporter: THE
SERIOUSLY INJURED WERE
EVERYWHERE, CARRIED ON
STRETCHERS AND
WHEELBARROWS.
THOSE THAT COULD HELP
DID.
>> RIGHT NOW, WE NEED
YOUR TRUCK.
WE JUST NEED TO GET
PEOPLE OVER TO THE
HOSPITAL, OKAY?
>> THERE WERE TRUCKS
THAT HAD EIGHT PEOPLE
IN THE BACK OF THEM.
>> Reporter: TRAUMA
SUPERVISOR TONY MULLEN
HAS NEVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE IT
BEFORE.
>> WE PUT GURNEYS
OUTSIDE.
WE HAD WHEELCHAIRS
OUTSIDE WAITING FOR
THE PEOPLE TO BE
BROUGHT IN.
>> Reporter: FOR HOURS
AMBULANCES FERRIED IN
THOSE CLINGING TO
LIFE.
OVERWHELMING FIVE
HOSPITALS.
>> UMC IS AT CAPACITY
FOR VICTIMS UNLESS
IT'S LIFE THREATENING.
>> Reporter: ALL
EMERGENCY PERSONNEL
CALLED IN TO HELP.
TODAY HUNDREDS WAITED
FOR HOURS TO DONATE
MUCH-NEEDED BLOOD TO
HELP VICTIMS LIKE NICK
RABON, SHOT IN THE
CHEST.
HIS BROTHER A
PARAMEDIC, SAVED HIS
LIFE, THEN THOSE OF
STRANGERS.
>> JUST COMBINED
EFFORT OF BYSTANDERS
JUST HELPING PEOPLE.
IT WAS ONE OF THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL CRAZIEST
THINGS I'VE EVER SEEN
INSIDE OF A TRAGEDY.
>> Reporter: THE WORST
OF TIMES BRINGING OUT
THE BEST INSIDE.
SO MANY SAVED AMONG SO
MUCH LOSS.
AT THE TWO LARGEST
TRAUMA CENTERS IN LAS
VEGAS, INCLUDING THIS
ONE, AT LEAST A DOZEN
REMAIN IN CRITICAL
CONDITION.
50 MORE FACE SERIOUS
SURGERIES AND WHILE SO
MANY LIVES WERE SAVED,
IT'S IMPORTANT TO
REMEMBER TONIGHT MANY
ARE STILL FIGHTING FOR
THEIR LIVES.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT, MIGUEL
ALMAGUER, PART OF OUR
TEAM ON THE GROUND
HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
IN HONOR OF THE
VICTIMS PRESIDENT
TRUMP LED A MOMENT OF
SILENCE AT THE WHITE
HOUSE THIS AFTERNOON.
HE ALSO CONDEMNED THIS
ATTACK AS, QUOTE, AN
ACT OF PURE EVIL AND
ORDERED FLAGS TO FLY
AT HALF-STAFF.
THE PRESIDENT SAID
HE'LL VISIT LAS VEGAS
ON WEDNESDAY AFTER HIS
TRIP TO
HURRICANE-RAVAGED
PUERTO RICO TOMORROW.
>>> THERE'S MUCH MORE
STILL AHEAD AS WE
CONTINUE TONIGHT FROM
LAS VEGAS INCLUDING
THE SHOOTER'S GUNS.
INSIDE THE ARSENAL HE
USED TO CARRY OUT HIS
RAMPAGE.
POLICE SAY SOME MAY
HAVE BEEN FULLY
AUTOMATIC.
HOW DID HE GE
I was wondering if an electric
toothbrush really cleans...
...better than a manual, and my
hygienist says it does. But...
...they're not all the same.
Turns out, they're really...
...different. Who knew? I had no
idea. So, she said look for...
...one that's shaped like a
dental tool with a round...
...brush head.
Go Pro with Oral-B.
Oral-B's rounded brush head
surrounds each tooth to...
...gently remove
more plaque and...
...Oral-B CrossAction is
clinically proven to...
...remove more plaque than
Sonicare DiamondClean.
My mouth feels so clean.
I'll only use an Oral-B!
The #1 Brand used by
dentists worldwide.
Oral-B. Brush like a Pro.
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
But he has
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
I can't wait for her to have
that college experience that I
had.
The classes,
the friends,
the independence.
And since we planned for it,
that student debt is the one
experience, I'm glad she'll miss
When you have the right
financial advisor, life can be
brilliant.
Ameriprise
Where are we?
About to see Progressive's
new Home Quote Explorer.
Where you can compare
multiple quote options online
and choose what's right
for you.
Woah.
Flo and Jamie here
to see HQX.
Flo and Jamie
request entry.
Slovakia.
Triceratops.
Tapioca.
Racquetball.
Staccato.
Me llamo Jamie.
Pumpernickel.
Pudding.
Employee: Hey, guys!
Home Quote Explorer.
It's home insurance made easy.
Password was "hey guys."
>>> TONIGHT LAW
ENFORCEMENT SOURCES
TELL NBC NEWS THE
GUNMAN HERE IN LAS
VEGAS MAY HAVE BEEN
USING SEMIAUTOMATIC
WEAPONS CONVERTED TO
FIRE TO FULL AUTOMATIC
MODE.
SEMIAUTOMATIC WEAPONS
ARE LEGAL IN THE U.S.,
BUT FOR THREE DECADES
NEW SALES OF AUTOMATIC
WEAPONS HAVE BEEN
ILLEGAL.
THE QUESTION IS HOW
MAY THE SHOOTER HAVE
GOTTEN HIS HANDS ON
WHAT WERE ESSENTIALLY
MILITARY GRADE MACHINE
GUNS?
HERE'S NBC'S TOM
COSTELLO.
>> GET DOWN.
GET DOWN.
>> Reporter: VETERAN
COPS COULD TELL FROM
THE SOUND OF THE
GUNFIRE THAT FULLY
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS WERE
LIKELY INVOLVED.
AMONG THE ARMORY OF
GUNS, AMMUNITION,
TRIPODS AND SCOPES
RECOVERED FROM THE
HOTEL ROOM WERE 0.223
CALIBER AND 0.308
CALIBER RIFLES
POSSIBLY ILLEGALLY
TURNED INTO AUTOMATIC
MACHINE GUNS USED BY
THE MILITARY.
>> IT GOES DOWN THE
BARREL WITH HIGH
VELOCITY.
THAT'S WHY IT'S SO
DEADLY.
IT WILL GO THROUGH A
POLICEMAN'S VEST
THROUGH HIM, OUT THE
BACK AND INTO THE NEXT
PERSON.
>> Reporter: FEDERAL
LAW HAS OUTLAWED THE
SALE OF NEW MACHINE
GUNS, SEMIAUTOMATIC
EPS WITH ARE LEGAL IN
MOST IF NOT ALL
STATES.
SOME GUN ENTHUSIASTS
AND CRIMINALS USE $50
KITS AVAILABLE ONLINE
TO CONVERT THEM INTO
AUTOMATIC GUNS.
YOUTUBE CLIPS SHOW HOW
IT'S DONE.
POLICE SAY THE NUMBER
OF FULLY CONVERTED
MILITARY GUNS HAS
RISEN SHARPLY.
FIRING OFF HUNDREDS OF
ROUNDS PER MINUTE.
>> MY VIEW IS THEY
HAVE NO PLACE IN OUR
SOCIETY.
THEY ARE WEAPONS OF
LAW.
>> Reporter: IN NERVE
NEVADA, THERE'S NO
LIMIT.
AND SHOOTING ONE
DOESN'T REQUIRE MUCH
SKILL.
>> HE'S JUST EMPTYING
THE WHOLE MAGAZINE
INTO THE CROWD.
MASS MURDER ON A
VULGAR SCALE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
AT LEAST TWO NEVADA
GUN DEALERSHIPS SAY
THE SUSPECT LEGALLY
PURCHASED WEAPONS
THERE, BUT WHAT'S NOT
CLEAR IS HOW HE GOT
HIS HANDS ON SO MANY
POWERFUL WEAPONS OF
WAR.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC
NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> WE'RE BACK IN A
MOMENT WITH MORE ON
THIS MASSACRE AND THE
LONG LINE OF MASS
Liberty Mutual saved us almost
eight hundred dollars when we
switched our auto and
home insurance.
With Liberty, we could afford
a real babysitter instead
of your brother.
Hey.
Oh. That's my robe.
Is it?
You could save seven hundred
eighty two dollars
when Liberty stands with you.
LIBERTY MUTUAL INSURANCE.
[radio alarm]
♪ ♪
Julie is living with metastatic
breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women with hormone receptor-
positive HER2- metastatic breast
cancer as the first
hormonal based therapy.
♪ ♪
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
And IBRANCE plus letrozole
shrunk tumors in over half of
these patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE can
develop low white blood cell
counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if you have
fever, chills,
or other signs of infection
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts...
...infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver
blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Julie calls it her "new" normal.
Because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one-prescribed,
FDA-approved oral combination
treatment for HR+/HER2- MBC.
[phone ring]
Hi Anne.
So those financial regulations
being talked about?
They could affect your accounts,
so let's get together and talk,
and make sure
everything's clear.
Yeah, that would be great.
Being proactive...
It's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
A heart attack doesn't
or how healthy you look.
No matter who you are,
a heart attack can
happen without warning.
A Bayer Aspirin regimen can help
prevent another heart attack.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Bayer Aspirin.
Liberty Mutual stood with me
when I was too busy with the
kids to get a repair estimate.
I just snapped a photo
and got an estimate in 24 hours.
My insurance company
definitely doesn't have that...
You can leave worry behind when
Liberty Stands With You™
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>>> WE'RE BACK FROM
LAS VEGAS NOW.
THE SITE OF THE WORST
MASS SHOOTING IN
MODERN AMERICAN
HISTORY.
IN THIS COUNTRY WE
HAVE WITNESSED EVENTS
LIKE THESE FAR TOO
OFTEN, BUT IT ALL
SEEMS THAT THE WORST
OF TYPES OFTEN BRING
OUT THE BEST IN
HUMANITY.
HERE'S NBC'S CYNTHIA
McFADDEN.
>> Reporter: IT'S
BECOME PAINFULLY
COMMON.
>> IT'S HAPPENED
AGAIN.
A MASS SHOOTING AT AN
AMERICAN SCHOOL IN
SUBURBAN DENVER.
>> WHAT UNFOLDED JUST
A FEW STEPS FROM HERE
LAST NIGHT IS ALMOST
TOO MUCH TO BEAR.
>> OUR COLLECTIVE
SENSE OF SECURITY WAS
SHATTERED AGAIN TODAY
BY TERROR.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER
MASS SHOOTING IN
AMERICA.
AT 10:08 P.M. IN LAS
VEGAS A GRIM NEW
RECORD IS ABOUT TO BE
SET.
THE MOST DEADLY MASS
SHOOTING EVER.
AMERICA ITSELF HAS A
GRIM DISTINCTION, WITH
5% OF THE WORLD'S
POPULATION, IT ENDURES
MORE THAN 30% OF THE
MASS SHOOTINGS.
THE SLAUGHTER IN LAS
VEGAS NOW ADDED TO A
TRAGIC TIMELINE.
50 YEARS AGO 16 DEAD
IN TEXAS, 13 AT
COLUMBINE, 32 DIE AT
VIRGINIA TECH, AT
SANDY HOOK ELEMENTARY,
26 DEAD.
IN ORLANDO, 49.
BUT THERE IS ANOTHER
LIST, TOO.
NOT OF THE MASSACRES
BUT OF THE HEROES.
THE PEOPLE WHO HELPED.
THE SANDY HOOK TEACHER
KATELYNN WHO SAVED
STUDENTS.
AND THE DOCTOR WHO
WORKED HOURS STRAIGHT
SABING THE NIGHTCLUB
VICTIMS.
AND IN OREGON,
30-YEAR-OLD CHRIS
MINTZ, A U.S. ARMY
VET, WHO WAS SHOT FIVE
TIMES AFTER DIRECTLY
CONFRONTING A HEAVILY
ARMED GUNMAN WHO HAD
ALREADY KILLED NINE
PEOPLE.
IT'S TOO EARLY TO KNOW
ALL THE NAMES OF THOSE
WHO HELPED OTHERS LAST
NIGHT, BUT IN THE
COMING DAYS AND WEEKS,
WE WILL.
AND WHEN WE DO,
PERHAPS A NEW TIMELINE
IS IN ORDER.
A TIMELINE OF THE
HEROES.
CYNTHIA McFADDEN, NBC
NEWS.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH
MORE FROM LAS VEGAS IN
JUST A MOMENT.
[Burker] At Farmers,
we've seen almost everything
so we know how to cover almost
anything.
Even a "Red-Hot Mascot."
[MASCOT] Hey-ooo!
Whoop, whoop!
[CROWD 1] Hey, you're on fire!
[MASCOT] You bet I am!
[CROWD 2] Dude, you're on fire!
[MASCOT] Oh, yeah!
[CROWD 3] No, you're on fire!
Look behind you.
[MASCOT] I'm cool. I'm cool.
[BURKE] That's one way to fire
up the crowd.
But we covered it.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
Hey, are you taking
the Tissue Test?
Yep, and my teeth are yellow. I
mean I knew they weren't
perfect, but, ugh.
Oh well, all hope is lost!
Oh thanks! Clearly my whitening
toothpaste is not cutting it.
Time for Whitestrips.
Crest Glamorous White
Whitestrips are the only
ADA-accepted whitening strips
proven to be safe and effective.
They work below the enamel
surface to whiten 25x better
than a leading
whitening toothpaste.
Hey, nice smile!
Thanks! I crushed
the Tissue Test!
Yeah you did!
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
♪♪
♪ I'm...
I'm so in love with you. ♪
♪ Whatever you want to do... ♪
♪ ...is alright with me. ♪
♪ Ooo baby let's... ♪
♪ ...let's stay together... ♪
Big news from Advil,
Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
Our first concentrated pill
that rushes powerful relief.
A small new size that's fast,
cause it's liquid.
Woohoo!
You'll ask, what pain?
New Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
If you're
approaching 65...
now's the time to get your ducks
in a row.
[Quack!]
Medicare only covers about 80%
of your Part B medical expenses.
The rest is up to you.
So think about an AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan,
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like any standardized Medicare
Supplement insurance plans,
they help cover some of what
Medicare doesn't pay.
So don't wait.
Call now to request your free
Decision Guide and learn more.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
FROM LAS VEGAS WHERE
WE WANT YOU TO KNOW,
FOR MOST OF YOU, OUR
SPECIAL COVERAGE WILL
CONTINUE FOR ANOTHER
HALF HOUR OF NEWS ON
THIS NBC STATION.
WE HOPE YOU CAN JOIN
US.
FOR EVERYONE ELSE, YOU
CAN WATCH OUR COVERAGE
ONLINE AT NBC
NEWS.COM.
THAT'S IT FOR THE
FIRST HALF HOUR OF
"NIGHTLY NEWS."
I'M LESTER HOLT.
AND FOR ALL OF US AT
NBC NEWS, THANK YOU
Prudential asked these couples:
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,