TO PUT B PUT IN ACATEGORY IS
SORT OF UNREAL I HAVE TO SAY.
>> UNREAL AND PRETTY COOL.
ALSO SAYS THIS AFFIRMED THE
IMPORTANCE OF THE SCIENTIFIC
PROCESS.
>>> THANKS SO MUCH FOR BEING
WITH US TONIGHT.
NBC NIGHTLY NEWS WITH LESTER
HOLT FROM LAS VEGAS STARTS NOW.
>>> TONIGHT, A
DEEPENING MYSTERY
AFTER THE MASSACRE
HERE IN LAS VEGAS.
WHY DID HE DO IT?
AS WE SEE INSIDE THE
KILLER'S HOTEL ROOM,
CHILLING NEW DETAILS
ON HIS ARSENAL, THE
DEVICE USED TO MODIFY
THE GUNS, HIDDEN
CAMERAS HE SET UP AND
BIG MONEY HE SENT
OVERSEAS SHO
BEFORE COMMITTING MASS
MURDER.
TONIGHT POLICE SAY THE
GIRLFRIEND IS A PERSON
OF INTEREST.
WHAT DID SHE KNOW?
ALSO THE HEROS IN THE
CROWD.
JUST KEEP TALKING TO
HER SO WE KNEW SHE WAS
CONSCIOUS.
I'LL NEVER FORGET HER
FACE, EVER.
>> EMOTIONAL STORIES
EMERGE.
PLUS PRESIDENT TRUMP
IN PUERTO RICO AFTER A
PUBLIC WAR OF WORDS.
AND ROCK LEGEND LOST.
TRIBUTES POURING IN
TONIGHT FOR TOM PETTY.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>> Announcer: LAS
VEGAS MASS SHOOTING,
THIS IS "NBC NIGHTLY
NEWS" WITH LESTER
HOLT, REPORTING
TONIGHT FROM LAS
VEGAS.
>> GOOD EVENING IN A
PLACE STILL
OVERWHELMED WITH THE
SADNESS OF LIVES LOST,
AT LEAST 59 AND MORE
THAN 500 INJURED,
THERE IS ALSO A
GROWING RECOGNITION
AND APPRECIATION OF
THE NUMBER OF LIVES
SAVED.
THERE'S NO TALLY OF
THE HEROES WHO DRAGGED
STRICKEN PEOPLE FROM
LINE OF FIRE, APPLIED
A TURN KIT OR APPLIED
PRESSURE TO WOUND.
BUT INSPIRING.
LIKE THE PARAMEDIC I
MET WHO RACED TO THE
SCENE SUNDAY NIGHT,
RADIOING AHEAD KNOWING
HIS DAUGHTER WAS
THERE.
>> TWO OR THREE
MINUTES LATER CAME
BACK AND SAID I HAVE
EYES ON HER, SHE'S
OKAY.
BIGGEST RELIEF OF MY
LIFE.
>> YOU CAN ONLY
IMAGINE.
HEAR MORE IN A MOMENT
BUT FIRST GETTING
FIRST GLIMPSE IN THE
KILLER'S HOTEL ROOM
TURNED SNIPER'S NEST
IN THE HOTEL BEHIND
ME.
INTRICATE SETUP,
WEAPONS MODIFIED FOR
MAXIMUM KILLING AND
STRATEGICALLY PLACED
CAMERAS.
PETE WILLIAMS WITH
LATE NEW DETAILS.
>> YELLOW POLICE TAPE
MARKS THE SCENE WHERE
THE RAIN OF GUNFIRE
CAME FROM, STEPHEN
PADDOCK'S HOTEL ROOM.
VISIBLE THERE ONE OF
THE 22 WEAPONS HE
BROUGHT THERE IN 13
SUITCASES.
HIGH-POWERED SNIPER
RIFLE WITH SCOPE AND
STABILIZING BIPOD.
AUTHORITIES NOW KNOW
WHY HE WAS ABLE TO
SHOOT SO QUICKLY WITH
DEADLY EFFECT.
BOUGHT TWO
ATTACHMENTS, SOLID
LEGALLY, THAT ALLOW
CONVENTIONAL ASSAULT
STYLE RIFLES TO BE
FIRED LIKE MACHINE
GUNS.
>> WE ARE AWARE OF A
DEVICE CALLED A BUMP
STOCK, AND THAT
ENABLES AN INDIVIDUAL
TO SPEED UP THE
DISCHARGE OF
AMMUNITION.
>> OFFICIALS SAY HE
FIRED MOST OF THE
SHOTS IN THE FIRST
NINE MINUTES OF THE
ATTACK.
SHERIFF ALSO SAYS
PADDOCK STATIONED
CAMERAS IN THE HOTEL
HALLWAY TO WATCH FOR
APPROACHING LAW
ENFORCEMENT.
POLICE ARE TRACING
WHAT HE WAS UP TO
BEFORE CHECKING INTO
THE MANDALAY BAY LAST
TUESDAY.
WEEKEND BEFORE HE
RENTED ROOMS IN HIGH
RISE CONDO BUILDING
OVERLOOKING EVEN
BIGGER TDOOR MUSIC
FESTIVAL.
WANT TO KNOW IF IT'S A
DRY RUN.
EARLIER WIRED $100,000
TO THE PHILIPPINES
WHERE HIS GIRLFRIEND
MARY LIEU DANLEY IS
FROM.
TYPICAL GENEROSITY HIS
BROTHER SAID TODAY.
>> STEVE TOOK CARE OF
THE PEOPLE HE LOVED.
HE HELPED MAKE ME AND
MY FAMILY WEALTHY.
HE'S THE REASON I WAS
ABLE TO RETIRE.
>> MARILOU DANLEY I
PERSON OF INTEREST,
RETURNS TO THE U.S.
SHORTLY.
IN THE WEEKS BEFORE
HIS ATTACK, PADDOCK
RACKED UP 16
TRANSACTIONS FOR MORE
THAN $10,000 EACH IN
LAS VEGAS CASINOS.
IN MESQUITE WHERE HE
LIVED, NEIGHBORS SAY
HE WAS INTENSELY
PRIVATE.
>> I HAD NO IDEA A
LUNATIC LIVED THREE
DOORS DOWN.
>> MORE IS KNOWN ABOUT
WORK BACKGROUND,
LETTER CARRIER FOR A
WEEK AND A HALF AND
WORKED AS IRS AGENT
BEFORE HE MADE
MILLIONS IN REAL
ESTATE.
POLICE HAVE SEARCHED
HOUSES, CARS AND HOTEL
ROOM BUT NOTHING HAS
TURNED UP TO EXPLAIN
WHY HE TURNED TO MASS
MURDER.
HOPING TO FIND CLUES
ON CELL PHONES AND
COMPUTER.
LESTER.
>> AS PETE MENTIONED,
ONE OF THE BIGGEST
QUESTION MARKS IS THE
SHOOTER'S GIRLFRIEND,
OUT OF THE COUNTRY
WHEN THE MASSACRE
HAPPENED BUT REMAINS A
PERSON OF INTEREST FOR
THE AUTHORITIES WHO
WANT TO FIND OUT WHAT
IF ANYTHING SHE KNEW
ABOUT THE DEADLY PLOT.
STEPHANIE GOSK HAS
MORE.
>> Reporter: WITHIN
HOURS OF THE SHOOTING
POLICE WERE ON THE
LOOKOUT FOR MARILOU
DANLEY.
>> WE ARE INTERESTED
IN COMPANION TRAVELING
WITH HIM.
>> Reporter: BUT SOON
REALIZED 62-YEAR-OLD
DANLEY WAS NOWHERE
NEAR LAS VEGAS THAT
NIGHT.
>> WE'VE LOCATED HER
OUT OF THE COUNTRY AND
HAD CONVERSATIONS WITH
HER AND BELIEVE HER AT
THIS POINT NOT TO BE
INVOLVED.
>> Reporter: SAY SHE
FLEW TO THE
PHILIPPINES AROUND
25th, SAME TIME
PADDOCK WIRED MONEY TO
BANK IN THAT COUNTRY.
NEPHEW SPEAKING OUT
TODAY.
>> SHE WOULD HAVE HAD
NOTHING TO DO WITH IT.
>> Reporter: DANLEY IS
AUSTRALIAN CITIZEN AND
TRAVELS MULTIPLE TIMES
TO THE PHILIPPINES
WHERE SHE WAS BORN.
THIS IS A PHOTO OF HER
WITH PADDOCK IN 2014.
MARRIED FOR MORE THAN
20 YEARS BEFORE
GETTING DIVORCED IN
2015.
AT THE TIME LIVING
WITH PADDOCK IN RENO,
NEVADA, WORKING AT
LOCAL CASINO.
>> SHE WAS HOSTESS AT
ATLANTIS, STEVE WAS A
BIG FISH THERE.
THEY WERE ADORABLE.
>> Reporter: LIVED
NEXT DOOR.
>> NEVER SAW THEM
TOGETHER.
I NEVER DID.
>> WALKED INTO THE
GARAGE, I NOTICED A
LARGE SAFE, HALF THE
SIZE OF A
REFRIGERATOR.
SINCE THIS HAS
HAPPENED WE DREW A
CONCLUSION IT WAS GUNS
IN THERE.
>> Reporter: LAW
ENFORCEMENT NOT
CALLING DANLEY A
SUSPECT BUT REMAINS A
PERSON OF INTEREST.
CRITICAL QUESTION
TONIGHT, DID SHE HAVE
ANY IDEA WHAT HE WAS
PLANNING?
>> ONLY PERSON WHO
LIKELY KNEW DAILY
ROUTINE WOULD HAVE
BEEN THE PERSON HE WAS
LIVING WITH.
THAT'S WHY I BELIEVE
SHE'S ESSENTIAL.
>> Reporter: LAS VEGAS
POLICE ARE IN CONTACT
WITH DANLEY AND SENIOR
OFFICIALS TELL US
SHE'S EXPECTED TO
RETURN TOMORROW.
NO INDICATION THAT
PLANS HAVE CHANGED.
LESTER.
>> THANK YOU
STEPHANIE.
NOT ALL THE FIRST
RESPONDERS SUNDAY
NIGHT WORE UNIFORMS
AND MANY WHO DID WERE
NOT PREPARED FOR WHAT
THEY FACED.
PEOPLE, COPS, FIREMEN,
REGULAR CIVILIANS DID
WHAT THEY HAD TO DO.
VIDEO OF PEOPLE HELPED
INTO THE EMERGENCY
ROOM SPEAKS TO ALL
HANDS EFFORT THAT
GIVES THIS CITY
SOMETHING TO BE PROUD
OF EVEN IN DARK DAYS.
>> BLOOD-STAINED
BANDAGE, DISCARDED
GLOVE AND TOURNIQUET
BY THE SIDE OF THE
ROAD.
>> REMINDS YOU OF
NIGHTMARE YOU HAD
WAKING UP.
>> THESE ARE THE ONES
THAT GOT OUT.
>> GOT THIS FAR AND
TREATED?
YEAH.
>> WORKING CONCERT
SECURITY SUNDAY NIGHT.
>> THERE WAS A POINT
WHERE I WAS BACKSTAGE,
LOOKED OUT AND
EVERYTHING WAS BLACKED
OUT.
AND TO SEE THE CELL
PHONES LIGHT UP, HEAR
THE RINGING, THAT WOKE
ME UP THE FIRST NIGHT.
>> PEOPLE CALLING TO
CHECK ON LOVED ONES?
CALLS THAT WEREN'T
GOING TO GET ANSWERED.
AS THE TWO MEN TREATED
BADLY WOUNDED AND
HELPED OTHER ESCAPE
OVER THE FENCE, 15
MILES AWAY, PARAMEDIC
BRIAN ROGERS WAS
RACING TO THE SCENE.
>> GET 911 CALL OR
DISPATCH ON YOUR OWN?
>> ON MY OWN BECAUSE
OF WHAT CAITLYN TOLD
ME.
>> 22-YEAR-OLD
DAUGHTER AT CONCERT.
>> I HID BEHIND A
POWER BOX AND CALLED
DAD THE SECOND I
COULD.
>> EXACT WORDS WERE
DADDY, THEY'RE
SHOOTING AT ME.
OH, MY GOD.
TO BE PERFECTLY HONEST
WENT OUTSIDE OF
PROTOCOL AND TOLD ONE
OF THE PEOPLE RUNNING
EVENT ITSELF OVER THE
RADIO, YOU FIND MY
DAUGHTER.
I COULDN'T HELP IT.
>> ANSWER CAME BACK
SOON.
>> THREE OR FOUR
MINUTES LATER, HE SAID
I HAVE EYES ON HER.
SHE'S OKAY.
IT WAS THE BIGGEST
RELIEF OF MY LIFE.
>> I SAW MY DAD AND
RAN INTO HIS ARMS
CRYING BECAUSE I KNEW
HE WAS OUT THERE.
AND I KNEW HE WAS
TAKING CARE OF
PATIENTS BECAUSE
THAT'S WHO MY DAD IS.
>> THEN BOTH PRESSED
INTO ACTION TO SAVE
LIVES.
>> I HAD TO STAND
THERE AND HOLD A
GIRL'S IV BAG AS SHE
WAS CRYING AND JUST
KEEPING TO HER SO THAT
WE KNEW SHE WAS
CONSCIOUS.
I'LL NEVER FORGET HER
FACE, EVER.
>> MEANTIME DARIUS
HARPER, RETIRED ARMY
COMBAT VETERAN SAYS
HIS TRAINING ONLY WENT
SO FAR.
>> AT SOME POINT YOU
REALIZE I DON'T HAVE
GEAR TO RESPOND BUT
YOU DO IT ANYWAY.
IT'S WHAT WE DO.
>> WHAT HE DID WAS NOT
LOST ON HIS
19-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER,
WHO WROTE IN A
FACEBOOK POST.
>> SHE WROTE I COULD
HAVE WOKEN UP THIS
MORNING WITHOUT MY DAD
BUT I DIDN'T.
PRAISE GOD THAT NOT
ONLY IS HE OKAY BUT HE
HELPED TO SAVE MANY
MORE PEOPLE'S LIVES
LAST NIGHT.
THANK YOU FOR
CONTINUING TO LOOK
AFTER OTHERS IN OUR
COUNTRY.
I LOVE YOU.
>> PRETTY POWERFUL AND
WRITTEN AS TRIBUTE TO
HER FATHER BUT COULD
BE A TRIBUTE TO ALL
THOSE WHO STEPPED
FORWARD SUNDAY NIGHT
AND PUT THE SAFETY OF
OTHERS IN FRONT OF
THEIR OWN.
AS WE RECOGNIZE THE
INCREDIBLE HEROISM,
ALSO LEARNING MUCH
MORE ABOUT THE 59
PEOPLE KILLED IN THE
TRAGEDY.
ALL BY THREE ALL
IDENTIFIED BY
AUTHORITIES AND TODAY
A NUMBER OF MOVING
TRIBUTES WERE HELD AS
STAGGERING LOSS SENDS
RIPPLES OF EMOTION
ACROSS THE NATION.
MORE FROM MIGUEL
ALMAGUER.
>> ACROSS THE COUNTRY,
SOUNDS OF MOURNING.
ALL TO REMEMBER THE
UNFORGETTABLE,
LIFETIMES LOST IN
INSTANCE.
ANGIE GOMEZ, 20, NEW
JOB AS NURSING ASSIST.
WRESTLING COACH IN
PENNSYLVANIA
CELEBRATING WEDDING
ANNIVERSARY.
HEATHER HAD A STORY
BOOK MARRIAGE.
SHE WAS SURGEON, HE
WAS NURSE.
ENDED TOO SOON.
>> COULDN'T TELL WHERE
THE BULLETS WERE
COMING FROM, HE
GRABBED ME FROM BEHIND
AND RUNNING WITH ME
AND THEN I FELT HIM --
I FELT HIM GET HIT IN
THE BACK.
>> Reporter: HER
HUSBAND SONNY SHIELDED
HER, SACRIFICING HIS
LIFE TO SAVE HERS.
>> HE TOOK CARE OF
OTHER PEOPLE, EVEN AT
HIS OWN EXPENSE.
>> Reporter: THE
SHOOTING LEFT SO MANY
CHILDREN WITHOUT LOVED
ONES.
54-YEAR-OLD TOM DAY
JR., THE BEST DAD SAY
HIS FOUR CHILDREN, WHO
WERE WITH HIM AT THE
CONCERT.
AT 28, CHRISTOPHER
ROIBL HAD SEEN A
BATTLEFIELD BEFORE,
SERVED IN AFGHANISTAN
AND MISSED BY HIS
MOTHER.
>> HE'S A VET.
HE HAS A SHIRT WITH A
GUNSHOT THROUGH IT.
SAT ON A LOT OF BOMBS,
NEVER BLEW HIM UP.
>> Reporter:
32-YEAR-OLD, BRIGHT
SMILE.
NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOR DAD
WHO LOVED GOLF.
>> BROTHER-IN-LAW THE
MOST PATRIOTIC PERSON
YOU EVER MET.
I GUARANTEE YOU HE'S
FULLY COVERED IN RED,
WHITE AND BLUE.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
SONNY MELTON'S MOTHER
SHARES THE PAIN,
HEARTBREAK FELT BY A
NATION.
>> I'LL MISS HIS SMILE
AND I'LL MISS HIM
SAYING I LOVE YOU
MAMA.
>> Reporter: WITH
DOZENS HOSPITALIZED
TONIGHT IN CRITICAL
CONDITION, STILL
FIGHTING FOR THEIR
LIVES, 59 FAMILIES ARE
PLANNING FUNERALS,
LIVES CUT TRAGICALLY
SHORT BUT CELEBRATED
BY ALL THEY KNEW.
LESTER.
>> ALL RIGHT.
MIGUEL.
THANK YOU.
TRAGEDY HERE HAS
PLUNGED THIS COUNTRY
BACK INTO MOST HEATED
DEBATES OF OUR TIME,
FIGHT OWN GUN LAWS.
SPECIFICALLY DEVICE
USED BY THIS KILLER TO
MODIFY HIS GUN INTO
MACHINE GUN.
SHOULD IT BE LEGAL?
CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT ALLEY
JACKSON TAKES A LOOK.
>> Reporter: REIGNITED
GUN DEBATE CENTERS ON
PIECE OF PLASTIC LIKE
THIS.
BUMP STOCK AND LAS
VEGAS SHOOTER
PURCHASED TWO BEFORE
THE ATTACK.
ALLOWS A SEMIAUTOMATIC
GUN TO FIRE FASTER
LIKE IN THIS YOUTUBE
DEMO VIDEO.
ALMOST LIKE AN
AUTOMATIC.
THEY'RE LEGAL BUT
CONGRESS MAY
RECONSIDER.
>> TURN SEMIAUTOMATIC
WEAPONS INTO VIRTUALLY
AUTOMATIC WEAPONS,
THAT'S SOMETHING I
THINK WE'LL TAKE A
LOOK AT.
>> ALL THINGS THAT
MAKE AMERICA SAFER AND
DON'T INFRINGE ON THE
SECOND AMENDMENT,
COUNT ME IN.
>> YOU THINK IT'S TIME
TO HAVE POLICY DEBATE?
>> GOOD TIME HAVE A
HEARING.
>> Reporter: SOME
DEMOCRATS AGREE.
>> I WOULD PRAY THAT
NRA DID SOUL SEARCHING
ABOUT THE BUMP STOCKS.
>> Reporter: NRA
GENERALLY OPPOSES MORE
REGULATIONS ON THINGS
LIKE BUMP STOCKED.
>> EVEN IF OUTLAWED
AND RESTRICTED, IT'S
UNENFORCEABLE.
>> Reporter: SAYS THEY
DON'T SELL ANY.
>> DUE TO THE COST OF
THE PART AND INCREASED
COST IN AMMUNITION
WHEN YOU FIRE, NOT
SOMETHING WE
NECESSARILY SEE VERY
OFTEN.
>> Reporter: IN D.C.
NEW GUN LAWS SEEM
UNLIKELY AND PRESIDENT
IS NOT ENGAGING, AT
LEAST NOT YET.
>> WE'LL BE TALKING
ABOUT GUN LAWS AS TIME
GOES BY.
>> Reporter: WITH A
SHOW SCHEDULED THIS
WEEKEND NOT FAR FROM
MANDALAY BAY, DEBATE
ABOUT GUNS LOOMS OVER
VEGAS AND BEYOND.
NBC NEWS, WHITE HOUSE.
>>> STILL AHEAD,
PRESIDENT TRUMP IN
PUERTO RICO SEEING
FIRSTHAND DEVASTATION
FROM HURRICANE MARIA,
TOSSING SUPPLIES TO
THE CROWD AND WHAT HE
SAID THAT'S RAISING
Needles.
THE CROWD AND WHAT HE
SAID THAT'S RAISING
Essential for vinyl,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and further
joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma
and other cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Tears in the stomach
or intestines,
low blood cell counts
and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels
have happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you start
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you
were in a region
where fungal infections
are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
A must for vinyl.
But for you,
one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
How can you make your
hair even stronger?
Use Pantene shampoo together
with 3 Minute Miracle Daily
Conditioner.
Their Pro-V formula is
like a multi-vitamin.
Making your hair 2x stronger
See the difference when you
add 3 Minute Miracle Daily
Conditioner.
Remember that accident I got in
with the pole, and I
had to make a claim
and all that?
Is that whole thing
still dragging on?
No, I took some pics
with the app and...
filed a claim, but...
You know how they send you
money to cover repairs and...
They took forever
to pay you, right?
No, I got paid
right away, but...
at the very end of
it all, my agent...
Wouldn't even call
you back, right?
No, she called to see
if I was happy.
But if I wasn't happy
with my claim experience
for any reason,
they'd give me
my money back,
no questions asked.
Can you believe that?
No.
The Claim Satisfaction
Guarantee,
only from Allstate.
Switching to Allstate
is worth it.
♪♪
only from Allstate.
From investing in communities,
hungry for growth.
Lending to small businesses
fueled by a dream.
And supporting causes
inspired by love...
Eastern Bank is here.
To do good.
To do right.
To do more.
To help all of us do better.
So join us.
For good.
♪♪
>>> BACK NOW FROM LAS
VEGAS, WE'LL HAVE MORE
FROM HERE IN A MOMENT
BUT FIRST A CHECK OF
SOME OF THE OTHER BIG
STORIES OF THE DAY,
INCLUDING PRESIDENT
TRUMP IN PUERTO RICO,
MAKING A VISIT TO
DEVASTATED ISLAND,
HOME TO MILLIONS OF
AMERICANS AFTER VERY
PUBLIC WAR OF WORDS
OVER HIS
ADMINISTRATION'S
RESPONSE.
RON MOTT IS THERE.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP MEETING FAMILIES
IN PUERTO RICO TODAY.
>> WE'RE GOING TO HELP
YOU OUT.
>> THANK YOU
MR. PRESIDENT.
>> Reporter: TOSSING
PAPER TOWELS TO
RESIDENTS IMPACTED BY
HURRICANE MARIA AND
PRAISING FEDERAL
RESPONSE, RAISING
EYEBROWS WHEN
COMPARING TO HURRICANE
KATRINA IN IT 2005.
>> LOOK AT REAL
CATASTROPHE LIKE
KATRINA AND
TREMENDOUS, HUNDREDS
AND HUNDREDS AND
HUNDREDS OF PEOPLE
THAT DIED, YOU CAN BE
PROUD OF ALL OF YOUR
PEOPLE, ALL OF OURS,
WORKING TOGETHER.
16 VERSUS THOUSANDS OF
PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: LAST
WEEK.
PRESIDENT AND RESPONSE
HAS BEEN CRITICIZED BY
OUTSPOKEN MAYOR CARMEN
YULE IZ CRUZ.
TODAY THEY SHOOK HANDS
BUT DIDN'T RECOGNIZE
HER WHEN MENTIONING
OTHERS.
>> THIS GOVERNOR
DIDN'T PLAY POLITICS
AT ALL.
>> Reporter: RAUZED
COST OF THE DISASTER.
>> THROWN OUR BUDGET
OUT OF WHACK.
>> Reporter: BASIC AID
JUST TRICKLING IN TO
SOME REMOTE TOWNS,
SURVIVAL TAKES
PRIORITY OVER
POLITICS.
>> WE'RE PUERTO RICAN,
STRONG PEOPLE, GOING
TO GROW UP AGAIN BUT
WE NEED HIS HELP.
>> Reporter: A FEW
SERVICES ARE IMPROVING
AND TODAY A NAVY
HOSPITAL SHIP PULLED
INTO PORT OFFERING
SUPPORT.
>> PRESIDENT HAS COME
TO THE ISLAND AND I
THINK HE'S GOING TO
HELP US STAND UP
AGAIN.
>> Reporter: TAKING
THE PRESIDENT AT HIS
WORD TO HELP A DAY AT
A TIME.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
LEFT PUERTO RICO AN
HOUR AHEAD OF
SCHEDULE, NO REASON
GIVEN FOR THAT AND
MAYOR YULLIN TWEETED
THAT WHITE HOUSE STAFF
UNDERSTANDS THE
DISCONNECT BETWEEN HOW
THINGS ARE SUPPOSED TO
HAPPEN AFTER A STORM
AND HOW THEY REALLY
HAPPENED.
LESTER.
>> BACK IN A MOMENT
WITH TRIBUTES POURING
I didn't know where I
was from ethnically.
So we sent that sample
off to Ancestry.
My Ancestry DNA results
are that I am 26% Nigerian.
I am just trying to
learn as much as I can
about my culture.
I put the Gele on my
head and I looked
into the mirror and I
was trying not to cry.
Because it's a hat,
but it's like the most
important hat I've
ever owned.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
♪ Lights, camera ♪
♪ Strike a pose ♪
Your eyes work
as hard as you do.
But do they need help
making more of
their own tears?
If you have Chronic Dry Eye
caused by reduced
tear production
due to inflammation,
RESTASIS MultiDose® can help,
with continued use,
twice a day, every day,
one drop at a time.
RESTASIS MultiDose®
helps increase your
eyes' natural ability
to produce tears,
which may be reduced
by inflammation
due to Chronic Dry Eye.
RESTASIS MultiDose® did
not increase tear production
in patients using
anti-inflammatory eye drops
or tear duct plugs.
To help avoid eye injury
and contamination,
do not touch the bottle tip
to your eye or other surfaces.
Wait 15 minutes after use
before inserting
contact lenses.
The most common side effect
is a temporary
burning sensation.
Ask your eye doctor about
RESTASIS MultiDose®.
Savings Card
holders pay as
little as $0
for three bottles.
Start saving today
at restasis.com.
[Burker] At Farmers,
we've seen almost everything
Start saving today
so we know how to cover almost
anything.
Even a "Red-Hot Mascot."
[MASCOT] Hey-ooo!
Whoop, whoop!
[CROWD 1] Hey, you're on fire!
[MASCOT] You bet I am!
[CROWD 2] Dude, you're on fire!
[MASCOT] Oh, yeah!
[CROWD 3] No, you're on fire!
Look behind you.
[MASCOT] I'm cool. I'm cool.
[BURKE] That's one way to fire
up the crowd.
But we covered it.
Talk to Farmers.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
Throughout my career, I've been
fortunate enough to travel to
many interesting places.
I've always wanted to create
those experiences for others.
With my advisor's help along the
way, it's finally my turn to be
the host.
When you have the right
financial advisor, life can be
brilliant.
Ameriprise
Prudential asked these couples:
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>>> IF YOU HAVE A
YAHOO E-MAIL ACCOUNT,
LISTEN UP.
COMPANY SAID TODAY
EVERY SINGLE ONE OF
ITS USER ACCOUNTS
LIKELY COMPROMISED IN
MASSIVE CYBERATTACK.
TRIPLE THE NUMBER
YAHOO REVEALED WHEN IT
DISCLOSED THE HACK
LAST YEAR.
SENDING E-MAIL
NOTIFICATIONS TO
BILLIONS OF ADDITIONAL
USERS IMPACTED.
>>> TONIGHT TRIBUTES
POURING IN ABOUT TOM
PETTY, ROCK LEGEND WHO
PASSED AWAY SUDDENLY
AFTER CARDIAC ARREST
AT CALIFORNIA HOME.
66 YEARS OLD, PACKING
STADIUMS AND ARENAS UP
UNTIL THE END OF HIS
LIFE.
FANS AND FAMOUS
FRIENDS ALIKE ARE
REMEMBERING THE
HEARTBREAKERS FRONT
MAN AND SINGING HITS
FROM HIS DECADE'S LONG
CAREER.
KATE SNOW.
>> Reporter: AT HIS
FINAL CONCERT ON
SUNDAY.
>> I WANT TO THANK YOU
FOR 40 YEARS OF A
REALLY GREAT TIME.
>> Reporter: GRATEFUL
FOR A CAREER SPANNING
FOUR DECADES.
♪ AMERICAN GIRL ♪
>> HE WAS AN AMERICAN
LEGEND.
♪ TAKE ME THROUGH THE
NIGHT ♪
>> Reporter: FIRST HIT
THE CHARTS IN THE
'70s.
MIX OF SOUTHERN BLUES
AND CALIFORNIA ROCK.
IN THE MID'80s, PLAYED
WITH BOB DYLAN AT FARM
AID, LED TO WORLDWIDE
TOUR.
>> ONE OF THOSE GIFTS
FROM GOD, THROWN IN
TOGETHER AND
ELECTRICITY CAME FROM
THE COMBINATION.
>> THEN THE SUPER
GROUP, TRAVELING
WILLBERRIES.
DYLAN TOLD "ROLLING
STONE" MAGAZINE, IT'S
SHOCKING, CRUSHING
NEWS, HE WAS GREAT
PERFORMER, FULL OF THE
LIGHT, I'LL NEVER
FORGET HIM.
NEITHER WILL WE, KATE
SNOW, NBC NEWS,
NEW YORK.
♪ FREE FALLING ♪
>>>
Hi, Mr. Powers, thanks for
calling UnitedHealthcare.
Hi, I need your help.
I've been trying to find
a knee specialist...
but nobody has an opening
for months!
UUUGGGHHH!!!
UUURRRGGGHHH!!!
Mr. Powers?
You can't always control
your feelings...
I found one in-network
next Tuesday.
but choosing UnitedHealthcare
can help you control your care.
Thanks, Stephanie.
I see on your
preventive checklist,
you're due
for a colonoscopy.
It's covered at no additional
cost to you.
Great!
No green.
UnitedHealthcare
It's great to finally meet you.
Your parents have been
talking about you for years.
They're all about
me saving for a house,
or starting a
college fund for my son.
Actually, I want to know
what you're thinking.
Knowing that the most
important goals are yours.
It's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
I accept I don't bike
I even accept I have a
higher risk of stroke
as far as I used to.
due to AFib,
a type of
irregular heartbeat
not caused by a
heart valve problem.
But no matter
where I ride,
I go for my best.
So if there's something
better than warfarin,
I'll go for that too.
ELIQUIS.
ELIQUIS reduced
the risk of stroke
better than warfarin,
plus had less
major bleeding
than warfarin.
ELIQUIS had both.
Don't stop taking ELIQUIS
unless your doctor
tells you to,
as stopping increases your
risk of having a stroke.
ELIQUIS can cause serious and
in rare cases fatal bleeding.
Don't take ELIQUIS if you
have an artificial heart valve
or abnormal bleeding.
While taking ELIQUIS,
you may bruise more easily...
...and it may take
longer than usual
for any bleeding to stop.
Seek immediate
medical care
for sudden signs
of bleeding,
like unusual bruising.
ELIQUIS may increase
your bleeding risk
if you take
certain medicines.
Tell your doctor about
all planned medical
or dental procedures.
I'm still going
for my best.
And for ELIQUIS.
Ask your doctor
about ELIQUIS.
♪♪
Start the interview with a
firm handshake.
Ay,no! Don't do that!
Try Head & Shoulders
Instant Relief.
It cools on contact, and also
keeps you 100% flake free.
Try Head & Shoulders
Instant Relief.
For cooling relief in a snap.
You owned your car
for four years.
You named it Brad.
You loved Brad.
And then you totaled him.
You two had been through
everything together.
Two boyfriends, three jobs...
you're like
nothing can replace Brad.
Then Liberty Mutual calls...
and you break into
your happy dance.
If you sign up for
Better Car Replacement™,
we'll pay for a car that's
a model year newer
with 15,000 fewer miles
than your old one.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT
HERE FROM LAS VEGAS,
SOMETHING WE'VE
NOTICED SPROUTING UP
IN BETWEEN THE LIGHTS
AND NEON SIGNS WE'RE
USED TO SEEING ON
VEGAS STRIP, TODAY
JOINED BY SIGNS OF
HOPE AND THANKS,
WEAVED IN AND AROUND
THE CASINOS.
JUMBOTRON THANKING
FIRST RESPONDERS,
SIGNS ASKING FOR
PRAYERS, MAKESHIFT
MEMORIALS, PEOPLE FROM
ALL OVER THE WORLD
ADDING THEIR OWN
MESSAGES TO
HEARTBROKEN COMMUNITY.
PLACE WHERE PEOPLE
COME TO GET AWAY FROM
IT ALL, HELPING
OTHERS.
COMMUNITY SHAKEN BY
TRAGEDY BUT SHOWING SO
MUCH KINDNESS, WORST
OF TIMES BRINGING OUT
BEST OF HUMANITY.
THAT'S IT
There's something happening.
It's purposeful.
It's inspiring.
It's the simple idea that good
is more than something you are.
It's something you do.
Eastern Bank is here.
Giving 10% of our net
income to local charities.
Here to do good.
To do right.
To do more.
To help all of us do better.
So Join Us.
For Good.