ALSO A GIANT MOSAIC TO TAKE PART
IN BUILDING.
THANKS FOR BEING WITH US
TONIGHT.
I AM PHIL LIPOF.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS," WITH LESTER
HOLD STARTS RIGHT NOW.
>>> TONIGHT, A
DEEPENING CRISIS IN
PUERTO RICO.
CHAOS AND CONFUSION
OVER EMERGENCY AID
THAT'S BOTTLED UP, AND
THE WHITE HOUSE UNDER
FIRE OVER THE
RESPONSE.
OUR TEAM REACHING
REMOTE VILLAGES CUT
OFF IN DESPERATE NEED.
>>> EMOTIONAL
HOMECOMING.
DMAN STEVE SCALISE
MAKES A SURPRISE
RETURN TO THE CAPITOL
FOR FIRST TIME SINCE
THE BASEBALL PRACTICE
SHOOTING THAT NEARLY
TOOK HIS LIFE.
>>> PAYBACK TIME.
WORD FROM TOM PRICE
FACING A FIRESTORM
OVER LEAVING TAXPAYERS
ON THE HOOK FOR PRICEY
PRIVATE JET FLIGHTS.
>>> TRAGEDY AT
YOSEMITE.
A SUDDEN SLIDE ON THE
ICONIC EL CAPITAN.
CLIMBERS WITH NO
CHANCE TO GET OUT OF
THE WAY.
>>> AND CANCER
DIAGNOSIS.
JULIA LOUIS-DREYFUS
GOES PUBLIC WITH HER
BATTLE WITH BREAST
CANCER AND SENDS A
MESSAGE ABOUT
HEALTHCARE.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" STARTS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN
NEW YORK, THIS IS NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND THANK YOU FOR
BEING WITH US TONIGHT.
SO CLOSE YET SO FAR.
THE ESSENTIAL
PROVISIONS A THIRSTY
AND HUNGRY PUERTO RICO
HAS BEEN CRYING OUT
FOR OVER A WEEK NOW.
ARE REACHING THE
ISLAND ONLY TO RUN UP
AGAINST A DISTRIBUTION
ROADBLOCK.
ADDING FRUSTRATION ON
TOP OF MISERY.
THINK FOR A MOMENT
ABOUT LIVING IN A ROAD
WHERE GROCERY STORE
SHELVES ARE BARE,
THERE'S NO CLEAN
WATER, YOU CAN'T BUY
GAS TO GET TO WORK
AND, OF COURSE, NO
WORK, NO PAY.
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION TODAY
WAIVED RULES THAT
PREVENTED SOME SHIPS
FROM DELIVERING GOODS,
BUT THE ROOT OF THE
PROBLEM RUNS MUCH
DEEPER.
NBC'S GABE GUTIERREZ
IS THERE WITH THE
LATEST.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THOUSANDS OF SHIPPING
CONTAINERS SIT AT SAN
JUAN'S MAIN PORT.
A DISTRIBUTION
BOTTLENECK STIFLING
THE RELIEF EFFORT.
>> IT IS EXTREMELY
HEARTBREAKING.
>> Reporter: JOSE WITH
THE SHIPPING COMPANY
SAYS IT DOESN'T MAKE A
DIFFERENCE THAT TODAY
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION
TEMPORARILY WAIVED THE
JONES ACT, A NEARLY
CENTURY OLD LAW THAT
RULES THAT ONLY U.S.
SHIPS SUPPLY THE
ISLAND.
>> WE DELIVER.
THE PROBLEM IS THE
DISTRIBUTION ON THE
ISLAND.
>> Reporter: WITH
LITTLE PHONE SERVICE
IN PUERTO RICO,
COMMUNICATION IS
CRIPPLED.
PRIVATE TRUCKERS
AREN'T SHOWING UP FOR
DELIVERIES.
THE FORMER GENERAL IN
CHARGE OF COORDINATING
MILITARY RELIEF
EFFORT
S AFTER HURRICANE
KATRINA IS BLASTING
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION.
>> THAT NEEDS TO BE
FIXED.
>> Reporter: BUT THE
ACTING HOMELAND
SECURITY SECRETARY IS
DEFENDING THE FEDERAL
RESPONSE.
>> THE RELIEF EFFORT
IS UNDER CONTROL.
IT IS PROCEEDING VERY
WELL CONSIDERING THE
DEVASTATION THAT TOOK
PLACE.
>> Reporter: TODAY THE
DEFENSE DEPARTMENT
DISPATCHED A
THREE-STAR GENERAL TO
PUERTO RICO.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYING
THERE ARE NOW ENOUGH
RESOURCES ON THE
GROUND INCLUDING
10,000 FEDERAL RELIEF
WORKERS AND 7200
TROOPS.
>> PRESIDENT TRUMP HAS
PUT PEOPLE FIRST AND
PAPERWORK SECOND.
HE'S HAD US CULL OUT
AND PULL OUT ALL THE
STOPS.
>> Reporter: BUT AT
THE CRUISE PORT, WE
SAW MOUNTING
FRUSTRATION.
THOUSANDS OF HURRICANE
MARIA EVACUEES
STANDING IN SWELTERING
HEAT TO BOARD A ROYAL
CARIBBEAN CRUISE SHIP
EN ROUTE TO THE U.S.
VIRGIN ISLANDS, THEN
FLORIDA.
>> WE DON'T HAVE
WATER, LIKE NOTHING.
>> Reporter: AMY
TEPPRANILLO IS WAITING
TO GET ON THE SHIP.
>> YOU LITERALLY CAN'T
GET OUT.
DESPERATION.
PEOPLE START GETTING
ANTSY AND CRAZY.
YOU LITERALLY CANNOT
GET OFF THIS ISLAND.
>> Reporter: GABE IS
AT THE PORT RIGHT NOW.
LET ME GIVE FOLKS A
PEEK BEHIND THE
CURTAIN.
YOU'VE GOT
SOPHISTICATED
EQUIPMENT.
TELL ME THIS, ARE THE
RELIEF WORKERS FACING
THE SAME ISSUES WITH
COMMUNICATIONS?
>> Reporter: LESTER,
YOU DON'T REALIZE HOW
ESSENTIAL PHONE
SERVICE IS UNTIL IT'S
WIPED OUT.
WE'VE SPOKEN WITH FEMA
SEARCH AND RESCUE
CREWS THAT SAY THEY'VE
HAD A TOUGH TIME
SPEAKING WITH LOCAL
OFFICIALS.
POWER CREWS SAY
THEY'RE NOT FIXING
LINES YET, JUST
CLEARING DEBRIS
BECAUSE THEY CAN'T
TALK WITH
HEADQUARTERS.
UNTIL PHONE SERVICE
IMPROVES, UNTIL PEOPLE
COMMUNICATE, THIS
RECOVERY IS AT A
VIRTUAL STANDSTILL.
>> GABE GUTIERREZ AND
HIS TEAM HAVE BEEN
THERE SINCE BEFORE
THAT HURRICANE STRUCK.
>>> THE DEVASTATION
ACROSS PUERTO RICO
PUERTO RICO IS TRULY
HARD TO IMAGINE.
CITIES AND RURAL AREAS
ALIKE LEFT IN RUINS.
AND TONIGHT OUR TEAM
HAS MADE ITS WAY TO
THE REMOTE VILLAGES
CUT OFF BY DEBRIS.
RESIDENTS UNABLE TO
GET OUT.
IT'S AN INCREASINGLY
DIRE SITUATION.
NBC'S GADI SCHWARTZ
TAKES US THERE.
>> Reporter: IN
COROSOL, PUERTO RICO,
SHE'S LOOKING FOR
THINGS THAT SURVIVED
HURRICANE MARIA.
SHE FINDS VINEGAR AND
WD-40.
>> THE WINDOWS WERE
SHAKING.
THE WATER WAS GOING
THROUGH THE DOOR.
>> Reporter: SHE'S THE
TYPE OF WOMAN THAT
HOLDS YOUR HAND WHILE
SHE SHOWS YOU WHERE
SHE ONCE SLEPT.
>> THERE WAS MY ROOM.
THERE'S MY BED.
>> Reporter: CANDIDA
AND HER SON JULIA.
>> PARADISE LOST.
>> Reporter: DOWN THE
ROAD OTHERS HOLDING ON
TO EACH OTHER AS THEY
MAKE THE LONG TREK FOR
GASOLINE.
EVERY DAY YOU WALK
SEVEN MILES?
>> TO FIND GAS.
>> Reporter: IN THESE
RURAL AREAS GAS CANS
ARE THE FIRST STEPS IN
GETTING BACK TO WORK.
THIS MAN WAITING NEAR
A WASHED-OUT BRIDGE, A
GOVERNMENT WELFARE
MANAGER, WANTS TO GET
BACK TO GIVING AID TO
PREGNANT WOMEN.
THE WOMAN SUPERVISING
THE ROADWORK, AN
ENGINEER WHO HAS LOST
EVERYTHING.
SHE SAYS THAT EVEN
THOUGH SHE LOST HER
HOUSE, THE REASON WHY
SHE'S HERE IS BECAUSE
SHE LOVES HER COUNTRY,
SHE LOVES PUERTO RICO,
AND THIS IS WHAT SHE
CAN DO TO HELP.
IN EVEN MORE REMOTE
AREAS BLACK HAWKS ARE
FLYING IN FOOD TO
PEOPLE LIKE VERONICA
AND HER 2-YEAR-OLD
SON.
HIS MOTHER WORRIES
ABOUT THEIR FUTURE.
BACK IN THE BLACK
HAWK --
>> I WANT TO BE
BUSIER.
>> Reporter: SOLDIERS
ANXIOUS FOR MORE
ORDERS TO HELP AS THEY
FLY OVER DEVASTATION
LIKE THE RUINS OF
CANDIDA'S HOME.
GADI SCHWARTZ,
COROSOL, PUERTO RICO.
>>> CHEERS AND TEARS
AS CONGRESSMAN STEVE
SCALISE MADE A
HOMECOMING TO THE
CAPITOL.
HIS FIRST TIME BACK
SINCE THE SHOOTING
ALMOST TOOK HIS LIFE.
KRISTEN WELKER HAS THE
EMOTIONAL MOMENT FOR
US.
>> Reporter: JUST 15
WEEKS AFTER NEARLY
LOSING HIS LIFE, A
POWERFUL HOMECOMING.
CONGRESSMAN STEVE
SCALISE ON CRUTCHES
WALKING ON TO THE
HOUSE FLOOR, A
BIPARTISAN STANDING
OVATION, A FIGHT HE
WASN'T SURE HE WOULD
WIN.
>> I'M DEFINITELY A
LIVING EXAMPLE THAT
MIRACLES REALLY DO
HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: IT WAS
JUNE 14th WHEN A
GUNMAN OPENED FIRE ON
REPUBLICANS PRACTICING
FOR A CONGRESSIONAL
BASEBALL GAME.
SCALISE WAS SHOT IN
THE HIP, GRAVELY
WOUNDED.
>> WHEN I WAS LAYING
OUT ON THE BALLFIELD,
THE FIRST THING I DID
ONCE I WAS DOWN AND
COULDN'T MOVE ANYMORE
WAS I JUST STARTED TO
PRAISE.
>> Reporter: TODAY
PRAISING CAPITOL HILL
POLICE WHO HELPED SAVE
HIS LIFE, OFFICERS
CRYSTAL GRINER AND
DAVID BAILEY.
>> CRYSTAL COULDN'T BE
WITH US TODAY, BUT
DAVID BAILEY IS WITH
US.
DAVID, YOU ARE MY
HERO.
YOU SAVED MY LIFE.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> Reporter: EMOTIONS
OVERFLOWED ON THE
HOUSE FLOOR.
>> OUR PRAYERS HAVE
BEEN ANSWERED.
>> TODAY WE ARE TEAM
SCALISE.
>> Reporter: FROM THE
HALLS OF CONGRESS --
WHAT DID YOU SAY TO
CONGRESSMAN SCALISE
TODAY?
>> FIRST, I HAD TO
TELL HIM I LOVE HIM.
>> Reporter: ALL THE
WAY TO THE WHITE
HOUSE.
>> WE'RE SO EXCITED.
WHAT HAPPENED TO HIM,
JUST HORRIBLE.
WE ARE SO HAPPY.
>> Reporter: SENATOR
JEFF FLAKE WAS WITH
SCALISE ON THAT
BALLFIELD.
>> BEING OUT THERE,
HEARING THOSE PRAYERS
THAT HE WAS TALKING
ABOUT.
IT WAS A DAY I'LL
NEVER FORGET.
>> Reporter: SEARING
MEMORIES AS SCALISE
MARKS A NEW BEGINNING.
>> IT FELT INCREDIBLE
JUST TO FEEL THE LOVE
AND WARMTH FROM MY
COLLEAGUES BEING BACK
WORKING WITH THEM.
>> Reporter: SHOWING
THAT WHILE PARTS OF
HIM MAY HAVE BEEN
SHATTERED, HIS SPIRIT
NEVER WAS.
KRISTEN WELKER, NBC
NEWS, THE CAPITOL.
>>> A REMARKABLE
MOMENT IN WASHINGTON
TODAY.
>>> THERE'S LATE WORD
ABOUT THE CONTROVERSY
SWIRLING AROUND HEALTH
SECRETARY TOM PRICE
FACING SCRUTINY OVER
HIS FREQUENT USE OF
PRIVATE JETS COSTING
TAXPAYERS HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF DOLLAR.
THE PRESIDENT SAYS
HE'S NOT HAPPY AND THE
SECRETARY APPEARS TO
HAVE GOTTEN THE
MESSAGE.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HALLIE
JACKSON HAS DETAILS ON
PRICE'S NEW PROCESS.
>> Reporter: LATE
TONIGHT THE HEALTH AND
HUMAN SERVICES
SECRETARY PROMISING TO
PAY BACK TAXPAYERS FOR
PRICEY PLANE TRAVEL
THAT'S PUTTING HIS JOB
IN PERIL.
THE PRESIDENT NOT
PLEASED.
TOM PRICE JUST MOMENTS
AFTER GETTING A FLU
SHOT LOOKING FOR A
BOOSTER FROM HIS BOSS.
>> WE'RE GOING TO WORK
THROUGH THIS AND, AS I
THINK WE'VE STILL GOT
THE CONFIDENCE OF THE
PRESIDENT.
>> Reporter: BUT THE
PRESIDENT TODAY WHEN
NBC NEWS ASKED -- TOM
PRICE SAYS HE HAS YOUR
CONFIDENCE.
IS THAT TRUE?
SILENCE.
PRICE NOW PROMISING TO
WRITE A CHECK FOR HIS
SEAT ON PRIVATE
FLIGHTS THAT,
ACCORDING TO POLITICO,
AT TIMES MIXED
GOVERNMENT BUSINESS
WITH PERSONAL TO THE
TUNE OF MORE THAN
$400,000.
PRICE SAYS HE'LL ONLY
FLY COMMERCIAL FROM
NOW ON, NO EXCEPTIONS,
AND WILL COOPERATE
WITH TWO REVIEWS INTO
THE TRAVEL
ACKNOWLEDGING HE WAS
NOT SENSITIVE ENOUGH
TO TAXPAYERS AND
REGRETS THE CONCERNS
INCLUDING SOME FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP
HIMSELF.
>> AAM NOT HAPPY ABOUT
IT AND I LET HIM KNOW
IT.
>> Reporter: PRICE'S
MEA CULPA.
>> WE'LL CONDUCT A
FULL REVIEW AND SEE
WHAT HAPPENS.
>> Reporter: BECAUSE
PRICE IS ONLY PAYING
FOR HIS SEAT, HE'LL
ONLY PAY ABOUT $51,000
OF THAT REPORTED
$400,000 PRICE TAG
ACCORDING TO A
SPOKESPERSON.
ALL OF IT HAS
REPUBLICAN SENATORS
CONCERNED.
CHUCK GRASSLEY WANTS
THE WHITE HOUSE TO
EXPLAIN WHAT THEY'RE
DOING TO MAKE SURE ALL
CABINET SECRETARIES
ARE BEING FISCALLY
RESPONSIBLE WHEN THEY
TRAVEL.
>>> TONIGHT, THE WHITE
HOUSE IS FACING A
BARRAGE OF QUESTIONS
STRUGGLING TO EXPLAIN
HOW THE REPUBLICAN TAX
PLAN MATCHES UP WITH
THE PRESIDENT'S
PROMISES ABOUT
BENEFITS FOR THE
MIDDLE CLASS AND NOT
BREAKS FOR THE
WEALTHY.
PETER ALEXANDER HAS
THOSE DETAILS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
FRESH OFF BRANDING HIS
TAX PLAN A WIN FOR
EVERYDAY AMERICANS --
>> IT'S CALLED A
MIDDLE CLASS MIRACLE.
>> Reporter: NOW
GROWING QUESTIONS.
WILL ALL MIDDLE CLASS
AMERICANS GET A TAX
CUT?
DOUBTS FUELED IN PART
BY THE PRESIDENT'S TOP
ECONOMIC ADVISER
REFUSING TO SAY THAT'S
TRUE.
>> I CANNOT GUARANTEE
THAT.
YOU COULD FIND ME
SOMEONE IN THE COUNTRY
THAT THEIR TAXES MAY
NOT GO DOWN.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS
TODAY POUNCING.
>> THE PRESIDENT AND
HIS PARADE OF
MILLIONAIRES ARE
EXECUTING A MIDDLE
CLASS CON JOB.
>> Reporter: EXPERTS
SAY A GUARANTEE IS NOT
POSSIBLE BECAUSE THE
DETAILS ARE LIMITED.
THE PLAN INCREASES THE
STANDARD DEDUCTION AND
KEEPS MORTGAGE
INTEREST AND
CHARITABLE DEDUCTIONS
BUT APPEARS TO GET RID
OF MANY OTHERS.
>> WHAT THERE ARE ARE
ELIMINATIONS OF
DEDUCTIONS THAT MIDDLE
CLASS EARNERS TAKE,
AND THAT WAY THEY
COULD ACTUALLY SEE AN
INCREASE IN WHAT THEY
PAY EVEN THOUGH THEIR
TAX RATE IS GOING
DOWN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
QUESTIONS ABOUT THIS
PRESIDENTIAL PROMISE,
THAT THE RICH WON'T
BENEFIT.
>> IT'S NOT GOOD FOR
ME, BELIEVE ME.
>> Reporter: IN FACT,
MR. TRUMP'S BLUEPRINT
SLICES THE TOP TAX
BREAK TO 35%.
WHILE ELIMINATING
SOME.
>> THE IDEA THAT THE
RICH DON'T BENEFIT
FROM THIS IS PATENTLY
FALSE.
>> Reporter: HOW WOULD
THE TAX PLAN BENEFIT
HIM PERSONALLY?
TONIGHT THE WHITE
HOUSE IS REFUSING TO
SAY.
THE PRESIDENT'S TOP
ECONOMIC ADVISER
INSISTING AMERICANS
CARE MORE ABOUT WHAT'S
IN THEIR OWN WALLETS
THAN WHAT'S IN HIS.
>> PETER ALEXANDER
TONIGHT, THANK YOU,
PETER.
>>> NOW TO TRAGEDY AT
YOSEMITE NATIONAL
PARK.
DEADLY ROCK SLIDES AT
THE FAMED EL CAPITAN.
MASSIVE BOULDERS
COMING DOWN WITHOUT
WARNING, STRIKING
PEOPLE, LEAVING THEM
WITH NO TIME TO TRY TO
GET OUT OF THE WAY.
THIS IS AT THE PEAK OF
ROCK CLIMBING SEASON.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER HAS
WORD OF A NEW SLIDE
TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: IT
HAPPENED AGAIN JUST
MOMENTS AGO IN ONE OF
THE NATION'S MOST
STUNNING SETTINGS,
YOSEMITE NATIONAL
PARK, THERE WAS NO
WARNING.
NOW EIGHT ROCK SLIDES.
>> I CAN STILL SEE IT
FALLING.
>> Reporter: ONE
BOULDER THE SIZE OF AN
APARTMENT BUILDING
CAREENING DOWN THE
FACE OF EL CAPITAN
KILLING ONE PERSON, A
SECOND SERIOUSLY
INJURED.
>> THE LAST THING I
SAW WAS HIM AT THE
RAPPEL AND THEN TURNED
BACK AND THEY WERE
GONE.
>> Reporter: EL CAP IS
A WORLD CLASS
DESTINATION FOR SOME
WHO LIVE ON THE EDGE.
THIS TRAGEDY COMES AT
THE PEAK OF CLIMBING
SEASON.
>> IF WE HAD NOT
CLIMBED AS QUICKLY AS
WE DID, WHICH IS
QUICKER THAN I USUALLY
CLIMB, WE'D BE DEAD
NOW.
>> Reporter: TODAY
IT'S STILL UNCLEAR
WHAT TRIGGERED THE
1300-TON SLIDE.
TONIGHT EL CAP REMAINS
OPEN TO ALL.
A BEAUTIFUL BUT ALSO
DANGEROUS REMINDER OF
WHAT MOTHER NATURE CAN
BRING.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> TRIBUTES ARE
POURING IN TONIGHT FOR
AN AMERICAN ICON WHO
BUILT A MULTIMEDIA
EMPIRE BY PUSHING AND
OFTEN BREAKING
BOUNDARIES.
HUGH HEFNER, FOUNDER
OF "PLAYBOY" HAS DIED
AT 91.
CYNTHIA McFADDEN WITH
A LOOK AT HIS LIFE AND
LEGACY.
>> Reporter: IT WAS A
REVOLUTION WAGED IN A
RED SILK ROBE WITH AN
$8,000 LOAN AND A
PHOTOGRAPH OF MARILYN
MONROE, HUGH HEFNER
CHANGED THE WAY THAT
AMERICANS LOOK AT
WOMEN AND SEX.
BEGINNING WITH THE
FIRST ISSUE OF
"PLAYBOY" BACK IN
1953.
THE MAGAZINE AN
INSTANT SUCCESS.
>> IT'S PROBABLY THE
MOST FAMOUS NUDE IN
THE WORLD.
>> Reporter: CERTAINLY
THE MOST PROFITABLE.
AS HEFNER'S EMPIRE
QUICKLY EXPLODED.
HEFNER LAUNCHED HIS
BUSINESS AT A VERY
DIFFERENT TIME.
SIX DECADES AGO, THE
WORD "PREGNANT"
COULDN'T BE SAID ON "I
LOVE LUCY."
>> HELLO THERE.
GLAD YOU COULD JOIN US
THIS EVENING.
>> Reporter: HEFNER
CHALLENGED WHAT HE SAW
AS THE PRIGGISH,
REPRESSED ATTITUDES
THAT WERE PART OF HIS
MIDWESTERN METHODIST
UPBRINGING.
HIS MAGAZINE WAS
SHOCKING TO SOME,
BANNED BY OTHERS.
THE U.S. POST OFFICE
AT ONE POINT REFUSED
TO DELIVER IT.
ALL THE WHILE COPIES
OF THE MAGAZINE
CAREFULLY HIDDEN UNDER
MATTRESSES BECAME
SECRET TREASURES FOR
GENERATIONS OF TEENAGE
BOYS.
AT ITS PEAK IN THE
1970s "PLAYBOY" SOLD 7
MILLION COPIES A MONTH
WHILE MAKING BUNNY
EARS AS FAMOUS AS THE
GOLDEN ARCHES.
>> THE DAY THAT YOU
ARE WILLING TO COME
OUT HERE WITH A
COTTONTAIL ATTACHED TO
YOUR REAR END --
>> Reporter: THOSE WHO
SAID THEY BOUGHT
"PLAYBOY" TO READ THE
ARTICLES MAY HAVE BEEN
TELLING THE TRUTH.
INTERVIEWS WITH THOSE
LIKE FIDEL CASTRO,
JIMMY CARTER AND
MUHAMMAD ALI ALL
CONSIDERED MUST-READS
AT THE TIME.
HE RAN HIS EMPIRE FROM
HIS BED.
LIFE IS TOO SHORT, HE
SAID, TO LIVE SOMEBODY
ELSE'S DREAM.
MISSION ACCOMPLISHED.
CYNTHIA McFADDEN, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> THERE'S MORE TO
TELL YOU ABOUT
TONIGHT.
STILL AHEAD EMMY AWARD
WINNING ACTRESS JULIA
LOUIS-DREYFUS
REVEALING HER BATTLE
WITH BREAST CANCER.
THE PASSIONATE PLEA
SHE'S MAKING ON
WOMEN'S BEHALF.
>>> ON THE BRINK OF
Start the interview with a
firm handshake.
Ay,no! Don't do that!
Try Head & Shoulders
Instant Relief.
It cools on contact, and also
keeps you 100% flake free.
Try Head & Shoulders
Instant Relief.
For cooling relief in a snap.
is is Not this John Smith.ith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
>>> TODAY THERE WAS A
SURPRISE ANNOUNCEMENT
BY ONE OF THE MOST
ACCLAIMED ACTRESSES ON
TELEVISION.
JULIA LOUIS-DREYFUS,
THE EMMY-WINNING QUEEN
OF COMEDY AND STAR OF
"VEEP" AND "SEINFELD"
REVEALED SHE'S
BATTLING BREAST CANCER
AND ISSUED A CALL THE
ACTION.
CATIE BECK HAS
DETAILS.
>> Reporter: THE DAY
AFTER SHE BROKE THE
RECORD FOR WINNING THE
MOST EMMYS IN A SINGLE
ROLE --
>> THANK YOU SO, SO
MUCH.
>> Reporter: --
BELOVED COMIC ACTRESS
JULIA LOUIS-DREYFUS
LEARNED SHE HAD BREAST
CANCER.
TODAY ON TWITTER, THE
56-YEAR-OLD WIFE AND
MOTHER WENT PUBLIC TO
SEND A MESSAGE.
ONE IN EIGHT WOMEN
GUEST BREAST CANCER.
TODAY I'M THE ONE.
THE GOOD NEWS, SHE
WROTE, IS THAT I HAVE
THE MOST GLORIOUS
GROUP OF SUPPORTIVE
AND CARING FAMILY AND
FRIENDS AND FANTASTIC
INSURANCE THROUGH MY
UNION.
THE BAD NEWS IS THAT
NOT ALL WOMEN ARE SO
LUCKY.
SO LET'S FIGHT ALL
CANCERS AND MAKE
UNIVERSAL HEALTHCARE A
REALITY.
AMERICA KNEW HER BEST
AS ELAINE BENES FROM
THE HIT COMEDY
"SEINFELD," LATER AS
THE SELF-CENTERED VICE
PRESIDENT ON THE HBO
SERIES "VEEP."
>> AND WHETHER YOU
VOTED FOR ME --
>> Reporter: AND A
THREE-TIME HOST OF
"SATURDAY NIGHT LIVE."
OFF CAMERA, SHE'S AN
ADVOCATE FOR CANCER
RESEARCH AND DOCTORS
SAY WHEN CELEBRITIES
SHARE THEIR DIAGNOSIS,
IT MAKES A DIFFERENCE.
>> I'VE PERSONALLY
SEEN WOMEN COME INTO
OUR CLINIC TO SAY, I
READ THIS STORY.
DO I NEED TO BE
CONSIDERED FOR THIS
PARTICULAR TESTING OR
TREATMENT?
>> Reporter: THE
AMERICAN CANCER
SOCIETY SAID WOMEN
OVER 55, LIE
LOUIS-DREYFUS SHOULD
HAVE MAMMOGRAMS EVERY
TWO YEAR.
WHILE SHE'S IN
TREATMENT, HBO SAYS
THEY'LL SHOOT AROUND
HER SCHEDULE, LIKE SO
MANY WISHING HER A
QUICK RECOVERY AND
MORE LAUGHS TO COME.
>> NO SOUP FOR YOU.
>> WE'LL BE BACK WITH
THE VIRAL VIDEO OF THE How de
with moderate to severe
rheumatoid arthritis?
Do what I did.
Ask your doctor about HUMIRA.
It's proven to help relieve pain
and protect joints
from further irreversible damage
in many adults.
HUMIRA works by targeting
and helping to block
a specific source
of inflammation
that contributes to RA symptoms.
HUMIRA has been clinically
studied for over 20 years.
HUMIRA can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening
heart failure.
Before treatment,
get tested for TB.
Tell your doctor
if you've been to areas
where certain fungal infections
are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if
you have an infection.
Ready for a new chapter?
Talk to your rheumatologist
about HUMIRA.
This is HUMIRA at work.
I can't wait for her to have
that college experience that I
had.
The classes,
the friends,
the independence.
And since we planned for it,
that student debt is the one
experience, I'm glad she'll miss
When you have the right
financial advisor, life can be
brilliant.
Ameriprise
My friends think doing this
at my age is scary.
I say not if you
protect yourself.
What is scary?
Pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's a serious disease.
My doctor said the risk is
greater now that I'm over 50!
Yeah...ya-ha...
Just one dose of the PREVNAR 13®
vaccine can help protect you
from pneumococcal pneumonia-
an illness that can cause
coughing, chest pain,
difficulty breathing,
and may even put you
in the hospital.
PREVNAR 13® is approved for
adults 18 and older to help
prevent infections from
13 strains of the bacteria that
cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
You should not receive
PREVNAR 13® if you have had
a severe allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
If you have a weakened
immune system,
you may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects
were pain, redness,
and swelling at
the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Get this one done!
Ask about PREVNAR 13®
at your next visit to your
doctor's office or pharmacy.
>>> TONIGHT, FEDERAL
HEALTH OFFICIALS SAY
THAT BRACING FOR A
POTENTIALLY ROUGH FLU
SEASON.
IT'S NEVER A FUN TIME
OF YEAR, BUT OFFICIALS
SAY THIS FALL AND
WINTER COULD BE
ESPECIALLY MISERABLE
BECAUSE OF THE
PARTICULAR STRAIN,
H3N2 THAT IS POPPING
UP.
>>> AN ADORABLE MOMENT
CAUGHT ON CAMERA WHEN
PRINCE HARRY,
ATTENDING THE INVICTUS
GAMES IN TORONTO,
DIDN'T REALIZE HIS
POPCORN WAS BEING
STOLEN BY THE TODDLER
SITTING NEXT TO HIM.
WHEN THE PRINCE
FINALLY NOTICED THE
SNACK THIEF, HE AGREED
TO SHARE.
HARRY IS FRIENDS WITH
THE GIRL'S PARENTS.
HER DAD IS A BRITISH
PARALYMPIAN.
>>> WHAT WOULD THE
PRESIDENTS CUP GOLF
TOURNAMENT BE WITHOUT
A FEW PRESIDENTS?
BARACK OBAMA, GEORGE
W. BUSH AND BILL
CLINTON ALL HELPED TEE
OFF THE COMPETITION IN
NEW JERSEY TODAY.
GOLF STAR PHIL
MICKELSON GOT IN THE
ACT TAKING A SELFIE OR
AT LEAST HALF A SELFIE
WITH THE TRIO.
>>> UP NEXT, THE
ROOKIE NFL STAR WHO
DECIDED OTHERS NEEDED
HIS PAYCHECK MORE THAN
HIM.
>>> NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS"
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY
PACIFIC LIFE.
PROTECTING GENERATIONS
OF FAMILIES FOR 150
What are the ingredients
of a life well lived?
Is it the places you go?
The things you own?
Or the people that fill it
with meaning?
For 150 years,
generations of families
have chosen Pacific Life
for retirement and
life insurance solutions.
Protecting what's most
important to you.
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask a financial advisor
about Pacific Life.
Do I use a toothpaste that
whitens my teeth or...
...one that's
good for my teeth?
Now I don't have to choose!
From Crest 3D White comes new
Whitening Therapy.
It's our best whitening
technology.
Plus, it has a fortifying
formula to protect your enamel.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
I'm Val. The Orange Money
retirement squirrel from Voya.
I represent the money you save
for the future.
Who's he?
He's the green money you can
spend now. What's up?
Gonna pay some bills, maybe buy
a new tennis racket.
He's got a killer backhand.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement, it's time to get
Voya.
>>> FINALLY, AS THE
DISASTER CONTINUES TO
UNFOLD IN PUERTO RICO
IN THE WAKE OF
HURRICANE MARIA, THERE
ARE ALSO MANY WHO
STILL NEED HELP AFTER
HURRICANES HARVEY AND
IRMA.
IN HOUSTON, A CITY
DEVASTATED BY THE
FLOODWATERS FROM
HARVEY, AN NFL STAR IS
MAKING A VERY PERSONAL
GIFT TO HELP VICTIMS
RECOVER.
OUR JOE FRYER HAS
TONIGHT'S "INSPIRING
AMERICA" REPORT.
>> Reporter: LIKE ANY
GOOD QUARTERBACK,
DESHAUN WATSON HAS A
PLAY FOR EVERY
POSSIBLE SCENARIO,
EVEN A HURRICANE.
>> I'M GOING TO DO A
LITTLE SURPRISE.
>> Reporter: THIS WEEK
THE HOUSTON TEXANS
ROOKIE THREW A
SURPRISE AT THREE
STADIUM EMPLOYEES WHO
LOST CARS AND HOMES
DURING HURRICANE
HARVEY.
>> YOU ALL DO FOR US
EVERY DAY AND NEVER
COMPLAIN.
I REALLY APPRECIATE
YOU ALL.
SO I WANTED TO GIVE MY
FIRST GAME CHECK TO
YOU ALL TO HELP YOU
ALL OUT.
>> THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>> NO PROBLEM.
>> Reporter: IN ALL
WATSON DONATED ABOUT
$27,000 FROM HIS BASE
SALARY OF $465,000.
THIS 22-YEAR-OLD KNOWS
FIRSTHAND ABOUT THE
POWER OF PHILANTHROPY.
GROWING UP IN GEORGIA
WITH A SINGLE MOM AND
THREE SIBLINGS THEY
RECEIVED A HOUSE
THROUGH HABITAT FOR
HUMANITY.
>> JUST BE AROUND THE
FAMILY AND BE HAPPY
AND BE SAFE AND NOT
WORRY ABOUT ANYTHING
HAPPENING WAS PRETTY
HELPFUL.
>> Reporter: ON THE
NIGHT HE WAS DRAFTED,
WATSON READ A LETTER
FROM HIS MOM DEANE WHO
HAS BEEN BATTLING
CANCER.
>> AS I LOOK BACK, WE
WERE NOT SUPPOSED TO
BE HERE.
>> Reporter: DAYS
LATER, HE BOUGHT HIS
MOM A CAR.
GRATEFUL FOR ALL HE
HAS RECEIVED, THIS
YOUNG QUARTERBACK IS
NOW HONORED TO GIVE
BACK.
>> HOPEFULLY IT WILL
HELP.
>> Reporter: JOE
FRYER, NBC NEWS.
>> WHAT A GREAT STORY.
>>> WE APPRECIATE YOU
SPENDING PART OF YOUR
EVENING WITH US.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS THURSDAY
NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
AND FOR ALL OF US AT
NBC NEWS, THANK YOU
FOR WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
♪♪
For every small business
fueled by a dream....
Eastern Bank is here.
Closing more
Small Business Loans
in New England
than any other bank.
♪♪
Here to do good.
To do right.
To do more.
To help all of us do better.
So join us.
For good.