SUNDAY.
>> LET'S HAVE A QUICK LOOK AT
THE FORECAST.
>> WE MAY DRY OUT THE SHOWERS IN
THE AFTERNOON AND NEXT WEEK
BEAUTIFUL ALL THE WAY INTO 70s.
>> I AM CHRIS EMMA.
>> AND I AM AUDREY ASISTIO.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT.
HEALTH SECRETARY TOM
PRICE IS OUT, UNDER
FIRE FOR HIS USE OF
PRIVATE JETS,
RESIGNING AFTER
PROMISING TO REPAY A
FRACTION OF TAXPAYER
MONEY.
>>> LASHING OUT.
GROWING ANGER OVER THE
PUERTO RICO DISASTER
RESPONSE.
>> WE ARE DYING, AND
YOU ARE KILLING US
WITH THE INEFFICIENCY.
>> LOCAL OFFICIALS
FURIOUS PRESIDENT
TRUMP INSISTING HIS
ADMINISTRATION IS
DOING AN INCREDIBLE
JOB.
TONIGHT MILLIONS
DESPERATE FOR HELP.
>>> CUBA TRAVEL ALERT.
AMERICANS WARNED NOT
TO VISIT CUBA.
EMBASSY STAFF ORDERED
OUT AFTER MYSTERY
ATTACKS ON DIPLOMATS.
>>> ANOTHER VIOLENT
COLLAPSE IN YOSEMITE'S
EL CAPITAN.
WHY ARE CLIERS NOT
BEING KEPT AWAY?
>>> AND HIDDEN HOTEL
FEES.
IF YOU'RE OFF FOR A
WEEKEND GETAWAY, WHAT
YOU NEED TO WATCH FOR.
HIDDEN EXTRA CHARGES
ON YOUR BILL.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> THIS IS NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
APOLOGIES AND
REIMBURSEMENTS WERE
NOT ENOUGH TO SAVE
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
EMBATTLED HEALTH AND
HUMAN SERVICES
SECRETARY WHO A SHORT
TIME AGO RESIGNED OVER
HIS HIGH FLYING TRAVEL
WAYS AT TAXPAYERS'
EXPENSE.
WE'LL GET TO THOSE
BREAKING DETAILS
SHORTLY, BUT WE WANT
TO START WITH THE
INCREDIBLY EMOTIONAL
PLEA TODAY FROM THE
MAYOR OF SAN JUAN,
PUERTO RICO.
A CRY FOR HELP.
WE ARE DYING, SHE
SAID, AS SHE ANGRILY
DEMANDED WASHINGTON
UNTANGLE THE
BOTTLENECK THAT HAS
PREVENTED AID FROM
REACHING SO MANY
PUERTO RICANS
SUFFERING FROM THE
AFTERMATH OF HURRICANE
MARIA.
THE DARK PICTURE SHE
PAINTED THIS AFTERNOON
IN SHARP CONTRAST TO
THE ROSY ASSESSMENT
BEING PUT FORWARD BY
THE ADMINISTRATION.
NBC'S GABE GUTIERREZ
HAS LATE DETAILS.
>> I'M DONE BEING
POLITE.
I AM DONE BEING
POLITICALLY CORRECT.
I AM MAD AS HELL.
>> Reporter: SAN
JUAN'S MAYOR THIS
AFTERNOON MAKING AN
EMOTIONAL PLEA
DIRECTLY TO THE
PRESIDENT.
>> I BEG YOU TO TAKE
CHARGE AND SAVE LIVES.
WE ARE DYING HERE.
AND I CANNOT FATHOM
THE THOUGHT THAT THE
GREATEST NATION IN THE
WORLD CANNOT FIGURE
OUT LOGISTICS FOR A
SMALL ISLAND.
>> Reporter: RIPPING
INTO FEMA FOR NOT
DISTRIBUTING AID FAST
ENOUGH.
>> WE DON'T GET THE
FOOD AND THE WATER
INTO PEOPLE'S HANDS,
WE ARE GOING TO SEE IS
SOMETHING CLOSE TO A
GENOCIDE.
>> Reporter:
REPRESENTATIVE ENRIQUE
MELENDEZ AGREES EVEN
THOUGH HE SUPPORTED
PRESIDENT TRUMP DURING
THE ELECTION.
>> WHERE IS THE NAVY?
WHERE IS THE ARMY?
WE NEED THEM RIGHT
NOW.
NOT NEXT WEEK.
>> Reporter: GOVERNOR
RICARDO ROSSELLO IS
STILL IN CHARGE OF THE
RECOVERY EFFORTS BUT
IS GETTING MORE
SUPPORT FROM THE
MILITARY.
>> WE'VE BEEN GETTING
MORE ASSETS, AND WE'RE
SHOWING IT.
>> Reporter: FEMA SAYS
THE ISLAND'S GEOGRAPHY
IS HAMPERING THE
EFFORT.
>> IT'S BEEN
INCREDIBLE THE RESULTS
THAT WE'VE HAD WITH
RESPECT TO LOSS OF
LIFE.
PEOPLE CAN'T BELIEVE
HOW SUCCESSFUL THAT
HAS BEEN RELATIVELY
SPEAKING.
>> I RESPECTFULLY
DISAGREE WITH
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
AND I AM SURE THAT HE
IS NOT GETTING THE
DATA THAT WE ARE
SEEING IN THE STREETS.
>> Reporter: TODAY
ACTING HOMELAND
SECURITY SECRETARY
ELAINE DUKE VISITED
THE NATION.
>> AFTER THE
DEVASTATING
EARTHQUAKE, THE
SITUATION HERE IS NOT
SATISFACTORY, BUT
TOGETHER WE ARE
GETTING THERE.
>> Reporter: BUT JUST
OUTSIDE SAN JUAN
ELIZABETH REYES STOOD
IN THE BLAZING SUN
WITH HER 2-MONTH-OLD
DAUGHTER FOR HOURS.
>> EVERYONE IS
DESPERATE.
EVERYONE WANTS WATER.
EVERYONE WANTS
SOMETHING TO EAT.
>> Reporter: TODAY SHE
GOT A FEW SUPPLIES.
BUT THEN THERE'S
TOMORROW.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, CATANIA, PUERTO
RICO.
>>> THIS IS TAMMY
LEITNER WITH THE
MARINES ON A CRITICAL
MISSION.
VIEQUES JUST EIGHT
MILES OFF THE COAST OF
PUERTO RICO IS STILL
DESPERATE FOR AID.
WE WENT IN ON A MARINE
CHOPPER FILLED WITH
FOOD, WATER AND
MEDICAL SUPPLIES.
THIS IS ONE OF MANY
TRIPS THEY'LL BE
MAKING TO THIS ISLAND.
FOOD IS DWINDLING,
WATER IS SCARCE, THERE
IS NO FUEL.
NATHAN PARENTS HAS
FLOWN 45 PEOPLE OFF
THE ISLAND.
>> A LOT OF PEOPLE
WANT TO GET OFF.
>> Reporter: REBECCA
ANDERSON HAS LIVED
HERE FOR NINE YEARS.
>> WE WANT TO STAY.
BUT THERE'S NO WORK
HERE FOR US.
WE WORK IN TOURISM AND
THERE WON'T BE ANY
TOURISM FOR A WHILE.
IT'S HEARTBREAKING.
>> Reporter: ONE
FAMILY GETTING OUT.
SO MANY OTHERS WAIT AT
THE AIRPORT DESPERATE
FOR NEWS.
>> WE NEED FUEL.
WE NEED WATER.
>> Reporter: FEMA
DIRECTOR ON THE GROUND
FOR FIRST TIME.
>> THE SITUATION
NATURAL SE BAD.
>> Reporter: FEAR
SETTING IN, THE FUTURE
UNKNOWN.
TAMMY LEITNER, NBC
NEWS, VEE ACHOUS,
PUERTO RICO.
>>> TOM PRICE
RESIGNING LATE TODAY
AFTER A FIRESTORM
ERUPTED OVER HIS USE
OF PRIVATE PLANES ON
THE TAXPAYERS' DIME.
CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HALLIE
JACKSON HAS THE LATE
DETAILS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
TOM PRICE'S BUMPY RIDE
NOW ENDING AT THE
HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES AGENCY AFTER
A GROWING CONTROVERSY
OVER HIS PRICEY TRIPS
ON PRIVATE JETS.
PRESIDENT TRUMP FIRST
LEAVING HIS SECRETARY
IN SUSPENSE.
>> HE'S A VERY FINE
MAN, BUT WE'RE GOING
TO MAKE A DECISION
SOME TIME TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: AN HOUR
LATER MAKING IT
OFFICIAL.
ACCEPTING PRICE'S
RESIGNATION.
>> I THINK HE'S A VERY
FINE PERSON.
I CERTAINLY DON'T LIKE
THE OPTICS.
>> Reporter: PRICE HAD
PROMISED TO PAY BACK
THE COST OF HIS SEAT
ON THOSE PRIVATE
PLANES, $51,000.
WITH TAXPAYERS ON THE
HOOK FOR THE REST OF
THAT REPORTED $400,000
TOTAL.
>> CLEARLY WE GOT --
WE'RE SENSITIVE TO THE
TAXPAYER ON THESE
INSTANCES.
>> Reporter: THAT
DAMAGE CONTROL TOO
LITTLE TOO LATE.
>> TAXPAYERS ARE
OUTRAGED BY THIS USE
OF THEIR MONEY
ESPECIALLY WHEN THEY
SEE BUDGETS BEING CUT.
>> Reporter: PRICE, A
DOCTOR AND FORMER
GEORGIA CONGRESSMAN,
LED THE HEALTH AGENCY
THROUGH A ROCKY SUMMER
THAT SAW HEALTHCARE
REFORM FAIL
REPEATEDLY.
>> HE BETTER GET THEM.
OH, HE BETTER.
OTHERWISE I'LL SAY,
TOM, YOU'RE FIRED!
>> Reporter: NOW, THE
TRAVEL SCRUTINY'S
SPREADING TO PRICE'S
CABINET COLLEAGUES.
TREASURY SECRETARY
STEVEN MNUCHIN IS
UNDER REVIEW AFTER
MAKING THEN DROPPING A
REQUEST TO USE A
GOVERNMENT JET FOR HIS
EUROPEAN HONEYMOON, HE
SAYS FOR SECURE
COMMUNICATIONS.
AND TODAY INTERIOR
SECRETARY RYAN
ZINKE --
>> I FLY COACH.
>> Reporter: HE'S NOW
ACKNOWLEDGING THREE
PRIVATE CHARTER
FLIGHTS HE'S TAKEN
THIS YEAR INCLUDING TO
THE VIRGIN ISLANDS AND
ONE TRIP FROM VEGAS TO
MONT THAT COST
TAXPAYERS $12,000.
>> EVERY TIME I
TRAVEL, I SUBMIT THE
TRAVEL PLAN TO THE
ETHICS DEPARTMENT.
THEY EVALUATE IT LINE
BY LINE.
>> Reporter: AND IN
THIS NEW LETTER
TONIGHT, THE BUDGET
DIRECTOR REMINDS ALL
AGENCIES EVERY PENNY
THEY SPEND COMES FROM
THE TAXPAYERS.
PRICE YET ANOTHER HIGH
PROFILE DEPARTURE FOR
THIS ADMINISTRATION
ALONG WITH SEAN
SPICER, REINCE
PRIEBUS, STEVE BANNON,
ALL LEAVING RIGHT
BEFORE A WEEKEND.
CALL IT FAREWALE
FRIDAYS AROUND HERE,
LESTER.
>>> THE UNITED STATES
TODAY ORDERED A
DRASTIC REDUCTION OF
ITS DIPLOMATIC STAFF
IN CUBA AFTER A SERIES
OF STRANGE ATTACKS
AGAINST AMERICANS
WORKING AT THE EMBASSY
THERE.
AT THE SAME TIME ALL
AMERICANS WERE WARNED
AGAINST TRAVELING TO
CUBA.
OUR CHIEF FOREIGN
AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT
ANDREA MITCHELL HAS
THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE STATE DEPARTMENT
ORDERING MOST OF THE
AMERICAN STAFF AT THE
U.S. EMBASSY IN CUBA
HOME, AND SECRETARY OF
STATE REX TILLERSON
ADVISING U.S. CITIZENS
TO AVOID TRAVEL TO
CUBA.
A MAJOR BLOW TO THE
NEW U.S./CUBA
RELATIONSHIP.
>> SOME VERY BAD
THINGS HAPPENED IN
CUBA.
VERY BAD THINGS.
>> Reporter: THE RARE
MOVE IN RESPONSE TO
MYSTERIOUS ATTACKS
AGAINST 21 U.S.
DIPLOMATS.
TILLERSON TONIGHT
DESCRIBING THEIR
INJURIES.
HEARING LOSS,
DIZZINESS, HEADACHE,
FATIGUE, COGNITIVE
ISSUES IS AND
DIFFICULTY SLEEPING.
EARLIER THIS WEEK
CUBA'S FOREIGN
MINISTER RUSHING TO
WASHINGTON, TELLING
TILLERSON CUBA WAS NOT
BEHIND IT.
THE FBI AND CIA IN
HAVANA NOW
INVESTIGATING WHAT
EXPERTS ARE CALLING
TARGETED ATTACKS FROM
SMALL SONIC DEVICES.
HOW DO THESE DEVICES
WORK, THESE ACOUSTIC
DEVICES?
>> WE'RE LIKELY
TALKING ABOUT
SOMETHING WHERE YOU
HAVE NO IDEA IT'S
HAPPENING.
IT'S BENEATH YOUR
ABILITY TO HEAR OR
ACTUALLY ABOVE THE
SOUND FREQUENCY THAT
YOU WOULD HEAR IT
AUDIBLY.
>> Reporter: THE
BIZARRE ATTACKS COMING
TWO YEARS AFTER THE
U.S. REOPENED ITS
HAVANA EMBASSY, ENDING
A HALF CENTURY COLD
WAR.
SUPPORTERS OF
DIPLOMATIC RELATIONS
SUGGEST RUSSIA COULD
BE TO BLAME, TRYING TO
BREAK UP HAVANA'S
FLEDGLING RELATIONSHIP
WITH THE U.S.
>> IF WE WERE SUDDENLY
TO LEAVE, RUSSIA
BENEFITS BY THAT A
GREAT DEAL.
>> Reporter: TODAY'S
TRAVEL WARNING COULD
HURT CRUISE SHIPS AND
AIRLINES, BUT ALTHOUGH
SOME OF THE ATTACKS
TOOK PLACE IN HOTELS,
AMERICAN TOURISTS
TONIGHT WERE UNFAZED.
>> EVERYTHING IS SAFE.
NOBODY IS TRYING TO
HURT US OR GET US OR
THREATEN US OR
ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: AND
TONIGHT STILL NO IDEA
WHO IS BEHIND THE
ATTACKS.
CUBA CALLING THE U.S.
DECISION HASTY, EVEN
AS FLORIDA SENATOR
MARCO RUBIO, A CUBAN
AMERICAN, SAYS THE
STATE DEPARTMENT WAS
NOT TOUGH ENOUGH.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT, ANDREA,
THANK YOU.
>>> HERE IN
CALIFORNIA, THERE'S
BEEN A SECOND MASSIVE
ROCK SLIDE IN AS MANY
DAYS AT YOSEMITE'S
FAMED EL CAPITAN,
FALLING BOULDERS HAVE
KILLED ONE TOURIST AND
INJURED OTHERS, BUT
CLIMBERS ARE NOT BEING
KEPT AWAY.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER IS
THERE TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: WHEN EL
CAPITAN BEGAN TO
SUDDENLY CRUMBLE,
MASSIVE SHEETS OF
GRANITE RATTLED, THEN
DROPPED 1800 FEET.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> Reporter: A
TOWERING WALL OF
BOULDERS AND DUST
THUNDERING INTO THE
YOSEMITE VALLEY,
PUSHING SOME CARS OFF
THE ROAD.
MANY VISITORS CAUGHT
IN THE PLUME.
SOME HIT BY ROCKS.
>> RELAX.
IT'S A CUT.
>> THIS IS THE DAY I
DIE.
>> NO, IT'S NOT.
IT'S NOT THE DAY YOU
DIE.
>> Reporter:
INCREDIBLY NO
FATALITIES.
ONE VICTIM AIRLIFTED
TO A REGIONAL
HOSPITAL.
THIS IS WHERE ROCK
CLIMBER PETER ZABROK
WATCHED.
>> WE WERE ON THE
SUMMIT AND WE WERE ALL
SAFE.
>> Reporter:
THURSDAY'S MASSIVE
SLIDE, OFFICIALS SAY,
IS 22 TIMES LARGER
THAN THE ONE JUST THE
DAY BEFORE WHEN A SLAB
OF ROCK THE SIZE OF AN
APARTMENT BUILDING
CAME CRASHING DOWN
WHILE AT LEAST 30
CLIMBERS WERE CLINGING
TO EL CAP.
ONE BRITISH TOURIST
WAS KILLED.
HIS WIFE SERIOUSLY
INJURED.
THERE'S NO CLEAR
REASON WHY EL CAP IS
CRUMBLING.
EIGHT MAJOR ROCK
SLIDES IN JUST TWO
DAYS.
>> YOSEMITE NATIONAL
PARK, BY DEFINITION,
IS A WILD PLACE.
ULTIMATELY, THESE
CLIMBERS NEED TO MAKE
DECISIONS ON THEIR OWN
AND GOOD DECISIONS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
CLEAR SIGNS OF DANGER
IN ALL OF THIS BEAUTY.
A SIGHT TO BEHOLD AND
BEWARE.
>> MIGUEL, YOU
MENTIONED EIGHT SLIDES
HERE IN THE LAST
COUPLE OF DAYS.
WHY ARE THEY NOT
PULLING CLIMBERS OFF
THE MOUNTAIN, CLOSING
IT FOR THE TIME BEING?
>> Reporter: LESTER,
RANGERS SAY THE PARK
IS SAFE, BUT WHAT HAS
HAPPENED BEHIND ME IS
PART OF THE NATURAL
PROCESS HERE IN
YOSEMITE PARK.
THEY SAY THIS HAPPENS
EVERY DAY THOUGH
USUALLY NOT IN THIS
SIZE.
AND AS YOU MENTIONED
RIGHT NOW, MORE THAN
TWO DOZEN CLIMBERS ARE
SCALING THAT HUGE
MOUNTAIN BEHIND ME.
>> MIGUEL ALMAGUER AT
YOSEMITE, THANK YOU.
>>> NOW TO A
DISTURBING STORY AT
ONE OF AMERICA'S ELITE
MILITARY ACADEMIES.
THIS MONTH THERE HAD
BEEN A NUMBER OF
REPORTED RACIAL SLURS
AND INCIDENTS CROPPING
UP ON COLLEGE CAMPUSES
NATIONWIDE.
THE LATEST AT THE U.S.
AIR FORCE ACADEMY
WHERE THE COMMANDER'S
RESPONSE HAS BEEN SO
POWERFUL IT HAS BEEN
SEEN AND SHARED ACROSS
THE COUNTRY TODAY.
NBC'S PETER ALEXANDER
HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: AT ONE OF
AMERICA'S PREMIER
SERVICE ACADEMIES, A
POWERFUL LESSON IN
LEADERSHIP.
>> YOU SHOULD BE
OUTRAGED NOT ONLY AS
AN AIRMAN BUT AS A
HUMAN BEING.
>> Reporter: THE HEAD
OF THE AIR FORCE XAED
LIEUTENANT GENERAL JAY
SILVERIA SUMMONING
CADETS AFTER FIVE
BLACK STUDENTS FOUND
THE WORDS GO HOME AND
A RACIAL SLUR ON THEIR
DOORS.
>> THIS IS OUR
INSTITUTION, AND NO
ONE CAN TAKE AWAY OUR
VALUES.
>> Reporter: SILVERIA
IMPLORING HIS CADETS
NOT TO BE TONE DEAF TO
THE RACIAL TENSIONS IN
THE COUNTRY.
>> LIKE
CHARLOTTESVILLE AND
FERGUSON, THE PROTESTS
IN THE NFL.
BECAUSE WHAT WE SHOULD
HAVE IS A CIVIL
DISCOURSE AND TALK
ABOUT THESE ISSUES.
>> Reporter: AMONG THE
STUDENTS TARGETED
JASON BLAND'S SON.
HIS FATHER TELLING NBC
NEWS THE REAL VICTIM
IS THE PERSON RAISEDED
WITH THAT KIND OF
HATRED.
ADDING, AMERICANS
SHOULD BOYCOTT HATE.
>> THE POWER THAT WE
COME FROM ALL WALKS OF
LIFE, THAT WE COME
FROM ALL PARTS OF THIS
COUNTRY, THAT WE COME
FROM ALL RACES, WE
COME FROM ALL
BACKGROUNDS, THE POWER
OF THAT DIVERSITY
COMES TOGETHER AND
MAKES US THAT MUCH
MORE POWERFUL.
>> Reporter: THEN THIS
UNUSUAL REQUEST.
>> REACH FOR YOUR
PHONES.
I'M SERIOUS.
REACH FOR YOUR PHONES.
>> Reporter: SO HIS
WORDS WOULD BE
INDELIBLE.
>> AND YOU USE THEM
AND YOU REMEMBER THEM
AND YOU SHARE THEM AND
YOU TALK ABOUT THEM.
IF YOU CAN'T TREAT
SOMEONE WITH DIGNITY
AND RESPECT, THEN GET
OUT.
>> Reporter: A MESSAGE
DELIVERED LOUD AND
CLEAR.
PETER ALEXANDER, NBC
NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> STILL AHEAD
TONIGHT, WHAT'S BEHIND
ALL THOSE HIDDEN NEW
FEES THAT SHOW UP ON
YOUR HOTEL BILL.
THEY MAY BE COVERING
THINGS YOU THOUGHT
WERE FREE.
>>> ALSO, THE BIG WIN
TODAY BY SKATERS FROM
NORTH KOREA, AND W
Whoa. This looks worse than
I thought.
Mike and Jen Doyle?
Yeah.
Time for Medicare, huh.
I have no idea how we're going
to get through this.
Follow me.
Choosing a plan can be
super-complicated.
But it doesn't have to be.
UnitedHealthcare can guide you
through the confusion,
with helpful people, tools and
plans.
Including the only plans with
the AARP name.
Well that wasn't so bad at all.
That's how we like it.
AARP Medicare plans, from
UnitedHealthcare.
My shoulders carry
a lot of names
Some I deserve
Others I don't
But in the end
Only one name really matters
Because shoulders were made for
greatness, not dandruff
♪ Stare with me into the abyss ♪
( ♪♪ )
♪♪Your body was made for better♪
things than
rheumatoid arthritis.
Before you and your
rheumatologist move to another
treatment, ask if XELJANZ is
right for you.
XELJANZ is a small pill for
adults with
moderate to severe RA for whom
methotrexate did not work well.
XELJANZ can reduce joint pain
and swelling in as little as
two weeks, and help stop further
joint damage.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma and other
cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ if you have
an infection.
Tears in the stomach or
intestines, low blood cell
counts and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you were in
a region where fungal
infections are common and if you
have had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or are prone
to infections.
XELJANZ can reduce the symptoms
of RA,
even without methotrexate, and
is also available
in a once-daily pill.
Ask about XELJANZ XR.
>>> BACK NOW WITH
SOMETHING THAT
FRUSTRATES SO MANY
TRAVELERS.
HAVE YOU EVER GOTTEN
YOUR HOTEL BILL AND
BEEN SHOCKED BY
UNEXPECTED CHARGES?
SO-CALLED RESORT FEES
ARE BEING CHARGED AT
SOME HOTELS THAT MANY
WOULDN'T CONSIDER
RESORTS AT ALL.
NBC'S TOM COSTELLO HAS
MORE.
>> Reporter: HOW OFTEN
HAS IT HAPPENED TO
YOU?
YOU CHECK OUT OF A
HOTEL IN ANY TOWN,
USA, AND THERE ON YOUR
BILL IS AN UNEXPECTED
CHARGE.
WHEN WISCONSIN DR.
AJIT PALI AND HIS
FAMILY WENT TO NEW
YORK HE EXPECTED THE
CHARGE FOR THE CROWN
PLAZA IN TIMES SQUARE
BUT NOT THE EXTRA $30
RESORT FEE IN THE FINE
PRINT ON THE INTERNET.
>> I THINK IT'S A BAIT
AND SWITCH.
I THINK THEY HOOK YOU
WITH THE LOWER FEE,
THEN ADD THIS TO MAKE
UP FOR IT.
>> Reporter: RESORT
FEES, SERVICE FEES,
URBAN DESTINATION
FEES.
HOTELS SAY THEY COVER
AMENITIES LIKE WIFI, A
NEWSPAPER, POOL
ACCESS, TURNDOWN
SERVICE AND SO-CALLED
COMPLIMENTARY DRINKS.
BUT 47 STATE ATTORNEYS
GENERAL ARE NOW
INVESTIGATING WHETHER
HOTELS ARE BEING
TRANSPARENT AND HONEST
ABOUT ADDING THE FEES.
>> WE DON'T THINK IT'S
FAIR TO CONSUMERS THAT
THEY'RE GOING IN
THINKING THEY'RE
PAYING ONE RATE AND
COMING OUT PAYING
ANOTHER.
>> Reporter: CROWN
PLAZA DIDN'T RESPOND
TO OUR REQUEST FOR
COMMENT.
MARRIOTT IS AMONG THE
HOTELS NAMED IN THE
INVESTIGATION ALTHOUGH
IT AND THE HOTEL
INDUSTRY TELL NBC NEWS
THOSE FEES REMAIN
TRANSPARENT WHETHER
CONSUMERS BOOK ONLINE
OR WITH THE HOTEL
DIRECTLY.
IF UNEXPECTED FEES
SOUND FAMILIAR,
EXPERTS SAY THE HOTELS
GOT THE IDEA FROM THE
AIRLINES WHICH NOW
CHARGE FOR EVERYTHING
FROM LUGGAGE TO LEG
ROOM.
>> THE AIRLINES HAVE
PROVED THAT IT IS
VERY, VERY PROFITABLE
TO CHARGE EXTRA FEES.
THEY'RE MAKING
BILLIONS OF DOLLARS IN
EXTRA FEES.
NOW THE HOTELS ARE,
TOO.
>> Reporter: DR. PALAI
SAYS LOYALTY GOES BOTH
WAYS.
>> IT'S NOT LIKE
STAYING AT EPCOT OR
DISNEYWORLD WHERE IT
TRULY IS A RESORT.
>> Reporter: HE'S
PLEDGING NEVER TO
RETURN TO HOTELS THAT
DON'T DISCLOSE ALL
THEIR FEES BEFORE HE
CHECKS IN.
TOM COSTELLO, NBC
NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>>> WE'LL TAKE A SHORT
BREAK AND BE BACK IN A
MOMENT WITH A BOLD NEW
PLAN FOR A MISSION TO
MARS AT HIGH SPE
Every day
people are fighting
type 2 diabetes...
with Fitness...
Food...
And the pill that
starts with F.
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA
if you have severe
kidney problems,
are on dialysis,
or have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary tract
infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious
and may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about
the pill that starts with F
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
is is Not this John Smith.ith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
Prudential asked these couples:
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>>> AS TENSIONS WITH
NORTH KOREA REMAIN AT
A BOILING POINT, MANY
ARE HOPING THAT WHAT
HAPPENED ON THE ICE
TODAY COULD LEAD TO A
LOWERING OF TENSIONS
IN THE REGION.
AT A COMPETITION IN
GERMANY, A PAIR OF
NORTH KOREAN FIGURE
SKATERS EARNED THEIR
COUNTRY'S FIRST SPOTS
AT THE WINTER OLYMPICS
NEXT YEAR IN SOUTH
KOREA.
WHETHER THEY'LL
PARTICIPATE REMAINS TO
BE SEEN.
WE GET MORE FROM NBC'S
JO LING KENT.
>> Reporter: FOR FOUR
MINUTES A PERFORMANCE
THAT MOVED A CROWD AND
LIFTED HOPES.
18-YEAR-OLD
TAE-OK RYUM AND JU-SIK
KIM.
THE KNOWLEDGE THAT I
COULD MAKE OUR
SUPPORTERS HAPPY
BROUGHT ME THE
GREATEST HAPPINESS.
SOUTH KOREA'S
PRESIDENT SAYING IF
THE NORTH PARTICIPATES
IT WILL BE A GREAT
OPPORTUNITY TO SEND A
MESSAGE OF PEACE TO
THE WORLD.
BUT SECURITY CONCERNS
LOOM OVER THESE GAMES.
LAST WEEK FRANCE
SUGGESTED THAT,
WITHOUT ASSURANCES
THAT THEIR ATHLETE WAS
BE SAFE, IT MAY SKIP
THE OLYMPICS.
AMERICAN FIGURE SKATER
ASHLEY WAGNER, WHO WON
BRONZE IN SOCHI IS
OPTIMISTIC.
>> I WOULD NEVER DO
ANYTHING THAT I FELT
WOULD THREATEN MY
LIFE, BUT THIS IS THE
OLYMPICS.
THIS IS WHERE THE
WORLD COMES TOGETHER
TO CELEBRATE SPORT AND
HARD WORK AND PEOPLE'S
DREAMS BEING
ACCOMPLISHED.
>> Reporter: DURING
THE RIO OLYMPICS, THIS
PHOTO OF NORTH AND
SOUTH KOREAN GYMNASTS
WENT VIRAL.
NORTH KOREA HAS UNTIL
OCTOBER 30th TO DECIDE
WHETHER TO USE THE
SPOT.
TODAY RYUM SAYING WE
WANT TO BECOME WORLD
CHAMPIONS.
IT'S A COMMON DREAM
THAT CONNECTS ATHLETES
ACROSS COUNTRIES IN A
WORLD WHERE SO MUCH
ELSE DIVIDES.
JO LING KENT, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> HOW WOULD YOU LIKE
TO GET ANYWHERE ON
EARTH IN UNDER AN
HOUR?
ELON MUSK HAS AN IDEA
TO DO IT WHICH
FEATURES A ROCKET.
MUSK CLAIMS THATTENT
WALLY A SEAT WOULD
COST ABOUT THE SAME AS
AN ECONOMY PLANE
TICKET, BUT THE
ROCKET, WHICH IS ALSO
INTENDED FOR MISSIONS
TO MARS, IS STILL IN
THE DESIGN PHASE.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK
WE'LL MEET AN
EXTRAORDINARY ATHLETE.
Each year Sarah climbs
58,007 steps.
That's the height of
Mount Everest.
Because each day she
chooses to take the stairs.
At work, at home...
even on the escalator.
That can be hard on
her lower body,
so now she does it
with Dr. Scholl's orthotics.
Clinically proven to
relieve and prevent
foot, knee or
lower back pain,
by reducing
the shock and stress
that travel up her body
with every step she takes.
So keep on climbing, Sarah.
You're killing it.
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
My friends think doing this
at my age is scary.
I say not if you
protect yourself.
What is scary?
Pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's a serious disease.
My doctor said the risk is
greater now that I'm over 50!
Yeah...ya-ha...
Just one dose of the PREVNAR 13®
vaccine can help protect you
from pneumococcal pneumonia-
an illness that can cause
coughing, chest pain,
difficulty breathing,
and may even put you
in the hospital.
PREVNAR 13® is approved for
adults 18 and older to help
prevent infections from
13 strains of the bacteria that
cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
You should not receive
PREVNAR 13® if you have had
a severe allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
If you have a weakened
immune system,
you may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects
were pain, redness,
and swelling at
the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Get this one done!
Ask about PREVNAR 13®
at your next visit to your
doctor's office or pharmacy.
There's only one egg
that just tastes better.
Fresher.
More flavorful.
Delicious.
With more great nutrition.
And 25% less saturated fat.
Only Eggland's Best.
Better taste.
Better nutrition.
Better eggs.
♪♪
Are you taking the Tissue Test?
Yep, and my teeth are yellow.
Time for Whitestrips.
Crest Glamorous White
Whitestrips are the only
ADA-accepted whitening strips
proven to be safe and effective.
And they whiten 25x better than
a leading whitening toothpaste.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
THEY ARE THE OLYMPICS
OF SORTS FOR THOSE
INJURED WHILE SERVING
THEIR COUNTRIES AROUND
THE WORLD.
THE INVICTUS GAMES
HAVE BEEN GOING ON ALL
WEEK IN TORONTO,
CHAMPIONED BY
BRITAIN'S PRINCE
HARRY.
AND FOR ONE AMERICAN
VETERAN, IT WAS A
REMARKABLE RUN AS SHE
RACKED UP A STRING OF
MEDALS.
NBC'S KEVIN TIBBLES
TONIGHT ON HOW SHE IS
INSPIRING AMERICA.
>> AND THEY ARE OFF.
>> Reporter: THEY ARE
COMPETITORS BUT ALSO
SOLDIERS AND
SURVIVORS.
>> YOU ARE ALL
WINNERS.
>> Reporter: THE
INVICTUS GAMES ARE THE
PASSION OF BRITAIN'S
PRINCE HARRY.
>> LET'S GET STARTED.
>> Reporter: THIS YEAR
HIS FIRST PUBLIC
OUTING WITH GIRLFRIEND
MEGHAN MARKLE CREATED
A BUZZ.
BUT THEY WANT THE
FOCUS TO BE ON THE
FIELD WHERE THE REAL
HEROES SHINE.
ATHLETES LIKE SARA
RUTTER, A FIERCE
COMPETITOR AND PROUD
MARINE.
SHE COPIES EVERY DAY
WITH THE LOSS OF HER
LEG.
>> I LOOK AT THIS
WALL, AND I TELL
MYSELF NO MORE
EXCUSES.
LET'S GO.
>> Reporter: WHEN SHE
IS NOT IN TRAINING,
SHE'S A MOM AND A
NEIGHBORHOOD COACH.
SHE WAS INJURED
SEARCHING THE RUBBLE
AFTER 9/11 WHEN A
FALLING SLAB OF
CONCRETE CRUSHED HER
ANKLE.
WHAT BOTHERS HER
MOST -- NOT BEING ABLE
TO FIGHT IN THE WAR ON
TERROR.
>> THAT ANGER INSIDE
OF ME STILL HAUNTS ME
DAILY, THAT I COULDN'T
GO AND SERVE WITH
THEM.
>> Reporter: SO
INSTEAD SHE SERVES AS
AN EXAMPLE.
>> CAN SHE CATCH
RUTTER?
>> Reporter: WHILE
LEADING THE 200 METERS
LAST YEAR SHE STUMBLED
AND FELL, BUT SHE DID
NOT STAY DOWN.
>> I SAID, GOT TO
FINISH THIS, SO I GOT
UP AND FINISHED
SECOND.
>> Reporter: THAT
SUPERHUMAN WILL COMES
FROM HER SUPERHUMAN
HERO, WONDER WOMAN.
>> WE STILL NEED TO
RISE EVERY SINGLE DAY,
NO MATTER HOW MUCH
WE'RE POUNDED DOWN.
>> Reporter: AT THIS
YEAR'S GAMES, SARA WON
SEV MEDALS, FIVE OF
THEM GOLD, OVERCOMING
CONSTANT PAIN TO REACH
THE TOP AND EMBODY THE
SPIRIT OF THE INVICTUS
GAMES.
KEVIN TIBBLES, NBC
NEWS, TEMECULA,
CALIFORNIA.
>>> WE APPRECIATE YOU
SPENDING PART OF YOUR
EVENING WITH US.
THAT'S "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
JOSE DIAZ-BALART WILL
BE HERE TOMORROW.
AND I'LL SEE YOU FOR
THE SEASON PREMIERE OF