QUOTE CUSTODY AND RETURNED IT
BACK TO THE FARM.
THE GOAT WENT ON A VACATION.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US
TONIGHT.
>> "NIGHTLY NEWS" IS NEXT.
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT.
DOUBLE DISASTERS
UNFOLDING AS WE COME
ON THE AIR.
HURRICANE MARIA
HAMMERING PUERTO RICO
WITH A DIRECT HIT.
STILL A MONSTER STORM.
THE STRONGEST TO SLAM
ASHORE ON THAT
AMERICAN ISLAND IN
NEARLY A CENTURY.
POWER REPORTEDLY
KNOCKED OUT TO 100% OF
THE ISLAND.
TORRENTIAL RAIN, AS
MUCH AS TWO FEET.
LIFE-THREATENING
FLOODS TURNING ROADS
INTO RAGING RIVERS.
OUR TEAM IS THERE AND
AL ROKER IS TRACKING
THE DANGER.
>>> WHILE IN MEXICO, A
RACE AGAINST TIME
AFTER THAT POWERFUL
EARTHQUAKE.
FIRST RESPONDERS AND
VOLUNTEERS DIGGING TO
RESCUE SURVIVORS IN
THE RUBBLE, INCLUDING
CHILDREN TRAPPED WHEN
THEIR SCHOOL
COLLAPSED.
THE DEATH TOLL SOARING
INTO THE HUNDREDS FROM
THE QUAKE THAT LEVELED
BUILDINGS AND SPARKED
EXPLOSIONS.
>>> TONIGHT, WE'RE
LIVE FROM BOTH
DISASTER ZONES.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN
NEW YORK, THIS IS NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>>> GOOD EVENING, AND
THANK YOU FOR BEING
HERE.
HORRIFIC IMAGES OF
DESTRUCTION AND MISERY
ARE COMING OUT OF
MEXICO AND PUERTO RICO
TONIGHT FRAMING MUCH
OF THIS NEWSCAST THIS
EVENING.
TWO MAJOR NATURAL
DISASTERS STILL
UNFOLDING AND
IMPACTING MILLIONS
LIVING HERE OUTSIDE
THE DISASTER ZONE,
FAMILIES ANXIOUS TO
KNOW THE FATES OF
LOVED ONE.
IN A FEW MOMENTS WE'LL
TAKE YOU TO
EARTHQUAKE-STRICKEN
MEXICO CITY WHERE
RESCUERS ARE INTENTLY
LISTENING FOR SOUNDS
OF LIFE IN THEIR
DESPERATE SEARCH FOR
SURVIVORS.
BUT FIRST TO PUERTO
RICO WHERE HUNDREDS OF
HOMES ARE DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED, STREETS ARE
FLOODED AND 100% OF
THAT U.S. ISLAND IS
WITHOUT POWER AFTER
HURRICANE MARIA
SLAMMED ASHORE.
WITH 155-MILE-AN-HOUR
WINDS TODAY.
OUR TEAM IS ON THE
GROUND.
WE WANT TO GET RIGHT
TO GABE GUTIERREZ WHO
LEADS OFF OUR COVERAGE
TONIGHT.
GABE, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER,
GOOD EVENING.
THE POWER OF THIS
STORM WAS IMMENSE.
WE'VE BEEN SEEING
OVERTURNED CAR KS AND
COLLAPSED BUILDINGS.
IT IS DIFFICULT TO GET
AROUND SAN WAUB
TONIGHT.
MANY STREETS ARE
FLOODED.
OTHERS JUST SIMPLY
IMPASSABLE.
THE GOVERNOR HAS
IMPOSED A CURFEW AND
THE MAYOR SAYS SEARCH
AND RESCUE MISSIONS
ARE GETTING UNDER WAY.
NO FIRM NUMBER ON THE
NUMBER OF DEAD OR
INJURED AS THIS ISLAND
BEGINS WHAT WILL NO
DOUBT BE A LONG
RECOVERY.
IT SHOWED LITTLE
MERCY.
TONIGHT MARIA'S
DESTRUCTIVE PATH IS
ONLY STARTING TO
BECOME CLEAR.
SWATHS OF PUERTO RICO
UNDER WATER.
ROADS TURNED TO RAGING
RIVERS.
ROOFS RIPPED OFF.
TREES TOPPLED.
CARS OVERTURNED.
POWER OUT TO VIRTUALLY
THE ENTIRE ISLAND.
HAVE YOU EVER SEEN
ANYTHING LIKE THIS?
>> ME?
NEVER.
>> Reporter: THIS MAN
SAYS HE FEARED FOR HIS
LIFE.
AS THE RELENTLESS
STORM SLAMMED INTO HIS
HOME THIS MORNING AS A
FEROCIOUS CATEGORY 4
HURRICANE.
THE SITUATION HERE IN
SAN JUAN IS DIRE.
THE WINDS HERE HAVE
BEEN INTENSIFYING AND
THE WORST IS YET TO
COME.
WE HAD SOUGHT SHELTER
IN A CONCRETE
STRUCTURE, BUT IT'S A
SCENE OF UTTER CHAOS.
AFTER DODGING MOST OF
HURRICANE IRMA'S WRATH
DAYS AGO PUERTO RICO
AND ITS 3.5 MILLION
AMERICAN CITIZENS BORE
THE BRUNT OF MARIA FOR
HOURS.
AS THE STORM PASSED WE
GOT OUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE DAMAGE.
SOME HOMES
OBLITERATED.
RESIDENTS IN SHOCK.
>> IT WAS SCARY.
>> Reporter: MARIA,
THE STRONGEST STORM TO
RAVAGE PUERTO RICO IN
NEARLY A CENTURY FIRST
SLICED THROUGH THE
CARIBBEAN.
OVERNIGHT IT BATTERED
ST. CROIX, THE LARGEST
OF THE U.S. VIRGIN
ISLANDS.
>> VERY SCARY.
>> Reporter: IN ST.
THOMAS WIDESPREAD
FLOODING AS RESIDENTS
WERE JUST BEGINNING TO
CLEAN UP AFTER
HURRICANE IRMA'S
DIRECT HIT.
THE STORM'S TRAIL OF
DEVASTATION LEAVING
MUCH OF THE REMOTE
ISLAND OF DOMINICA IN
RUINS.
MARIA'S FURY CUT OFF
COMMUNICATIONS.
AS PUERTO RICO BEGINS
TO ASSESS ITS DAMAGE,
MANY RESIDENTS DON'T
KNOW IF THEY'LL HAVE
HOMES TO RETURN TO.
HOW HORRIBLE IS IT TO
LOOK AROUND AND SEE
THIS ISLAND LIKE THIS?
>> IT'S VERY SAD.
IT'S VERY, VERY SAD.
VERY HEARTBROKEN.
>> Reporter: AN ISLAND
WITHOUT POWER AND NOW
SEEMINGLY WITHOUT
ENOUGH RESOURCES TO
COPE WITH AN UNFOLDING
DISASTER.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, SAN JUAN, PUERTO
RICO.
>>> THIS IS GADI
SCHWARTZ.
IN THE DARK HALLS OF
THIS SAN JUAN SPORTS
COLISEUM, ONE OF
PUERTO RICO'S
STURDIEST HURRICANE
SHELTERS.
HERE HUDDLED SHAPES
HUNCH OVER RADIOS.
CHILDREN PLAY IN
SHADOWS.
AND OUTSIDE HURRICANE
MARIA'S WINDS AND RAIN
RAVAGED PUERTO RICO.
>> IT'S A RUDE
AWAKENING.
>> Reporter: THIS IS
THE LAST 24 HOURS FOR
FAMILIES LIKE THIS
WOMAN'S TAKING SHELTER
FROM THE STORMS.
>> WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN WHEN WE GET OUT
OF HERE?
WHAT WILL WE END UP
SEEING?
IT'S VERY HARD.
>> Reporter: AT FIRST
IN COTS SPREAD OUT
ACROSS THE MASSIVE
COLISEUM CONCRETE
FLOOR, THEN THE WORST
OF HURRICANE MARIA
BURSTING METAL DOORS
OPEN.
PEOPLE JOINING HANDS
TO PRAY.
QUICKLY THEY MOVE TO
THE SAFETY OF THE
OUTER WINGS AS WATER
AND DEBRIS RAIN DOWN
FROM THE ROOF.
AND THROUGH THE STORM
ONE VOICE TRYING TO
CALM THE REFUGEES.
THIS IS THE MAYOR OF
SAN JUAN, CARMEN YULIN
CRUZ, WHO STAYED HERE
WITH HER FAMILY AT THE
COLISEUM.
>> I UNDERSTAND HOW
DIFFICULT IT IS.
>> Reporter: SHE'S
GOTTEN REGULAR REPORTS
OF WHAT LIES OUTSIDE,
AND HER HEART BREAKS
FOR THOSE THEY
COULDN'T REACH.
>> I'M JUST CONCERNED
THAT WE MAY NOT GET TO
EVERYBODY IN TIME.
AND THAT IS A GREAT
WEIGHT ON MY
SHOULDERS.
>> Reporter: SHE'S
AMONG THOSE WHO WILL
FIND THEIR HOMES
DEVASTATED, BUT FOR
NOW SHE CAN'T THINK OF
THAT.
SHE CAN ONLY THINK OF
KEEPING HER CITY
TOGETHER.
>> WE NEED EACH OTHER.
I NEED THEM MORE THAN
THEY NEED ME.
>> Reporter: A FEELING
SHARED AMONG MANY
HOLDING ON TO EACH
OTHER FOR STRENGTH IN
WHAT'S TO COME.
AND A VERY GRIM
REALITY FOR SOME OF
THE FAMILIES THAT ARE
GOING TO BE LEAVING
THIS SHELTER AFTER 24
HOURS.
MANY OF THEM ARE GOING
TO FIND THEIR HOMES IN
RUIN AND THEY'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO COME BACK
TO SHELTERS LIKE THIS
TO SPEND ANOTHER
NIGHT, ANOTHER WEEK
AND POSSIBLY EVEN
MONTHS.
LESTER?
>> GADI SCHWARTZ, SOME
OF THAT DAMAGE IS
INCREDIBLE, THANK YOU.
>>> THIS HURRICANE
THREAT IS FAR FROM
OVER.
WE'RE JOINED HERE BY
AL ROKER WHO IS
TRACKING THE STORM.
WHAT'S THE LATEST?
AND IS THE U.S. EAST
COAST IN JEOPARDY?
>> IT'S STILL UP IN
THE AIR RIGHT NOW.
MARIA IS A CATEGORY 2
BUT WILL PROBABLY
INTENSIFY.
IT'S MOVING NORTHWEST
AT 12, WITH
110-MILE-PER-HOUR
WINDS.
THE DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
TOMORROW GETS ABOUT 75
MILES PER HOUR.
4 TO 6 FEET OF SURGE,
8 TO 16 INCHES OF
RAIN.
TURKS AND CAICOS MAY
BE THE NEXT REALLY BIG
DEVASTATED AREA WITH
125-MILE-PER-HOUR
WINDS, A STORM SURGE
OF 9 TO 12 FEET AND 9
TO 16 INCHES.
AND THEN IT CONTINUES
UP INTO THE ATLANTIC
BY MONDAY AFTERNOON.
WE PUT THE ENSEMBLE
MODEL INTO PLAY.
YOU SEE THOSE
SPAGHETTI STRANDS WE
CALL.
AND BASICALLY FOR THE
MOST PART THEY KEEP IT
OFF THE COAST, BUT YOU
CAN SEE THERE'S SOME
DISAGREEMENT ON THE
WESTERN SIDE OF THIS.
SO LESTER, RIGHT NOW
WE STILL CAN'T GIVE
YOU A DEFINITIVE
ANSWER WHETHER THIS
THING STAYS OFF SHORE
OR NOT.
>> WE'LL KEEP
WATCHING.
AL ROKER, THANKS VERY
MUCH.
>>> LET'S TURN THOUGH
THAT OTHER MAJOR
DISASTER STILL
UNFOLDING AT THIS
HOUR.
IN CENTRAL MEXICO,
HUNDREDS ARE DEAD,
THOUSANDS ARE STILL
MISSING AFTER THAT
DEVASTATING 7.1
MAGNITUDE EARTHQUAKE
STRUCK THERE.
NOW A DESPERATE SEARCH
IS ON FOR SURVIVORS AT
SITES THAT INCLUDE A
SCHOOL THAT COLLAPSED
WITH STUDENTS INSIDE.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER
IS THERE AND HAS THE
LATEST.
MIGUEL, GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER,
GOOD EVENING.
THEY ARE ASKING US TO
WHISPER BECAUSE IT
APPEARS THEY HAVE DONE
IT AGAIN.
TWO RESCUES MIGHT BE
UNDER WAY RIGHT NOW AT
THIS HOUR AT THAT
SCHOOL YOU MENTIONED.
THEY'RE LISTENING FOR
SIGNS OF LIFE.
DOZENS OF BODIES HAVE
BEEN RECOVERED THERE,
BUT DOZENS HAVE ALSO
BEEN SAVED.
THE DEATH TOLL STANDS
AT 225 AND GROWING,
BUT THIS IS A SIGN OF
HOPE.
TONIGHT, THIS IS THE
HEART-POUNDING DRAMA
PLAYING OUT ACROSS
MEXICO CITY.
RESCUE TEAMS AT AN
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
FINDING CHILDREN
BURIED BENEATH PILES
OF DEBRIS.
ONE BY ONE, PULLING
THEM TO SAFETY.
THIS WAS THE SCHOOL
BEFORE.
NOW LITERALLY
FLATTENED.
THEY CALL THIS THE
MIRACLE IN THE RUBBLE.
THE CRISIS STILL
UNFOLDING TODAY.
JUST MOMENTS AFTER THE
CHEERS --
>> SILENCIO.
>> Reporter: THE FISTS
GO UP, THE SIGNAL FOR
SILENCE.
THEY CAN FAINTLY HEAR
A CRY FOR HELP.
THIS TIME TWO LITTLE
GIRLS RESCUED.
THIS SEARCH COMMANDER
SAYS HE HAS CHILDREN
OF HIS OWN.
THESE KIDS ARE MY
FAMILY.
I WANT TO BRING THEM
HOME.
BUT MORE THAN 20
STUDENTS HERE DIDN'T
MAKE IT.
LUIS CARLOS SAYS HE
HAS NO IDEA HOW HE GOT
OUT.
I SAW THE WHOLE SCHOOL
FALL DOWN, BUT I NEVER
FOUND MY FRIENDS.
ACROSS THIS SHATTERED
COUNTRY, THERE IS MORE
HEARTBREAK THAN
DEBRIS.
THESE ARE THE FACES OF
ANGUISH.
PARENTS DESPERATELY
CLINGING TO HOPE.
GLORIA HERNANDEZ
CLUTCHES THE PHOTO OF
HER 24-YEAR-OLD SON
IVAN BURIED BENEATH
SIX FLOORS OF RUBBLE
IN HIS OFFICE.
TIME IS SLIPPING AWAY
RIGHT BEFORE HER EYES.
SHE SAYS, I'M PLEADING
TO THE GOVERNMENT FOR
HELP.
MY SON HAS BEEN BURIED
FOR HOURS.
NOBODY WILL TELL ME A
THING.
TUESDAY'S MASSIVE 7.1
EARTHQUAKE LEVELED 38
BUILDINGS AND AN
UNTOLD NUMBER OF
HOMES.
AND THREATENED TO SINK
TOUR BOATS IN THE
WATER.
>> OH, MY GOSH.
>> Reporter: 75 MILES
AWAY, THE EPICENTER IS
A DISASTER.
CHURCHES HAVE
CRUMBLED, MANY ARE
LOSING FAITH.
SOCIAL MEDIA IS
INUNDATED WITH
DESPERATE PLEAS FOR
HELP FOR THOSE LOOKING
FOR LOVED ONES.
WHILE THE NAMES OF
THOSE PULLED FROM THE
RUBBLE ARE WRITTEN
DOWN ON PAPER FOR
WAITING FAMILIES TO
SEE.
BUT TONIGHT THERE IS
NO MATCH FOR THIS MOM.
IVAN REMAINS AMONG THE
MISSING.
AN EARTHQUAKE
SHATTERING HOMES AND
NOW SO MANY LIVES.
TONIGHT ON THE HEELS
OF THOSE TWO GIRLS
THAT WERE RESCUED, IT
APPEARS TWO MORE
PEOPLE ARE BEING
PULLED FROM THE
RUBBLE.
OFFICIALS SAY AT LEAST
54 PEOPLE HAVE BEEN
PULLED FROM THIS
DEBRIS FIELD.
IT IS A GLIMMER OF
HOPE ACROSS A REGION
SURROUNDED BY SO MUCH
LOSS.
LESTER?
>> MIGUEL, OUR HATS
OFF TO THOSE BRAVE
RESCUERS.
WE WISH THEM GREAT
SUCCESS AS THEY
CONTINUE THEIR WORK.
THANK YOU.
>>> THE WELL KNOWN ROM
ROMA NORTE
NEIGHBORHOOD, JOSE
DIAZ-BALART.
>> Reporter: GOOD
AFTERNOON.
WHAT IS HAPPENING
RIGHT HERE IS
HAPPENING THROUGHOUT
THE CITY OF MEXICO.
THIS IS ONE OF AT
LEAST 44 STRUCTURES
AND BUILDINGS THAT
COLLAPSED AFTER THIS
EARTHQUAKE STRUCK
MEXICO CITY AND OTHER
PARTS OF THIS COUNTRY.
AND WHAT YOU'RE SEEING
NOW ARE ACTUALLY
EXPERTS IN FINDING
SURVIVORS BURIED
THROUGH RUBBLE.
THEY LITERALLY BURROW
THROUGH TONS OF
CONCRETE, STEEL AND
CABLES SEARCHING FOR
VICTIMS THAT MAY HAVE
SURVIVED THIS.
THIS IS GOING ON
THROUGHOUT THE CITY.
IT'S AN EXTREMELY
DANGEROUS JOB.
THERE ARE SOME GAS
LEAKS AROUND HERE.
PEOPLE ARE VERY
CONCERNED ABOUT THAT.
AND THE WHOLE PROCESS
IS BEING HANDLED HERE
AS THERE ARE LITERALLY
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
THAT HAVE COME OUT
HERE TO VOLUNTEER, TO
DO WHAT THEY CAN TO
HELP.
THAT'S THE VERY LATEST
FROM MEXICO CITY.
LESTER, BACK TO YOU.
>> ALL RIGHT, JOSE,
THANK YOU.
>>> THE QUAKE IN
MEXICO WAS A JARRING
REMINDER OF THE BIG
ONE THAT EXPERTS WARN
MAY BE IN CALIFORNIA'S
NOT TOO DISTANT
FUTURE.
SMALL QUAKES ARE A
FACT OF LIFE ALONG THE
WEST COAST.
THE MOST RECENT A 3.6
MAGNITUDE THAT RATTLED
NEIGHBORHOODS ON
L.A.'S WEST SIDE
MONDAY NIGHT.
BUT HISTORY SUGGESTS A
MAJOR QUAKE IS COMING.
THE QUESTIONS ARE WHEN
AND WILL CALIFORNIA BE
READY.
NBC'S JO LING KENT
REPORTS.
>> Reporter: IT'S NOT
A MATTER OF IF BUT
WHEN.
AS MEXICO REELS FROM
ITS 7.1 MAGNITUDE
EARTHQUAKE,
CALIFORNIA, FROM LOS
ANGELES TO SAN
FRANCISCO, IS ANXIOUS
AND ON EDGE ABOUT WHAT
SO MANY FEAR WILL BE
THE BIG ONE.
>> DID YOU FEEL THAT?
>> Reporter: A SMALL
EARTHQUAKE SHOOK L.A.
EARLIER THIS WEEK.
BUT A STUDY FROM THE
U.S. GEOLOGICAL SURVEY
SAYS THE CHANCE OF A
QUAKE MAGNITUDE 8 OR
LARGER IN THE NEXT 30
YEARS HAS DOUBLED
SINCE 2008.
EXPERTS SAY A MAJOR
QUAKE ALONG THE SAN
ANDREAS FAULT COULD
KILL 1800 PEOPLE,
INJURE 53,000.
DESTROY 1500
BUILDINGS.
AND DAMAGE 300,000
MORE.
A SERIOUS QUAKE COULD
ALSO CRIPPLE THE
CITY'S WATER SUPPLY
AND TAKE AS LONG AS
SIX MONTHS TO REPAIR.
>> WHO THINKS ABOUT
THE PIPES IN THE
GROUND?
WE DON'T WANT TO SPEND
MONEY ON THAT.
IT'S OUT OF SIGHT, OUT
OF MIND.
>> Reporter: WHILE
NEARLY $14 BILLION HAS
BEEN SPENT ON SEISMIC
UPGRADES TO
INFRASTRUCTURE
INCLUDING BRIDGES, THE
CITY OF LOS ANGELES
NOW REQUIRES PROPERTY
OWNERS TO RETROFIT
BUILDINGS THAT CANNOT
WITHSTAND A STRONG
EARTHQUAKE.
DO YOU FEEL LIKE L.A.
IS READY?
>> L.A. IS GETTING
READY AND IS PROBABLY
FAR MORE READY THAN A
LOT OF OTHER CITIES,
BUT THERE'S -- L.A.'S
HUGE.
THERE'S A LOT OF OLD
STRUCTURES.
>> Reporter: A NEW
PREPAREDNESS PLAN HAS
LANDED ON MAYOR ERIC
GARCETTI'S DESK AND
HAS NOT YET BEEN
RELEASED.
THE U.S. HOUSE
RECENTLY APPROVED
FEDERAL FUNDING FOR AN
EARTHQUAKE EARLY
WARNING SYSTEM AS
CALIFORNIA PREPARES
NOW FOR A WORST-CASE
SCENARIO THAT MAY COME
WITH NO WARNING AT
ALL.
JO LING KENT, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> THERE'S STILL MORE
AHEAD ON THIS DEADLY
DISASTER.
THE URGENT RESCUE
MISSION WITH
VOLUNTEERS COMING FROM
FAR AND WIDE TO HELP
SAVE LIVES.
>>> ALSO THE DAY'S
OTHER HEADLINES
INCLUDING WHY ONE
LATE-NIGHT HOST IS
ACCUSING A SENATOR OF
LYING TO HIS FACE.
HOPE YOU CAN STAY WITH
US.
Patrick woke up
with a sore back.
But he's got work to do.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
When a critical patient is far
from the hospital,
the hospital must come to the
patient.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
The AT&T network is helping
first responders
connect with medical teams in
near real time...
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
...Saving time when it matters
most.
Stay with me, Mrs. Parker.
That's the power of and.
The day after chemo might mean
a trip back to
the doctor's office,
just for a shot.
But why go back there,
when you can stay home...
...with Neulasta Onpro?
Strong chemo can put you
at risk of serious infection,
which could lead to
hospitalizations.
In a key study,
Neulasta reduced the risk
of infection from 17% to 1%...
...a 94% decrease.
Applied the day of chemo,
Neulasta Onpro is designed to
deliver Neulasta the next day,
so you can stay home.
Neulasta is for
certain cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta
if you're allergic to
Neulasta or Neupogen
(filgrastim).
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries,
and capillary leak syndrome
have occurred.
Report abdominal or
shoulder tip pain,
trouble breathing
or allergic reactions
to your doctor right away.
In patients with
sickle cell disorders,
serious, sometimes
fatal crises can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
So why go back there?
If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH A
NEW BATTLE HEATING UP
IN THE HEALTHCARE
WARS.
THE LATEST ATTEMPT BY
REPUBLICANS TO REPEAL
OBAMACARE.
THEY PLAN TO PUT THEIR
NEW BILL TO A VOTE
NEXT WEEK AND ALREADY
IT IS HIGHLY
CONTROVERSIAL.
NUMBERS'S KASIE HUNT
TONIGHT ON WHAT THE
BILL WOULD DO AND A
CELEBRITY RIGHT IN THE
MIDDLE OF THE FIGHT.
>> HE GOT TO THE
HOSPITAL --
>> Reporter: FOR LATE
NIGHT COMIC JIMMY
KIMMEL THE NEW PUSH TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE IS
DEEPLY PERSONAL.
>> BILLY WAS BORN WITH
A HEART DISEASE.
>> Reporter: IN MAY,
KIMMEL TOLD THE WORLD
HIS SON WAS BORN WITH
A PRE-EXISTING
CONDITION.
SENATOR BILL CASSIDY
HEARD THE STORY AND
MADE IT HIS LITMUS
TEST.
>> I WANT IT TO PASS
THE JIMMY KIMMEL TEST.
>> I DO, TOO.
I THINK THAT'S A GOOD
THING.
>> Reporter: AFTER
REPUBLICANS FAILED TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE IN
JULY, THEY'RE NOW
UNDER INTENSE PRESSURE
FROM MAJOR DONORS TO
SHOW THEY'RE ACTUALLY
DOING SOMETHING.
AND CASSIDY IS
SPEARHEADING THE
EFFORT.
LAST NIGHT JIMMY
KIMMEL SAID HE'S HAD
ENOUGH.
>> THIS GUY, BILL
CASSIDY, JUST LIED
RIGHT TO MY FACE.
>> Reporter: DO YOU
THINK THIS LEGISLATION
PASSES THE JIMMY
KIMMEL TEST?
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THERE WILL BE PEOPLE
IN STATES LIKE --
>> Reporter: HE CALLED
YOU A LIAR LAST NIGHT.
>> IT WAS A PERSONAL
ATTACK.
AND I CAN'T HELP THAT.
>> Reporter: CASSIDY'S
BILL WITH LINDSEY
GRAHAM WOULD ELIMINATE
THE INDIVIDUAL MANDATE
TO BUY INSURANCE,
REDISTRIBUTE MEDICAID
EXPANSION AND SUBSIDY
MONEY TO INDIVIDUAL
STATES.
BUT STATES COULD OPT
OUT OF COVERING
PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS, THOUGH
THEY WOULD HAVE TO
EXPLAIN HOW THEY
INTEND TO KEEP THOSE
PEOPLE COVERED.
BUT EXPERTS WARN --
>> THAT IS THE ONLY
BILL WE'VE SEEN SO FAR
THAT EFFECTIVELY LETS
STATE JUST DUMP THAT
PRE-EXISTING CONDITION
REQUIREMENT.
IT ALLOWS INSURANCERS
TO DISCRIMINATE
AGAINST YOU IF YOU'RE
SICK.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
OBAMA TODAY DEFENDING
HIS SIGNATURE
LEGISLATION.
>> HAD TO MOBILIZE
EVERY COUPLE OF MONTHS
TO KEEP OUR LEADERS
FROM INFLICTING REAL
HUMAN SUFFERING ON OUR
CONSTITUENTS.
>> Reporter: LATE
TODAY THE PRESIDENT
WEIGHING IN.
>> I THINK IT'S MUCH
BETTER THAN THE
PREVIOUS SHOT.
>> Reporter:
REPUBLICANS HAVE UNTIL
SEPTEMBER 30th TO FIND
50 VOTES AND ALL EYES
WILL BE ON SENATORS
LISA MURKOWSKI AND
JOHN McCAIN WHEN THE
BILL COMES TO THE
FLOOR NEXT WEEK.
KASIE HUNT, NBC NEWS,
THE CAPITOL.
>>> WE'LL TAKE A SHORT
BREAK AND BE BACK IN A
MOMENT WHAT AIRLINES
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
TECH: When you schedule
with Safelite AutoGlass,
You get a text
when we're on our way.
You can see exactly
when we'll arrive.
I'm Micah with Safelite.
CUSTOMER: Thanks for coming,
it's right over here.
TECH: Giving you a few more
minutes for what matters most.
Take care.
KIDS SINGING:
Safelite® repair,
Safelite® replace.
When you have a cold
stuff happens.
Shut down cold
symptoms fast
with Maximum Strength
Alka Seltzer Plus
Liquid Gels.
Hey!
Are you taking the tissue test?
Yep, and my teeth are yellow.
Time for Whitestrips.
Crest Whitestrips whiten...
...25x better than a leading
whitening toothpaste.
Nice smile!
Thanks! I crushed
the tissue test.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP
SAYS HE'S MADE UP HIS
MIND ABOUT THE IRAN
NUCLEAR DEAL, BUT HE'S
NOT SAYING IF THE U.S.
WILL STAY IN THE
AGREEMENT.
NBC NEWS HAS LEARNED
FROM FOUR SOURCES
FAMILIAR WITH THE
DISCUSSIONS THAT THE
PRESIDENT IS LEANING
AGAINST RECERTIFYING
IRAN'S COMPLIANCE WITH
THE DEAL.
THAT WOULD MOVE IT TO
CONGRESS AND LIKELY
BEGIN THE DIFFICULT
TASK OF TRYING TO
CONVINCE AMERICA'S
ALLIES AND IRAN TO
RENEGOTIATE.
THE ALLIES STRONGLY
OPPOSE A U.S. EXIT AND
THE SOURCES WARN THAT
NO DECISION IS FINAL.
>>> HE WAS A BOXING
LEGEND WHO INSPIRED A
CLASSIC AMERICAN
MOVIE.
TODAY WE LEARNED THAT
JAKE LaMOTTA HAS DIED
AFTER BATTLING
PNEUMONIA.
HE WAS A FORMER
HEAVYWEIGHT CHAMPIONS
WHO TURBULENT LIFE WAS
CAPTURED IN THE FILM
"RAGING BULL."
ROBERT DE NIRO WHO WON
A BEST ACTING OSCAR
FOR PORTRAYING LaMOTTA
SAID REST IN PEACE,
CHAMP.
HE WAS 85.
>>> IF THE EXTRA FEES
ARE PAYING ARE ADDING
UP TO A RECORD AMOUNT.
PASSENGERS PAID $7
MILLION TO CHECK BAGS
AND CHANGE FLIGHTS.
THE AIRLINES, OF
COURSE, HAVE ALL KINDS
OF OTHER FEES BUT
THOSE ARE THE ONLY TWO
TYPES THEY'RE REQUIRED
TO REPORT TO THE
GOVERNMENT.
>>> UP NEXT HERE
TONIGHT, DISASTER
STRUCK AND THEY'RE
ANSWERING THE CALL.
LIFE-SAVING HELP FROM
ALL OVER THE WORLD IN
THE AFTERMATH OF
MEXICO'S DEADLY
EARTHQUAKE.
>>> NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS"
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY
PACIFIC LIFE.
PROTECTING GENERATIONS
OF FAMILIES FOR 150
YEARS.
THAT'S THE POW
What is the Power of Pacific?
It's life insurance and
retirement solutions to
help you reach your goals.
It's having the confidence
to create the future
that's most meaningful to you.
It's protection for generations
of families,
and 150 years of strength
and stability.
And when you're able to
harness all of that,
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask a financial advisor
about Pacific Life.
Americans,
83% try to eat healthy,
yet up to 90% fall short
on getting key nutrients.
Let's do more.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
Complete with 100% daily value
of more than 15 key nutrients.
One-A-Day 50 plus.
♪♪
♪
♪You are loved♪
My shoulders carry
a lot of names
Some I deserve
Others I don't
But in the end
Only one name really matters
Because shoulders were made for
greatness, not dandruff
I take pictures of sunrises,
but with my back pain
I couldn't sleep
and get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
Throughout my career, I've been
fortunate enough to travel to
many interesting places.
I've always wanted to create
those experiences for others.
With my advisor's help along the
way, it's finally my turn to be
the host.
When you have the right
financial advisor, life can be
brilliant.
Ameriprise
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT WE
HAVE BEEN WATCHING A
REMARKABLE EFFORT
UNFOLD IN MEXICO CITY
TODAY AFTER THE
EARTHQUAKE.
THE RESCUE MISSION IS
NOT JUST ONE MISSION
BUT HUNDREDS OF
THOUSANDS OF PEOPLE
JOINING THE EFFORT TO
SAVE PEOPLE.
TEAMS ARE ALSO ON
THEIR WAY TONIGHT FROM
OTHER COUNTRIES
INCLUDING THE UNITED
STATES.
NBC'S RON MOTT TONIGHT
FROM MEXICO CITY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
ACROSS THE EARTHQUAKE
ZONE, THE FIRST
RESPONDERS WERE OFTEN
THOSE WHO JUST SHOWED
UP FIRST.
SO MANY EVERYDAY
CITIZENS RUNNING IN TO
HELP.
A SEA OF HANDS IN
MOTION MOVING WATER
WHERE IT'S NEEDED.
THIS IS QUITE AN
ORGANIZATIONAL FEAT
HERE.
>> I WAS 5 YEARS OLD
WHEN THE LAST
EARTHQUAKE HAPPENED,
THE BIG ONE.
AND WE HAVE BEEN
GRILLING FOR THIS.
>> Reporter: MEXICO
CITY WAS ROCKED BY A
DEADLY QUAKE IN 1985.
YESTERDAY MORNING THEY
HELD A ROUTINE
EARTHQUAKE DRILL TO
PREPARE FOR THE NEXT
DISASTER.
THE DRILL FINISHING
JUST HOURS BEFORE THE
REAL NIGHTMARE BEGAN.
ANOTHER QUAKE HITTING
ON THE SAME DAY 32
YEARS LATER.
AND NOW WAVES OF
VOLUNTEERS MOBILIZING,
COMING FAR AND WIDE,
INCLUDING AN URBAN
SEARCH AND RESCUE TEAM
DEPLOYING FROM L.A.,
ISRAEL SENDING 25
ENGINEERS.
A NUMBER OF BUILDINGS
HAVE COLLAPSED IN THIS
NEIGHBORHOOD.
AND WHAT FOLKS ARE
DOING NOW IS FERRYING
WATER LITERALLY BY
HAND.
BY HUMAN CHAIN.
A LONG CHAIN OF
HUMANITY HERE TAKING
WATER SEVERAL BLOCKS
THIS WAY TO A HIGH
SCHOOL WHERE THEY'RE
GOING TO BE GIVING OUT
THAT WATER.
PEOPLE KNOW THESE ARE
THE CRITICAL HOURS TO
FIND SURVIVORS.
SO MANY ARE NOW
ANSWERING THE CALL.
>> THIS IS MEXICO CITY
AT ITS BEST.
>> Reporter: WHILE THE
TOLL IS HEAVY, ALONG
WITH HEARTS, A SENSE
OF PURPOSE REIGNS
SUPREME.
OUT OF ONE DISASTER,
MANY AT THE READY
DOING WHATEVER IT
TAKES.
RON MOTT, NBC NEWS,
MEXICO CITY.
>>> WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO FOLLOW THE
DEVELOPMENTS IN MEXICO
AND THE DISASTROUS
HURRICANE IN PUERTO
RICO.
YOU CAN SEE MORE ON
THE "TODAY" SHOW
TOMORROW MORNING.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS WEDNESDAY
NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
AND FOR ALL OF US AT
NBC NEWS, THANK YOU
FOR WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
Sweet 4K TV, Mr. Peterson.
Thanks. Pretty psyched.
Did you get Fios too?
No.
Mr. Peterson, Fios is a 100%
fiber optic-network.
What does that mean?
Think about it.
If you got an awesome new car
you'd put the best gas in it,
right.
So why hook up your
awesome technology
to anything other than
a fiber-optic network?
I got to go. Peterson.
Peterson's wife.
Counting on you guys.
Your internet deserves the 100%
fiber-optic network.
And now get our fastest
internet ever
plus TV and phone for just
$79.99 per month.