>> A HOT DAY FOR THAT.
HOLY COW.
>> NEAR 85 DEGREES, PULLING THAT
PLANE.
>> WOULD RATHER DO THAT THAN IN
RAIN AND COLD.
>> TRUE.
>> HAVE A GOOD DAY.
SEE YOU BACK AT 11:00 TONIGHT.
>>> ON THIS SUNDAY NIGHT,
POLITICAL FOOTBALL.
A DAY OF SOLIDARITY AROUND THE
NFL.
PLAYERS AND COACHES KNEELING AND
JOINING ARMS DURING THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM.
IN PROTEST AGAINST PRESIDENT
TRUMP.
WHILE THE PRESIDENT SAYS THE
LEAGUE SHOULD FIRE OR SUSPEND
PLAYERS WHO REFUSE TO STAND.
>>> DEADLY CHURCH SHOOTING.
IN TENNESSEE.S FIRE AT A CHURCH
KILLING A WOMAN AND WOUNDING
SEVEN OTHER PEOPLE BEFORE HE WAS
CONFRONTED BY A CHURCH USHER
BEING CALLED A HERO.
>>> CRITICAL CONDITION.
THE NEWEST REPUBLICAN HEALTH
CARE BILL MAY BE DOOMED.
AFTER TWO MORE REPUBLICANS SAY
THEY HAVE BROIT IT.
>>> LIFELINE, THE DRAMATIC
SCENES IN PUERTO RICO AS
RESCUERS FINALLY REACH HURRICANE
SURVIVORS CUT OFF FOR DAYS.
>>> AND ANCIENT WORLD.
WE EXPLORE REMANENTS OF THIS
COUNTRY MORE THAN 60,000 YEARS
OLD.
PRESERVED AT THE BOTTOM OF THE
SEA.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN NEW YORK, THIS
IS NBC NIGHTLY NEWS WITH KATE
SNOW.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
WE HAVE TWO BIG STORIES WE'RE
FOLLOWING AS WE COME ON THE AIR
AT A CHURCH JUST OUTSIDE
NASHVILLE, A GUNMAN ATTACKS
CONGRESS BEGAN THES THIS MORNING
AS THE SERVICE WAS JUST LETTING
OUT.
FULL REPORT ON THAT IN JUST A
MOMENT.
WE BEGIN ON THIS FOOTBALL SUNDAY
WITH NFL PLAYERS TAKING ON
PRESIDENT TRUMP THROUGHOUT THE
LEAGUE.
AFTER THE PRESIDENT USED A
VULGARITY TO REFER TO PLAYERS
WHO PROTEST DURING THE NATIONAL
ANTHEM AND ENCOURAGED TEAM
OWNERS TO FIRE THEM.
SCORES OF PLAYERS TOOK THEIR
PROTEST TO A NEW LEVEL TODAY.
KNEELING, JOINING ARMS, SOME
TEAMS NOT EVEN TAKING THE FIELD
FOR THE STAR SPANGLED BANNER.
POWERFUL TEAM OWNERS INCLUDING
SEVERAL WHO HAVE BEEN POLITICAL
SUPPORTERS CAME OUT IN SUPPORT
OF THEIR PLAYERS.
ALL OF IT PROMPTING STRONG
REACTION JUST MOMENTS AGO FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> WE HAVE GREAT PEOPLE
REPRESENTING OUR COUNTRY.
ESPECIALLY OUR SOLDIERS, OUR
FIRST RESPONDERS, AND THEY
SHOULD BE TREATED WITH RESPECT.
AND WHEN YOU GET ON YOUR KNEE
AND YOU DON'T RESPECT THE
AMERICAN FLAG OR THE ANTHEM,
THAT'S NOT BEING TREATED WITH
RESPECT.
>> SPORTS AND POLITICS IS WHERE
WE BEGIN TONIGHT WITH MORGAN
RADFORD.
♪ SO PROUDLY WE HAIL -- ♪♪
>> Reporter: A POWERFUL DISPLAY
OF PROTEST.
MORE THAN 100 NFL PLAYERS
KNEELING IN DEFIANCE OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
THE DAY STARTED OFF IN LONDON.
PLAYERS TOOK A KNEE AND LOCKED
ARMS DURING THE NATIONAL ANTHEM.
HOURS LATER, BACK HOME, PLAYERS
ACROSS THE NFL SHOWED
SOLIDARITY.
♪ AND THE ROCKETS -- ♪♪
>> Reporter: OTHERS RAISING
THEIR FIST.
A FORMER ARMY RANGER WAS THE
LONE TEAMMATE FROM THE STEELERS
TO TAKE THE FIELD DURING THE
ANTHEM.
AND AT THE SEAHAWKS TITANS GAME,
NO PLAYER FROM EITHER TEAM TOOK
THE FIELD.
TOM BRADY WHO HAS DESCRIBED THE
PRESIDENT AS A FRIEND STOOD WITH
HIS TEAMMATES TODAY.
LINKING HIS ARM.
THIS COMES AFTER THE PRESIDENT
DOUBLED DOWN ON HIS CALL TO END
SPORTS PROTEST.
TAKING AIM AT PLAYERS LIKE COLIN
KAEPERNICK WHO STARTED THE TREND
LAST YEAR TO STAND AGAINST
POLICE BRUTALITY.
>> WOULDN'T YOU LOVE TO SEE ONE
OF THESE NFL OWNERS, WHEN
SOMEBODY DISRESPECTS OUR FLAG,
TO SAY GET THAT SON OF A BITCH
OFF THE FIELD RIGHT NOW.
RIGHT NOW.
OUT.
HE'S FIRED.
HE'S FIRED!
>> Reporter: THE PRESIDENT
RESPONDED TODAY, TWEETING, GREAT
SOLIDARITY FOR OUR NATIONAL
ANTHEM AND FOR OUR COUNTRY.
STANDING WITH LOCKED ARMS IS
GOOD, KNEELING IS NOT
ACCEPTABLE.
BAD RATINGS.
THE ADMINISTRATION TODAY SAYING
THE PROTESTS ARE AN AFFRONT TO
THE VETERANS.
FANS FILED INTO STADIUMS ACROSS
THE COUNTRY.
SOME SAYING THIS ISN'T ABOUT
DISRESPECT.
IT'S ABOUT FREEDOM.
>> IT'S NOT A PROTEST AGAINST
THE MILITARY.
IT'S A PROTEST ABOUT INEQUALITY
IN THIS COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: OTHERS SIDED WITH
THE PRESIDENT.
>> I UNDERSTAND THE FREEDOM OF
SPEECH, BUT ALSO THIS IS THE
PLAYER'S JOBS AND I DON'T GET TO
SPEAK FREELY AT MY JOB ALL THE
TIME.
SO THEY SHOULD HAVE TO FOLLOW
THE RULES AND RESPECT OUR
COUNTRY AND OUR FLAG.
>> Reporter: THE PROTEST NOT
JUST LIMITED TO THE FOOTBALL
FIELD.
THE FIRST MAJOR LEAGUE BASEBALL
PLAYER ALSO TOOK A KNEE.
THE OAKLAND A'S BRUCE MAXWELL.
EVEN MUSIC ICON STEVIE WONDER
KNEELING ON THE STAGE AT LAST
NIGHT'S GLOBAL CITIZEN MUSIC
FESTIVAL.
CALLING FOR PRAYER FOR NATIONAL
UNITY.
TODAY'S ACT OF DEFIANCE NOW
MAKING THE PRESIDENT'S CALL TO
FIRE THOSE WHO REFUSE TO STAND
TOO COSTLY.
>> COLIN KAEPERNICK HAS REALLY
BEEN UNFAIRLY BLACKLISTED.
YOU CAN'T DO THAT TO EVERY
PLAYER.
TOO MANY ARE TOO VALUABLE TO THE
BUSINESSES THAT THESE OWNERS
OPERATE.
>> Reporter: WHILE PROTESTS HAVE
ERUPTED ACROSS THE COUNTRY, AT
STADIUMS LIKE THE ONE HERE
BEHIND ME, THE DEBATE MOVED FAR
BEYOND THE GRIDIRON FROM
BASEBALL TO HOCKEY, IAN TONIGHT,
SEVERAL NASCAR OWNERS COMING
FORWARD TO SAY THEY WOULD FIRE
ANYONE WHO DEMONSTRATED IN
SIMILAR PROTEST, KATE.
>> MORGAN RADFORD.
THANK YOU.
>>> NOW BACK TO THE HARROWING
AND DEADLY SCENE AT A CHURCH IN
NASHVILLE WHERE A GUNMAN KILLED
A WOMAN AND WOUNDED SEVEN OTHER
PEOPLE.
OUR JUSTICE CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS HAS LATE DETAILS.
>> Reporter: THE SUNDAY MORNING
SERVICE HAD JUST ENDED AT
BURNETT CHAPEL CHURCH OF CHRIST
IN NASHVILLE WHEN A MAN DROVE IN
AND LEFT THE ENGINE RUNNING.
ARMED WITH A HANDGUN
INVESTIGATORS SAY, HE SHOT AND
KILLED A WOMAN COMING OUT OF THE
CHURCH THEN WENT INSIDE AND
OPENED FIRE.
>> DISPATCH, THIS IS A
LEVEL-ONE, MASS CASUALTY
INCIDENT.
>> PEOPLE WERE JUST RUNNING AND
HIDING AND TRYING TO GET OUT.
GET AWAY.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY THE
CHURCH USHER TACKLED THE GUNMAN
WHO BEAT HIM WITH A PISTOL AND
THEN ANOTHER SHOT.
>> DURING THE STRUGGLE, THE
GUNMAN SHOT HIMSELF, PROBABLY
NOT INTENTIONALLY, IN THE LEFT
PECTORAL MUSCLE.
IN THE LEFT CHEST.
>> Reporter: A WOMAN WHO WAS IN
THE CHURCH SAYS THE MAN FIRING
THE SHOTS NEVER SAID A WORD.
>> HE CAME IN FRONT OF THE
CHURCH FROM THE PARKING LOT AND
HE WAS SHOOTING AND THEN HE
STARTED SHOOTING MORE AND
LOOKING TO HIS LEFT.
AND THAT'S WHEN HE CAME IN THE
FRONT, IN THE MIDDLE, AND THEN
THIS GUY CAME UP FIGHTING WITH
HIM AND TACKLED HIM DOWN.
>> Reporter: SHE WORKS AT A VA
HOSPITAL AND HELPED CONTROL THE
BLEEDING ON ONE OF THE GUNSHOT
VICTIMS.
POLICE SAY THAT INJURED USHER,
22-YEAR-OLD ROBERT ANGLE RAN TO
HIS CAR AND GOT A GUN, THEN MADE
SURE NO FURTHER SHOTS WERE FIRED
WHILE WAITING FOR THE POLICE TO
ARRIVE.
>> HE'S THE HERO.
HE'S THE PERSON THAT STOPPED
THIS MADNESS.
AND SO, WE'RE VERY, VERY, VERY
GRATEFUL TO HIM.
>> Reporter: SIX OTHERS WERE
SHOT INSIDE THE CHURCH, ALL
ADULTS, FOUR IN THEIR 60s AND
TWO IN THEIR 80s.
THEY WERE TAKEN TO A NEARBY
HOSPITAL.
POLICE TONIGHT SAY THE GUNMAN IS
25-YEAR-OLD EMANUEL SAMPSON FROM
NEARBY.
HE'LL BE JAILED TONIGHT AND FACE
MURDER AND ATTEMPTED MURDER
CHARGES.
NASHVILLE POLICE HAVEN'T YET
SAID WHY THEY THINK THIS
HAPPENED, THOUGH THEY SAY
SAMPSON ATTENDED THAT CHURCH A
FEW YEARS AGO, BUT FEDERAL
OFFICIALS SAY TONIGHT THE FBI
HAS OPENED A SEPARATE CIVIL
RIGHTS INVESTIGATION LOOKING AT
WHETHER RACE WAS THE MOTIVE.
KATE.
>> PETE WILLIAMS, THANK YOU.
>>> THE NEWEST REPUBLICAN PLAN
TO REPLACE OBAMACARE FACES A
CRITICAL TEST THIS WEEK, PASSING
THE MEASURE, LOOKING MORE AND
MORE DIFFICULT NOW WITH TWO MORE
REPUBLICANS TODAY SAYING THEY
HAVE BIG PROBLEMS WITH THIS
BILL.
WE GET THE LATEST FROM NBC'S
KELLY O'DONNELL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT A GOP
REPEAL OF OBAMACARE IS BACK ON
LIFE SUPPORT.
DAYS BEFORE A DEADLINE.
AS REPUBLICANS ATTEMPT TO
OVERHAUL HEALTH CARE INSURANCE,
ONE MORE TIME.
>> THE ONLY WAY YOU'LL KNOW HOW
PEOPLE VOTE IS WHEN YOU ACTUALLY
VOTE.
>> Reporter: SIGNS POINT TO
OUTRIGHT OPPOSITION AND WAVERING
RELUCTANCE FROM A FEW
REPUBLICANS WHOSE VOTES ARE
CRITICAL.
>> WELL IT IS HARD FOR ME TO
ENVISION GETTING TO YES ON THIS
BILL BECAUSE MY CONCERNS ARE SO
FUNDAMENTAL.
>> THIS IS A BAD IDEA.
IT'S NOT REPEAL.
>> Reporter: THIS ALTERNATIVE
NAMED FOUR SENATORS, LINDSEY
GRAHAM AND BILL CASSIDY WOULD
SHIFT CONTROL AND FUNDING FROM
THE FEDERAL GOVERNMENT TO
STATES, USING BLOCK GRANTS.
>> TAKE THE MONEY AND POWER OUT
OF WASHINGTON, THE SAME A. MONEY
SPENT ON OBAMACARE AND LET
STATES DESIGN SYSTEMS.
>> Reporter: THAT FORMULA IS
STILL TOO COSTLY FOR DECLARED
NO-VOTE RAND PAUL.
>> UNFORTUNATELY THE
GRAHAM-CASSIDY BILL BASICALLY
KEEPS MOST OF THE OBAMACARE
SPENDING, ALMOST ALL OF THE
SPENDING AND JUST RESHUFFLES IT.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER CONCERN,
MEDICAID EXPANSION THAT HELPED
LOWER INCOME AMERICANS GET
COVERAGE UNDER OBAMACARE WOULD
BE REDUCED OVER TIME.
AND THERE IS DISPUTE OVER THE
IMPACT ON INSURANCE BUYERS WITH
PREEXISTING MEDICAL CONDITIONS.
THE WHITE HOUSE SAYS, NO CHANGE.
>> PREEXISTING CONDITIONS ARE
PROTECTED IN THIS LEGISLATION.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE.
IT DOES NOT CHANGE THE
LEGISLATION THAT OBAMA HAD IN
OBAMACARE.
>> Reporter: BUT STATES COULD
PERMIT PLANS THAT WOULD NOT
COVER ALL COSTS FOR PREEXISTING
CONDITIONS, MAKING COVERAGE MORE
EXPENSIVE.
SENATOR CASSIDY DEFENDS THE PLAN
AS FAIR.
>> SO WE GIVE THE STATES THE
LATITUDE TO ESTABLISH, IT MAY BE
THAT SOMEONE WHO'S A MILLIONAIRE
WOULD PAY MORE AND LOWER INCOME
WOULD PAY A LITTLE LESS.
>> Reporter: AND REPUBLICANS
HAVE A VERY NARROW NEEDLE TO
THREAD TO SEE THIS BILL PASSED.
TWO REPUBLICANS, JOHN McCAIN,
RAND PAUL, HAVE ALREADY SAID
THEY ARE FIRM NOES AND WHEN YOU
CONSIDER THE SENATE MAP, EVERY
OTHER REPUBLICAN MUST SUPPORT
IT.
AND WE'VE ALREADY SEEN A FEW
OTHERS WHO ARE SAYING, THEY HAVE
CONCERNS, THE WHITE HOUSE THINKS
THERE MAY BE ENOUGH TIME TO TRY
TO SHORE UP SUPPORT FOR A
POTENTIAL VOTE ON WEDNESDAY, AND
KATE TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT WAS
ASKED ABOUT THIS, HE SAID THEY
MAY NOT WIN THIS TIME, BUT
THEY'LL WIN EVENTUALLY.
>> IT'S GOING TO BE AN
INTERESTING WEEK.
THANK YOU SO MUCH.
>>> OVERSEAS TONIGHT, GERMAN
CHANCELLOR ANGELA MERKEL IS
HEADED FOR A FOURTH TERM.
A FAR RIGHT ANTI-IMMIGRATION
PARTY WILL NOW HAVE A PLACE IN
PARLIAMENT FOR THE FIRST TIME IN
MORE THAN HALF A CENTURY.
MATT BRADLEY IS FOLLOWING IT ALL
FROM BERLIN.
>> Reporter: SHE'S WORKED
ALONGSIDE THREE AMERICAN
PRESIDENTS AND TODAY, GERMAN
CHANCELLOR ANGELA MERKEL WON HER
FOURTH TERM.
IT WASN'T ALWAYS EASY, SHE'S
GUIDED GERMANY THROUGH A GLOBAL
FINANCIAL CRISIS, CONFRONTATION
WITH RUSSIA, A SURGE OF
REFUGEES, AND NOW, A HOSTILE
AMERICAN PRESIDENT.
ANK ANGELA MERKEL AND PARTY
STALE YIELDED A LOT OF GROUND TO
THE FAR RIGHT.
IT'LL BE THE FIRST TIME IN 50
YEARS A NATIONALIST, FAR RIGHT
PARTY WILL SIT IN THE GERMAN
PARLIAMENT.
UNLIKE MERKEL, THEY'RE
ANTI-IMMIGRANT, ANTI-EUROPEAN
UNION, AND ANTI-ISLAM.
>> VERY DESTRUCTIVE FORCE.
THEY ARE PROTEST PARTY.
>> Reporter: THEY'RE THE KIND OF
CHALLENGE MERKEL HAS SURVIVED
BEFORE.
MATT BRADLEY, NBC NEWS, BERLIN.
>>> FOUR DAYS AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA SWEPT ACROSS PUERTO RICO,
RESCUE TEAMS ONLY NOW ARE
REACHING SOME OF THE MORE REMOTE
PARTS OF THAT ISLAND.
GABE GUTIERREZ WAS WITH A RESCUE
TEAM TODAY AS IT FINALLY MADE IT
TO ONE COMMUNITY.
>> Reporter: THEY BRING ALL THEY
CAN CARRY, WADING THROUGH
RUSHING WATER, HOLDING ON TO A
DEAD POWER CABLE, NOW AN
IMPROMPTU LIFELINE.
A COMMUNITY IN PUERTO RICO CUT
OFF WHEN HURRICANE MARIA WASHED
THIS BRIDGE AWAY.
THIS WOMAN TELLS US EVERYTHING
ON THE OTHER SIDE IS DEVASTATED.
THE NEED HERE IS MASSIVE.
RURAL PARTS OF THE ISLAND
RAVAGED, INCLUDING THE MOUNTAIN
TOWN.
>> I'M TAMMIE LITHER IN, PEOPLE
ARE DESPERATE FOR WATER.
HERE OUTSIDE THIS AREA, THEY'VE
JERRY RIGGED A PVC PIPE TO GET
RIVER WATER BECAUSE THERE'S NO
DRINKING WATER ANYWHERE ON THE
ISLAND.
>> Reporter: IN NORTHWEST PUERTO
RICO, ENGINEERS INSPECTING THE
DAM AFTER FINDING A CRACK IN IT.
IF IT BURSTS, AUTHORITIES WARN
OF LIFE-THREATENING FLOODING.
TODAY WE RODE ALONG WITH A FEMA
SEARCH AND RESCUE TEAM FROM
SOUTH FLORIDA AS IT MADE IT'S
WAY TO THE CENTRAL PART OF THE
ISLAND.
GREG IS A FIREFIGHTER FROM
MIAMI.
HE'S WORKED HURRICANES HARVEY,
IRMA, AND NOW MARIA.
>> SO WE JUST SPENT THE LAST
HOUR TRYING TO DRIVE AROUND AND
FIND OUT WHERE TO GO AND WHAT
NEEDS TO HAPPEN.
WE'RE COMING UP WITH A DEAD END.
>> Reporter: AS THEY MEET LOCAL
OFFICIALS, THEY'RE FINDING A
SIMILAR STORY, OVER AND OVER
AGAIN.
NO CELL SERVICE AND NO
COMMUNICATION IS HAMPERING
RESCUE EFFORTS.
THIS MAN IS A POLICE OFFICER.
THE HURRICANE DESTROYED HIS HOME
TOO.
>> IT'S PRETTY HARD BECAUSE I
HAVE TO DO TWO JOBS AT THE SAME
TIME.
YOU KNOW, I HAVE TO WORK WITH
THE PEOPLE THAT NEEDS US, AND I
ALSO HAVE TO WORK WITH MY OWN
NEEDS, YOU KNOW.
>> Reporter: THROUGHOUT THE
ISLAND, THE HUNT FOR FUEL IS
GROWING MORE DIRE.
>> THESE ARE PEOPLE THAT COME
FROM MILES AWAY, CARS WITHOUT
GAS, VERY TOUGH, VERY TOUGH.
>> Reporter: AS THESE SEARCH AND
RESCUE TEAMS CLEAR THE WAY FOR
THE ISLAND'S LONG RECOVERY ONE
MISSION AT A TIME.
TONIGHT, THERE IS AN URGENT RUSH
TO CLEAR THESE ROADS AND OPEN UP
LINES OF COMMUNICATION.
BUT THE MORE PEOPLE WE SPEAK
WITH, IT'S CLEAR THIS RECOVERY
WON'T BE MEASURED IN WEEKS, BUT
MONTHS.
EVEN YEARS.
KATE.
>> GABE, INCREDIBLE PICTURES.
>>> AND A CLOSE EYE ON MARIA
TONIGHT AS IT MOVES CLOSER TO
THE UNITED STATES.
NATIONAL HURRICANE CENTER SAYS
THE STORM WILL GRADUALLY WEAKEN,
BUT WILL COME CLOSE TO THE COAST
OF NORTH CAROLINA.
ESPECIALLY THE OUTER BANKS.
HIGH SURF, DANGEROUS RIP
CURRENTS ARE EXPECTED UP AND
DOWN THE EAST COAST OVER THE
NEXT SEVERAL DAYS.
>>> STILL AHEAD TONIGHT, AFTER
SURVIVING THE BRUTALITIES OF
ISIS, HELPING THE VICTIMS HEAL.
AND WHAT AN AMERICAN SUPERSTAR
IS DOING TO HELP THEM FIND A
BETTER LIFE.
>>> ALSO WE'LL TAKE YOU
UNDERWATER OFF THE COAST OF
ALABAMA FOR A LOOK AT A WORLD
THAT WILL EXISTED ON LAND MOR
I just saved a bunch of money on
my car insurance with GEICO.
Huh.
I should take a closer
look at GEICO...
GEICO can help with way
more than car insurance.
Boats, homes, motorcycles...
even umbrella coverage.
This guy's gonna wish
he brought his umbrella.
Fire at will!
How'd you know the guy's
name is Will?
Yeah?
It's an expression, ya know?
Fire at will?
You never heard of that?
Oh, there goes Will!
Bye, Will!
That's not his name!
Take a closer look at GEICO.
Great savings.
And a whole lot more.
DI just drank tons of water all
the time, it was never enough.
My dentist suggested Biotene,
my mouth felt more lubricated.
I use the Biotene rinse
and I use the spray.
Biotene did make a difference.
I NEEDED SOMETHING MORE TO HELP
CONTROL MY TYPE 2 DIABETES.
MY A1C WASN'T WERE
IT NEEDED TO BE.
SO I LIKED WHEN
MY DOCTOR TOLD ME
THAT I MAY REACH MY BLOOD
SUGAR AND A1C GOALS
BY ACTIVATING WHAT'S WITHIN ME
WITH ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT HELPS ACTIVATE MY BODY TO
DO WHAT IT'S SUPPOSE TO DO,
RELEASE ITS OWN INSULIN.
I TAKE IT ONCE A WEEK,
AND IT WORKS 24/7.
IT COMES IN AN EASY-TO-USE PEN
AND I MAY EVEN LOSE
A LITTLE WEIGHT.
TRULICITY IS A ONCE-WEEKLY
INJECTABLE PRESCRIPTION MEDICINE
TO IMPROVE BLOOD SUGAR IN
ADULTS WITH TYPE 2 DIABETES
WHEN USED WITH
DIET AND EXERCISE.
TRULICITY IS NOT INSULIN.
IT SHOULD NOT BE THE FIRST
MEDICINE TO TREAT DIABETES,
OR FOR PEOPLE WITH
TYPE 1 DIABETES
OR DIABETIC KETOACIDOSIS.
DO NOT TAKE TRULICITY
IF YOU OR A FAMILY MEMBER
HAS HAD MEDULLARY
THYROID CANCER,
IF YOU'VE HAD MULTIPLE ENDOCRINE
NEOPLASIA SYNDROME TYPE 2,
OR IF YOU ARE
ALLERGIC TO TRULICITY.
STOP TRULICITY AND CALL
YOUR DOCTOR RIGHT AWAY
IF YOU HAVE A LUMP OR
SWELLING IN YOUR NECK,
SEVERE PAIN IN
YOUR STOMACH,
OR SYMPTOMS SUCH AS ITCHING,
RASH, OR TROUBLE BREATHING.
SERIOUS SIDE EFFECTS MAY
INCLUDE PANCREATITIS,
WHICH CAN BE FATAL.
TAKING TRULICITY WITH A
SULFONYLUREA OR INSULIN,
INCREASES YOUR RISK
FOR LOW BLOOD SUGAR.
COMMON SIDE EFFECTS INCLUDE
NAUSEA, DIARRHEA, VOMITING,
DECREASED APPETITE
AND INDIGESTION.
SOME SIDE EFFECTS CAN
LEAD TO DEHYDRATION,
WHICH MAY MAKE EXISTING
KIDNEY PROBLEMS WORSE.
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY MAY HELP
ME REACH MY BLOOD SUGAR GOALS.
WITH TRULICITY, I CLICK TO
ACTIVATE WHAT'S WITHIN ME.
IF YOU WANT HELP IMPROVING
YOUR A1C AND BLOOD SUGAR,
ACTIVATE YOUR WITHIN.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT
ONCE-WEEKLY TRULICITY.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH A LOOK AT A
PROGRAM THAT HELPS WOMEN AND
GIRLS WHO WERE HELD BY ISIS.
HUNDREDS HAVE BEEN TAKEN AGAINST
THEIR WILL AND EVEN AFTER
THEY'RE FREED, THE HEALING
PROCESS CAN TAKE YEARS.
NBC'S KELLY COBIA WENT TO
GERMANY TO SHOW HOW THE PROGRAM
IS GIVING THEM A NEW START.
>> Reporter: THIS 11-YEAR-OLD
HAS JUST BEEN FREED FROM ISIS.
SO TRAUMATIZED, SHE WON'T SPEAK
OR EAT.
SHE'S YAZIDI, A RELIGIOUS
MINORITY FROM NORTHERN IRAQ.
BRUTALLY TARGETED BY ISIS
FIGHTERS THREE YEARS AGO.
ISIS MASSACRED MANY OF THE
YAZIDI MEN AND TOOK NEARLY 7,000
WOMEN AND GIRLS AS SEX SLAVES.
GERMAN TRAUMA SPECIALIST HAS
INTERVIEWED MORE THAN 1400
SURVIVORS.
>> THEY HAVE NIGHTMARES.
THEY HAVE FEAR.
THEY COULD NOT SLEEP.
THEY HAVE NO CONCENTRATION.
THEY'RE STILL AWAKE AND
AWAITING.
>> Reporter: WHEN HE FIRST MET
THIS WOMAN IN 2015, SHE WAS
LIVING IN A CAMP IN NORTHERN
IRAQ, BROKEN AND ASHAMED.
THIS IS NOT HER REAL NAME SAYS
SHE WAS REPEATEDLY RAPED,
BEATEN, AND DRUGGED BY ISIS
MILITANTS FOR NEARLY A YEAR.
HOW ARE YOU?
THIS MONTH, WE FOUND HER AT A
SHELTER FOR YAZIDI SURVIVORS IN
GERMANY.
DO YOU THINK YOU'RE BETTER?
I'M DOING MUCH BETTER SHE TOLD
ME.
THE DOCTOR HAS FOUGHT TO BRING
HER AND MANY OTHER SURVIVORS
HERE.
THEY'RE GIVEN A SAFE PLACE TO
LIVE AND TREATMENT FOR BODY AND
MIND.
>> THEY ARE STRONGER, THEY WILL
FIGHT TO SURVIVE, AND HOPEFULLY
WITH OUR SUPPORT, THEY WILL
CONTINUE THIS.
>> Reporter: THE HEALING PROCESS
IS LONG AND DIFFICULT.
>> I KNOW VICTIMS OF THE
HOLOCAUST LOOKED LIKE FROM
PICTURES, AND FILMS, AND THIS IS
WHAT THEY REMINDED ME OF.
IF YOU LOOK INTO THE EYES, YOU
SEE THE FACES, YOU SEE VERY DEEP
SADNESS.
>> Reporter: AND NOW?
>> I SEE A DIFFERENCE.
YEAH.
>> Reporter: SOME ARE SPEAKING
OUT AND SEEKING JUSTICE.
WHO IS HE?
SHE SAYS SHE SPOTTED ONE OF HER
KAPTERS ONLINE LAST MONTH.
APPARENTLY TRYING TO BLEND IN
WITH INNOCENT CIVILIANS OUTSIDE
MOSUL.
SHE SAYS, I'M READY TO TESTIFY
AGAINST HIM ANYWHERE.
HE SOLD ME AND MANY OTHER YAZIDI
WOMEN AND CHILDREN.
THE MAN HASN'T BEEN CAUGHT.
IT'S BELIEVED ISIS IS STILL
HOLDING MORE THAN 2,400 WOMEN
AND CHILDREN.
HER SISTERS ARE STILL MISSING.
HER DREAM, ONE DAY SOON THEY'LL
BE HERE TOO.
HEALING WITH HER.
NBC NEWS, GERMANY.
>>> AND YAZIDI REFUGEES WERE IN
THE SPOTLIGHT YESTERDAY AT THE
GLOBAL CITIZEN FESTIVAL HERE IN
NEW YORK BROADCAST ON MSNBC.
POP ICON DEMI LOVATO ANNOUNCED
SHE'LL JOIN FORCES WITH SAVE THE
CHILDREN USING ART THERAPY TO
SUPPORT THEIR MENTAL HEALTH.
I SPOKE WITH HER ABOUT THE NEW
PROJECT.
AND YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT MENTAL
HEALTH BECAUSE THAT'S SUCH A BIG
PART OF WHAT, WHAT CHILDREN
NEED.
>> IT'S SOMETHING THAT I
REALIZED PEOPLE NEEDED WHEN I
WENT TO REFUGEE CAMPS MYSELF IN
IRAQ.
AND I MET WITH REFUGEES WHO HAD
TONS OF NEEDS.
THEY ASKED A YOUNG GIRL WHAT SHE
WANTED, AND I SAID HOW CAN I
HELP?
WHAT DO YOU NEED?
AND SHE SAYS, I JUST WANT TO BE
HAPPY AGAIN.
AND TO HEAR THAT, IT REALLY
STUCK WITH ME.
AND I THOUGHT, THAT'S SOMETHING
THAT I CAN GET INVOLVED WITH.
>> DEMI TELLS ME SHE HOPES TO
HEAD BACK WITH GLOBAL CITIZENS
SOON.
>>> WE'RE BACK WITH A SECRET
MISSION INTO SPACE.
WE'LL TE
COPD makes it hard to breathe.
So to breathe better,
I go with ANORO.
♪Go your own way♪
COPD tries to say,
“Go this way.”
I say, “I'll go my own way”
with ANORO.
♪Go your own way♪
Once-daily ANORO contains
two medicines called
bronchodilators,
that work together to
significantly improve
lung function all day
and all night.
ANORO is not for asthma .
It contains a type of medicine
that increases risk of death
in people with asthma.
The risk is unknown in COPD.
ANORO won't replace rescue
inhalers
for sudden symptoms
and should not be used more than
once a day.
Tell your doctor if you have a
heart condition,
high blood pressure,
glaucoma, prostate, bladder,
or urinary problems.
These may worsen with ANORO.
Call your doctor if you have
worsened breathing, chest pain,
mouth or tongue swelling,
problems urinating,
vision changes, or eye pain
while taking ANORO.
Ask your doctor about ANORO.
♪Go your own way♪
Get your first
prescription
free at ANORO.com.
BOOST.
It's about moving forward,
not back.
It's looking up, not down.
It's being in motion.
In body, In spirit,
In the now.
BOOST® High Protein
It's intelligent nutrition with
15 grams of protein
and 26 vitamins and minerals.
For when you need
a little extra.
BOOST®
The number one high protein
complete nutritional drink.
Be Up for It
Listen up, Heart Disease.
You too, Unnecessary ER Visits.
And hey, Unmanaged Depression,
don't get too comfortable.
We're talking to you,
Cost Inefficiencies,
and Data without Insights.
And Fragmented Care,
stop getting in the way
of patient recovery
and pay attention.
Every single one of you
is on our list.
At Optum, we're partnering
across the health system
to tackle
its biggest challenges.
>>> THE SCENE OVERNIGHT AT THE
AIR FORCE BASE IN CALIFORNIA.
AN ATLAS FIVE ROCKET BLASTING
OFF AND HEADED FOR OTHER BIT
WITH A SPY AT LITE ON BOARD, AND
THAT'S ABOUT ALL WE KNOW.
WHAT EXACTLY THE SATELLITE WILL
BE DOING AS IT ORBITS EARTH IS
CLASSIFIED.
IT'S BUILT AND OPERATED BY THE
AGENCY RESPONSIBLE FOR THIS
COUNTRY'S EYES IN THE SKY.
>>> AND CHECK OUT THIS
NERVE-WRACKING VIDEO.
A MAN IN PETR, AUSTRALIA, WAS
CAPTURED ON CAMERA CLINGING TO
THE BACK OF A MOVING TRAIN.
IT WAS TRAVELING UP TO 68 MILES
PER HOUR AND THE MAN WAS
STANDING AS YOU SEE ON THE EDGE
HOLDING ON TO ONLY A WINDSHIELD
WIPER.
HE WAS ARRESTED AT THE NEXT
STATION.
THE TRANSPORT AUTHORITIES SAID
IT WAS THE FIRST TIME IT WAS
EVER MADE AWARE OF SO-CALLED
TRAIN SURFING STUNT.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK, THE
SECRET WAS AN ANCIENT WORLD
REVEALED AFTER TENS OF THOUSANDS
OF YEARS.
Don't let dust and allergens
get between you
and life's beautiful moments.
Flonase outperforms the #1
non-drowsy allergy pill.
It helps block 6 key
inflammatory substances
that cause symptoms.
Pills block one
and 6 is greater than 1.
Flonase changes
everything.
[phone ring]
Hello.
Hi, it's Anne from Edward Jones.
I'm glad I caught you.
Well I'm just leaving the office
so for once I've got plenty of
time. What's going on?
So those financial regulations
being talked about?
They could affect your accounts,
so let's get
together and talk,
and make sure
everything's clear.
Thanks. Yeah.
That would be great.
We've grown to over $900
billion in assets under care...
by being proactive,
not reactive.
It's how Edward Jones
makes sense of investing.
When heartburn hits,
fight back fast
with TUMS Smoothies.
It starts dissolving
the instant it
touches your tongue.
And neutralizes
stomach acid at the source.
♪ TUM -TUM -TUM -TUM ♪
Smoothies! Only from TUMS
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, LET'S
JOURNEY TO ANOTHER WORLD HIDDEN
AT THE BOTTOM OF THE SEA AND OUT
OF SIGHT FOR TENS OF THOUSANDS
OF YEARS.
THE REMAINS OF AN ANCIENT FOREST
DISCOVERED RECENTLY IN THE GULF
OF MEXICO OFF THE COAST OF
ALABAMA.
NBC'S KERRY SANDERS GOT A LOOK.
>> Reporter: ALONG THE ALABAMA
COAST, WE HEAD TO A SECRET SPOT.
WHAT LIES HERE, 60 FEET BELOW
THE SURFACE, A REMARKABLE
DISCOVERY.
AN ANCIENT FOREST TEAMING WITH
SEA LIFE, BALD CYPRESS TREES
THAT LOOKED LIKE THIS LONG
CONCEALED AND PRESERVED UNDER A
THICK LAYER OF SEDIMENT.
SCIENTISTS BELIEVE THE FOREST
HERE WAS UNCOVERED BY MOTHER
NATURE IN 2004, WHAT HURRICANE
IVAN ROYALED THE SEABED.
THAT'S ABOUT 65 MILES AN HOUR
RIGHT THERE.
IT WASN'T UNTIL ALMOST A DECADE
LATER THAT A FISHERMAN OVER THIS
SPOT LOOKED AT HIS SONAR AND
NOTICED SOMETHING ODD.
HE THEN CALLED SKUB BAA DIVER.
COULD YOU FIGURE IT OUT.
>> WE COULDN'T.
WE DIDN'T KNOW WHAT IT WAS.
THAT'S WHEN WE THOUGHT WE NEEDED
TO GET SCIENTISTS OUT HERE.
>> Reporter: THIS FILM MAKE ORE
DOCUMENTED IT.
>> YOU'RE IN A FAIRY WORLD
ALMOST WITH THE STUMPS ARE
COVERED IN ATHEMTIES AND
EVERYTHING, BUT THEY'RE TREES.
>> Reporter: TEAMS CORD SAMPLES,
FLOATED TREE TRUNKS, RADIO
CARPETED THE WOOD BACK TO 60,000
YEARS AGO.
RESEARCHERS FROM LOUISIANA STATE
UNIVERSITY ESTIMATE THAT THE
FOREST HERE WAS ABOUT A HALF
SQUARE MILE.
THAT'S BECAUSE THEY BELIEVE
WHERE WE SEE THE GULF OF MEXICO
NOW, THERE WAS AN ISLAND, AND
RUSHING AROUND IT, A FRESH WATER
RIVER.
SO THE MUCK FEELS LIKE
PLAY-DOUGH.
THEY'RE BEGINNING TO DECOMPOSE.
>> THE WOOD ACTUALLY COMES OUT.
IT'S LIKE BRITTLE.
>> Reporter: SCIENTISTS SAY
THESE ANCIENT RELICS MAY HOLD
CLUES TO HOW IT COULD AFFECT OUR
FUTURE.
>> THESE TREES DIED VERY
QUICKLY.
AND WE WANT TO SEE HOW THAT'S
TIED TO SEA LEVEL RISE.
>> Reporter: A UNIQUE UNDERSEA
FOREST ONLY STARTING TO REVEAL
IT'S SECRETS.
KERRY SANDERS, NBC NEWS OFF THE
COAST OF ALABAMA.
>> THAT'S GOOD STUFF.
THAT IS NBC NIGHTLY NEWS FOR
THIS SUNDAY NIGHT.
BIG DAY HERE TOMORROW, MEGYN
KELLY TODAY PREMIERS AT 9:00
A.M. EASTERN.
LESTER HOLT WILL BE WITH YOU FOR
NIGHTLY NEWS.
FOR ALL OF US HERE AT NBC NEWS,
HAVE A GREAT NIGHT.