HUMID, VERY STICKY AND THE
HOTTEST DAY IS SUNDAY.
>> STILL TALKING ABOUT 80.
>> WILD.
>> THANKS FOR JOINING US
TONIGHT.
>> "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT STARTS NOW.
♪♪
>>> BREAKING NEWS
TONIGHT.
STATE OF EMERGENCY.
THEY'RE BRACING FOR
IMPACT FROM NEW
ORLEANS TO BILOXI TO
PENSACOLA.
MANDATORY EVACUATIONS
HAVE BEEN ORDERED AS
TROPICAL STORM NATE
CLOSES IN.
IT COULD HIT AS A
HURRICANE
>>> DID ANYONE ELSE
KNOW ABOUT THE PLOT TO
KILL IN LAS VEGAS?
NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN
THE INVESTIGATION.
POLICE NOT CONVINCED
AT THE ATTACKER KEPT
IT TO HIMSELF.
>>> BIRTH CONTROL
BATTLE.
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION ROLLS
BACK OBAMA ERA RULES,
ALLOWING MORE
EMPLOYERS TO OPT OUT
OF PAYING FOR
CONTRACEPTION COVERAGE
>>> SHOCK WAVES
RIPPLING ACROSS
HOLLYWOOD.
A NEW FALLOUT FOR A
POWERFUL MOVIE MOGUL
FACING A STORM OF
ACCUSATIONS OF SEXUAL
MISCONDUCT, INCLUDING
FROM A MAJOR STAR
>>> AND SONG AND A
PRAYER.
LYNN MANUEL MIRANDA
LEADS AN ALL-STAR
TRIBUTE FROM PUERTO
RICO.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>> Announcer: FROM NBC
NEWS WORLD
HEADQUARTERS IN
NEW YORK, THIS IS "NBC
NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>> GOOD EVENING AND
THANKS FOR BEING WITH
US.
LATE TODAY THE MAYOR
OF NEW ORLEANS ORDERED
MANDATORY EVACUATION
AND A CURFEW AS THE
GULF COAST BRACES FOR
ANOTHER POSSIBLE
HURRICANE.
IT IS CALLED NATE, A
TROPICAL STORM NOW BUT
THREATENING TO BUILD
TO HURRICANE STRENGTH
BEFORE HITTING THE
GULF COAST THIS
WEEKEND, POSING A
MAJOR FLOOD DANGER
AFTER LEAVING NEARLY
TWO DOZEN DEAD ACROSS
CENTRAL AMERICA.
HURRICANE AND TROPICAL
STORM WARNING ARE
POSTED TONIGHT FROM
LOUISIANA TO THE
FLORIDA PANHANDLE.
OUR KERRY SANDERS  HAS
THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: NATE HIT
CENTRAL AMERICA AS A
WEAK TROPICAL STORM,
BUT THE IMPACT
POWERFUL.
IN HARD-HIT NICARAGUA,
UP TO 15 INCHES OF
RAIN, TURNING ROADS
LIKE THIS ONE INTO
RIVERS.
THIS WOMAN SAYS THE
STORM HAS LEFT SO MANY
CHILDREN CRYING.
THEY'RE HUNGRY AND
THIRSTY.
IN MOUNTAINOUS COSTA
RICA MAJOR MUDSLIDES
AND WIDE-SPREAD POWER
OUTAGES, THOUSANDS NOW
HOMELESS, AT LEAST 22
DEAD, AMONG THEM TWO
KIDS SWEPT AWAY IN
FAST-RISING WATERS.
HURRICANE WARNING IN
PLACE FOR PARTS OF
LOUISIANA, MISSISSIPPI
AND ALABAMA.
IN NEW ORLEANS, A RACE
TO SANDBAG TONIGHT.
RESIDENTS HERE NOT
WORRIED SO MUCH ABOUT
THE LEVY SYSTEM GIVING
WAY AS HAPPENED
12 YEARS AGO DURING
KATRINA, RATHER FEARS
THE CITY'S CRIPPLED
PUMPING SYSTEM WILL
FAIL.
>> IT WAS RECENTLY
TESTED, THE SYSTEM
ITSELF AND IT DIDN'T
HOLD.
>> Reporter:
AUGUST 2017 CRITICAL
PUMPS IN THE CITY LOST
POWER, ONLY EIGHT
INCHES OF RAIN TURNING
TO A CALAMITY.
>> I WANT TO BE CLEAR.
WE HAVE SUFFICIENT
PUMPS AND MANPOWER TO
HANDLE THE THREAT IF
THE RAIN TOTALS REMAIN
AS FORECAST AND THE
INTENSITY IS DIRECTED.
>> Reporter: ALL
ATTENTION IS ON THE
PUMPS LIKE THE ONE
OVER MY SHOULDER HERE
WITH THE EXPECTATION
THAT NATE WILL BECOME
A HURRICANE.
AS YOU NOTED AT THE
TOP, LESTER, THE MAYOR
OF NEW ORLEANS HAS
ISSUED MANDATORY
EVACUATIONS FOR
CERTAIN PARTS OF THE
CITY.
>> CAREY SANDERS,
THANK YOU.
LET'S TURN TO AL ROCHA
WITH THE LATEST
FORECAST TRACK WHICH
HAS SHIFTED SLIGHTLY
FROM LAST NIGHT, AND
WHETHER IT HITS AS A
TROPICAL STORM OR A
CATEGORY 1 HURRICANE,
IT DOESN'T MAKE A LOT
OF DIFFERENCE TO FOLKS
ALONG THE GULF COAST
AFTER WHAT THEY'VE
SEEN THIS STORM
SYSTEM.
>> ABSOLUTELY.
THE TRACK HAS SHIFTED.
80 MILES EAST OF
COZUMEL, MEXICO.
IT IS BOOKING AT
21 MILES AN HOUR.
AT THIS POINT IT IS
ABOUT 200 MILES AWAY
FROM NEW ORLEANS.
SATURDAY 1:00 P.M.,
70-MILE PER HOUR
WINDS.
THEN IT MAKES LANDFALL
ABOUT 1:00 A.M. AND
CONTINUES TO MOVE
RATHER RAPIDLY, ABOUT
140 MILES OF THAT CONE
OF UNCERTAINTY, AND
THEN MOVES VERY
QUICKLY OUT TO SEA.
HOWEVER, HERE IS WHAT
WE LOOK FOR.
HURRICANE WARNING
RIGHT NOW FROM
LOUISIANA ALL THE WAY
TO ABOUT THE
PENSACOLA/MOBILE,
ALABAMA AREA.
HEAVY RAIN, FLASH
FLOODING, TROPICAL
STORM SURGE.
NEW ORLEANS, FIVE TO
EIGHT FEET.
FOUR TO SIX FOR
FLORIDA.
AGAIN, LESTER, WE HAVE
TO WATCH AND WAIT
BECAUSE A TRACK CHANGE
OF 50 MILES PER HOUR
CAN -- 50 MILES CAN
MAKE A BIG, BIG
DIFFERENCE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
AL ROCHA, THANK YOU.
NOW TO NEW
DEVELOPMENTS IN THE
MASS SHOOTING IN LAS
VEGAS.
INVESTIGATORS
EMPHASIZING LATE TODAY
THEY DON'T BELIEVE
THERE WAS A SECOND
SHOOTER, BUT A LOT OF
QUESTIONS REMAINED
ABOUT HOW ELSE MAY
HAVE KNOWN ABOUT THIS
PLOT.
MEANWHILE, ALL 58
VICTIMS KILLED HAVE
BEEN IDENTIFIED.
WE WILL GET THE LATEST
FROM NBC'S MIGUEL
ALMAGUER.
>> Reporter: REPLACING
THE WINDOWS WHERE HE
UNLEASHED THE
NIGHTMARE.
INVESTIGATORS HAVE
SCOURED MULTIPLE CRIME
SCENES, THE HOTEL, THE
CONCERT-TURNED KILLING
FIELD AND THE HOMES
WHERE HE LIVED.
>> Reporter: WHAT CAN
YOU TELL US ABOUT
MOTIVE?
>> I CAN TELL YOU I
DON'T HAVE AN ANSWER
AS TO MOTIVE.
HE WAS THE ONLY
SHOOTER, I'M CONFIDENT
TO THAT.
I'M ALSO
CONFIDENTIALITY THERE
WERE NO OTHER PEOPLE
IN THE ROOM LEADING TO
THIS EVENT.
BUT DID ANYBODY ELSE
KNOW WHAT HE WAS
PLANNING AND WHY?
THAT IS THE MAIN FOCUS
OF OUR INVESTIGATION
TODAY.
>> Reporter: IRS
RECORDS SHOW PADDOCK
EARNED AT LEAST FIVE
MILLION DOLLARS
GAMBLING IN 2015.
TWO SOURCES SAY THE
GUNMAN BOUGHT SOME
AMMO  FROM A RECENT
GUN SHOW IN PHOENIX.
AN PURCHASED TRACER
ROUNDS, BULLETS THAT
LEAVE A VISIBLE TRAIL
IN THE DARK.
SHOT FOUR TIMES,
SAMANTHA FARONDA, WAS
ABLE TO GO HOME TODAY.
>> I'M JUST GRATEFUL
THAT I DIDN'T HAVE TO
COMPLETELY SAY GOODBYE
TO ALL OF THE PEOPLE
THAT I LOVE.
>> Reporter: WHAT
HAPPENED IN VEGAS IS
BEING FELT NATIONWIDE.
TODAY IN CHICAGO AND
AUSTIN, STEPPED-UP
SECURITY AS THOUSANDS
GATHER FOR CONCERTS
AND BASEBALL GAMES.
TONIGHT WE NOW KNOW
THE NAMES OF ALL 58
VICTIMS, 30 WITH TIES
TO SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA.
THE YOUNGEST, JUST 20,
BAILEY SCHWEITZER.
THE OLDEST,
67-YEAR-OLD
PATTI MESTAS, LOVED
LIFE AND HER EIGHT
GRANDCHILDREN.
LAS VEGAS POLICE
OFFICER CHARLESTON
HARTFIELD SERVED
16 YEARS IN THE
MILITARY, DYING ON A
BATTLEFIELD AT HOME IN
THE CITY HE LOVED.
♪♪ AMAZING GRACE ♪
>> TONIGHT GROWING
MEMORIALS IN LAS VEGAS
AS 58 FAMILIES BEGIN
TO PLAN FUNERALS.
>> Reporter: AS
INVESTIGATORS POUR
OVER THE CRIME SCENE
BEHIND ME, THEY SAY
THEY ARE CONFIDENT THE
GUNMAN ACTED ALONE.
WHAT THEY'RE UNCERTAIN
ABOUT IS AFTER MONTHS,
POSSIBLY EVEN YEARS OF
METICULOUS PLANNING,
HOW COULD NO ONE ELSE
KNOW ABOUT THE
MURDEROUS PLAN.
LESTER.
>> MIGUEL ALMAGUER IN
LAS VEGAS.
WE ARE LEARNING ABOUT
ANOTHER PLOT TO
ATTRACT OTHER VENN
YOURS SUCH AS TIMES
SQUARE HERE IN NEW
YORK CITY.
FEDERAL PROSECUTORS
SAY THREE MEN WERE
ARRESTED FOR THE
ISIS-INSPIRED PLAN
BROKEN UP THANKS IN
PART TO AN UNDERCOVER
FBI AGENT.
NBC JUSTICE
CORRESPONDENT PETE
WILLIAMS IS FOLLOWING
THAT.
GOOD EVENING, PETE.
>> Reporter: LESTER,
PROSECUTORS SAY THAT
THE DISCOVERY OF THIS
PLOT INSPIRED BY ISIS
WAS KEPT SECRET UNTIL
TONIGHT BECAUSE THE
FBI WANTED TO FIND OUT
IF OTHERS WERE
INVOLVED.
COURT DOCUMENTS SAY
THREE MEN FROM CANADA,
PAKISTAN AND THE
PHILIPPINES PLANNED TO
SET OFF BOMBS IN TIMES
SQUARE AND SHOOT AT
PEOPLE ATTENDING
CONCERTS AROUND THE
CITY.
THEY TALKED ABOUT THE
2015 ATTACKS IN FRANCE
AT THE BATACLAN
THEATER AND SAID, "WE
JUST WALK IN WITH GUNS
IN OUR HANDS, THAT'S
HOW THE PARIS GUYS DID
IT."
THEY ALSO TALKED ABOUT
SETTING OFF BOMBS IN
THE CROWDED NEW YORK
SUBWAY AND IDENTIFIED
WHICH LINES THEY WOULD
FOCUS ON.
THIS PLOT WAS ACTUALLY
BROKEN UP IN MAY OF
2016.
PROSECUTORS SAY WHEN
THE MEN WERE
DISCOVERED
COMMUNICATING ABOUT
TERRORISM AN FBI
UNDERCOVER AGENT SOON
JOINED IN AND THE
THREE WERE UNDER CLOSE
SURVEILLANCE.
ONE HAS NOW PLEADED
GUILTY, THE OTHER TWO
UNDER ARREST.
LESTER.
>> PETE WILLIAMS IN
OUR WASHINGTON
NEWSROOM.
A NEW TURN IN THE
BATTLE OVER BIRTH
CONTROL AND RELIGIOUS
FREEDOMS IN
WASHINGTON.
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION IS
ROLLING BACK OBAMA ERA
RULES AND ALLOWING
MORE EMPLOYERS TO OPT
OUT OF PAYING FOR
CONTRACEPTION
COVERAGE, AN
ANNOUNCEMENT THAT HAS
WOMEN'S HEALTH
ADVOCATES VOWING TO
FIGHT BACK.
OUR CHIEF WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT HALLIE
JACKSON HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
IT IS GETTING HARDER
FOR SOME WOMEN TO GET
BIRTH CONTROL THROUGH
THEIR INSURANCE AFTER
A SWEEPING CHANGE BY
THE TRUMP
ADMINISTRATION THAT
WILL LET MORE
EMPLOYERS OPT OUT OF A
REQUIREMENT TO PAY FOR
CONTRACEPTIVE
COVERAGE.
THE NEW RULE ALLOWS
MORE BUSINESSES WHO
DON'T WANT TO
SUBSIDIZE BIRTH
CONTROL FOR EMPLOYEES
TO ASK FOR EXEMPTIONS
FOR MORAL OR RELIGIOUS
REASONS, NOT JUST
RELIGIOUS
ORGANIZATIONS BUT
BUSINESSES OF ALL
SIZES, SCHOOLS AND
UNIVERSITIES, AND
NONPROFITS, TOO.
THE DECISION TODAY
CELEBRATED BY
RELIGIOUS LIBERTIES
ADVOCATES.
>> WHAT IT DOES DO IS
CREATE A NARROW AND
TARGETED EXEMPTION FOR
THOSE WHO CANNOT IN
GOOD CONSCIENCE
PROVIDE THIS AS PART
OF THEIR HEALTH CARE
PLAN.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP, FULFILLING A
CAMPAIGN PLEDGE.
>> THE FIRST PRIORITY
OF MY ADMINISTRATION
WILL BE TO PRESERVE
AND PROTECT OUR
RELIGIOUS LIBERTY.
>> Reporter: HIS
ADMINISTRATION SAYS
THE NEW EXEMPTIONS
MIGHT ONLY APPLY TO
200 COMPANIES AND WILL
NOT AFFECT THE VAST
MAJORITY OF WOMEN, BUT
THAT'S ONLY BASED ON
GROUPS THAT SO FAR
HAVE SUED THE
GOVERNMENT TO BE ABLE
TO OPT OUT OF
OBAMACARE'S
CONTRACEPTIVE
REQUIREMENT.
WHAT'S UNKNOWN IS WHO
ELSE MIGHT ASK FOR
EXEMPTIONS.
ADVOCATES FOR BROADER
ACCESS TO BIRTH
CONTROL DESCRIBE THIS
AS A SETBACK WITH THE
ACLU ALREADY
ANNOUNCING A LAWSUIT.
>> WHAT THIS RULE DOES
IS PUT THAT COVERAGE
IN JEOPARDY BECAUSE IT
PUTS CONTROL IN THEIR
BOSS'S HANDS AS TO
WHETHER THEY HAVE
ACCESS TO BIRTH
CONTROL COVERAGE THAT
IS CURRENTLY
GUARANTEED.
>> Reporter: AS FOR
TIMING, THE NEW RULE
GOES INTO EFFECT
IMMEDIATELY.
LESTER.
>> ACTION OF THE WHITE
HOUSE.
THANKS.
>>> NOW NOR THE
CRYPTIC COMMENT FROM
PRESIDENT TRUMP
RIPPLING ACROSS
WASHINGTON TONIGHT.
SURROUNDED BY MILITARY
LEADERS AND THEIR
SPOUSES, THE PRESIDENT
TOLD REPORTERS THEY
MIGHT BE SEEING, "THE
CALM BEFORE THE
STORM," A REMARK THAT
HAS PROMPTED MANY TO
ASK WAS HE REFERRING
TO SOMETHING SPECIFIC.
THE WHITE HOUSE ISN'T
SAYING AND NBC'S PETER
ALEXANDER HAS MORE.
>> THANK YOU VERY
MUCH, EVERYBODY.
>> Reporter: FROM THE
OVAL OFFICE TONIGHT
PRESIDENT TRUMP WITH A
WINK AND A TEASE.
>> THANK YOU VERY
MUCH.
YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: REVEALING
NO NEW DETAILS ABOUT
THE MEANING OF THIS
CRYPTIC COMMENT DURING
A RECEPTION WITH
MILITARY LEADERS AND
THEIR SPOUSES THURSDAY
NIGHT.
>> YOU KNOW WHAT THIS
REPRESENTS.
MAYBE IT IS THE CALM
BEFORE THE STORM.
WHAT THIS COULD BE,
THE CALM BEFORE THE
STORM.
>> Reporter: WHAT
STORM, MR. PRESIDENT?
>> YOU'LL FIND OUT.
>> Reporter: WHAT'S HE
TALKING ABOUT?
THE WHITE HOUSE
INSISTING PRESIDENT
TRUMP NEVER TIPS HIS
HAND.
>> WE ARE NEVER GOING
TO SAY IN ADVANCE WHAT
THE PRESIDENT IS GOING
TO DO.
>> Reporter: IT IS
UNCLEAR WHETHER THE
PRESIDENT WAS TOYING
AROUND, DEFLECTING
FROM THE POLITICAL
STORM AND HOPING HIS
ADMINISTRATION OR
PREVIEWING NEW ACTION.
TONIGHT MULTIPLE U.S.
OFFICIALS TELLING NBC
NEWS PRESIDENT TRUMP
WILL LIKELY ANNOUNCE
HE WON'T CERTIFY IRAN
IS COMPLYING WITH THE
NUCLEAR DEAL, A MOVE
THAT COULD LEAD TO NEW
SANCTIONS.
HIS PRESS SECRETARY,
UNPROMPTED, ALSO
BRINGING UP NORTH
KOREA.
>> WE'RE CONTINUING TO
PUT MAXIMUM ECONOMIC
AND DIPLOMATIC
PRESSURE ON COUNTRIES
LIKE NORTH KOREA.
WE'RE GOING TO
CONTINUE TO DO THAT.
>> Reporter: WHITE
HOUSE VETERANS WARN
WORDS MATTER.
>> THOSE WORDS THAT
COME OUT OF THE
PRESIDENT'S MOUTH HAVE
AN IMPACT ALL AROUND
THE GLOBE, AND
SOMETIMES THERE ARE
UNINTENDED
CONSEQUENCES BECAUSE
OF THE WORDS THAT ARE
SPOKEN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE FORMER REALITY TV
STAR TURNED PRESIDENT
IS LEAVING AMERICAN
ALLIES AND ADVERSARIES
WITH A CLIFFHANGER.
PETER ALEXANDER, NBC
NEWS, THE WHITE HOUSE
>>> NOW TO THE LATE
CONFIRMATION FROM THE
PENTAGON THAT A FOURTH
AMERICAN SOLDIER WAS
KILLED, LEFT BEHIND
AFTER ISLAMIC FORCES
AMBUSHED A U.S.
SPECIAL FORCES PATROL
ON WEDNESDAY.
WE GET THE LATEST FROM
NBC CORRESPONDENT HANS
NICHOLS.
>> Reporter: THE
BODIES OF THREE FALLEN
GREEN BERETS BACK HOME
TONIGHT AFTER KILLED
IN AN AMBUSH IN THE
WEST AFRICAN NATION.
STAFF STARGT BRYAN
BLACK, 35, A SHARP
SHOOTER FROM
WASHINGTON.
STAFF SERGEANT DUSTIN
WRIGHT FROM LYONS,
GEORGIA, 29 YEARS OLD.
STAFF SERGEANT
JEREMIAH JOHNSON, 39,
FROM OHIO WHERE THE
COMMUNITY IS
DEVASTATED.
>> WE KNEW WHERE HE
WAS AND HE WASN'T IN A
GOOD PLACE, AND --
>> Reporter: YEAH.
>> -- IT WAS JUST
HEARTBREAKING.
>> Reporter: THE GREEN
BERETS JUST A FEW OF
THE 800 AMERICAN
TROOPS IN NIGER WHERE
DRONES WATCHED ISLAMIC
EXTREMISTS.
THEY ENCOUNTER
TERRORISM, BUT A
ROUTINE MISSION TURNED
INTO FULL-PLEDGE
COMBAT WHEN NEARLY A
DOZEN U.S. AND NIGER
FORCES WERE SURPRISED
BY ISLAMIC MILITANTS.
A DEADLY FIRE FIGHT
ENSUED.
FRENCH HELICOPTERS
EVACUATED THEM.
IN THE CHAOS OF
BATTLE, ONE WAS
MISSED.
SPECIAL OPERATORS WERE
FLOWN IN FROM ACROSS
THE GLOBE, BUT IT WAS
TOO LATE, HIS BODY
FOUND TODAY BY
NIGERIAN TROOPS.
>> YOU TRY NEVER TO DO
A SOLDIER BEHIND.
IT IS UNUSUAL TO DO
SO.
IT MUST HAVE BEEN ONE
HECK OF A FIRE FIGHT
FOR THAT TO HAPPEN.
>> Reporter: MILITARY
OFFICIALS TELL NBC
NEWS THE GREEN BERETS
DID KILL SOME ISLAMIC
EXTREMISTS BUT THEY
CAN'T SAY HOW MANY,
WHERE THEY CAME FROM
OR IF THEY WILL STRIKE
AGAIN.
HANS NICHOLS, NBC
NEWS, PENTAGON
>>> MIX NEWS ON THE
ECONOMY IN EVENING.
THE U.S. LOST 33,000
JOBS IN SEPTEMBER, THE
FIRST DECLINE IN
MONTHLY JOB NUMBERS
GOING BACK SIX YEARS.
BACK-TO-BACK
HURRICANES LIKELY HAD
A SIGNIFICANT SLOW
DOWN IN HIRING, BUT
THE EMPLOYMENT RATE
DECLINED TO 4.2%, THE
LOWEST SINCE FEBRUARY
OF 2001 AND A SIGN THE
JOB MARKET REMAINS
STRONG
>>> STILL AHEAD AS WE
CONTINUE TONIGHT, THE
SCANNED WILL ROCKING
HOLLYWOOD.
NEW FALLOUT FROM
SEXUAL HARASSMENT
ACCUSATIONS AGAINST
ONE OF THE INDUSTRY'S
LEADING POWER PLAYERS.
Every day
people are fighting
type 2 diabetes...
with Fitness...
Food...
And the pill that
starts with F.
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA
if you have severe
kidney problems,
are on dialysis,
or have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary tract
infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious
and may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about
the pill that starts with F
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
When heartburn hits,
fight back fast
with TUMS Smoothies.
It starts dissolving
the instant it
touches your tongue.
And neutralizes
stomach acid at the source.
♪ TUM -TUM -TUM -TUM ♪
Smoothies! Only from TUMS
♪One way or another,
I'm gonna find ya'♪
♪I'm gonna get ya', get
ya', get ya', get ya'♪
♪One day maybe next week,♪
♪I'm gonna meet ya'♪
♪I'm gonna meet
ya', I'll meet ya'♪
A heart attack doesn't
or how healthy you look.
No matter who you are,
a heart attack can
happen without warning.
A Bayer Aspirin regimen can help
prevent another heart attack.
Be sure to talk to your doctor
before you begin an
Aspirin regimen.
Bayer Aspirin.
I love you, Droolius Caesar,
but sometimes you stink.
Febreze Car Vent Clip cleans
away odors for up to 30 days.
Because the things
you love can stink.
>>> BACK NOW WITH NEW
FALLOUT FROM THE
FIRESTORM GRIPPING
HOLLYWOOD.
MOVIE MOGUL HARVEY
WEINSTEIN TAKING A
LEAVE OF ABSENCE FROM
HIS OWN COMPANY AFTER
REPORTS OF MULTIPLE
SEXUAL HARASSMENT
COMPLAINTS AGAINST
HIM.
WEINSTEIN IS JUST THE
LATEST POWER PLAYER
ACCUSED OF MISCONDUCT
AGAINST WOMEN.
WE GET MORE FROM NBC'S
ANNE THOMPSON.
>> Reporter: DURING
AWARD SEASONS HARVEY
WEINSTEIN'S POWER IS
ON FULL DISPLAY.
>> I WANT TO THANK MY
AGENT KEVIN AND GOD,
HARVEY WEINSTEIN.
>> Reporter: HIS FILMS
INCLUDING "THE KING'S
SPEECH," "PULP
FICTION," AND
"SHAKESPEARE IN LOVE"
WINNING 75 OSCARS.
A "NEW YORK TIMES"
INVESTIGATION ALLEGES
HE USED HIS POWER FOR
MORE SORDID ENDS,
UNCOVERING SEXUAL
HARASSMENT ALLEGATIONS
SPANNING ALMOST THREE
DECADES, FROM
ACTRESSES ASHLEY JUDD
TO ROSE McGOWAN TO
YOUNG FEMALE
ASSISTANTS LOOKING TO
START CAREERS IN
HOLLYWOOD.
>> NOBODY WITH ANY
AMOUNT OF MONEY OR
GLAMOUR OR PROFILE
SHOULD BE HELD TO
DIFFERENT STANDARDS
THAN EVERY SINGLE MAN
RESPONSIBLE FOR AND
FRIENDS WITH WOMEN IN
THIS WORLD.
>> Reporter: THE STORY
STRIKING A NERVE.
WHEN DID YOU MEET YOUR
HARVEY WEINSTEIN?
GETTING MORE THAN 24
RESPONSES ON TWITTER
FROM WOMEN IN ALL
WALKS OF LIFE.
THE MOVIE MOGUL, THE
LATEST POWERFUL MAN
ACCUSED OF PREYING ON
FEMALE EMPLOYEES.
FOX NEWS PLAYING
MILLIONS FOR CLAIMS
AGAINST FORMER ANCHOR
BILL O'REILLY AND CEO
ROGER AILES.
RIDE-SHARING UBER
ACCUSED OF FOSTERING A
TOXIC CULTURE OF
SEXIVELY AND
HARASSMENT.
WEINSTEIN SAID, I
APPRECIATE THE WAY
I'VE BEHAVED WITH
COLLEAGUES IN THE PAST
HAS CAUSED A LOT OF
PAIN, AND I SINCERELY
APOLOGIZE FOR IT.
LISA BLOOM, WHO HAS
REPRESENTED WOMEN IN
CLAIMS AGAINST BILL
COSBY, FOX NEWS AND
THEN-CANDIDATE DONALD
TRUMP IS ALSO
REPRESENTING
WEINSTEIN.
HE IS MAKING A
DOCUMENTARY OF ONE OF
HER BOOKS.
>> IT IS TIME FOR A
LOT OF OLD DINOSAURS
IN THE INDUSTRY, AND
ALL INDUSTRIES, TO
UPDATE THEIR THINKING
AND THEIR BEHAVIOR.
>> Reporter: A MAN
WITH THE POWER TO MAKE
OR BREAK CAREERS MAY
HAVE HARMED HIS OWN.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC
NEWS NEW YORK.
>> BACK IN A MOMENT
WITH A BIG-NAME STORE
CHAIN LOOKING TO SHAKE
UP THE GROCERY DELIVER
WARS.
♪♪
Liberty Mutual stood with me
when this guy got a flat tire
in the middle of the night.
Hold on Dad...
Liberty did what?
Yeah, Liberty Mutual 24-Hour
Roadside Assistance
helped him to fix his flat
so he could get home safely.
My dad says our insurance
doesn't have that.
Don't worry - I know what a
lug wrench is, Dad.
Is this a lug wrench?
Maybe?
You can leave worry behind
when Liberty stands with you™.
Liberty Stands With You™.
Liberty Mutual Insurance.
When you have a cold
stuff happens.
Shut down cold
symptoms fast
with Maximum Strength
Alka Seltzer Plus
Liquid Gels.
My shoulders carry
a lot of names
Some I deserve
Others I don't
But in the end
Only one name really matters
Because shoulders were made for
greatness, not dandruff
Needles.
Essential for vinyl,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and further
joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma
and other cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Tears in the stomach
or intestines,
low blood cell counts
and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels
have happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you start
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you
were in a region
where fungal infections
are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
A must for vinyl.
But for you,
one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
♪♪
Looking for clear answers
for your retirement plan?
Start here.
Or here.
Even here.
And definitely here.
At Fidelity,
we're available 24/7
to make
retirement planning simpler.
We let you know
where you stand,
so when it comes
to your retirement plan,
you'll always be
absolutely...clear.
♪ Time to think of your future ♪
It's your retirement.
Know where you stand.
>>> NEW SALVO TONIGHT
IN THE GROCERY WARS AS
BIG NAMES BATTLE FOR
YOUR MONEY, TAKING AIM
AT AMAZON, COSTCO HAS
ANNOUNCED IT IS
GETTING IN THE
SAME-DAY GROCERY
DELIVERY GAME WHICH
THE COMPANY SAYS WILL
BE AVAILABLE IN MOST
METROPOLITAN AREAS AND
OFFER TWO-DAY DELIVERY
FOR DRY GOODS.
>>> IT IS THE END OF
AN ERA ONLINE.
AOL INSTANT MESSENGER
KNOWN AS AIM IS
SIGNING OFF FOR GOOD
IN DECEMBER.
FOR FACEBOOK AND
TWITTER IT WAS THE WAY
TO CHAT WITH SO MANY
PEOPLE THROUGHOUT THE
LATE '90s AND INTO THE
2000s WITH YOUR SCREEN
NAME AND BUDDY LIST
AND CREATE AWAY
MESSAGES THAT MIGHT
MAKE YOU CRINGE
>>> SCARY MOMENTS
CAUGHT ON CAMERA WITH
A JUMBO JET CAME IN
FOR A ROUGH LANDING IN
POWERFUL CROSS WINDS.
TAKE A LOOK.
THE PLANE WOBBLED AS
IT TOUCHED DOWN,
APPEARING TO COME
CLOSE TO SLIDING OFF
THE RUNWAY IN GERMANY
BEFORE THE PI LAT WAS
ABLE TO FINALLY
STRAIGHTEN IT OUT.
THE AIRBUS A-380 PLANE
IS THE LARGEST
COMMERCIAL AIRCRAFT IN
THE WORLD.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK
THE CREATOR OF THE
SMASH HIT HAMT,
Rethink what's possible.
Rethink your allergy pills.
>>> WHEN WE COME BACK
THE CREATOR OF THE
SMASH HIT HAMT,
Flonase Sensimist Allergy Relief
helps block 6 key
inflammatory
substances
with a
gentle mist.
Most allergy
pills
only block
one.
And 6 is greater
than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
♪
How can you make your
hair even stronger?
Use Pantene shampoo together
with 3 Minute Miracle Daily
Conditioner.
Their Pro-V formula is
like a multi-vitamin.
Making your hair 2x stronger
See the difference when you
add 3 Minute Miracle Daily
Conditioner.
[Bullfighting Music]
[Burke] Billy-Goat Ruffians.
Seen it. Covered it.
We know a thing or two because
we've seen a thing or two.
♪ We are Farmers. Bum-pa-dum,
bum-bum-bum-bum ♪
Patrick woke up
with back pain.
But he has
work to do.
So he took Aleve.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the strength
to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT,
MORE THAN TWO WEEKS
AFTER HURRICANE MARIA
SLAMMED PUERTO RICO,
THAT U.S. TERRITORY
REMAINS IN DIRE NEED.
THAT'S WHY LIN-MANUEL
MIRANDA, TONY AND
CREATOR OF THE SMASH
HIT "HAMILTON" GOT
SOME OF HIS FELLOW
MUSIC SUPERSTARS
TOGETHER FOR A SONG
BENEFITTING THE RELIEF
EFFORT.
TONIGHT OUR GABE
GUTIERREZ HAS AN
INSIDE LOOK
♪
>> Reporter: IF THE
SONG WAS ONLY ABOUT A
STORM IT WOULDN'T BE
SO PERSONAL.
♪ IT'S ALMOST
LIKE -- ♪
>> Reporter: BUT FOR
LIN-MANUEL MIRANDA,
HIS NEW SINGLE "ALMOST
LIKE PRAYING" INSPIRED
BY THE WEST SIDE STORY
SONG "MARIA" CUTS
DEEPER, FEATURING
JENNIFER LOPEZ, MARC
ANTHONY AND GLORIA
ESTEFAN.
THE MUSIC GIVES
ATTENTION TO PUERTO
RICO'S TOWNS.
>> LIKE MANY PEOPLE I
HAVE FAMILY ON THE
ISLAND, AND WHAT WE
ALL EXPERIENCED IF WE
WEREN'T ON THE ISLAND
WAS A TERRIBLE SILENCE
IN THE WAKE OF THE
STORM.
OUR SOCIAL MEDIA FEEDS
WERE FULL OF THE NAMES
OF TOWN.
>> Reporter: THE
LATEST PRIVATE VOICE
IN THE HURRICANE
RELIEF EFFORT, STEPHEN
COLBERT RAISING MORE
THAN A MILLION DOLLARS
GETTING CELEBRITIES TO
POST AWKWARD PICTURES.
A GROUP RALLYING FOR
THE SOUTH EASTERN
HARDEST HIT COAST.
>> AND WE GIVE BACK TO
ANY IN NEED AS THE
NATION HAS DONE SO FOR
US.
>> TO NEW JERSEY TODAY
WHERE SUPPLIES WERE
RUSHED TO THE LOCAL
FOOD BANK EN ROUTE TO
SAN JUAN.
>> IT IS DEVASTATING.
>> Reporter:
D.D.MONTENERO GREW UP
IN PUERTO RICO AND
DIDN'T HEAR FROM HER
75-YEAR-OLD MOTHER ON
THE ISLAND FOR DAYS
AFTER THE STORM.
>> THE PAIN IS SO DEEP
TRIBUTE HELPING MAKE
SURE 78 TOWNS ARE NOT
FORGOTTEN.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>> WE APPRECIATE YOU
SPENDING PART OF YOUR
EVENING WITH US.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS FRIDAY NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
NIGHT.
♪♪
TO NEWS THE LAS
VEGAS GUNMAN
>>> RIGHT NOW ON NBC BOSTON NEWS
AT 7:00, POLICE TAKING ACTION IN
RESPONSE TO NEWS THAT THE LAS
VEGAS GUNMAN SCOUTED BOSTON
LOCATIONS AS WELL.
WHAT FANS CAN EXPECT AT SUNDAY'S
RED SOX GAME.
>>> AND A STUDENT CAUGHT ON
CAMERA AT MELROSE HIGH SCHOOL
AND THE PHONE CALL THAT LED TO
THIS INCIDENT.
>>> PLUS --
>>■ç IF WE COULDN'T GO TOGETHER
WE WEREN'T GOING TO GO UNTIL WE
COULD FIND A WAY TO DO THAT.
>> A FAMILY PLEAS PUERTO RICO
AND ENDS UP IN BRAINTREE AND THE
SACRIFICES THEY MADE SO THEIR
PETS COULD JOIN THEM.
>>> FIVE DAYS AFTER THE
DEADLIEST SHOOTING IN MODERN
U.S. HISTORY AN THERE IS STILL
NO KNOWN MOTIVE TONIGHT.
GOOD EVENING, I'M PHIL LIPOF.
>> AND I'M JOY LIM NAKRIN.
INVESTIGATORS ARE PUTTING UP
BILLBOARDS PLEADING FOR ANY
INFORMATION AS THEY TRY TO
UNCOVER WHAT TRIGGED THE LAS
VEGAS MASSACRE.
TODAY INVESTIGATORS SAID THEY
ARE FOLLOWING MORE THAN A
THOUSAND LEADS AND SO FAR THEY
HAVE COME UP EMPTY AS THEY TRY
TO DETERMINE WHAT CAUSED STEPHEN
PADDOCK TO OPEN FIRE.
THEY BELIEVE HE ACTED ALONE AT
THE TIME OF SUNDAY'S SHOOTING.
>> WE'RE VERY CONFIDENT THAT HE
DID NOT -- THERE WAS NOT ANOTHER
SHOOTER IN THAT ROOM.
WHAT I CANNOT CONFIRM TO YOU
TODAY AND WHAT WE CONTINUE TO
INVESTIGATE IS WHETHER ANYBODY
ELSE MAY HAVE KNOWN ABOUT THIS
INCIDENT BEFORE HE CARRIED IT
OUT.
>> INVESTIGATORS STILL WANT TO
KNOW IF ANYONE WAS INSIDE OF
THAT ROOM BEFORE THE SHOOTING
AND AFTER PADDOCK CHECKED IN.
A CHARGER WAS FOUND INSIDE BUT
IT DID NOT MATCH ANY OF HIS CELL
PHONES AND NOW BOSTON POLICE ARE
TAKEK REACTION TO THE RESPONSE
THAT THE GUNMAN SCOUTED
LOCATIONS HERE IN BOSTON.
EXTRA MEASURES WILL BE PUT IN
PLACE AT FENWAY PARK THIS
WEEKEND.
CAROLINE CONNELLY HAS THAT PART
OF THE STORY FROM FENWAY.
>> >> Reporter: ON SUNDAY FENWAY
PARK IS FILLED WITH SOX FANS AND
HEIGHTENED SECURITY.
>> IT BRINGS FEAR.
>> Reporter: A NEW REALITY
GETTING MIXED REVIEWS TODAY.
>> THERE IS NOTHING YOU COULD
DO.
ALL YOU COULD DO IS COME AND
ENJOY YOUR LIVE ■çLIFE.
>> THE GUNMAN RESEARCHED THE
PARK AND NEARBY HOTELS.
>> PEOPLE ARE SAFE.
>> Reporter: THIS WEEKEND THAT
MEANS A BIGGER POLICE PRESENCE
HERE WITH METAL DETECTORS AND
BAG CHECKS, BOSTON POLICE WILL
DO A FULL SWEEP OF THE PARK FOR
KBLOESIVES AND A TACTICAL TEAM
WILL BE INSIDE AND OUTSIDE AND
UNDERCOVER OFFICERS WILL MONITOR
THE CROWDS.
>> EVERY TIME WE HAVE A INCIDENT
WE ADJUST OUR SECURITY PLANS AND
ADJUST OUR POLICING.
>> Reporter: SOX FANS WILL ALSO
HAVE TO ADJUST.
THE SACRIFICE MOST SEEM WILLING
TO MAKE TO CATCH A GAME.
>> JUST MAKES ME MORE DETERMINED
TO COME.
>> Reporter: NOW BOSTON POLICE
HAVE BEEN IN CONSTANT CONTACT
WITH FENWAY PARK AND NEARBY
HOTELS AND AS ALWAYS THEY ARE
ASKING ANYONE COMING TO THE
GAME, IF YOU SEE SOMETHING
SUSPICIOUS, CONTACT POLICE.
OUTSIDE OF FENWAY PARK, I'M
CAROLINE CONNELLY, NBC BOSTON.
>> THANK YOU.
>>> AND WE HAVE MUCH MORE ON THE
LAS VEGAS MASSACRE ON OUR
WEBSITE AND THE NBC BOSTON
MOBILE NEWS APP.
JUST SEARCH LAS VEGAS FOR
LINKEDS TO SUPPORT THE VICTIMS
AND STORIES OF HEROISM AND THOSE
WHO LOST THEIR LIVES.
>>> WE HAVE DEVELOPING NEWS OUT
OF NEW YORK CITY.
A PLOT TO ATTACK CONCERTS AND
LANDMARK.
A LIVE LOOK AT TIMES SQUARE.
THE MEN HAD TALKED ABOUT SETTING
OFF BOMBS THERE AS WELL AS IN
NEW YORK SUBWAY.
THE ALLEGED PLOT WOULD HAVE
TARGETED THE CITY DURING THE
ISLAMIC HOLY MONTH AFTER RAMADAN
IN THE SPRING OF 2016.
ONE OF THE MAN IS A U.S. CITIZEN
AND THE OTHERS ARE FROM CANADA
AND THE PHILIPPINES.
>>> EARL WE WARNING WEATHER AND
THE COLUMBUS DAY WEEK
LIKE WEATHER.
HERE IS PETE BOUCHARD.
>> TODAY IN THE UPPER 70s.
WE MADE IT TO 78 IN BOSTON.
WHEN WAS THAT?
BEFORE WE GOT INTO THE SHOWERS.
PLEASANT EVENING AND COOLISH AND
THE WINDS OUT OF THE SOUTH
SOUTHEAST, THIS IS A
PRODOMINANTLY TROPICAL PATERN
AND A LOT OF HUMIDITY.
SHOWERS ARE JUST ABOUT DOWN.
WE MIGHT SEE A SPRINKLE RUN
THROUGH QUICKLY.
BUT OVER THE HOLIDAY WEEKEND, WE
HAVE THAT THREAT FOR A SHOWER IN
THE MORNING EACH DAY AND OUR
TEMPERATURES DO CLIMB.
BACK TO 80 ON SUNDAY.
MONDAY, THAT DAY, LOOKS A LOT
WETTER.
WE'LL TALK ABOUT THE TIMING ON
THE SHOWERS AND THE LATEST TRACK
ON TROPICAL STORM NATE AS WELL.
STATE TUNED.
>>> THE RED SOX COMING BACK TO
BOSTON DOWN TWO GAMES TO NOTHING
IN THE ALDS.
THE SOX ONCE AGAIN GOT BLOWN OUT
BY THE ASTROS DOWN IN HOUSTON.
THEY HAD EIGHT RUNS IN THE
SECOND STRAIGHT GAME.
SOX STARTER DREW POMERANZ GOT
CHASED OUT OF THE GAME EARLY ON.
GAME THREE IS SUNDAY AT FENWAY
PARK.
THE SOX WILL BE LOOKING TO AVOID
A SWEEP FOR THE SECOND STRAIGHT
YEAR.
>>> AND A FRIGHTENING SCENE AT
MELROSE HIGH SCHOOL.
STUDENTS WITNESS A CLASSMATE
BEING TACKLED BY POLICE AND
POLICE ARE TALKING ABOUT WHAT
SPARKED THAT VIOLENT
CONFRONTATION.
CASSY ARSENAULT HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: A STRESSFUL AND
FRIGHTENING SITUATION AND ONE
STUDENT TELLING ME SHE WAS NEAR
TEARS BUT THE SCHOOL SAID IN
THIS DAY AND AGE THEY CAN'T TAKE
ANY CHANCES.
>> IT IS NOT A DRILL.
>> Reporter: OFFICERS TAKING
DOWN A 16-YEAR-OLD MELROSE HIGH
SCHOOL STUDENT IN THE VIDEO.
>> IT WAS KIND OF SCARY AND I
WAS HAVING A PANIC ATTACK.
>> Reporter: CAUGHT ON CAMERA
FROM A STUDENT'S CELL PHONE
WATCHING FROM A PANIC INSIDE.
>> AND THEN THEY SAID GET AWAY
FROM THE WINDOWS AND EVERYBODY
STARTED TO GET OUT AND START
RUNNING.
>> Reporter: WHAT LED TO THE
MOMENT STARTED WITH AN ALARMING
SCHOOL.
>> THIS INDIVIDUAL HAD MADE
SUGGESTIONS ONLINE THAT HE WAS
EITHER LOOKING FOR A WEAPON --
>> Reporter: IMMEDIATELY SCHOOL
WENT ON LOCKDOWN AND THE STUDENT
BECAME AGITATED WHEN THEY TRIED
TO TALK TO HIM AND THEN THEY
FLED OUT OF THE BUILDING AND TWO
OFFICERS HAD TO WRESTLE HIM TO
THE GROUND AND USE PEPPER SPRAY.
>> WE ARE AT A POINT WHERE
THROWING AROUND THE TERM GUN, WE
HAVE TO RESPOND.
YOU CANNOT DEBATE IT.
>> Reporter: IN THAT SCUFFLE ONE
OF THE OFFICER'S LEG WAS INJURED
AND HE WAS TAKEN TO THE
HOSPITAL.
>> THERE IS NO TIME -- WHERE
STUDENTS SAFETY BEING
COMPROMISED.
>> THE KIDS GET UP SET AND WE
COULD UNDERSTAND BUT WE WOULD
RATHER GO THROUGH THE STRESS
THEN TAKE A CHANCE.
>> THE PARENTS SATISFIED WITH
HOW IT WAS HANDLED BUT
UNSETTLED.
>> IT IS NERVOUS BUT I TRUST
THESE GUYS.
>> Reporter: THAT STUDENT HAS
BEEN ARRAIGNED.
THE SCHOOL TELLS ME THEY CAN'T
EXPEL CHILDREN, THEY ARE
RESPONSIBLE FOR PROVIDING THEM
AN EDUCATION.
THEY MEET ON MONDAY TO DISCUSS
HOW TO PROCEED WITH THIS
STUDENT'S EDUCATION FOR THE REST
OF THE NEAR.
CASSY ARSENAULT, NBC BOSTON.
>>> TONIGHT A DRIVER IS
RECOVERING AFTER BEING INVOLVED
IN A TRACTOR-TRAILER ACCIDENT IN
WESTFORD.
TAKE A LOOK.
SKY RANGER OVER THE SCENE AFTER
THE ACCIDENT.
IT HAPPENED LATE IT MORNING ON
THE MIDDLETON ROAD.
THE TRACTOR-TRAILER WAS ON TOP
OF THE CAR.
THERE IS A DOWNED POWER POLE.
EMERGENCY CREWS COULD NOT RESCUE
THE DRIVER FROM THE CAR FOR
ABOUT 20 MINUTES.
THAT IS BECAUSAL OF THE LIVE
POWER LINES WERE DOWN NEARBY.
THE DRIVER WAS HOSPITALIZED AND
IS EXPECTED TO RECOVER.
>>> AND TONIGHT THERE ARE NEW
DEVELOPMENTS IN A STRING OF
THREATS IN WALTHAM.
PROSECUTORS ARE LIRNG -- LINKING
THE THREAT TO A MAN INVOLVED IN
A CYBER■ç STALKING CASE.
WE HAVE THE LATEST IN BOSTON.
>> CUFFED AND SHACKLED, RYAN LIN
OF NEWTON APPEARED IN FORWARD
COURT CHARGED WITH CYBER
STALKING HIS ROOMMATE IN A
CHILLING YEAR AND I HALF LONG
CAMPAIGN THAT INCLUDED DODS
DOZENS OF LOCAL BOMB THREATS.
HE LIVED WITH THE 24-YEAR-OLD
FEMALE VICTIM AND HER ROOMMATE
IN THE SPRING OF 20 # 16 AFTER
ANSWERING A CRAIG'S LIST AD FOR
A ROOM.
THE COMPLAINT ALLEGED THAT HE
BEGAN ACCESSING THE VICTIM'S
ONLINE ACCOUNT AND PASSWORD AND
HARASSING HER SO INTENTLY SHE
MOVED OUT LESS THAN TWO MONTHS
AFTER HE MOVED IN.
BUT INVESTIGATORS SAY THE CYBER
STALKING AND HARASSMENT DIDN'T
STOP THERE.
HE CREATED AND POSTED ONLINE
FRAUDULENT PROFILES OF THE
VICTIM ON WEBSITES DEDICATED TO
PROSTITUTION, SEXUAL FETISHES
AND OTHER SEXUAL ENCOUNTERS,
CAUSING THREE MEN TO SHOW UP HER
HOME IN SEARCH OF SEXUAL
ACTIVITY.
>>> AUTHORITIES ALLEGE HE WAS
BEHIND DOZENS OF THREATS TO BOMB
OR SHOOT UP SCHOOLS AND DAY CARE
CENTERS IN WALTHAM AND CHELM
FORD, PINNING THOSE ON THE WOMAN
HE WAS CYBER STALKING.
THOSE HAVE WASTED POLICE
RESOURCES AND LEFT PARENTS
UNEASY FOR MONTHS.
>> MY SON, EVERY DAY, IT WAS
SCARY.
>> IT WAS DEFINITELY GOOD TO
KNOW THEY HAVE TARGETED SOMEONE
WHO IS RESPONSIBLE FOR THE
OFFENSE.
>> Reporter: PROSECUTORS SAID
LIN IS BEING INVESTIGATED FOR
SEVERAL OTHER CRIMES.
HE'S BEING HELD WITHOUT BAIL
PENDING A DETENTION HEARING
SCHEDULED FOR WEDNESDAY IN
WORCESTER.
IN SOUTH BOSTON, ALYSHA PALUMBO,
NBC BOSTON.
>>> AND THE PRAYER OF
SPRINGFIELD IS CRITICIZING THE
DECISION TO REMOVE A
CONTROVERSIAL MURAL FROM THE DR.
SEUSS MUSEUM.
THE MUSEUM ANNOUNCED IT WOULD
CHINESE CHARACTER WHICH THREE
AUTHORS CLAIM PERPETUATED A
RACIAL STEREO TYPE.
THEY SAID THEY WOULD BOYCOTT AN
UPCOMING EVENT AND SUS WAS A
NATIVE AND THE MAYOR SAYING THIS
IS WHAT IS WRONG WITH OUR
COUNTRY.
WE HAVE EXTREME FRINGE ON THE
RIGHT AND LEFT DICTATING AGENDA
TO VIVE DIVIDE AND I WOULD ASK
DR. SEUSS ENTERPRISE AND OUR
MOOUX TO RECONSIDER.
>> AND A CAMBRIDGE LINE RAREAB
REJECTED A GIFT OF THE BOOKS
FROM MELANIA TRUMP AND THAT
LIBRARIAN CLAIMED THE BOOK'S
CONTENT WAS RACIALLY INSENSITIVE
AND CONTAINED RACIST PROPAGANDA.
THE MAYOR HAS CALLED BOTH
INSTANCES POLITICAL CORRECTNESS
AT ITS WORST.
>>> AND STILL AT 7:00, A LIVE
STAGE SHOW OF THE HIT CARTOON
P.J. MASKS COMING TO BOSTON.
>>> AND TONIGHT ON THE SCENE,
JACKIE BRUNO GIVES US A SNEAK
PEEK.
>> AND PLUS, LEAVING PUERTO RICO
WITH WET PET, NO WALK IN THE
PARK.
A FAMILY TO GET OUT AND THE
MISSION NOW THAT THEY ARE HERE
IN MASSACHUSETTS.
THE ROAD TO
RECOVERY IN PUERTO
RICO-- INCLUDES NEW
CHALLENGES FOR PET
OWNERS. THAT
>>> WELCOME BACK TO NBC BOSTON.
THE ROAD TO RECOVERY IN PUERTO
RICO INCLUDES NEW CHALLENGES,
INCLUDING FOR PET OWNERS AND
THAT ALSO INVOLVED ONE FAMILY
WHO JUST ARRIVED IN BRAINTREE
AFTER THEY LOST NEARLY
EVERYTHING FROM HURRICANE MARIA.
AND THEY REFUSED TO LEAVE THEIR
BELOVED PET BEHIND.
ABBEY NIEZGODA HAS MORE ON THE
JOURNEY.
>> SUCH A GOOD BOY.
>> Reporter: WHEN IT COMES TO
TRAINING ANIMALS, EXPERT TERRY
HAYWARD HAS LITERALLY WRITTEN
BOOKS ON IT BUT IN THIS EMPTY
APARTMENT SHE IS THE FIRST TO
TELL YOU HOW TO GET HER ANIMALS
HERE.
AFTER A HURRICANE HIT HER HOME
IN PUERTO RICO.
>> WATER STANDS AND WATER COMING
IN THROUGH WINDOWS.
>> Reporter: WITH RESOURCES
DWINDLING AND HER FAMILY IN
MASSACHUSETTS WORRYING.
>> I HAD MY PHONE AT ALL TIMES.
>> Reporter: SHE AND HER HUSBAND
KNEW THIS WAS NO WAY TO KEEP
LIVING.
>> WHAT HAPPENS WHEN THERE ISN'T
ANY MORE WATER OR THE STORES
DON'T GET RESUPPLIED AND THERE
IS NO MORE FOOD.
>> BUT WITH NO VET TO FILE
PAPERWORKS, THEIR ONLY OPTION
WAS CHARTERING A PLANE TO
FLORIDA FOR $18,000.
>> SEVEN ANIMALS AND SEVEN
PEOPLE.
>> Reporter: THEN DRIVING 27
HOURS TO THIS BRAINTREE
APARTMENT.
TERRY IS GRATEFUL TO BE SAFE
WITH HER FOUR-LEGGED FAMILY BUT
CONSTANTLY THINKING OF THE OTHER
PET OWNERS IN PUERTO RICO WHO
AREN'T ABLE TO MAKE THIS KIND OF
JOURNEY.
>> I USED WATER FROM THE TAP TO
GIVE MY DOGS WATER IN THEIR
BOWLS.
I USED THE WASHING MACHINE AND
THE DRYER TO CLEAN MY CLOTHES.
NONE OF THAT IS HAPPENING IN
PUERTO RICO.
>> Reporter: SOON THEY HOPE TO
BE ABLE TO WALK THEIR DOGS BACK
IN PUERTO RICO.
BUT WHILE THEY ARE HERE, THEY
ARE FOCUSED ON RAISING MONEY AND
AWARENESS FOR THE HUMANS AND THE
ANIMALS STILL IN NEED BACK HOME.
IN BRAINTREE, ABBEY NIEZGODA,■ç
NBC BOSTON.
>>> AND REMEMBER, YOU COULD GO
TO THE NBC BOSTON MOBILE NEWS
APP TO GET THE LATEST ON THE
RECOVERY EFFORTS IN PUERTO RICO
AND DETAILS ON YOU HOW DBER ON
HOW YOU COULD HELP.
>>> HOW DO YOU PREPARE STUDENTS
FOR AFTER HIGH SCHOOL.
EDUCATION NATION BUILD THE
FUTURE AND THE TOWN HALL BRINGS
EDUCATION AND GOVERNMENT
BUSINESS LEADERS TOGETHER FROM
BOSTON AND AROUND THE STATE TO
TALK ABOUT A PATH TOWARD HIGHER
EDUCATION AND CAREER
OPPORTUNITIES.
CHIEF EDUCATION CORRESPONDENT
RAHIMA ELLIS WILL MODERATE THE
PANEL DISCUSSION NEXT WEDNESDAY
FROM 6:00 TO 8:00 P.M. AT THE
JFK LIBRARY AND MUSEUM AND FRANK
HOLLAND WILL LEAD THE AUDIENCE
DISCUSSION.
THE ENTIRE FORUM WILL BE LIVE
SCREENS ON EDUCATION NATION.COM
AND LEARN HOW COULD YOU TAKE
PART IN THE LIVE AUDIENCE.
>>> STILL TO COME ON TONIGHT AT
7:00, A LIVE THEATER PRODUCTION
OF THE CARTOON PJ. MASKS IS
COMING TO BOSTON.
>> JACKIE BRUNO IS TAKING US
BEHIND THE SCENES AND SURPRISED
ONE FAMILY.
>>> IT IS ABNORMALLY DRY.
THAT IS THE YELLOW SHADING HERE.
I'LL SHOW YOU HOW WE COULD SOLVE
THAT WITH RAIN BUT JEOPARDIZES
THE HOLIDAY WEEKEND COMING UP
NEXT.
You can't have this Frenchie.
Sam just snagged it from
HomeGoods.
It reminds him of Bennie.
Only quieter.
You can't have this Frenchie.
But new finds are always
arriving.
So you can find something
so you,
for less.
At HomeGoods.
Raise a glass
to Simply Smart from Hood.
It gives you what most low-fat
milks don't.
The rich, creamy taste
you love,
with more of the nutrition
you want.
And less fat and calories
than whole milk.
Simply Smart.
Always Good.
Always Hood.
SEVEN. COLUMBUS DAY
WEEKEND IS HERE.
AND THE FORECAST
>>> WELCOME BACK TO NBC BOSTON
NEWS AT 7:00.
COLUMBUS DAY WEEKEND IS HERE.
>> SO THE FORECAST SHAPING UP TO
BE KIND OF LIKE ■çSUMMER.
HERE IS METEOROLOGIST PETE
BOUCHARD.
IT IS THAT TIME OF THE YEAR
WHERE IT IS SUPPOSED TO COOL
OFF.
>> SUPPOSED TO.
IT IS NOT DOING THAT AT ALL.
MAYBE IN THE EXTENDED RANGE BUT
ONLY BACK TO NORMAL.
HOLIDAY WEEKEND COMING UP, WET
COLUMBUS DAY AND THAT DAY HAS
DOWNPOURS AND TROPICAL IN NATURE
AS AN IN TENSE RAIN.
NORMAL TEMPERATURES WILL FOLLOW
THIS WET PATTERN.
IT IS OKAY THAT WE GET INTO A
WET PATTERN.
IN THE 60s, AFTER HITTING 78.
THE FIRST PART OF THE DAY WAS
DRY.
SECOND HALF GOT INTO THE CLOUDS
AND SPRINKLES.
WAIT UNTIL THE HUMIDITY HITS
TOMORROW.
A WARM FRONT TO THE NORTH OF NEW
YORK CITY.
IT IS A DEW POINT.
AND 66 IN NEW YORK CITY.
THE SPRINKLES HAVE FADED FOR THE
NIGHT.
THE CLOUDS WILL REMAIN AND
THEY'LL BE IN OUR HAIR FOR THE
ENTIRE WEEKEND.
THIS IS A WEATHER FRONT THAT
LIFTS THROUGH TOMORROW MORNING
SO IF YOU ARE THINKING IT IS
DRY, WELL, MOSTLY.
WE'LL SAY THAT.
BUT THERE MIGHT BE A SPRINKLE OR
A RENEGADE SPRINKLE GOING
THROUGH AND THEN IN THE
AFTERNOON WE OPEN UP SUNSHINE
AND THAT IS WHEN WE GET UP INTO
THE MID AND UPPER 70s.
THE WINDS KICKING UP THIS
WEEKEND.
LATE OFTEN SATURDAY AND
ESPECIALLY SUNDAY INTO EARLY
MONDAY.
75 TOMORROW.
72 IN WORCESTER.
MIDDLE 70s SHOULD DO IT.
LOW 70s ON CAPE COD AND THE
TOPSFIELD FAIR ON GOING THROUGH
THE WEEKEND.
MILD AND MANY CLOUDS AROUND
TOMORROW AND ABOUT 75 DEGREES.
AND WE'RE IN THE HUMID AIR.
FEEDING THE SHOWERS ON MONDAY,
THIS IS OVERPLAYED.
THEY ARE NOT THAT ROBUST.
I THINK MAYBE A PASSING SPRINKLE
ON SUNDAY.
UP UNTIL MIDDAY, VERY HUMID.
TROPICAL DOWNPOURS ON MONDAY AND
THAT IS THE ODD MAN OUT.
THE TEMPERATURES KIND OF JUMP UP
AND THEN SLIDE BACK DOWN ONCE
AGAIN.
81 DEGREES ON SUNDAY.
THE RED SOX GAME LOOKING■ç GOOD.
ABOUT 79 BUT WE'LL HIT THE 80
LATER IN THE DAY.
HAZY SUNSHINE GOING OUT TO
CENTER FIELD.
PART OF THE REASONS WE'RE SEEING
THE TROPICAL DOWNPOURS IS THIS,
NATE.
A LOT OF HEAVY RAIN.
BUT THE WINDS NOT ALL THAT
IMPRESSIVE.
MOST OF THESE TO THE EAST OF THE
CENTER OF CIRCULATION.
60 MILES PER HOUR, COULD
STRENGTHEN IN A HURRICANE AS IT
HEADS FOR NEW ORLEANS AND THEN
GOES UP INTO THE DEEP SOUTH AND
AS IT GOES ACROSS THE
APPALACHIANS WEAKENS BUT STILL A
SEMBLANCE OF A STRUCTURE TO GIVE
US THE DOWNPOUR.
A LOT OF HUMIDITY.
WE NEED SOMETHING TO TRIGGER IT
AND NATE WOULD BE JUST WHAT THE
DOCTOR ORDERS.
NOT TO BANISH THE BROUGHT
ALTOGETHER OR THE DRY SPELL.
BUT AT LEAST PUT A GOOD DENT
THERE IT.
AN INCH TO THREE INCHES.
CAREFUL FOR FLASH FLOODING ON
MONDAY FOR THE DOWNPOURS.
PLENTY OF CLOUDS TONIGHT AND 75
TOMORROW WITH THE EARLY CHANCE
FOR A SPRINKLE AND THEN A MIX OF
SUN AND CLOUDS.
DITTO ON SUNDAY, MONDAY.
WASHED OUT IN THE AFTERNOON.
THE TEMPERATURES DO GET BACK TO
NORMAL ON THURSDAY AND FRIDAY.
MAYBE AN OUTSIDE CHANCE OF A
SPRINKLE THERE TOO.
I'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT 11:00.
>> THANK YOU, PETE.
>> AND STAY WITH NBC BOSTON FOR
THE LATEST ON THE HOLIDAY
WEEKEND WEATHER.
NEW ENGLAND'S LARGEST TEAM OF
METEOROLOGIST CONSTANTLY
UPDATING YOUR FORECAST.
YOU COULD FIND THEM ANY TIME ON
FREE NBC BOSTON MOBILE NEWS APP.
>>> TONIGHT ON THE SCENE, THE
HIT CARTOON P.J. MASK HAS BEEN
TURNED INTO A LIVE THEATER
PRODUCTION.
>> AND IT IS COMING TO BOSTON.
JACKIE BRUNO GOT A PREVIEW OF
THE SHOW AND EVEN SURPRISED A
YOUNG FAMILY WITH A SPECIAL MEET
AND GREET.
♪♪
>> P.J. MASK HAVE FLOWN IN THE
BOX CENTER WANG THEATER FOR A
SERIES OF LIVE SHOWS THIS
WEEKEND■ç BUT EARLY ON FRIDAY O
FAMILY GOT TO MEET THE STARS OF
THE SHOW.
>> GOOD MORNING.
>> HI.
>> CAN WE GET SOME HIGH FIVE.
LET'S DO IT.
>> 7-YEAR-OLD COLE AND
5-YEAR-OLD QUINN ARE BROTHER AND
SISTER AND BOTH LOVE. IT J. MASK
BUT FOR COLE THIS WAS SPECIAL.
HE HAS AUTISM BUT HE IS LEARNING
LANGUAGE.
>> HE WILL MEMORIZE IT AND START
SCRIPTING IT ON HIS iPAD AND HIT
PAUSE AND SAY THE LINE AND HIT
PLAY AND THEN THE LINE WILL GO.
SO SOMETIMES WHEN HE'S NOT SURE
WHAT HE WANTS TO SAY, HE TAKES
THOSE LINES FROM THE EPISODES OF
P.J. MASK AND COMMUNICATES WITH
US FOR HIS WANTS AND NEEDS.
>> DO YOU HAVE A FAVORITE COLOR.
>> [ INAUDIBLE ].
>> THE KIDS GOT HIGH FIVE AND A
HUGS AND A PICTURE WITH THE
CAST.
>> I WAS HOLDING BACK TEARS
BECAUSE JUST TO SEE THE
EXCITEMENT AND LOVE IN HIS FACE
AND HIS REACTION HERE.
SO EXCITED.
WAS JUST THE MOST HEARTWARMING
THING.
>> Reporter: THE FAMILY WILL ALL
SEE THE SHOW THIS WEEKEND AND
SINCE THERE ARE STILL TICKETS
AVAILABLE.
SO CAN YOU.
>> THEY COULD EXPECT THEIR HERO
AND BRAND-NEW SONGS THAT WE
WROTE FOR THE SHOW AND TONS OF
AUDIENCE INTERACTION.
>> FOR THE SCENE, JACKIE BRUNO,
NBC BOSTON.
>>> IT LOOKS COOL.
WHEN YOUR KIDS GET OLDER, YOU
HAVE --
>> RIGHT.
>> MY KIDS ARE 14 -- 15 AND 12.
SO I HAVE ASK --
>> IT MAKES YOU FEEL OLD.
>> IT LOOKS GREAT.
I WOULD GO SEE IT.
NOT OLD YET.
>>> STILL TO COME AT 7:00, TBTS
WE ARE GOING■ç BACK IN TIME TO E
RENAISSANCE.
>> COLTON BRADFORD TRYING HIS
HAND AT 16th CENTURY FUN AT KING
RICHARD'S FAIR.
,!SEVEN. TONIGHT
GO BACK IN TIME AT
KING RICHARD'S FAIRE
IN CARVER.
ITS THEL
>>> WELCOME BACK TO NBC BOSTON
NEWS AT 7:00, TONIGHT WE GO BACK
IN TIME AT KING RICHARD'S FAIR
IN CARVER.
>> I'VE BEEN CURIOUS.
THIS IS THE LONGEST RUNNING
FESTIVAL IN NEW ENGLAND.
COLTON BRADFORD HEADS THERE TO
CHECK OUT MEDIEVAL FAMILY FUN.
>> I'M GOING TO TAKE YOU BACK A
FEW CENTURIES RIGHT HERE IN OUR
OWN BACKYARD.
LET'S CHECK OUT KING RICHARD'S
FAIR.
>> HI LADIES.
HOW IS IT GOING.
>> BETTER NOW.
>> I'M SUPPOSED TO MEET THE KING
HERE --
>> WHAT?
>> YOU WANT TO MEET THE KING.
>> I'M SURPRISED TO MEET THE
KING.
>> YOU CAN'T MEET HIM LOOKING
LIKE THAT.
WE HAVE TO SEAMS LIKE A DREAM.
>> GET IN HERE.
>> HOW DID I DO?
>> YEAH.
YOU LOOK WONDERFUL.
>> AM I WORTHY OF THE KING.
>> YES.
>> WE INTRODUCE YOU TO COLTON.
>> WE ARE GOING TO UNITE YOU FOR
YOUR TALKING ABILITY.
KNEEL, SIR.
IN THE FAME OF LORD AND SAINT
GEORGE, I DUB YOU SIR COLTON,
RISE UP.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> NICE TO MEET YOU.
HAVE FUN.
FEEL GOOD.
>> YOUR MAJESTY.
>> COME ON COLTON.■ç
>> WHAT IS THIS HOW DO YOU DO
THAT?
>> DOING SOME IS STRETCHES, THIS
IS THE ONE.
I GOT NONE OF THEM ON THE BOARD.
>> AFTER THE WHOLE KNIFE
THROWING INCIDENT, I FEEL LIKE I
NEED TO GET MY MAN HOOD BACK A
LITTLE BIT.
CAN I BORROW THAT.
THE APPRECIATE IS ON.
YES!
>> I'M LOOKING TO FIGHT, WHICH
ONE OF THESE AM I LOOKING TO
SHOP FOR.
>> THIS IS DEFINITELY NOT
FITTING IN THE BACKSEAT OF MY
HATCHBACK.
IT WILL BE GREAT.
>> EVEN THE RIDES ARE MEDIEVAL.
DON'T DO THIS AFTER DRINKING A
GUINNESS.
>> I'M LOOKING FOR A YOUNG MAN
WHO IS BRAVE.
>> IT LOOKS SO FUN.
>> ESPECIALLY AFTER ALL OF OUR
GAME OF THRONES BINK WATCHING.
>> IT IS SCARY AFTER THAT.
WE'LL SEE YOU TONIGHT AT 11:00.
>> I'M PHIL LIPOF.
>> AND I'M JOY LIM NAKRIN.
ACCESS HOLLYWOOD IS NEXT.