BE FROM THE REVERE FAMILY
OUTHOUSE WHICH DATES BACK TO THE
17th CENTURY.
IT'S THE FIFTH OLDEST HOUSE IN
THE CITY.
THANKS FOR JOINING US TONIGHT,
EVERYONE.
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH LESTER
HOLT IS LIVE TONIGHT FROM
SAVANNAH, GEORGIA.
IT BEGINS RIGHT NOW.
>>> TONIGHT, ISLAND
EMERGENCY, MILLIONS
RAPIDLY RUNNING LOW ON
FOOD AND WATER IN
SWELTERING HEAT.
GROWING FEARS OF MASS
EXODUS FROM PUERTO
RICO AS PRESIDENT
TRUMP DEFENDS HIS
ADMINISTRATION'S
RESPONSE.
FLATLINE, GOP'S LAST
EFFORT TO REPEA
OBAMACARE IS NOW DEAD
AND EYES TURN TO
ALABAMA, AND INSURGENT
CANDIDATE.
CEO OF EQUIFAX IS OUT
AS MANY STRUGGLE TO
FREEZE CREDIT.
BASKETBALL BRIBERY
SCANDAL ROCKED BIGGEST
UNIVERSITIES IN
AMERICA.
AND THE RESCUE, A
GROOM WHO SAVED THE
DAY.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>> Announcer: THIS IS
"NBC NIGHTLY NEWS"
WITH LESTER HOLT,
RECORDING TONIGHT FROM
SAVANNAH, GEORGIA.
>> GOOD EVENING FROM
THE 165th AIR LIFT
WING.
MAKING WAY BACK FROM
PUERTO RICO, STOPPING
IN SAVANNAH WHERE THE
NATIONAL GUARD
CONTINUES TO LAUNCH
ROUND THE CLOCK RELIEF
FLIGHTS INTO THE
HURRICANE ZONE.
PUERTO RICO IS WHERE
WE START TONIGHT AS
ITS GOVERNOR WARNS OF
IMPENDING HUMANITARIAN
KRIES S, ISSUES A PLEA
FOR MORE HELP,
REMINDING US THEY'RE
AMERICANS IN NEED.
PRESIDENT TRUMP IS
SPEAKING OUT AND
DEFENDING HIS RESPONSE
TO THE DISASTER THAT'S
LEFT THE ISLAND MOSTLY
IN THE DARK, SHORT ON
FOOD, CLEAN WATER,
CASH AND RELIABLE
COMMUNICATIONS.
GABE GUTIERREZ REMAINS
THERE WITH THE LATEST.
>> Reporter:
TEMPERATURES
APPROACHED 100 DEGREES
TODAY.
A STIFLING HEAT.
NEARLY 12,000 PEOPLE
STILL IN EMERGENCY
SHELTERS AND HALF OF
PUERTO RICO DOESN'T
HAVE DRINKING WATER AS
ARMY CORP. OF
ENGINEERS IS NOW
TASKED WITH REBUILDING
THE ISLAND'S POWER
GRID.
TONIGHT IN PUERTO
RICO, LINES ARE LONG
AND TEMPERS SHORT.
>> I NEED TO GET OUT
OF HERE.
WHY?
BECAUSE WE FEEL
DESPERATE.
NOT JUST ME, SCARY
SITUATION.
>> Reporter: IN THE
AIRPORT, EXODUS ON FEW
FLIGHTS.
RUNNING LOW ON BABY
FORMULA AND
FRANTICALLY TRYING TO
ESCAPE TO FLORIDA.
>> IT'S A NIGHTMARE,
NOT WHERE I PLANNED TO
BE OR WANTED TO BE
DURING FIRST FEW WEEKS
OF MY BABY'S LIFE.
>> Reporter: TODAY
PRESIDENT TRUMP
ANNOUNCED HE WOULD
VISIT PUERTO RICO NEXT
WEEK AND DEFENDED
FEDERAL RESPONSE.
>> WE GOT A PLUSES ON
TEXAS AND FLORIDA AND
WILL ON PUERTO RICO
BUT THIS IS AN ISLAND
IN MIDDLE OF THE
OCEAN.
>> Reporter:
ANNOUNCING THOUSANDS
OF ADDITIONAL TROOPS
AND NAVY SHIP HEADED
TO THE ISLAND.
SAN JUAN'S MAYOR
APPRECIATES FEMA's
RESPONSE BUT LOT OF
RED TAPE.
>> BOOTS ON THE
GROUND.
BUT YOU HAVE TO START
WALKING.
SEEMS TO BE TAKING A
LITTLE BIT TOO LONG.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
ALSO TWEETING BECAUSE
OF THE INFRASTRUCTURE
AND MASSIVE DEBT,
PUERTO RICO IS IN DEEP
TROUBLE.
DIDN'T SET WELL WITH
PUERTO RICANS WHO FEEL
THE U.S. TERRITORY IS
AN AFTERTHOUGHT.
NOW MOST HOSPITALS AT
STAND STILL ON BACKUP
GENERATORS.
NOT ENOUGH POWER FOR
CRITICAL SURGERIES.
>> ONLY ONE AVAILABLE.
ALL THE OTHER AREAS
ARE WITHOUT
ELECTRICITY.
PROBLEM IS HUMIDITY IS
TOO HIGH TO WORK.
>> Reporter: HELP ON
THE WAY.
MORE THAN 90
HUMANITARIAN SUPPLIES
ON THE WAY.
THESE FROM THE DALLAS
MAVERICKS AND POINT
GUARD CORA.
>> TAKES TIME TO GET
BACK TO NORMAL.
>> Reporter: SAN JUAN,
PUERTO RICO.
>> IN SOME REMOTE
PARTS OF PUERTO RICO
CRIES FOR HELP WRITTEN
ON ROOFTOPS.
FAMILIES DESPERATE FOR
AID.
>> MIGHT BE STUCK IN
AREA THEY JUST CAN'T
LEAVE.
>> HELICOPTERS GETTING
AID TO REMOTE AREAS
LIKE HERE WHERE
EIGHT-YEAR-OLD SAYS
HER FAMILIES NEED
SUPPLIES.
WORRIED ABOUT
GRANDPARENTS SHE
HASN'T HEARD FROM IN
DAYS.
>> I HOPE YOU ARE
FINE.
AND I LOVE YOU.
>> THIS CHOPPER CREW
ALSO RESPONSIBLE FOR
PREVENTING MAJOR
ENVIRONMENTAL
CATASTROPHE AS NEARBY
OIL RIG DAMAGED BY
HURRICANE.
>> IF HAD HIT PUERTO
RICO HOW BAD COULD
THINGS HAVE GOTTEN?
>> PRETTY BAD, WOULD
HAVE HAD OIL SPILL.
>> ONE OF THE
COUNTLESS MISSIONS,
AMERICAN SOLDIERS
PROTECTING THEIR
ISLAND, LOOKING FOR
MORE PEOPLE TO SAVE.
PUERTO RICO.
>>> ROUGH DAY FOR
REPUBLICANS IN
WASHINGTON AND COULD
BE A ROUGH NIGHT.
LAST DITCH EFFORT TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE IS
NOW DEAD.
SHORT OF VOTES FORCED
TO PULL THE BILL
BEFORE ANOTHER
EMBARRASSING FAILURE
ON THE SENATE FLOOR.
ATTENTION TURNS TO
CLIFF HNGER ELECTION
IN ALABAMA, PRESIDENT
TRUMP'S PREFERRED
CANDIDATE VERSUS
INSURGENT WHO COULD
CAUSE TROUBLES FOR
REPUBLICAN LEADERS.
>> Reporter:
REPUBLICANS IN DEFEAT.
CALLING OFF VOTE TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE.
PRESIDENT LET DOWN
AGAIN.
>> WE'RE DISAPPOINTED
AT CERTAIN SO-CALLED
REPUBLICANS.
>> Reporter: ANOTHER
EMBARRASSING DEFEAT
FOR MAJORITY LEADER
MITCH McCONNELL.
TRIED AND FAILED TWICE
TO FOLLOW THROUGH ON
CAMPAIGN PROMISE.
>> WOULD YOU SAY THIS
IS A TOUGH DAY?
>> WE HAVEN'T GIVEN UP
ON CHANGING THE
AMERICAN HEALTH CARE
SYSTEM.
>> Reporter: BUT THE
REALITY, HEALTH CARE
IS ON THE BACK BURNER.
STARTING TOMORROW, TAX
REFORM.
LAST HOPE FOR MAJOR
REPUBLICAN
ACCOMPLISHMENT.
>> WILL REPUBLICANS
FORGIVE YOU IF YOU
PASS TAX REFORM?
>> MOST IMPORTANT
THING TO DO TO RESTORE
CONFIDENCE TO THE
COUNTRY AND GET JOBS
AND PROSPERITY.
THAT'S WHY FOCUSED ON
GETTING IT DONE.
>> Reporter: IF THEY
CAN'T, COULD HAUNT
THEM.
ELECTION TONIGHT IN
ALABAMA COULD BE FIRST
TASTE.
>> DON'T BE FOOLED,
HELP TRUMP DRAIN THE
SWAMP, VOTE NO TO
LUTHER STRANGE.
>> Reporter:
ESTABLISHMENT GROUPS
SPENDING MONEY TO GET
LUTHER STRANGE.
PRESIDENT EVEN
CAMPAIGNED FOR HIM.
BUT CONSERVATIVE JUDGE
MOORE AHEAD IN THE
POLLS.
CALLED HIMSELF THE
BIGGEST THREAT TO
ESTABLISHMENT POWER IN
WASHINGTON AND SOME
VOTERS BELIEVE HE'S
BETTER DEFENDER OF
PRESIDENT TRUMP.
>> NEED TO GET BEHIND
OUR PRESIDENT AND
LISTEN TO US.
WE'RE FED UP AND WE'LL
VOTE YOU OUT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
ANOTHER REPUBLICAN IS
TAKING HIMSELF OUT OF
THE RUNNING.
SENATOR BOB CORKER OF
TENNESSEE ANNOUNCING
HE WON'T RUN FOR
RE-ELECTION NEXT YEAR.
HE'S A CLOSE FRIEND OF
MITCH McCONNELL'S AND
ANOTHER SIGN OF HOW
TOXIC THINGS ARE IN
WASHINGTON RIGHT NOW.
>>> TONIGHT HEARING
FOR THE FIRST TIME
DISTURBING DETAILS
FROM PARENTS OF OTTO
WARNBEER, FIRST
INTERVIEW OF WHAT
HAPPENED TO THEIR SON
IN CAPTIVITY IN NORTH
KOREA, WHAT HE ENDURED
COMING HOME IN COMA
WHERE HE PASSED AWAY
DAYS LATER.
>> Reporter: PRESIDENT
TRUMP TODAY WITH MORE
HARSH WORDS AGAINST
NORTH KOREA, SAYING
PREPARED TO USE
MILITARY FORCE IF
NECESSARY.
>> IF WE TAKE THAT
OPTION IT WILL BE
DEVASTATING, I CAN
TELL YOU THAT.
DEVASTATING FOR NORTH
KOREA, THAT'S CALLED
THE MILITARY OPTION.
IF WE HAVE TO TAKE IT,
WE WILL.
>> Reporter: AS
TENSIONS ESCALATE,
HORRIFYING ACCOUNT
FROM PARENTS REVEALING
HOW SON WAS TORTURED
IN 17 MONTHS IN NORTH
KOREAN PRISON.
SENT HOME IN COMA.
>> HAD A SHAVED HEAD,
FEEDING TUBE COMING
OUT OF HIS NOSE,
STARING BLANKLY INTO
SPACE, JERKING
VIOLENTLY, BLIND,
DEAF.
AS WE LOOKED AT HIM,
TRIED TO COMFORT HIM,
LOOKED LIKE SOMEONE
HAD TAKEN A PAIR OF
PLIERS AND REARRANGED
HIS BOTTOM TEETH.
>> Reporter: HE DIED
DAYS LATER.
SUPPOSED CRIME,
STEALING A SOUVENIR.
FRED AND CINDY
SPEAKING ABOUT HOW THE
REGIME DESTROYED THEIR
22-YEAR-OLD SON.
>> THEY KIDNAPPED
OTTO, TORTURED HIM.
>> NORTH KOREAN
MENACE.
>> Reporter: DESPITE
ANGRY WORDS AND NEW
SANCTIONS, SECRETARY
OF STATE SAYING THE
GOAL IS DIPLOMATIC
SOLUTION AND PENTAGON
SEEING SIGNS OF
MILITARY THREAT.
>> WE HAVEN'T SEEN A
CHANGE IN POSTURE, WE
WATCH THAT CLOSELY.
>> Reporter: SHOWDOWN
WITH ROGUE REGIME AND
FOR ONE FAMILY,
ALREADY A HORRIFIC
TRAGEDY.
NBC NEWS NEW YORK.
>>> NEW DEVELOPMENTS
IN THE MASSIVE EQUIFAX
HACK THAT COMPROMISED
PERSONAL INFORMATION
OF 143 MILLION
AMERICANS.
COMPANY CEO IS
STEPPING DOWN A WEEK
BEFORE SCHEDULED TO
APPEAR BEFORE CONGRESS
TO ANSWER QUESTIONS.
MEANWHILE PLENTY OF
CONFUSION AMONG
AMERICANS WONDERING
HOW TO PROTECT
THEMSELVES.
MORE FROM TOM
COSTELLO.
>> Reporter: LESS THAN
THREE WEEKS AFTER
ANNOUNCING LARGEST
FINANCIAL DATA BREACH
IN HISTORY, CEO
RICHARD SMITH RESIGNED
TODAY, ALTHOUGH
KEEPING $18 MILLION IN
PENSION BENEFITS AND
POSSIBLY $30 MILLION
IN STOCK OPTIONS.
TWO OTHER SENIOR EXECS
HAVE ALREADY LEFT.
EXPECTING TO GET AN
EARFUL ON CAPITOL HILL
NEXT WEEK.
>> IT'S NOT ENOUGH.
>> Reporter: A CASCADE
OF FEDERAL AND FOUR
STATE INVESTIGATIONS.
>> GOING TO GET TO
BOTTOM OF HOW THE
BREACH OCCURRED, WHEN
IT OCCURRED AND
HOLDING EQUIFAX
ACCOUNTABLE FOR
ACTIONS SINCE THE
BREACH.
>> Reporter: CONSUMER
EXPERTS URGE ALL
ADULTS TO FREEZE
CREDIT REPORTS AT ALL
THREE AGENCIES SO THEY
HAVES CAN'T USE IT.
BUT AMERICANS STRUGGLE
TO GET IT DONE OVER
THE PHONE OR ONLINE.
SOME BLOCKED BY ERROR
MESSAGES.
>> AT WHAT POINT WILL
WE SEE A SOLUTION?
>> Reporter: EQUIFAX
HACK AND WALL STREET
REGULATOR HACK HAVE
EXPERTS ISSUING RED
ALERT.
>> THIS ABSOLUTELY
UNDERMINES FUNDAMENTAL
PILLARS THAT MAKE OUR
SYSTEM WORK.
>> Reporter: WANT TO
KNOW IF LAX SECURITY
WAS TO BLAME.
WHY A PATCH IN MARCH
WHEN FIRST ALERTED
RATHER THAN JULY AND
WHY TAKE SIX WEEKS TO
NOTIFY CUSTOMERS?
>> IN SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA,
FAST-MOVING WILDFIRE
FORCED MORE THAN 1,000
FROM HOMES.
CORONA, JUST OUTSIDE
OF LOS ANGELES, HAS
EVERYBODY ON EDGE.
ALL ADDING TO THE MOST
EXPENSIVE FIRE SEASON
IN HISTORY.
MIGUEL ALMAGUER IS
THERE.
>> Reporter: THIS IS
THE SIGHT AND SOUND OF
LOSING GROUND IN LOS
ANGELES.
SANTA ANA WINDS
TURNING FIRE INTO A
BLOW TORCH BEFORE
SUNRISE IN CORONA.
>> IT'S SCARY.
FREAKS YOU OUT KNOWING
IT'S SO CLOSE.
>> EVACUATE.
>> 1,500 PEOPLE IN
SCRAMBLE TO ESCAPE THE
FLAMES CLOSING IN.
500 HOMES IN PATH OF
THE FIRE.
FREEWAYS AND ROADS
LEADING TO SAFETY
SURROUNDED BY THE
BLAZE.
KNOWN AS THE CANYON
FIRE, 25-MILE-AN-HOUR
WINDS WHIP THROUGH THE
DRY HILLS, FUNNELING
FLAMES LIKE A RIVER
TOWARDS HOMES.
NONSTOP AIR ATTACK,
HELICOPTERS USING
NIGHT VISION SOARING
INTO NEIGHBORHOODS.
WITH SOUTHERN
CALIFORNIA NOW
BEGINNING SANTA ANA
WIND SEASON, THE MOST
DANGEROUS WEEKS ARE
AHEAD.
BUT FIRE SEASON HAS
ALREADY COST A RECORD
$2 BILLION AND NOW THE
FIRE FIGHT IS GETTING
MORE DANGEROUS HERE
EVERY DAY AND EVERY
NIGHT.
NBC NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> TURNING OVERSEAS
TO THE MIDDLE EAST,
THERE IS A BIG CHANGE
COMING TO WAY OF LIFE
IN SAUDI ARABIA.
MAJOR VICTORY FOR
WOMEN'S RIGHTS THERE.
FIRST TIME EVER, WOMEN
LEGALLY ABLE TO DRIVE
THERE FOLLOWING A
ROYAL DECREE.
MORE ON THE MOVE THAT
CRITICS SAY WAS A LONG
TIME COMING.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
SAUDI WOMEN WHO FOUGHT
FOR RIGHT TO DRIVE ARE
CELEBRATING.
WILL NEVER BE THE SAME
ONE TWEETED, RAIN
BEGINS WITH SINGLE
DROP.
ARRESTED AFTER POSTING
THIS VIDEO OF HERSELF
BEHIND THE WHEEL.
IN 2017, SAUDI ARABIA
STILL HAD A BAN ON
WOMEN DRIVING CARS.
ONLY COUNTRY IN THE
WORLD TO DO SO.
PENALTY, FINES,
FLOGGING, FOR SOME
WOMEN JAIL TIME.
HAD BEEN JUSTIFIED BY
THE GOVERNMENT UNDER
STRICT ISLAMIC LAW
♪ NO WOMAN NO DRIVE ♪
>> Reporter: ACTIVISTS
PUSHING FOR CHANGE SAY
BEEN GAINING GROUND.
LIMITED VOTING RIGHTS
IN 2015, LAST WEEKEND
ALLOWED IN NATIONAL
STADIUM FIRST TIME AND
TODAY THIS SURPRISE
ANNOUNCEMENT.
>> A ROYAL DECREE HAS
BEEN ISSUED IN SAUDI
ARABIA, GIVING WOMEN
THE RIGHT TO DRIVE.
>> Reporter: CHANGE
WILL TAKE EFFECT IN
JUNE OF NEXT YEAR.
GIVING ULTRA
CONSERVATIVE COUNTRY
TIME TO ADJUST TO
HAVING A WOMAN IN THE
DRIVER'S SEAT.
NBCSN NEWS.
>>> MORE TO COME.
BRIBERY SCANDAL
ROCKING COLLEGE
BASKETBALL.
FBI ARRESTING NUMBER
OF COACHES FOR FRAUD
AND CORRUPTION.
>>> CAUGHT ON CAMERA,
GROOM
♪♪
AND CORRUPTION.
>>> CAUGHT ON CAMERA,
GROOM
♪ I'm...
I'm so in love with you. ♪
♪ Whatever you want to do... ♪
♪ ...is alright with me. ♪
♪ Ooo baby let's... ♪
♪ ...let's stay together... ♪
Hey!
Are you taking the tissue test?
Yep, and my teeth are yellow.
Time for Whitestrips.
Crest Whitestrips whiten...
...25x better than a leading
whitening toothpaste.
Nice smile!
Thanks! I crushed
the tissue test.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
Every day
people are fighting
type 2 diabetes...
with Fitness...
Food...
And the pill that
starts with F.
FARXIGA, along with
diet and exercise,
helps lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms
of a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA
if you have severe
kidney problems,
are on dialysis,
or have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary tract
infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and
call your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis
which is serious
and may lead to death.
Ask your doctor about
the pill that starts with F
and visit FARXIGA.com
for savings.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may
be able to help.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH THE SCANDAL
SENDING SHOCK WAVES
THROUGH THE WORLD OF
COLLEGE BASKETBALL.
FBI ARRESTING
ASSISTANT COACHES FOR
ALLEGED BRIBERY
SCHEMES AND
INFLUENCING STUDENT
ATHLETES.
ANNE THOMPSON WITH THE
CHARGES.
>> Reporter: THIS IS
THE DARK UNDERBELLY OF
COLLEGE BASKETBALL SAY
PROSECUTORS, ARRESTED
FOUR PROMINENT
COACHES.
EVANS, RICHARDSON
ALONG WITH SIX OTHERS.
CHARGES INCLUDE
BRIBERY, CONSPIRACY
AND FRAUD.
CASE BUILT ON HUNDREDS
OF WIRE TAPS AND
VIDEOTAPES, ALLEGING
NUMEROUS INSTANCES OF
BRIBES.
SAY AGENTS AND
ADVISERS PAY THE
COACHES TO PRESSURE
PLAYERS AND FAMILIES
TO SIGN WITH THEM WHEN
PLAYER TURNS PRO.
>> SHOW LITTLE REGARD
FOR PLAYER'S
WELL-BEING.
>> Reporter: BRAG, CAN
MOLD THE PLAYERS AND
PUT THEM IN LAP OF YOU
GUYS.
DELGADO FUNNELED UP TO
DOLLARS TO FAMILIES TO
ATTEND UNIVERSITIES
SPONSORED BY THE
COMPANY.
INCLUDING BUT NOT
NAMED UNIVERSITY OF
LOUISVILLE.
>> ALL CONTRIBUTE TO
PAY TO PLAY THAT
DOESN'T BELONG IN
COLLEGE BASKETBALL.
>> Reporter: NCAA SAYS
IT HAS NO TOLERANCE
FOR THIS ALLEGED
BEHAVIOR.
BUT REFORMING A SPORT
WHICH GENERATES A
BILLION DOLLARS FROM
MARCH MADNESS IS LONE
IS UNLIKELY SAYS
SPORTS WRITER JOHN
FEINSTEIN.
>> SCHOOLS ARE MAKING
SO MUCH MONEY, DON'T
WANT TO CHANGE THINGS.
WANT TO PRETEND THAT
COLLEGE ATHLETICS ARE
CLEAN.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
ALL THE COACHES ARE
SUSPENDED AND THEY
INVESTIGATE THE
FLAGRANT FOULS
TAINTING THE GAME.
NBC NEWS NEW YORK.
>>> BACK IN A
Diabetes can be
a daily struggle,
even if you're
trying your best.
Along with diet
and exercise,
once-daily Toujeo® may help
you control your blood sugar.
Get into a daily groove.
♪ Let's groove tonight. ♪
♪ Share the spice of life. ♪
♪ Baby, slice it right. ♪
From the makers of Lantus®,
♪ We're gonna groove tonight. ♪
Toujeo® provides blood
sugar-lowering activity
for 24 hours and beyond,
proven blood sugar control
all day and all night,
and significant
A1C reduction.
Toujeo® is used to control
high blood sugar in adults
with diabetes.
It contains 3 times
as much insulin
in 1 milliliter as
standard insulin.
Don't use Toujeo® to treat
diabetic ketoacidosis,
during episodes
of low blood sugar
or if you're
allergic to insulin.
Get medical help right away
if you have a serious
allergic reaction
such as body rash
or trouble breathing.
Don't reuse needles
or share insulin pens.
The most common side
effect is low blood sugar,
which can be
life threatening.
It may cause shaking,
sweating, fast heartbeat,
and blurred vision.
Check your blood
sugar levels daily.
Injection site
reactions may occur.
Don't change your
dose of insulin
without talking
to your doctor.
Tell your doctor about
all your medicines
and medical conditions.
Check insulin label
each time you inject.
Taking TZDs with
insulins, like Toujeo®,
may cause heart failure
that can lead to death.
Find your rhythm and
keep on grooving.
♪ Let's groove tonight. ♪
Ask your doctor about Toujeo®.
♪ Share the spice of life. ♪
I'm Vern, the Orange Money
retirement rabbit, from Voya.
I'm the money you save for
retirement.
Who's he?
He's green money, for spending
today.
Makes it easy to tell you apart.
That, and I am better looking.
I heard that.
When it's time to get organized
for retirement, it's time to get
Voya.
Big news from Advil,
Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
Our first concentrated pill
that rushes powerful relief.
A small new size that's fast,
cause it's liquid.
Woohoo!
You'll ask, what pain?
New Advil Liqui-Gels Minis.
is is Not this John Smith.ith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
>>> LOOKS LIKE A BIG
CHANGE IS COMING FOR
SOCIAL MEDIA USERS
AFTER YEARS OF
LIMITING TWEETS TO 140
CHARACTERS, TWITTER IS
TESTING OUT 280
CHARACTERS, DOUBLE THE
CURRENT LIMIT.
IF YOU'RE ON TWITTER
AND ALWAYS RUN OUT OF
ROOM TO FINISH YOUR
THOUGHT OR ADD EXTRA
EMOJI, MAY BE IN LUCK.
>>> IN WEDDING AFTER
COUPLE SAID I DO,
GROOM NOTICED A CHILD
IN DANGER, JUMPED INTO
ACTION, FANCY SUIT AND
ALL.
WEDDING PHOTOGRAPHER
CAUGHT IT ALL ON
CAMERA.
>> Reporter: WHEN
BRITTANY AND CLAYTON
TIED THE KNOT, FIRST
BIG LEAP.
SECOND COMES LATER.
>> I LOOK OVER AND SEE
CLAY IN THE WATER AND
THINK WHAT IS HE
DOING?
>> Reporter: GROOM
JUMPED INTO A RIVER TO
SAVE A YOUNG BOY HE
DIDN'T EVEN KNOW.
>> IT WAS SCARY.
I WAS A LITTLE BIT
SHOCKED MYSELF.
I WENT OVER THERE, HIS
FACE UNDER WATER.
HE WAS FIGHTING.
>> Reporter: NEWLY
WEDS POSING FOR PHOTOS
IN THE PARK.
NOTICED HIM STRUGGLING
AFTER APPARENTLY
PUSHED IN BY ANOTHER
KID.
>> I GRABBED HIM LIKE
THIS AND JUST HUCKED
HIM UP.
>> Reporter:
UNCONVENTIONAL WEDDING
IMAGES CAPTURED BY
DARREN HAPP.
>> WHEN I REALIZED
WHAT WAS GOING ON, HE
HAD SAVED THE DAY.
>> QUITE THE MARRIAGE
MEMORY, FOR BETTER OR
WORSE, RICHER OR
POORER, DRIER OR
WETTER.
NBC NEWS.
>>> ST. LOUIS CARDINAL
FAN GOT CLOSER TO THE
ACTION THAN HE
BARGAINED FOR WHEN
PLAYER SPILLED HIS
NACHOS WHEN DIVING IN
TO CATCH A FOUL BALL
BUT RUSSELL MADE
AMENDS.
NOW CHANGED HIS HANDLE
ON SOCIAL MEDIA TO
NACHOMAN.
>>> NATIONAL GUARDSMEN
ANSWERING THE CALL FOR
HELP IN STORM-RAVAGED
PUERTO RICO.
>> Announcer: BROUGHT
TO YOU BY
♪♪
Some moments can
change everything.
You can't always predict them,
but you can game plan for them.
For 150 years,
generations of families
have chosen Pacific Life
for retirement and
life insurance solutions
to help them reach their goals.
Being ready for wherever
life leads.
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask a financial advisor
about Pacific Life.
I will never
Never
Wash my hair again
Now, I fuel it
Pantene is the first shampoo and
conditioner system with active
Pro-V nutrient blends that
Fuel 100% stronger hair.
Because Strong is Beautiful.
Needles.
Essential for vinyl,
but maybe not for people with
rheumatoid arthritis.
Because there are options.
Like an "Unjection™".
XELJANZ XR.
A once daily pill for adults
with moderate to severe RA
for whom methotrexate
did not work well.
XELJANZ XR can reduce pain,
swelling and further
joint damage,
even without methotrexate.
XELJANZ XR can lower your
ability to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma
and other cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ XR
if you have an infection.
Tears in the stomach
or intestines,
low blood cell counts
and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels
have happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you start
and while taking XELJANZ XR,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you
were in a region
where fungal infections
are common
and if you have had TB,
hepatitis B or C,
or are prone to infections.
Needles.
A must for vinyl.
But for you,
one pill a day
may provide symptom relief.
Ask your doctor
about XELJANZ XR.
An "Unjection™".
Your brain changes
as you get older.
But Prevagen helps your brain
with an ingredient
originally discovered...
in jellyfish.
In clinical trials,
Prevagen has been shown
to improve short-term memory.
Prevagen. The name to remember.
We come into this world
needing others.
♪ ♪
Then we are told
it's braver to go it alone.
♪ ♪
But there is another
way to live.
♪ ♪
A way that sees the only
path to fulfillment-
is through others.
♪ ♪
>>> A C-130 ON THE
RAMP HERE IN SAVANNAH
AWAITING ITS NEXT
MESSAGE.
BEFORE WE GO, MY TIME
ON THE GROUND IN
PUERTO RICO WAS SHORT
BUT DON'T HAVE TO BE
THERE LONG TO
UNDERSTAND THE DEPTH
OF THE NEED.
ESSENTIAL THINGS IN
LIFE FROM MAKING A
CALL TO BUYING A
GALLON OF GAS TO
GETTING ENOUGH FOOD
AND WATER ARE A
STRUGGLE THERE.
BRINGS ME TO THE
NATIONAL GUARD, WE
TRAVELED WITH INTO THE
HURRICANE ZONE.
SOME FULL TIME AND
SOME PART-TIME
GUARDSMEN BUT ALL
ANSWERING THE CALL TO
DELIVER ESSENTIALS TO
FELLOW AMERICANS IN
NEED.
WE KNOW THE PEOPLE OF
PUERTO RICO ARE
GRATEFUL AND WE'RE
GRATEFUL TO THE AIR
NATIONAL GUARD.
THANKS FOR BEING HERE.
THANK YOU ALL FROM
BEING HERE AS WELL.
165th AIR LIFT WING IN