COMES WHEN I'M ABLE TO SEE
SOMETHING THAT NO ONE ELSE'S
GENIUS WHEN I SEE THAT
UNUSUAL ACTIVITY I HIT IT AND
I HAD A HARD FAST MONEY IS
AMERICA'S MOST MARKETS GO
FAST MONEY WITH THESE FIVE
EASTERN ON CNBC DON'T DO IT
FOR THE BODY TO DO IT FOR
THE LOVE OF THE GAME DICTATED
THE GAME. THE MONEY WILL
FOLLOW THE BUSINESS MODEL AND
WE DON'T DISRUPT WE FOCUS ON
THE MOVIE THE EXPONENTIAL
GROWTH WE'VE DONE FROM JUST
SIXTEEN THOUSAND CUSTOMERS TO
THE DOWNLOADS IN JUST TWELVE
MONTHS THE MONEY AND WERE
CENTERS OF INNOVATION IN
TERMS OF FUNDING IN TERMS OF
USAGE AND EVERYTHING GROWING
HE'S GREAT FOR THE LAST
THREE YEARS IN THE PRECEDING
FOURTEEN YEARS WITH TWO
HUNDRED AND SIXTY MILLION
ONLINE USERS AND SEVEN
HUNDRED BILLION MOBILE
CONNECTIONS SOUTHEAST ASIA IS
SEEN AS THE NEXT PROMISING
MARKET FOR TECH STARTUPS AS
COMPANIES LIKE CRAP. GO CHECK
THE SUNDAY AND TOGO PG A BAG
MORE FUNDING RAMPED UP
OPERATIONS IN THE REGION
LOOKS LIKE FOR OPPORTUNITIES
COMPETITION AND INVESTMENT
FROM GIANT CHECK PLEASE WAIT
FOR BUSINESS OR ABOUT
COMPETITION THE OCEAN NOWHERE
IN THIS WORLD THERE'S NO
COMPETITION YET TO GET USE TO
USE SOUTHEAST ASIA GOING TO
BE THE NEXT BATTLEGROUND FOR
TECH STARTUPS AND THEIR
INVESTORS A DISCUSSION WITH
OUR PAL JOEL NEO FOUNDER OF
THE FORMER HEAD OF GROUP ON A
SHOW TO SIT HIM CIGAR CEO OF
ONLINE BUSH REPUB WARM UP
THE FRENCH LUCAS' NEW CO
FOUNDER AND CHIEF TECHNOLOGY
OFFICER OF COVERS OH AND
BILLY LAURI A FOUNDING
PARTNER OF GOLDEN GATE
VENTURES. THIS IS THE CNBC
DEBATE WITH YOUR MOST ECO
FUJITA THE YEAR THE EAGLES
LOST THE STUDY SHOWED THAT
THE DIGITAL ECONOMY ITS
REGION IS EXPECTED TO GROSS
IT'S FULL OF TWO HUNDRED
BILLION DOLLARS BY TWO
THOUSAND THE TWO THOUSAND AND
FIFTEEN THE NUMBERS WERE JUST
OVER THIRTY BILLION DOLLARS
SO THE QUESTIONS ALL OF YOU
WHERE YOU THINK WE ARE IN
THAT BROADER TIME WE ORDER
MORE OF YOUR TIME
THE RECESSION SEE THE POINT
THAT THE SAUDIS ISSUES THAT
ARE VERY EXCITED. SIX HUNDRED
PEOPLE ARE MORE THAN I DID
NOT SOON ON THE INTERNET AND
OVER THE NEXT FEW YEARS TO
COME ON MY SHOE. ALTHOUGH IN
GENERAL BE IN THE VERY
EXCITING SEE THE BIG FUSS BUT
IT IS I'M ALL FOR IT
ESPECIALLY FOR NEWCOMERS FOR
THE SIX MONTHS. THIS IS
THE TIME THE HOW WHY WOULDN'T
WE WERE GOING TO GET THEIR
BUTTS WONDER WHAT ALL OF US
TO A FEW YEARS AGO THE FIRST
LAST FIVE YEARS. WE GOT WHAT
I THINK THE STRIPES ARE FROM
LOGISTICS AS SAFE FROM
THE BIRDS INSIDE THE BOMBERS
ONTO THE PAVEMENT WITH BRODY
AT RIGHT NOW IS JUST STARTING
TO ENABLE WHAT THE NEXT
GENERATION OF BROTHERS ARE
USING IT SINCE I WAS GOING TO
SEE THE NEXT FIVE YEARS GRAY
WERE SOLD IN THE EARLY STAGES
DIVERSITY SAFE I THINK THIS
IS A MATTER OF DECIDING A
PROBABLY OPTIMISTICALLY AT A
FOSTER MOM TO WRITE IN IT AND
WHAT TO WRITE SO IF YOU THINK
ABOUT THAT TOO VERY LAST
SECOND CITY THAT IT'S NOT
BEEN THE DEFENSE WON THIS
CUTE SEGMENT OF CONSUMERS
TODAY THAT I THINK NEXT WEEK
AND GET ACCESS TO ALL
THE PARTS OF THE BILL BECAUSE
IT DIDN'T HAPPEN NEEDS TO BE
I THINK THE SECOND SEGMENT
IS THIS IS A LOCAL BASIS AS
WE DON'T ACTUALLY NOT
CONNECTED TO DATE TWO WEEKS
OF DIGITAL MEANS SOUL OF MAN
THAT SAT IN THAT BUILDING AND
TIME OF FULL HUMAN EAR BUT SO
WHAT REALLY STINGS EVERY
INNING BUT THIS THOUGH FUTURE
AHEAD OF US BUT WE'RE LOOKING
AT IS THIS THE FIRST IN REACH
THIS IS THE VERY EARLY DAYS
SO STRONG THIS BIG IT'S
BETWEEN THE FIRST GENERATION
IN EVERY START TONIGHT ABOUT
SEVEN YEARS REALLY SAYING SEE
THAT FLY OVER THE NEXT AND
FIFTY YEARS THE QUESTION TO
YOU BECAUSE YOU'VE BEEN
INVOLVED IN IN SEVEN STARTS
OBVIOUSLY WITH ALL EIGHT OF
HERS WHO WON A PACK A FIT AND
THEY'LL SAY HOW HAVE YOU SEEN
THE OPPORTUNITIES CHANGE OVER
THE YEARS IN TERMS OF FUNDING
THAT IS IN PLACE AND
THE TALENT THAT'S AVAILABLE
TO SOC LIKE IN THE PAST YEARS
THE US BECAUSE IT IS
EXTREMELY FRAGMENTED SO YOU
HAVE A LOT OF DIFFERENT TOPS
WAS FACING THE PROBLEMS AND A
LOT OF IT. I THINK IN
THE NEXT TEN YEARS AGO IS
STILL AUDIBLE IN ADDITION TO
LOVE ON LOGITECH SIZES ARE
COMING TO VJ AND A LOT LAR
INVESTORS PUTTING MONEY IN
SEOUL. WE LOVE TO SEE IF THIS
ALL THE DIFFERENT COMPONENTS
SO YOU SEE A LOT MORE
SYNERGISTIC PARTNERSHIPS
ACQUISITIONS MERGERS WILL NOT
I THINK WHAT HAPPENED IN
THE NEXT FIVE YEARS THE ORTHO
THE VERY IMPORTANT THING FOR
STARTUPS AND WE HAVE SEEN IN
THIS REGION. UM NOT USE IN
MALAYSIA AND INDONESIA AND
SINGAPORE AS WELL IS AN
INCREASING NUMBER OF REPORTS
OF COURSE THE BIG NAMES
MENTIONED EARLIER RATHER LAZE
ON THE GO J FOR THE NAMES
BEFORE WAS THE QUESTION TO
YOU THE NUMBER OF CAROUSEL
HAS THE NAMES HELPS INCREASE
THE CHANCES OF YOU KNOW YOU
YOU RECENTLY AT THIRTY FIVE
MILLION ROUNDS LAST YEAR. DO
YOU FIND OTHERS MORE FUNDING
COMING IN THE WAR SEEM TO BE
UNIFORMS AND RECOGNIZE
THE OPPORTUNITIES AND SO I
GUESS SCHOOL IS KIND OF BIKE
IS GOING TO STOP THE CAROUSEL
FUNDING WAS SPEEDED UP WITH A
BOSS FIGHT IS TO SEE A LOT OF
INTERESTING STUFF COMING OUT
AS A RESULT OF THE INVESTORS
WILL BUY THE STUFF THAT
DECISION ON THE SAUCE IS
DEFINITELY THE BEST ACTUALLY
ACCELERATE THE LAW ON
RECENTLY IS THAT YOU SEE ON
CHINA AS HE SAID THE REGION
ARE AS FOLLOW THE USA MEANS
THAT THIS MIGHT NOT HAVE TO
BE HONEST AND NOT SO IT'S NO
LONGER JUST AS IMPORTANT BUT
HAS TO BE ABLE TO HAVE GOOD
WILL IS BLESSED WITH MY
POSITION A SPA AND IT'S NOT
JUST SEEING THE COUNTRY GIVEN
THAT SHE WOULD STOP
THE CAROUSEL ON THE LINE
STATING THAT HE HAS TO BE A
LOCAL COMPANY HAS MORE THAN
SINGAPORE THE ASK IS SOMEBODY
WHO WILL PROVIDE THE BEST OF
YOU MENTIONED THAT
INCREASINGLY YOU'RE SEEING
FUNDS FLOW FROM CHINA BUT
ALSO FROM THE US SOME OF
THOSE PCS THAT MAY HAVE
PERHAPS LOOK TO CHINA BEFORE
THE OPPORTUNITY SEEN
THE MARKET INCREASINGLY
SATURATED THEY'RE SHIFTING
THEIR ATTENTION TO THIS REACH
GET SUSHI LOT OF MONEY HE
DEFTLY FROM CHINA AND
THE MONEY FROM THE US. IT'S
ONE DEGREE REMOVED FROM
THE START UP SO A LOT OF US
HE SEES ARE STILL FOCUSED ON
THE US BUT WILL WE SEE IS
THE INSTITUTIONAL MONEY
BEHIND A LIMITED PARTNERS TO
INVEST IN THE U S THE SEASONS
DINER HE SEES ARE NOW IN
INVESTING HERE IN THE REGION
AND WHEN THEY LOOK AT IT FROM
THE US TO LOOK AT THE AGE
BEFORE IT WAS DEFTLY CHINA
MAYBE INDIA AND ARE YOU
SPENDING TIME COMING THROUGH
SOUTHEAST ASIA AN HOUR SEEN
PEOPLE SPEND TIME ON
THE GROUND COMING THROUGH SE
ASIA SO THAT EXCISE IS THAT
THE OLDIES ARE LOOKING AT ART
THIRTY MILLION FIFTY MILLION
SO LOOKING AT PUTTING SERIOUS
MONEY IN THE REGION. WHAT
ELSE FROM THE PERSPECTIVE OF
THE EC LOOKING FOR MORE
STARTS. ARE YOU FINDING THAT
THE EFFECTS OF THE FIRST
GENERATION COULD ARGUE IS
REALLY PUSHING
THE ENTREPRENEUR REALISM IN
THE SECOND GENERATION OF
THE SECOND WAY TO THE HUNDRED
PERCENT SO THE NUMBER OF
STARTS INCREASED THIS YEAR
AND SEE ABOUT TWELVE HUNDRED
STARTS THE YEAR. THAT'S
HIGHER BY ABOUT TWENTY
PERCENT THAN LAST YEAR BUT
WHAT'S MORE IMPORTANT IS
THE QUALITY OF THAT OR IT'S
GROWING VERY RAPIDLY AND SO
WHERE FIVE YEARS AGO ME THERE
WERE DOZENS OF COMPANIES OR
HANDFUL IN THE SERIES ACE
SPACE. NOW THEY ARE ON
THE ORDER OF ONE HUNDRED
COMPANIES IN THE SERIES IS AN
ORDER OF MAGNITUDE GROWTH
THAT'S HAPPENED I SEE THAT
CONTINUING OVER THE NEXT
YEARS YOU START A LARGER AND
YOU ARE IN SEVERAL MARKETS
SINCE THEN YOU DOWNSIZE TO
FOCUS ON THAILAND'S INDONESIA
AND MALAYSIA KNEW WE LEFT
TAIWAN IS LOVES
THE PHILIPPINES WILL EVEN OUT
SKIN. WHAT IS THE STRATEGY
BECAUSE WE'VE SEEN COMPANIES
LIKE KRAFT RIGHT APPLE A
MARKET SOMEONE'S COURSE WE'VE
ALSO SEEN SOMEBODY LIKE GO TO
REALLY HONE IN ON ONE MARKET
A BIG MARKET IN INDONESIA IS
IT BETTER TO TRY TO FIND
SUCCESS IN ONE COUNTRY HERE
IN THE REGION BEFORE YOU
BOUGHT OR STARTED TO THINK
IT'S COOL AS NANNIES YOU VERY
MUCH DEPENDS ON WHAT TO BUY
THE PURSE LINE IS I WOULD BE
A PILOT MIGHT BE SECOND ONE
IS HOW DID I GO POCKETS ARE
THE PEOPLE THAT IT'S SO
OBVIOUS YOU HAD THE RIGHT
OTHER MARKETS IT WILL HAVE
MORE INDEPENDENCE FINANCIALLY
SO YOU CAN STILL PROCESS
OPENS ITS EYES TO SO I THINK
IT'S NOT A BLACK OR WHITE
ANSWER TO THAT IS VERY MUCH
DEPENDS ON WHAT GOT IS
NOTHING MORE IMPORTANT EVEN
MY VACATION THE NEED TO BOOK
A HOTEL. I WANT SOMEONE WHO
MAKES IT EASY COOKING DUCK ON
GUNS AND THUS THEIR PRICE
MATCH. I KNOW I'M GETTING
THE BEST PRICE EVERY TIME I
VISIT BOOKING DOT COM BOOKING
DONE YET. YOU COMPARE PRICES
ON EVERYTHING FLIGHTS HOTELS
YOU NAME IT. NOW YOU CAN DO
IT WITH LIFE INSURANCE AND
JUST FIVE MINUTE POLICY
GENIUS COMPARE QUOTES FROM
TOP INSURERS TO GET YOU
THE BEST VALUE COMPARE AND
SAVE WITH POLICY GENIUS DOT
COM SAM HAS THE HEART OF
INNOVATION INNOVATION DOES
NOT THE I DON'T SEE THE MORE
WE COME AND HEAR THE WAR WE
KNOW THE MORE WE CAN HELP YOU
MAKE MONEY WITH SIMPSON OF
GOD'S WILL BY THESE COMPANIES
I AM SO GLAD I DID BECAUSE
IT'S BEEN HUNDREDS OF
BILLIONS OF VALUATION AND WE
PRAYED AND I WAS IN ORDER TO
HAVE TO FACE TO FACE
THE GRAND SLAM IS GOING TO
COME FROM DEEP LEARNING. SHE
LEARNED THIS IS EVERYTHING
THAT I KNOW TO BE ABLE TO
HELP YOU GET BETTER AT CNBC
PRO PRINTER BACK SISTER WAS
GIVING YOU THE EDGE TO INVEST
LIKE A PRO PRO STOCK BUBBLE
TEA TIME CUP LIVE STREAMING
FC IN THE WEST OR FINISH YOUR
SUBSCRIPTION GIVES YOU ACCESS
TO THE EXPERTS INTO EFFECT
WITH EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEWS
INSIGHTS AND ANALYSIS FROM
THE PROBES THE SPEC MARKET
DATA ANALYZED TO HELP YOU
UNCOVER NEW INVESTMENT
OPPORTUNITIES TO INVEST LIKE
A PRO. THE CNBC DOT COM SLASH
AT THE THIRTY DAY FREE TRIAL
GOVERNMENT IS ACTUALLY A
WHOLLY OWNED BY THE RESULTS
OF THESE ARE THE E R WHAT WE
DO IS PRETTY MUCH TO TELL ME
HOW WE ARE AT THE TWO
DIVISIONS AND PAWN IN THIS
THE MOST PART IT'S ABOUT
CONNECTIVITY OF THE SYSTEM
AND BUILDING A SUSTAINABLE
ECOSYSTEM THAT'S ONE OF
THE FOUR ACTIVITIES THAT WE
DO AND THE OTHER BIT IS
ACTUALLY DEPRESSING ABOUT NOT
SO MUCH FROM TENNESSEE WHERE
RISHI AND IT'S NOWHERE
THE ISLAND WEATHER HAS BEEN A
MAJOR RESTORATION IS
SOUTHEAST ASIA SHOULD BE
THE HOT POSSIBLE AND
THE LEVERAGING OF EACH OF
THE STRENGTHS WITHIN
THE RESPECTIVE COUNTRIES AND
PULL AS SOME OF
THE HIGHLIGHTS IN
THE POSITION ON THE MARKET
SPACE IN BULL SESSION NOT HE
FIGHTS TO BE A HOUSE THE GOAL
IS HOW DO YOU FIND ME TO
COLLABORATE IN A MANNER THAT
WOULD HELP BUILD THE SYSTEM
OF LAW THE BIG MARKETS HERE
IN THE US AND CHINA. WE SEEM
TO GET STARTED TRY TO MAKE AN
ENTRY IN SOUTHEAST ASIA
THROUGH DIFFERENT MEATS WERE
BROUGHT IN THEIR BRAND NAME
THEY HAD THEIR STRATEGY READY
READY TO GO HAVEN'T
NECESSARILY DOMINATED ANY
MARKET IN SOUTHEAST ASIA WHEN
YOU'VE GOT SOME OTHER CHINESE
LEADERS HAVE COME AND LOOK
FOR PARTNERSHIPS ANYONE WANT
TO JUMP IN TERMS OF WHAT SHE
THINKS IT'S A SMALL BETTER
BECAUSE WE TALK ABOUT
SOUTHEAST ASIA AS IF IT'S ONE
MARKET BUT REALLY IT'S QUITE
FRAGMENTED FROM COUNTRY AND
THE AGGIES MADE IT PRETTY
WELL A DIFFERENT KIND OF A US
COMPANY COMING INTO
THE REGION OWN TACK OWN BRAND
NEW CHANGES VERSUS CHINESE
COMPANY ALIBABA INVESTING OR
BUYING GO JACK AS
THE AMERICANS OUT HERE
ACTUALLY THINK THE CHINESE
MODEL IS MUCH STRONGER WAY OF
GOING GLOBAL. BASICALLY
VOCALS MOBILIZING NOT THROUGH
LANGUAGE BUT SCREW BRAND AND
PRODUCT OFFERING PRODUCTS AND
SO I THINK THE LONG RUN
THAT'S ACTUALLY GOING TO BE
THEM THROUGHOUT BE A VERY
STRONG ADVANTAGE. I THINK
THAT'S ONE REASON THE MARKET
DOES NOT CHANGE YOUR STRATEGY
IN ANY WAY YOU'VE GOT THE WAY
YOU OPERATE CAROUSEL RIGHT
NOW. DO YOU THINK WHAT AMAZON
TO ORDER THIS PART OF
THE MARKET HOW DO WE AS LOCAL
PLAYER TRY TO MAINTAIN AND
KEEP OUR PIECES OF POSITIONS
THERE FOR ME SOMETHING THIS
BABY AS YOU MENTIONED. SO
ABBY EVERY COUNTRIES THAT
WISH THAN TO ACTUALLY HAPPEN
IT SEEMS THAT BROUGHT UP AND
MAKE YOU REALIZE THAT
THE BICYCLE AND ONE THING
THAT MAKES UP AS A REALLY
DIFFERENT FROM YOU COMES OUT
AS A COMMUNITY THAT BUILDS
OVER THE YEARS AND THINK
ABOUT AMAZON ALL OF YOU GUYS
STARTED MOBILE FIRSTS CARE
SERVICES BUT IN THE US THAT'S
NOT THE CASE MOST COMPANIES
EVEN AMAZON START BUT FIRST
SO EVEN AMAZON IN SINGAPORE
HAS A MOBILE YOU CAN ONLY
ORDER OFF THEIR MOBILE APP
BUT THE THING IS THEY'RE NOT
IN THE MOBILE COMPANY THEIR
MOBILE APP TO THE WEBSITE
WITH A RAPPER OR JUST
SOMETHING AS SIMPLE AS THAT
OF IN SOUTHEAST ASIA PEOPLE
ARE THINKING ABOUT REAL TIME
LOCAL CHAT INSTEAD. THESE ARE
THINGS THAT ARE VERY
DIFFERENT MINDSET FOR SOME OF
THESE US COMPANIES COULD NOT
IN THEIR DNA SO IT REALLY
GIVES A MUCH STRONGER
FIGHTING CHANCE WHEN YOU'RE
BUILDING IT FOR AUTUMN AWE ON
THE GAZE OF AMAZON
SPECIFICALLY FOR OUR DAYS AT
A FIRE. WHAT IS HAPPENING IS
THAT THAT HAS BEEN
ACCELERATING A LOT OF
RETAILERS. WELL WE'VE SEEN IS
THAT WHERE SIX TWO MM ON
THE GO TO YET AT SOME OF
THE REGATTA IS WHERE IT'S
THAT THE CALL ABOUT HOW AND
WHEN THAT HAPPENED TODAY NO
ONE IS ITB LESSON IN THAT
ANYMORE AND WAS SOO
DISGUSTING EYES AND CYNICAL
IT'S WHAT WE GET THE BEST DAD
A FEW NEW TRADITION OF
VISITING A NEW REALM OF I
WILL START THE NEXT HURDLE IN
HALF TO GET A LOT OF ISSUES
TO READ THE SOLVING OF
THE CONDITIONS THAT IS SOME
PRECISION FOR EXAMPLE THINGS
THAT SHOULD BE OR SOMETHING
THAT EVERY COUNTRY THEY SAW
THAT ENOUGH WAS WE NEEDED TO
SEE OURSELVES AS AN ECOSYSTEM
RATHER THAN TRYING TO TACKLE
ABOUT SELVES. SO RECENTLY
BEEN OTHER GUESTS FELL TO
THE EYE CAN SEE THE BEAST
BABY CAN ACTUALLY GET IT AT
ALBERTSON'S ECONOMIC
COLLABORATION. I THINK HAVING
COLLABORATION WITH MULTIPLE
PARTNERS TO BUILD THAT
ECOSYSTEM IS FABIO NEXT
HURDLE RATHER THAN GOING TO I
AM PREGNANT AND THIRD ALL
TIME HOME LOANS FOR ALL TYPES
OF PEOPLE. FHA LOANS JUMBO
LOANS VA LOANS CONDO LOANS
AND MANY MORE. CHOOSING
THE RIGHT MORTGAGE CAN SAVE
YOU THOUSANDS OF DOLLARS
GUARANTEE RATE HAS HELPED
OVER FIVE HUNDRED THOUSAND
HAPPY CUSTOMERS FIND
THE RIGHT MORTGAGE WITH LOW
LOW RATES GENERATE DOT COM
RIGHT NOW TO TRY GUARANTEE
RATES EASY INTUITIVE LOAN
FINDER JUST ANSWER A SERIES
OF SIMPLE QUESTIONS ABOUT
YOUR SPECIFIC MORTGAGE FROM
HEAT AND INTO THE BLOODLINE
OF POWERFUL DECISION ENGINE
WILL GENERATE A CUSTOMIZED
LIST OF THE BEST LOAN
PRODUCTS AT THE LOWEST RATES
FOR YOU ALL IN LESS THAN
SIXTY SECONDS AND ALL FOR
FREE GUARANTEE RATE THE TOP
TEN NATIONAL AND OR WITH OVER
NINETY FIVE PERCENT CUSTOMER
SATISFACTION. THE LINEAR
BUYING OR REFINANCING YOUR
HOME LOAN LOW RATE FROM
GUARANTEED RATE TODAY CALL
ONE EIGHT SIX SIX EIGHT ZERO
ZERO SIX SIX OR VISIT RATE
DOT COM THE IS A GOVERNMENT
AGENCY AND AMY ON THE ATTEMPT
IN THE DIGITAL ECONOMY IS IN
THE NATION ENTERED ALL MY
FRIENDS AND WE MEASURE OUR
SELF IN THE MACRO LEVEL
THE ATTORNEY AND SEVENTY ONE
PERCENT OF THE TWO OF
THE ENEMY HAS AN INSPIRATION
TO THE HUGE NEED IN UH
THE CROSS WHEN IT RAINS ON
TWO COUNTRIES PAINSTAKINGLY
NEGOTIATED AT THE END BY
TROLLS BUT TO ONLY BE ABLE TO
BE KEPT ALIVE BY BOTH
COMPANIES WITH THE SAUCE BUT
HE COULDN'T TAKE THE TRACH
THE ACTION AND PUT IT INTO A
PLATFORM WITH THE TECHNOLOGY
PLATFORMS WHAT I CALL
THE RISE ASIAN CHICK
THE STATION PARTS THERE'S ANY
CONNECTION TO
THE OPPORTUNITIES FOR US AND
HE HAS NEVER BEEN ABLE TO GET
TO THE COMPLEXITY OF SUCH
COSTS FOR THE INFECTION OF
AHEAD ALL THE AS YOU WILL NOT
USE THE ABOVE THREE OF OUR
LIVES ARE REALLY COMING
TOGETHER ON CONDITION OF
THE OBJECT MODEL WHICH IS
THE WILL TO APPLY FOR THIS IS
A SECULAR BUT THAT'S
THE NATION THAT IS OPTIMIZED
TO LET THEM USE THE LAUNCH
THIS YEAR THE NATION TAKE
THE POTS A PROGRAM WHERE WE
WILL EAT YOUR UH YOUR UH AND
YOU KNOW YOU'RE IN JAPAN
THE ONLY SHIA IF YOU ARE FIVE
PLUS LIKE THE MESSAGE IN POTS
IF YOU ARE JUST NO
EXPERIENCE WHATSOEVER DOES
HAVE A GREAT IDEA YOUR TUMMY
WILL BE A ONE YET IPHONE
THE LAST TEN STARTS LAST YEAR
AND SIX HUNDRED AND FIFTY
MILLION POPULATION AND
THE ONE WE TRAIN IN COMBINED
CITY THE NOT HOMOGENEOUS IS
NOT HOMOGENEOUS MARKET BUT
THE FORMATION AND FOR
THE LAST TEN AND ALSO ON
THE CAUSE OF THE WOODS TO
FIND A WAY THAT YOU CAN EAT
EAT SOMETHING. THE EMERGING
MARKET. I SEMI HIT THE HAY
LEAD INTO THE REST OF US THEN
AND THEN FROM THE EMERGING
MARKETS THUS YOU THINK
THE GOVERNMENT PLAYS WELL IN
SUSTAINING THE GROWTH WE
HEARD FROM THE NAME OF
THE TALKING ABOUT ITS ONE
MALAYSIA IS DOING TO TRY AND
NOT ONLY FOSTER THE START OF
THE CULTURE HERE THAT BRING
IN TALENT FROM THE OUTSIDE AS
WELL. WHAT MORE NEEDS TO BE
DONE ON THAT YOU KNOW AS
AMERICANS THE GOVERNMENT
SHOULD BE MORE ABOUT LIKE
GETTING OUT OF THE WAY BUT I
THINK THE IDEA OF
THE ECOSYSTEM POURING IN TAX
DOLLARS EXPERIENCE. I THINK
THAT'S VERY HELPFUL
THE THING THAT ALWAYS
OVERLOOKED AS YOU WOULD SAY
TO US SO IT'S COMPLETELY OUT
OF THE HANDS OF GOVERNMENT
THE REALITY IS MOST DC HAS
GOVERNMENT DOLLARS IS STATE
PENSION FUNDS IT IS THESE
VERY LARGE STATE OF FUNDS AND
ENDOWMENTS THE FACT HE SEES
THAT MAY NOT HAVE KIND OF
THE POLITICAL SAY HEY WANT
YOU TO INVEST IN XYZ OR
THEY'RE BASICALLY SAYING IS
THE TYPE OF MONEY. HOW ABOUT
LONG TERM MULTI DECADE VIEW
HE BELIEVES TAKE HIGH RISKS
USUALLY COME FROM THE STATE
ANYWAY WE DON'T THINK ABOUT
THAT THE US BUT SO SEEING
LOCAL GOVERNMENTS HERE GET
MORE INVOLVED IN FINANCIALLY
SUPPORTING THE ECOSYSTEM WITH
A HANDS OFF APPROACH BEING A
GOOD CAREER TO REMOVE I THINK
IS THE PATH I SEE SOUTHEAST
ASIAN MARKETS BEING DOMINATED
BY WELL FUNDED IN APPEARANCE
LIKE GRAVEL IS NOT UNTIL
THE MEDIA IS THE WORST FACE
WITH A SMALLER PLAYER IN
THE SIX HUNDRED MILLION
PEOPLE HIT THE STREETS WHO IS
THIS TO ME SAID MARKET SO
THE QUESTION OF HIS DAY WHO
WILL NOT BE YES MEN MOSTLY
BUT NOT ON THE INTERNET ID
AGE. THIS LOSS OF MUSCLE
WHICH IN SOMEBODY WHO HAS
INVESTED IN CAROUSEL AT THIS
POINT IN THE START OF GAME IN
SOUTHEAST ASIA WAS IT THAT
YOU'RE LOOKING YOU THINK OF
WHICH COMPANIES YOU WANT TO
START NEXT. SO EVERY
INVESTMENT VALUE PEOPLE SO
THEY TOO ARE THE FOUNDERS WHY
WHY ARE THEY DOING WHAT WAS
CRUCIAL TO THE EXPERIENCE
IT'S HANDS DOWN THE QUESTIONS
YOU KNOW THAT THERE ARE
CERTAIN PIECES THAT WE HAVE
IN TERMS OF THE BIGGER PAIN
POINTS THAT CONSUMERS NEED
RIGHT NOW AROUND CONFERENCE
ARE TO PLACE HIS PAYMENTS SO
YOU HAVE THIS INTERSECTION OF
TOWNERS A CERTAIN PROFILE
CERTAIN AREAS THAT ARE CLEAR
IN POINTS BUT IT'S MUCH MORE
NUANCE NOT LIKE WHY DO WE
WRITE ABOUT AND WHY AS WE
PASS IN SOME GREAT
INVESTMENTS AND THAT YOU
PROBABLY WELL AND WE MAY KNOW
THAT ONE HAS SEEN ME NOTS ARE
PIECES PERFECTLY OR MAKE A
DIFFERENCE THEY ARE. YOU KNOW
WHAT WE'RE ALSO LOOKING FOR
IS THEIR THEIR BELIEFS YOU
INSPIRE PEOPLE BEHIND THEM
THEIR ABILITY TO OPERATE IN
MULTIPLE MARKETS. THERE'S SO
MANY LITTLE NUANCES THAT IT'S
HARD TO SAY WHY YES I KNOW
THE OTHER THING IS JUST
THE COMPETITIVE LANDSCAPE
LATE YET SOME OF THE QUESTION
WAS HOW DO YOU COMPUTE
THE BILL IS NOT A NEWSMAN SAY
A BILLION NEW STUFF FROM
SCRATCH RIGHT NOW TO COMPETE
WITHOUT A PROBLEM BE A VERY
DIFFICULT TIME AROUND
INVESTORS BUT THOSE OTHER
COMPANIES ARE MENTIONED
COOKIE A AND GRAB FIVE YEARS
AGO THOSE WITH A SMALL START
UPS GO JACK ONLY REASON SERIE
DE TWO AND A HALF YEARS AGO
THAT IS NO REASON BILLION
DOLLARS. SO WHAT IS KIND OF
SMALL SOMETIMES YOU DON'T
REALLY REALIZE UNTIL YOU TALK
ABOUT THE NEXT WAVE THAT
WE'RE GOING TO SEE IS
THE MEASURE OF SUCCESS THERE
BEING ABLE TO EXPORT THE STAR
OUTSIDE OF THE REGION. WHAT
DO YOU SEE AS A MARKER FOR
THE NEXT GENERATION STARTS
SITE GOES COMES AND GO BUT AT
THE END OF THE CYCLE
THE COMPANIES THAT MISSED OUT
ON HIS FEET COMPANIES THAT
YOU ARE BASED ON THE SHOW I
SAW THIS ON THE EAST AND
THAT'S WHAT WE'LL BE FOCUSING
ON DUTY IN THAT I DON'T I
BELIEVED IRAN OR EVEN
OUTWEIGH HER BY SAYING THAT
THE SOUL OF THE LOGISTICS
INFRASTRUCTURE E COMMERCE
MARKETPLACE BUT INSTEAD OF
PAVEMENT THAT'S WHY WE KEEP
ON TALKING ABOUT WAS OUT I
WAS ON PBS THAT IS IS THIS
DOES THAT BIRD GOES LIVE IF
THIS TRANSACTION IT SO MANY
OTHER THINGS THAT WE DO GOES
FROM NOW THE INTERESTS OF
FINANCE IS SO MANY THINGS
THAT THAT'S DONE AND I
THOUGHT THAT I THINK THE NEW
GENERATION WOULD BE PROBABLY
PEOPLE THAT LOVE GOD MY DAD
IS MY WAYS AND I LOVE LITTLE
SOMETHING TO BE OUT THE BOX
I THINK I CANNOT SAY THAT
THIS IS THAT I'M LOOKING ON
RIGHT NOW SO I ASK MYSELF
THE WHOLE BIG OF A PROBLEM
SOLVING AND ON ONE THING IS
GETTING OFF AND WE TILL MY
REST SONGS RETAILERS TO BE ON
MY CITY LOOK AT IT ACROSS
THE REGION BY GOVERNMENTS
HAVE BEEN APPEALING TO
BUSINESSES LOCAL BUSINESSES
TO ADOPT TECHNOLOGY TO
DIGITAL PAYMENTS FOR EVER AND
I DID TODAY. IF THE PIECES
JUST DON'T SEE VALUE IN
ACTUALLY GOING ON RIGHT THING
TO DO THE DEMONS THEN YOU
WOULD NEVER HAPPEN SOUL
THE PROBLEM THAT WE'RE
TRYING TO SOLVE THE PROBLEM
THAT ALL THESE GOVERNMENTS OF
ASIA. SO THERE'S A PHENOMENAL
AMOUNT OF VALLEY VICTORY IN
THIS REGION AND THAT'S WHY
THESE COMPANIES THAT HAVE
THESE MULTIBILLION DOLLAR
VALUATIONS JUST FOCUS ON
SOUTHEAST ASIA. YOU HAVE A
FEW COMPANIES THAT HAVE KIND
OF A GLOBAL AUDIENCE TO RAISE
THEIR COMPANY STARTED IN
SINGAPORE AS AN INVESTOR
CONSUL I ALSO THINK THAT THEY
HAVE VERY VERY LARGE COPPER
FUTURES THEIR REACH. I THINK
IT'S VERY INTERESTING IN
TERMS OF YOU KNOW AS A MOBILE
CLASSIFIED SAY THAT WAS
SOMETHING THAT WAS STARTED IN
THIS FOR THE WORLD FIRST AS
OPPOSED TO BEING LOOKED AT
WHAT HAPPENED ENTIRELY US TO
SOME IT HAPPENS HERE AND NOW
WE SEE COMPANIES THE US OR
CHINA BUT IS THIS WORLD THAT
LOVE THE ADJOINING OF TODAY
IN UH THE UH IT WAS ALL ABOUT
RATINGS RUMORS IN FACT
THE BACK OF THE AMISH IT WAS
A PROFESSIONAL TRADER
THE EASY MONEY IT MADE GOING
WITH THE CONSENSUS THE BIG
MONEY IS MADE ON WITH
THE FINALISTS FOR THE TREE
NOT WHAT IS THE OBVIOUS TRADE
THE TRADE THAT NOBODY HAS
TAKEN A LOOK AT. NOBODY HAS
PUT ON THAT YOU CAN PUT ON
TOMORROW THE MONEY WEEKDAYS
FIVE EASTERN ON CNBC
THE NOTHING MORE IMPORTANT TO
ME THE NATION IN THE HOTEL
ROOM I WENT THE EASY TO FIND
WHAT I WANT THE COOKING DOT
COM GET FIT AND WITH A PRICE
MATCH. I KNOW I'M GETTING
THE BEST PRICE. EVERY TIME
THE CONCERT RELAXING EVEN
BEFORE THE VACATION BEGAN ON
YOUR VACATION IS VERY
IMPORTANT THAT'S WHY BOOKING
THE COMICS FINDING THE RIGHT
HOTEL FOR THE RIGHT PRICE
EASY IS IT LOOKING
THE COMMON NOTIFY KNOW WHY
WE'RE BOOKING DONE YET.  WHY
IS YOUR HEAD COVERED IN
BUBBLE WRAP FROM NOT COVERED
IN LIFE INSURANCE NEEDS TO
CHECK OUT POLICY GENIUS
DOCTOR THEY COMPARE ALL
THE BEST INSURERS TO HELP YOU
FIND THE RIGHT POLICY. IT'S
SUPER EASY LIKE THIS. COMPARE
AND SAVE WITH POLICY GENIUS
DOT COM AT CNBC PRO IN DEPTH
ACCESS TO WAS THE BEST LIKE A
PRO THE LIVE STREAMING OF
CNBC US THE EXCLUSIVE
INTERVIEW TO CNBC DOT COM
SLASH DEBT PROBLEM FOR YOUR
THIRTY DAY FREE TRIAL PROM ON
THE OTHER STORY OF HOW UNDER
ARMOUR IS TRYING TO TAKE
THE LOCAL CURRY IS THERE TO
THE ROBUST VOICE LIKE THAT. I
GOT THIS OUR SCHEDULE HERE IS
THE GOING TILL FOUR AND THIS
REALLY HIT THE GYM
THE BATHTUB ON HE WILL NOT
GET THE OTHER NETWORKS
BECAUSE THE TOPICS THE CAT
CNBC THROUGH THE END OF
THE AXIS TOWARDS GIVING YOU
THE EDGE TO INVEST LIKE A PRO
POSED THE QUILTY TIME CUP
LIVE STREAMING OF CNBC
THE WEST OR FINISH YOUR
SUBSCRIPTION GIVES YOU ACCESS
TO THE EXPERTS INTO EFFECT
WITH EXCLUSIVE INTERVIEWS
INSIGHTS AND ANALYSIS FROM
T PROBES THE SPEC MARKET
DATA ANALYZED TO HELP YOU
UNCOVER NEW INVESTMENT
OPPORTUNITIES TO INVEST LIKE
A PRO. THE CNBC DOT COMS MUCH
FOR YOUR THIRTY DAY FREE
TRIAL THE JAMES L CARTER
JUNIOR WAS SWORN IN AS
THE THIRTY NINTH PRESIDENT OF
THE MARIN ON JANUARY
TWENTIETH NINETEEN SEVENTY
SEVEN A CHAMPION FOR HUMAN
RIGHTS PEACE FROM
THE ENVIRONMENT IS TELLING US
THIS WAS OVERSHADOWED BY
INTERNATIONAL CRISES AND
DOMESTIC RECESSION OFTEN
LEAVING THE WHITE HOUSE THAT
LANDSLIDE DEFEAT IN NINETEEN
NINETY ONE YEARS BY
DEDICATING HIS LIFE TO
IMPRO