NEXT COUPLE OF DAYS.
IT GETS DOWN RIGHT CHILLY ON
SATURDAY.
57 DEGREES.
SUNDAY LOOKS GOOD NEXT WEEK TOO.
>> "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" STARTS
NOW.
PLEAS FOR HELP GROWING
LOUDER AND AID ISN'T
FLOWING INTO PUERTO
RICO NEARLY FAST
ENOUGH.
A DEEPENING EMERGENCY,
A WEEK SINCE MARIA
LEFT THE ISLAND IN
RUINS.
>>> TRUMP'S TAX PLAN.
THE PRESIDENT TAKES
HIS PITCH ON THE ROAD
PUSHING CUT, BUT WHO
P
BENEFITS MOST, THE
CH OR THE MIDDLE
CLASS?
WHAT WILL IT MEAN FOR
YOU.
>>> STAR COACH
SIDELINED.
ONE OF THE BIGGEST
NAMES IN COLLEGE
BASKETBALL A CASUALTY
OF A GROWING BRIBERY
SCANDAL ROCKING MAJOR
UNIVERSITIES.
>>> PRICE TAG.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S HIGH
FLYING HEALTH
SECRETARY UNDER FIRE
OVER HIS FREQUENT USE
OF PRIVATE JETS.
TAXPAYERS ON THE HOOK.
CONGRESS
INVESTIGATING.
>>> AND ADULT FOOD
ALLERGIES.
DOCTORS REPORT A
DRAMATIC INCREASE IN
CASES HITTING LATER IN
LIFE.
YOUR FAVORITE FOODS
SUDDENLY DANGEROUS.
>>> "NIGHTLY NEWS"
BEGINS RIGHT NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN
NEW YORK, THIS IS NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>> GOOD EVENING AND
THANK YOU FOR BEING
WITH US TONIGHT.
WE'VE SEEN FOR
OURSELVES THE TONS OF
WATER AND FOOD POURING
INTO PUERTO RICO'S
CAPITAL BY AIR EVERY
DAY, BUT OFFICIALS
THERE TONIGHT
ACKNOWLEDGE THAT ON
THE GROUND THEY'RE
RUNNING UP AGAINST
PROBLEMS GETTING IT TO
WHERE IT IS NEEDED
MOST ON THE ISLAND.
IT WAS A WEEK AGO
TODAY THAT HURRICANE
MARIA SCORED ITS
DIRECT HIT ON PUERTO
RICO WITH
155-MILE-PER-HOUR
WINDS OBLITERATING
VITAL INFRASTRUCTURE
AND PLUNGING THE
AMERICAN COMMONWEALTH
INTO A DIFFERENT KIND
OF DARK AGE.
BUT SEVEN DAYS IN, A
MASSIVE RELIEF
OPERATION IS STILL
PLAYING CATCH-UP.
OUR GABE GUTIERREZ
REMAINS ON THE ISLAND
AND HAS THE LATEST.
GOOD EVENING.
>> Reporter: LESTER, A
WEEK AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA RIPPED THROUGH
THESE HOMES, THERE IS
STILL NO POWER, NO
WATER AND NO PHONES.
THE MAGNITUDE OF THIS
DISASTER IS JUST
SINKING IS IN.
MANY RESIDENTS HERE
KNOW THAT HELP IS ON
THE WAY, BUT THEY
HAVEN'T SEEN IT YET.
IT'S BEEN ONE WEEK.
SEVEN DAYS.
168 HOURS.
AND BETSY CHILEA IS
STILL LOOKING FOR
WATER FOR HER
CHILDREN.
>> WE DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: SHE'S
AMONG THE MANY PUERTO
RICANS DESPERATE FOR
HELP IN HURRICANE
MARIA'S WAKE.
THE DESTRUCTION IS
IMMENSE.
THESE GRANDPARENTS
LOST THEIR HOME OF 40
YEARS.
THE ROOF RIPPED OFF.
THE STORM'S AFTERMATH
IS DEVASTATING.
>> NO WATER.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN
ONE WEEK, AND ACROSS
THE ISLAND SUPPLIES
STILL AREN'T GETTING
WHERE THEY'RE SUPPOSED
TO.
THIS GROCERY STORE
RATIONING WATER AND
RICE AND FINDING IT
HARD TO RESTOCK
SHELVES BECAUSE ITS
TRUCKS ARE LOW ON
FUEL.
THE GOVERNOR SAYS
SUPPLIES ARE SITTING
IN STORAGE BECAUSE
PRIVATE SECTOR DRIVERS
ALSO AREN'T SHOWING UP
FOR DELIVERIES.
>> WE DON'T KNOW IF
FUEL SHORTAGES ON THE
ISLAND OF PUERTO RICO.
THE CHALLENGE FOR US
TODAY IS GETTING IT
DISTRIBUTED.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN
ONE WEEK AND THE
AGONIZING LINES FOR
GAS BEGIN BEFORE DAWN
STRETCHING FOR BLOCKS
IN THE SWELTERING
HEAT.
>> THEY HAVE NO
DIESEL.
OUR PEOPLE HAS NO
>> Reporter: AND IT
CAN BE LIFE
THREATENING.
HOW DO YOU DEAL WITH
SOMETHING LIKE THIS
LONG-TERM?
>> THERE'S NO
LONG-TERM POSSIBILITY
TO THIS.
>> Reporter: THIS
HOSPITAL HAD TO
EVACUATE SEVERAL
CHILDREN ON
VENTILATORS BECAUSE
ITS BACKUP GENERATOR
RAN OUT OF DIESEL.
>> WE DON'T HAVE ANY
ELECTRICITY.
AND THERE WERE
PATIENTS ON
VENTILATORS DEPENDENT
AT THE TIME ON THE
BATTERY THAT LASTS
APPROXIMATELY EIGHT
HOURS.
>> Reporter: ROYAL
CARIBBEAN CANCELING A
CRUISE AND USING THE
SHIP TO ATTACK
EVACUEES TO THE U.S.
MAINLAND.
IN NEW YORK, RELIEVED
TRAVELERS WHO GOT OUT
ON ONE OF THE FEW
COMMERCIAL FLIGHTS OFF
THE ISLAND.
AS BETSY CHILEA
WAITING FOR WATER.
THEY TELL YOU THE
FEDERAL HELP IS
COMING, BUT YOU
HAVEN'T SEEN IT.
>> NO, WE HAVEN'T SEEN
ANYTHING.
>> Reporter: BEFORE
HER PATIENCE RUNS DRY.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, PUERTO RICO.
>>> THIS IS TAMMY
LEITNER IN CENTRAL
PUERTO RICO WHERE TIME
IS CRITICAL.
>> THIS IS THE DEEPEST
PART RIGHT HERE.
>> Reporter: THIS TEAM
OF RESCUERS SEARCHING
FOR A FAMILY OF SIX
NOT SEEN SINCE THE
HURRICANE WIPED OUT
THE BRIDGE.
THIS TOWN ONE OF 11 NO
ONE HAS BEEN ABLE TO
REACH.
GABRIEL DESPERATE TO
FIND HIS RELATIVES
LEADS A TEAM OF
RESCUERS UP A MUDDY
MOUNTAIN.
SOME PARTS BARELY
PASSABLE.
WE'VE BEEN TALKING FOR
ABOUT 15 MINUTES.
IT'S SLOW GOING
BECAUSE THERE'S TREES
DOWN, POWER LINES
DOWN.
FINALLY HE SPOTS HIS
SISTER IN THE
DISTANCE.
>> WE HAVE A VISUAL ON
THEM NOW.
>> Reporter: A HUG TWO
WEEKS IN THE MAKING.
THE ENTIRE FAMILY
TOGETHER AGAIN.
GABRIEL'S SISTER AND
HUSBAND PACK UP A FEW
THINGS.
HIS PARENTS CHOOSING
TO STAY BEHIND.
>> SAYING SHE HAS
ARTHRITIS IN THE LEFT
LEG AND CAN'T MAKE THE
WALK DOWN.
>> WE'RE GOING TO BE
SEPARATED.
I KNOW IT'S JUST GOING
TO BE TEMPORARY, YOU
KNOW, BUT IT HURTS ME
TO SEE MY LITTLE
GRANDDAUGHTER'S NOT
GOING TO BE WITH ME
FOR A WHILE.
>> Reporter: THE
REUNION CUT SHORT,
ANOTHER STORM MAKING
THE DANGEROUS JOURNEY
DOWN THE MOUNTAIN MORE
TREACHEROUS.
STILL SO MANY
CHALLENGES, BUT FOR
NOW A MOMENT OF
RELIEF.
TAMMY LEITNER, NBC
NEWS, PUERTO RICO.
>>> SO MANY FAMILIES
LOOKING TO MAKE THEIR
CONNECTIONS.
AND TONIGHT, MARIA HAS
REGAINED HURRICANE
STRENGTH IN THE
ATLANTIC.
THE CATEGORY 1 WITH
WINDS OF 75 MILES PER
HOUR.
IT'S ABOUT 200 MILES
AWAY FROM CAPE
HATTERAS, NORTH
CAROLINA, WHILE IT'S
IN THE A THREAT TO
LAND, IT IS A DANGER
ALONG THE COAST.
WE'RE PICKING UP ROUGH
SURF AND RIP CURRENTS
THAT WILL DECREASE AS
THE STORM TURNS AWAY.
TONIGHT, THE WHITE
HOUSE AND
CONGRESSIONAL
REPUBLICANS ARE
TURNING THEIR
ATTENTION TO TAXES AND
TODAY PRESIDENT TRUMP
HIT THE ROAD TO TALK
ABOUT THE SWEEPING
PLAN THAT SLASHES
TAXES FOR
CORPORATIONS, BUT HE
WAS SHORT ON SPECIFICS
ON HOW MIDDLE CLASS
FAMILIES WOULD
BENEFIT.
NBC'S PETER ALEXANDER
BREAKS DOWN WHAT WE
KNOW.
>> FRESH OFF ANOTHER
DEFEAT OR HIS PUSH TO
REPEAL OBAMACARE,
PRESIDENT TRUMP
TONIGHT TURNING TO
TAXES.
MIDDLE CLASS MIRACLE.
IT'S CALLED A MIDDLE
CLASS MIRACLE.
>> Reporter: TAKING
HIS PITCH TO MIKE
PENCE'S HOME STATE,
INDIANA.
PART OF WHAT HE CALLS
A ONCE IN A GENERATION
OPPORTUNITY.
>> THIS IS A
REVOLUTIONARY CHANGE
AND THE BIGGEST
WINNERS WILL BE THE
EVERYDAY AMERICAN
WORKERS AS JOBS START
POURING INTO OUR
COUNTRY.
>> Reporter: THE
SWEEPING OVERHAUL
STILL JUST A BLUEPRINT
SIMPLIFYING AND
CUTTING INDIVIDUAL TAX
RATES, SLASHING
CORPORATE TAXES AT 20%
AND EXPANDING THE
CHILD TAX CREDIT.
THAT'S CRUCIAL TO THE
BOREES FAMILY IN
INDIANA.
>> IT'S IMPORTANT TO
US TO GET THOSE TAX
BREAKS, AND WE COUNT
ON THEM AS PART OF OUR
INCOME.
>> Reporter: STILL,
THE LONG-AWAITED
ROLLOUT IS LACKING KEY
DETAILS, LEAVING MANY
QUESTIONS UNANSWERED.
EXPERTS WARN IT COULD
COST THE COUNTRY MORE
THAN $2 TRILLION OVER
A DECADE.
>> WITHOUT ALL THE
DETAILS WE'RE STILL
FIGURING IT OUT, BUT
THE WINNERS ARE
TODAY'S TAXPAYERS
BECAUSE WE'RE GOING TO
HAVE A BIG TAX CUT
WHERE THE BILL IS
ADDED TO THE DEBT AND
THE LOSERS ARE OUR
KIDS WHO ARE GOING TO
HAVE TO PAY FOR THAT.
>> Reporter: THEY SAY
THE PLAN WON'T BENEFIT
WEALTHY PEOPLE LIKE
HIMSELF.
>> I'M DOING THE RIGHT
THING, AND IT'S NOT
GOOD FOR ME, BELIEVE
ME.
>> Reporter: DEMOCRATS
NOT BUYING IT.
>> HE AIN'T WALKING
THE WALK.
THIS IS AIMED AT THE
WEALTHIEST PEOPLE IN
AMERICA.
THEY DO FAR AND AWAY
THE BEST.
>> Reporter: THIS TAX
CUT CRITICAL TO A
PRESIDENT WHO EIGHT
MONTHS IN STILL
BATTLING AND NEEDS A
LEGISLATIVE WIN
PROMISING HE'LL
REVISIT HEALTHCARE
AFTER REACHING ACROSS
THE AISLE.
>> I'LL MEET WITH
DEMOCRATS AND SEE IF I
CAN GET A HEALTHCARE
PLAN THAT'S EVEN
BETTER.
>> Reporter: ALSO
TONIGHT, THE PRESIDENT
DEALING WITH ANOTHER
EMBARRASSING SETBACK
AFTER THE
ESTABLISHMENT
CANDIDATE HE ENDORSED
LOST IN ALABAMA
SENATE'S PRIMARY.
OVERNIGHT THE
PRESIDENT DELETING HIS
TWEETS PROMOTING
LUTHER STRANGE AND
POSTING A NEW ONE
PRAISING THE WINNER
ROY MOORE BACKED BY
STEVE BANNON.
LESTER?
>> PETER ALEXANDER AT
THE WHITE HOUSE,
THANKS.
>>> TONIGHT ONE OF THE
PRESIDENT'S TOP AIDES,
HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICE SECRETARY TOM
PRICE IS UNDER FIRE
AND FACING SCRUTINY
FROM CONGRESS OVER THE
NUMBER OF FLIGHTS HE'S
BEEN TAKING ON PRIVATE
JETS, LEAVING
TAXPAYERS ON THE HOOK
FOR THE COST INSTEAD
OF FLYING COMMERCIAL.
WE GET DETAILS NOW
FROM OUR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT KRISTEN
WELKER.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT,
WITH A FIRESTORM
GROWING OVER HIS
HEALTH AND HUMAN
SERVICES SECRETARY TOM
PRICE FOR CHARGING
TAXPAYERS FOR PRIVATE
JET TRAVEL, PRESIDENT
TRUMP UNLEASHING THIS
WARNING.
>> I WAS LOOKING INTO
IT, AND I WILL LOOK
INTO IT.
AND I WILL TELL YOU
PERSONALLY I'M NOT
HAPPY ABOUT IT.
I AM NOT HAPPY ABOUT
IT.
AND I LET HIM KNOW IT.
>> Reporter: AND ASKED
IF HE PLANS TO FIRE
PRICE, THE PRESIDENT
ONLY SAYING --
NOW THE PRESSURE'S
MOUNTING WITH POLITICO
REPORTING TODAY PRICE
TOCK AN AUGUST CHARTER
FLIGHT THE AN
EXCLUSIVE RESORT IN
GEORGIA WHERE HE AND
HIS WIFE OWN PROPERTY.
THE STATED PURPOSE --
A MEDICAL CONFERENCE,
BUT PRICE ARRIVED A
DAY AND A HALF EARLY.
FEDERAL TRAVEL
REGULATIONS SAY AN
OFFICIAL CAN ONLY
CHARTER A PLANE IF NO
SCHEDULED COMMERCIAL
AIRLINE SERVICE IS
REASONABLY AVAILABLE.
BUT TONIGHT BIPARTISAN
CONGRESSIONAL
INVESTIGATORS ARE
DEMANDING ANSWERS.
>> WHETHER YOU'RE
REPUBLICAN OR
DEMOCRAT, YOU HAVE A
RESPONSIBILITY TO BE A
GOOD STEWARD OF THE
TAXPAYER DOLLAR.
>> CLEARLY WE'VE GOT
SOME ABUSE HERE AND WE
HAVE GOT TO ADDRESS
IT.
>> Reporter: IN ALL
POLITICO REPORTS THAT
TWO DOZEN CHARTER
FLIGHTS THIS YEAR WITH
A PRICE TAG OF MORE
THAN $300,000 TO
TAXPAYERS INCLUDING
ONE CHARTER FLIGHT
FROM WASHINGTON, D.C.,
TO PHILADELPHIA THAT
COST AN ESTIMATED
$25,000.
A COMMERCIAL FLIGHT
WOULD HAVE COST $725.
HHS HAS INSISTED PRICE
DIDN'T BREAK ANY
RULES.
LAST WEEK PRICE
INDICATED HE WOULD
STOP TAKING PRIVATE
FLIGHTS.
>> WE'VE HEARD THE
CRITICISM.
WE'VE HEARD THE
CONCERNS.
AND WE TAKE THAT VERY
SERIOUSLY AND HAVE
TAKEN IT TO HEART.
>> Reporter: NOW IN
TOTAL THERE ARE THREE
CABINET SECRETARIES
THE UNDER SCRUTINY FOR
THEIR TRAVEL INCLUDING
TREASURY SECRETARY
STEVEN MNUCHIN WHO
REQUESTED A GOVERNMENT
FLIGHT FOR HIS
EUROPEAN HONEYMOON BUT
DROPPED THE IDEA.
LATE TONIGHT, THE
DEPARTMENT OF HEALTH
AND HUMAN SERVICES
RESPONDED SAYING
SECRETARY PRICE
SUPPORTS THE INSPECTOR
GENERAL'S
INVESTIGATION AND HAS
INITIATED HIS OWN
REVIEW OF TRAVEL
PROCEDURES.
LESTER?
>> KRISTEN WELKER,
THANK YOU.
>>> THERE IS NEW
FALLOUT FROM THAT
BRIBERY SCANDAL
ROCKING COLLEGE
BASKETBALL.
LOUISVILLE HEAD COACH
RICK PITINO, ONE OF
THE BIGGEST NAMES IN
THE SPORT, WHO IS
ALREADY IN THE HALL OF
FAME, WAS PLACED ON
UNPAID LEAVE TODAY
AFTER THE FBI ARRESTED
A NUMBER OF ASSISTANT
COACHES FROM OTHER
PROMINENT COLLEGES.
NBC'S ANN THOMPSON HAS
THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: RICK
PITINO, COLLEGE
BASKETBALL'S HIGHEST
PAID COACH FOR
PERENNIAL POWERHOUSE,
THE UNIVERSITY OF
LOUISVILLE.
>> COACH, DID THEY
FIRE YOU?
>> Reporter: TODAY
PLACED ON UNPAID
ADMINISTRATIVE LEAVE.
AFTER A FEDERAL
CRIMINAL INVESTIGATION
TUESDAY ALLEGED TWO
UNNAMED LOUISVILLE
COACHES WORKED WITH AN
ADIDAS EXECUTIVE TO
PAY HIGH SCHOOL
RECRUITS SIX FIGURES
TO GO TO LOUISVILLE, A
SCHOOL SPONSORED BY
ADIDAS.
LOUISVILLE INTERIM
PRESIDENT GREG POSTEL
TOLD REPORTERS HOSE
ANGRY AND EMBARRASSED.
IN THE COMPLAINT ONE
OF THE COACHES SAYS OF
THE PAY TO PLAY
SCHEME, WE GOT TO BE
VERY LOW KEY BECAUSE
THE SCHOOL WAS ALREADY
ON NCAA PROBATION.
SOME OF THE SCANDAL
THAT HAS DOGGED
PITINO'S REMARKABLY
SUCCESSFUL PROGRAM.
IN JUNE, THE NCAA
SANCTIONED LOUISVILLE
AFTER AN ASSISTANT
COACH HIRED STRIPPERS
AND PROSTITUTES FOR
PLAYERS AND RECRUITS.
PITINO, WHO DENIED
KNOWLEDGE, WAS
SUSPENDED FOR THE
FIRST FIVE GAMES OF
THE CONFERENCE SEASON.
IS THIS ONE SCANDAL
TOO MANY?
>> FOR RICK PITINO,
YES.
HE'S GOING TO BE
BASICALLY BE VIEWED AS
SOMEONE THAT IS
POLARIZING TO THE
POINT WHERE NOBODY IN
COLLEGE BASKETBALL'S
GOING TO WANT ANY PART
OF HIM.
>> Reporter: PITINO'S
ATTORNEY INSISTS THE
COACH HAS DONE NOTHING
WRONG.
AS FOR LOUISVILLE,
THERE'S THE RISK THE
NCAA COULD ISSUE THE
DEATH PENALTY, BANNING
THE STORIED BASKETBALL
PROGRAM FOR AT LEAST A
YEAR.
>> IF THE NCAA WANTS
TO SEND A MESSAGE THAT
IT REALLY CAN ENFORCE
ITS RULE BOOK, THIS
WOULD SEEM LIKE THE
PERFECT TIME TO DO SO.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
LOUISVILLE IS ALREADY
PAYING A PRICE, WHICH
TWO TOP RATED HIGH
SCHOOL RECRUITS
ANNOUNCING THEY'LL GO
ELSEWHERE.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> THE MYSTERY IS
DEEPENING OVER WHAT
HAPPENED TO AMERICAN
STUDENT OTTO WARMBIER.
AFTER HIS PARENTS
BROKE THEIR SILENCE
AND CLAIM HE WAS
TORTURED, INFORMATION
FROM THE CORONER WHO
EXAMINED HIS BODY IS
RAISING NO QUESTIONS
TONIGHT.
WE GET THE LATEST FROM
NBC NEWS FOREIGN
AFFAIRS CORRESPONDENT
ANDREA MITCHELL.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE CORONER GOING
PUBLIC FOR FIRST TIME
ABOUT 22-YEAR-OLD
AMERICAN OTTO
WARMBIER'S MYSTERIOUS
DEATH JUST DAYS AFTER
RETURNING FROM
CAPTIVITY IN NORTH
KOREA.
>> THERE ARE WERE A
FEW SMALL SCARS THAT
WE DOCUMENTED.
>> Reporter: SHE SAYS
THERE'S EVIDENCE OF A
BREATHING TUBE, NOTES
SCARS ON HIS KNEES,
ANKLE, FEET AND ARMS
INCLUDING A TRACHY OT
OMY SCAR, BUT NO WAY
OF KNOWING WHEN THAT
PROCEDURE WAS DONE.
>> I MEAN, COULD THAT
HAVE BEEN TORTURE AT
THE TIME?
WE DON'T KNOW.
WE DON'T KNOW WHAT
HAPPENED TO HIM.
AND THAT'S THE BOTTOM
LINE.
>> Reporter: HIS
PARENTS DESCRIBING HIS
HORRIFIC CONDITION TO
FOX NEWS TUESDAY.
>> THEY KIDNAPPED
OTTO, THEY TORTURED
HIM, THEY
INTENTIONALLY INJURED
HIM.
>> Reporter: ONLY DAYS
LATER HE DIED FROM
COMPLICATIONS OF A
LONG-TERM BRAIN INJURY
CAUSED BY LACK OF
OXYGEN.
THE PARENTS ALSO SAY
THEIR SON'S TEETH WERE
DAMAGED.
>> IT LOOKED LIKE
SOMEONE HAD TAKEN A
PAIR OF PLIERS AND
REARRANGED HIS BOTTOM
TEETH.
>> Reporter: ALTHOUGH
THE CORONER SAYS A
FORENSIC DENTIST SAW
NO EVIDENCE OF THAT.
AT THE PARENTS'
REQUEST NO AUTOPSY WAS
PERFORMED BUT THE
CORONER SAYS AN
AUTOPSY WOULD NOT
INVOLVE MORE THAN
THEIR RIGOROUS
POSTMORTEM EXAMS
INCLUDING A CT SCAN.
>> I WISH WE HAD SOME
ANSWERS, AND I KNOW
THAT THE FAMILY IS
LOOKING FOR ANSWERS,
BUT AT THIS POINT,
WE'RE NEVER GOING TO
KNOW.
>> Reporter: UNLESS
HIS CAPTORS COME
FORWARD AND REVEAL
WHAT THEY DID TO OTTO
WARMBIER IN PRISON.
ANDREA MITCHELL, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> TURNING OVERSEAS
NOW, BOTH ISIS AND THE
TALIBAN CLAIM THEY
TARGETED DEFENSE
SECRETARY JAMES MATTIS
IN A ROCKET ATTACK ON
AFGHANISTAN'S MAIN
AIRPORT TODAY, BUT
MATTIS HAD ACTUALLY
LEFT THE AIRPORT HOURS
BEFORE, ACCORDING TO
THE AFGHAN PRESIDENT.
THE UNANNOUNCED TRIP
HAS MANAGED HIS FIRST
TRIP TO THE COUNTRY
SINCE PRESIDENT TRUMP
REVEALED HIS NEW
STRATEGY FOR THE
ONGOING WAR THERE.
>>> STILL AHEAD AS WE
CONTINUE, FOOD ALLERGY
ALERT.
THE SKYROCKETING
NUMBER OF ADULTS
SUDDENLY HIT BY SEVERE
REACTIONS OFTEN
WITHOUT ANY WARNING
SIGNS.
WHAT YOU NEED TO KNOW
TO PROTECT YOURSELF.
>>> ALSO THE NEW
INFLIGHT PERK ON ONE
AIRLINE THAT LETS YOU
ALWAYS STAY CONNECTED
EVEN AT
Throughout my career, I've been
fortunate enough to travel to
many interesting places.
ALWAYS STAY CONNECTED
EVEN AT
I've always wanted to create
those experiences for others.
With my advisor's help along the
way, it's finally my turn to be
the host.
When you have the right
financial advisor, life can be
brilliant.
Ameriprise
Patrick woke up
with a sore back.
But he's got work to do.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
There's a denture adhesive that
holds strong until evening.
Fixodent Plus adhesives.
Just one application gives
you superior hold
even at the end of the day
Fixodent. Strong more
like natural teeth.
It's date night and...
ugh... nothing fits.
You're just bloated from gas.
I can see it
and I know you feel it.
Take Gas-X®,
the #1 gas relief brand.
It relieves pressure
and bloating fast!
So you can wear
whatever you want.
is is Not this John Smith.ith.
Or this John Smith.
Or any of the other hundreds of
John Smiths that are
Humana Medicare Advantage
members.
No, it's this John Smith.
Who we paired with a Humana team
member to help address his
own specific health needs.
At Humana, we take a personal
approach to your health,
to provide care that's just as
unique as you are.
No matter what your name is.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH SOME SURPRISING
HEALTH NEWS FROM
DOCTORS ABOUT FOOD
ALLERGIES.
THEY'RE COMMONLY
DIAGNOSED IN KIDS, BUT
RESEARCHERS SAY
THERE'S BEEN A
DRAMATIC INCREASE IN
CASES FIRST DIAGNOSED
AMONG ADULTS WHEN
FOODS THEY'VE EATEN
ALL THEIR LIVES
SUDDENLY BECOME
DANGEROUS.
NBC'S KRISTEN DAHLGREN
HAS OUR REPORT.
>> HOW ARE YOU TODAY?
>> I'M REAL GOOD,
THANK YOU.
>> Reporter: GOING OUT
TO EAT ISN'T EASY
ANYMORE FOR MARVY.
>> I WOULD LIKE THE
CHEF'S SALAD.
>> Reporter: THREE
YEARS AGO SHE HAD AN
ALLERGIC REACTION SO
SEVERE SHE SPENT TWO
DAYS IN INTENSIVE
CARE.
>> I COULDN'T BREATHE,
I COULDN'T SWALLOW.
>> WE NEED TO DO A
SKIN PRICK TEST.
>> Reporter: DOCTORS
GAVE HER AN ALLERGY
TEST.
THE RESULTS WERE
SHOCKING.
AT AGE 50 SHE SUDDENLY
DEVELOPED AN ALLERGY
TO ONE OF HER FAVORITE
FOODS, SHELLFISH.
>> IT IS MIND BOGGLING
TO ME.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND HOW
IT HAPPENED.
>> Reporter: CASES
LIKE HERS ARE ON THE
RISE.
A NEW STUDY FINDING
SEVERE ALLERGIC
REACTIONS TO FOOD HAVE
SKYROCKETED MORE THAN
300% OVER THE LAST TEN
YEARS.
HALF OF ADULTS WITH
FOOD ALLERGIES DEVELOP
THEM AFTER AGE 18.
>> IT'S VERY
CONCERNING BECAUSE
THERE AREN'T ANY
WARNING SIGNS.
>> Reporter: ADULTS
OFTEN HAVE DIFFERENT
SYMPTOMS THAN CHILDREN
AND REACTIONS CAN BE
MORE SEVERE.
>> RESPIRATORY
DIFFICULTY AND AS WELL
AS GI SYMPTOMS THAT
KIDS DON'T GET
SOMETIMES.
>> Reporter: PEOPLE
WITH SEASONAL
ALLERGIES ARE MORE
PRONE TO DEVELOPING
FOOD ALERJS.
IT COULD BE TOO MANY
PROCESSED FOODS MAKING
YOU SENSITIVE.
STICK TO A VARIED DIET
WITH A LOT OF FRESH
FOODS.
SHE NOW MAKES SURE TO
KEEP AN EPIPEN AND IS
EXTRA CAUTIOUS.
>> I HAVE A VERY
SEVERE ALLERGY TO
SHELLFISH.
>> Reporter: ONE WRONG
BITE --
>> I COULD SWELL UP
AND I DON'T KNOW WHAT
WOULD HAPPEN.
I DON'T WANT TO TEST
IT FOR SURE.
>> Reporter: NOT JUST
KIDS BUT GROWN-UPS
FACED WITH A GROWING
RISK.
KRISTEN DAHLGREN, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> UP NEXT, AS WE
CONTINUE TONIGHT,
PRESIDENT TRUMP TAKING
A SWIPE AT FACEBOOK.
HOW THE SOCIAL
I didn't know where I
was from ethnically.
So we sent that sample
off to Ancestry.
My Ancestry DNA results
are that I am 26% Nigerian.
I am just trying to
learn as much as I can
about my culture.
I put the Gele on my
head and I looked
into the mirror and I
was trying not to cry.
Because it's a hat,
but it's like the most
important hat I've
ever owned.
Discover the story only
your DNA can tell.
Order your kit now
at AncestryDNA.com.
Approaching Medicare
eligibility?
Don't put off checking out your
options until sixty-five.
Now is a good time to get the
ball rolling.
Consider an AARP Medicare
Supplement Insurance Plan
insured by UnitedHealthcare
Insurance Company.
Like any of these types
of plans,
it could help you with
out-of-pocket
medical costs.
Call now and request your free
Decision Guide
and explore the range of AARP
Medicare Supplement Plans.
Start gathering the information
you need...
to roll into sixty-five with
confidence.
>>> BACK NOW WITH A
WAR OF WORDS BETWEEN
PRESIDENT TRUMP AND
FACEBOOK AFTER THE
PRESIDENT TWEETED,
QUOTE, FACEBOOK WAS
ALWAYS ANTI-TRUMP,
FACEBOOK'S CEO MARK
ZUCKERBERG FIRED BACK
SAYING BOTH SIDES ARE
UPSET ABOUT IDEAS AND
CONTENT THEY DON'T
LIKE.
BUT ZUCKERBERG ALSO
SAID HE WAS SORRY FOR
DISPUTING CONCERNS
THAT FACEBOOK MAY HAVE
BEEN USED TO INFLUENCE
THE OUTCOME OF THE
LAST ELECTION.
HE SAID, QUOTE,
CALLING THAT CRAZY WAS
DISMISSIVE, AND I
REGRET IT.
FACEBOOK, TWITTER AND
GOOGLE HAVE ALL BEEN
ASKED TO TESTIFY IN
THE SENATE'S RUSSIA
PROBE.
>>> UP IN THE AIR,
DELTA SAYS IT WILL
BEGIN PROVIDING FREE
TEXTING ON FLIGHTS
STARTING SUNDAY.
THE MOVE MAKES THE
AIRLINE THE FIRST
U.S.-BASED CARRIER TO
OFFER FREE MOBILE
MESSAGING, ALLOWING
PASSENGERS TO TEXT VIA
I-MESSAGE, WHAT'SUP
AND FACEBOOK MESSENGER
THROUGH NO EXTRA COST
THROUGH ITS GO GO
INTERNET SERVICE.
IF YOU ARE WORRIED
ABOUT YOUR SEATMATE
YAPPING ON THE PHONE
THE WHOLE FLIGHT,
PHONE CALLS ARE STILL
BANNED.
>>> HE WAS PRESIDENT
FOR EIGHT YEARS BUT
HE'LL BE A DAD FOR THE
REST OF HIS LIFE.
AND LIKE MANY FATHERS,
BARACK OBAMA HAD A
TOUGH TIME DROPPING
HIS DAUGHTER OFF AT
COLLEGE AFTER HE TOLD
19-YEAR-OLD MALIA
GOOD-BYE AT HARVARD,
THE FORMER PRESIDENT
SAID HE WAS MOVED TO
TEARS COMPARING THE
EXPERIENCE TO, QUOTE,
OPEN HEART SURGERY.
WELCOME TO THE CLUB,
SIR.
>>> UP NEXT, AFTER
SUFFERING A TERRIBLE
TRAGEDY AT A DISNEY
RESORT, PARENTS NOW ON
A MISSION TO HELP
OTHER FAMILIES.
>>> NBC "NIGHTLY NEWS"
IS BROUGHT TO YOU BY
PACIFIC LIFE.
PROTECTING GENERATIONS
OF FAMILIES FOR 150
YEARS.
What is the Power of Pacific?
It's life insurance and
retirement solutions to
help you reach your goals.
It's having the confidence
to create the future
that's most meaningful to you.
It's protection for generations
of families,
and 150 years of strength
and stability.
And when you're able to
harness all of that,
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask a financial advisor
about Pacific Life.
[radio alarm]
♪ ♪
Julie is living with metastatic
breast cancer,
which is breast cancer
that has spread
to other parts of her body.
She's also taking prescription
IBRANCE with an aromatase
inhibitor,
which is for postmenopausal
women with hormone receptor-
positive HER2- metastatic breast
cancer as the first
hormonal based therapy.
♪ ♪
IBRANCE plus letrozole was
significantly more effective
at delaying disease progression
versus letrozole.
And IBRANCE plus letrozole
shrunk tumors in over half of
these patients.
Patients taking IBRANCE can
develop low white blood cell
counts,
which may cause serious
infections
that can lead to death.
Before taking IBRANCE,
tell your doctor if you have
fever, chills,
or other signs of infection
liver or kidney problems,
are pregnant, breastfeeding,
or plan to become pregnant.
Common side effects include
low red blood cell
and low platelet counts...
...infections, tiredness,
nausea, sore mouth,
abnormalities in liver
blood tests,
diarrhea, hair thinning or loss,
vomiting, rash,
and loss of appetite.
Julie calls it her "new" normal.
Because a lot has changed,
but a lot hasn't.
Ask your doctor about IBRANCE,
the number-one-prescribed,
FDA-approved oral combination
treatment for HR+/HER2- MBC.
Are you taking the Tissue Test?
Yep, and my teeth are yellow.
Time for Whitestrips.
Crest Glamorous White
Whitestrips are the only
ADA-accepted whitening strips
proven to be safe and effective.
And they whiten 25x better than
a leading whitening toothpaste.
Crest. Healthy, beautiful
smiles for life.
Rethink what's possible.
Rethink your allergy pills.
Flonase Sensimist Allergy Relief
helps block 6 key
inflammatory
substances
with a
gentle mist.
Most allergy
pills
only block
one.
And 6 is greater
than one.
Flonase Sensimist.
♪
>>> FINALLY, AN UPDATE
ON THE FAMILY THAT
MADE NATIONAL
HEADLINES AFTER A
TRAGEDY AT A DISNEY
WORLD RESORT.
IN AN INSTANT THEY
LOST THEIR 2-YEAR-OLD
SON TO AN ALLIGATOR
ATTACK.
NOW THEY'RE LAUNCHING
A NEW EFFORT TO HONOR
HIS MEMORY WHILE
HELPING OTHER
FAMILIES.
OUR KERRY SANDERS HAS
THE STORY.
>> Reporter: IT'S BEEN
A PAINFUL YEAR SINCE
2-YEAR-OLD LANE GRAVES
SHOCKING DEATH AT A
DISNEY RESORT.
>> LANE IN A VERY
SPECIAL LIGHT ABOUT
HIM.
>> Reporter: TODAY THE
NEBRASKA TODDLER'S
PARENTS TURNING THEIR
GRIEF TO COMFORT FOR
OTHERS.
>> WE DON'T KNOW IF
WE'RE GOING TO BE ABLE
TO PAY OUR UTILIIES
BACK HOME.
>> Reporter: WITH THE
HELP OF A PUBLIC
SERVICE VIDEO THEY
ANNOUNCED PARENTS AT
NEBRASKA MEDICINE WILL
NO LONGER HAVE THE
ADDED BURDEN OF HOW TO
PAY EXPENSES LIKE
ELECTRIC BILLS OR THE
MORTGAGE WHILE THEIR
CHILDREN ENDURE ORGAN
TRANSPLANTS.
>> MOST TIMES A PARENT
AND SOMETIMES A SINGLE
PARENT HAS TO LEAVE
THEIR JOB.
>> SO OUR JOB IS TO
MAKE SURE WE'RE TAKING
CARE OF ANY EXPENSES
THAT THEY HAVE WHILE
THEY'RE GOING THROUGH
THE TRANSPLANT AS WELL
AS IF THERE'S ANY
EXPENSES THAT THEY
HAVE AT HOME.
>> THIS ONE FLIES,
TOO.
>> Reporter:
3-YEAR-OLD EVIE HAD
MULTIPLE ORGAN
TRANSPLANTS IN SKRL.
HER SINGLE MOTHER AT
HER SIDE EVERY DAY
SINCE.
>> SHE NEEDS YOU, AND
HER LIFE COUNTS ON IT.
>> Reporter: WHAT DID
SHE SAY, SHE WANTS YOU
TO BE HERE, MOM.
>> YEAH, I KNOW.
>> Reporter: AND YOU
FEEL THAT BEYOND HER
ASKING FOR IT.
YOU KNOW YOU NEED TO
BE HERE.
>> MM-HMM.
IT DOESN'T STOP
OUTSIDE THESE WALLS.
LIFE GOES ON.
IT DOESN'T MATTER.
YOU STILL HAVE TO PAY
YOUR BILLS.
>> Reporter: LANE
GRAVES' PARENTS WITH
AN UNIMAGINABLE LOSS
NOW GIVING WHERE FEW
REALIZED THERE WAS A
NEED.
♪ BABA BLACK SHEEP ♪
>> Reporter: ALL IN
MEMORY OF THEIR SON.
KERRY SANDERS, NBC
NEWS, OMAHA.
>>> WE APPRECIATE YOU
SPENDING PART OF YOUR
EVENING WITH US.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS WEDNESDAY
NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS, THANK YOU FOR
WATCHING AND GOOD
♪♪
From investing in communities,
hungry for growth.
Lending to small businesses
fueled by a dream.
And supporting causes
inspired by love...
Eastern Bank is here.
To do good.
To do right.
To do more.
To help all of us do better.
So join us.
For good.
♪♪