THANK YOU, TAMMIE.
THANK YOU FOR WATCHING.
I'M JACQUELINE LONDON.
UP NEXT "NBC NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
WE'LL SEE YOU BACK HERE TONIGHT
AT 11:00.
>>> TONIGHT, POWERLESS
AND PARALYZED.
HURRICANE MARIA
GAINING STRENGTH AND
ON THE MOVE.
AFTER KNOCKING OUT ALL
POWER IN PUERTO RICO.
NEIGHBORHOODS
DEMOLISHED, STREETS
UNDER WATER.
WE'RE LIVE IN THE
DISASTER ZONE.
>>> SIGNS OF LIFE.
THE URGENT SEARCH FOR
VICTIMS TRAPPED IN
THAT COLLAPSED SCHOOL.
MORE THAN 48 HOURS
AFTER MEXICO'S
EARTHQUAKE.
TONIGHT NEW HOP AS
RESCUERS PULL
SURVIVORS FROM THE
RUBBLE.
>>> PUNISHING NORTH
KOREA.
PRESIDENT TRUMP'S
TOUGH NEW ACTIONS
TURNING UP THE HEAT ON
KIM JONG-UN'S REGIME.
>>> FACEBOOK AND
RUSSIA.
CEO MARK ZUCKERBERG
CAVING TO CONGRESS.
THE SENSITIVE INFO
HE'S AGREED TO TURN
OVER IN THE RUSSIA
PROBE.
>>> DEADLY EPIDEMIC.
A PHARMACY GIANT
TAKING A STAND.
WHAT IT MEANS FOR YOUR
PRESCRIPTIONS.
>>> AND BIRTHDAY
WISHES.
GIVING EVERY KID A
CHANCE TO CELEBRATE
THEIR SPECIAL DAY.
"NIGHTLY NEWS" BEGINS
RIGHT NOW.
>>> FROM NBC NEWS
WORLD HEADQUARTERS IN
NEW YORK, THIS IS NBC
"NIGHTLY NEWS" WITH
LESTER HOLT.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
AND THANK YOU FOR
BEING WITH US.
36 HOURS AFTER
HURRICANE MARIA
STORMED ASHORE IN
PUERTO RICO RIPPING
APART HOMES AND
FLOODING STREETS, IT'S
POSSIBLE WE HAVE NOT
YET SEEN THE WORST OF
IT.
THAT'S BECAUSE ENTIRE
AREAS REMAIN CUT OFF
THIS EVENING.
POWER IS OUT ACROSS
THE ISLAND.
COMMUNICATIONS ARE
SPOTTY.
WATER IS RUNNING
SHORT.
AND THE NUMBER OF
POSSIBLE CASUALTIES IS
STILL UNKNOWN.
TONIGHT THE MILLIONS
OF AMERICANS THERE
WAIT AS AN URGENT
RELIEF EFFORT KICKS
INTO HIGH GEAR.
LET'S GET THE LATEST
FROM OUR GABE
GUTIERREZ.
GABE?
>> Reporter: LESTER,
MARIA'S DEATH TOLL IS
NOW UP TO 18 ACROSS
THE CARIBBEAN
INCLUDING ONE DEATH
HERE IN PUERTO RICO.
BUT THE TRUE EXTENT OF
THE DAMAGE IS NOT YET
KNOWN.
HERE MANY ROADS ARE
IMPASSABLE AND
COMMUNICATIONS SYSTEMS
ARE DOWN WHICH MEANS
IT COULD TAKE QUITE A
WHILE TO GET A HANDLE
ON THE FULL SCOPE OF
MARIA'S DESTRUCTION.
TONIGHT, IN THE WAKE
OF HURRICANE MARIA,
PARTS OF PUERTO RICO
ARE DESPERATE.
RESIDENTS FORCED TO
WADE THROUGH
WAIST-HIGH WATER TO
SAFETY.
MANY AREAS UNREACHABLE
BY LAND OR BY PHONE
AND VIRTUALLY THE
ENTIRE U.S. TERRITORY
IS WITHOUT POWER.
SEARCH AND RESCUE
OPERATIONS FROM
MULTIPLE AGENCIES IN
PUERTO RICO AND THE
U.S. MAINLAND NOW
UNDER WAY.
DOZENS OF FAMILIES
RESCUED DURING THE
EARLY MORNING WITH
JUST FLASHLIGHTS TO
GUIDE THEM IN THE SAN
JUAN COMMUNITY.
TODAY WE RODE ALONG
WITH THE NATIONAL
GUARD AND GOVERNOR
RICARDO ROSSELLO WHO
HASN'T BEEN ABLE TO
COMMUNICATE NOT JUST
WITH MAYORS IN SOME
PARTS OF THE ISLAND
BUT EVEN HIS OWN
PARENTS OUTSIDE SAN
JUAN.
>> EVERYBODY HAS FELT
THE PAIN AND THE
ANXIETY OF NOT
SPEAKING TO LOVED
ONES.
>> Reporter: MARIA'S
PATH OF DESTRUCTION IS
RELENTLESS,
DEVASTATING THE
DOMINICAN REPUBLIC
OVERNIGHT.
DANGEROUS STORM SURGE
AND DAMAGING WINDS
THAT RIP ROOFS OFF
HOMES.
NEW VIDEO OUT OF ST.
CROIX TODAY SHOWS THE
EXTENT OF THE
DESTRUCTION THERE.
>> BIG MAHOGANY TREES
THAT WERE ROOTED UP.
>> Reporter: IN
HARD-HIT DOMINICA
OFFICIALS CONFIRM 15
PEOPLE DIED FROM THE
STORM.
FOR MANY IN PUERTO
RICO, THE CLEANUP IS
JUST BEGINNING.
IT IS STILL EXTREMELY
DIFFICULT TO GET
AROUND SAN JUAN.
AND THIS IS PART OF
THE REASON WHY.
POWER LINES ACROSS
THIS AREA ARE DOWN.
VIRTUALLY THE ENTIRE
ISLAND IS WITHOUT
POWER.
MANY ROADS ARE
IMPASSABLE.
AS YOU CAN SEE, WE'RE
JUST NOW STARTING TO
GET OUR FIRST LOOK AT
THE DEVASTATION.
>> IT'S TOO MUCH.
IT'S TOO MUCH.
>> Reporter: ERNESTO
PEDRON RODE OUT THE
STORM IN HIS HOME AND
TODAY RETURNED TO HIS
BUSINESS.
>> IT'S SHOCKING.
REALLY DEVASTATING.
A LOT OF MONEY IN A
SHORT TIME.
>> Reporter: EARLY
ESTIMATES SHOW THE
DAMAGE ACROSS PUERTO
RICO COULD TOTAL $30
BILLION.
THE EMOTIONAL TOLL
CAN'T BE MEASURED.
GABE GUTIERREZ, NBC
NEWS, SAN JUAN, PUERTO
RICO.
>>> THIS IS GADI
SCHWARTZ.
DARK DAYS IN PUERTO
RICO EXPECTED TO LAST
MONTHS AFTER HURRICANE
MARIA RIPPED APART THE
ISLAND'S ENTIRE POWER
GRID.
NEARLY ALL OF ITS 3.5
MILLION RESIDENTS
WITHOUT ELECTRICITY
TONIGHT.
CELL PHONE SERVICE SO
UNRELIABLE THAT PEOPLE
LIKE THIS WOMAN STILL
HAVEN'T HEARD FROM
THEIR FAMILY.
>> WE'RE DESPERATE.
I HAVE LIVED HERE FOR
35 YEAR AND THIS IS
TOO MUCH.
>> Reporter: SHE'S
DESPERATE FOR ANY NEWS
OF HER MOTHER.
>> I HAVEN'T TALKED TO
MY MOM EITHER.
SO I'M TRYING TO GO TO
MY MOM'S HOUSE.
IT'S SAD.
>> Reporter: THE
STREETS ARE LITTERED
WITH DOWNED POWER
LINES.
THIS STORM EVEN
CRACKING CONCRETE IN
HALF.
DAMAGING AN
INFRASTRUCTURE THAT
WAS ALREADY CRUMBLING.
OFFICIALS SAY HELP IS
ON THE WAY, BUT A FULL
RECOVERY COULD TAKE
HALF A YEAR.
WHICH ONE'S GOING TO
BE WORSE, THE STORM OR
WHAT COMES AFTER THE
STORM?
>> AFTER THE STORM.
>> Reporter:
TERRIFYING FOR THOSE
STANDING IN LINE FOR
HOURS TO GET GAS TO
POWER THEIR GENERATOR.
SHE SAYS SHE'S SCARED
WHAT THE NEXT SIX
MONTHS ARE GOING TO
BRING.
SHE'S A SINGLE MOTHER.
SHE HAS TO TAKE CARE
OF HER DAUGHTER, AND
SHE DOESN'T KNOW
WHAT'S GOING TO
HAPPEN.
NOW FAMILIES ACROSS
THE I ISLAND TRYING TO
PREPARE FOR THE HUMAN
DARKNESS OF LIFE OFF
THE GRID.
GADI SCHWARTZ, NBC
NEWS, SAN JUAN, PUERTO
RICO.
>>> THE DANGER FROM
HURRICANE MARIA IS NOT
OVER YET.
THE MONSTER STORM
REGAINED STRENGTH
AFTER IT STRUCK PUERTO
RICO.
IT'S EXPECTED TO CUT
CLOSE TO TURKS AND
CAICOS LATE TONIGHT,
AND AFTER THAT THE
CURRENT TRACK SHOWS IT
BARRELING BETWEEN THE
U.S. EAST COAST AND
BERMUDA.
>>> NOW TO THE RACE
AGAINST TIME IN MEXICO
TO FIND SURVIVORS FROM
THE EARTHQUAKE.
AUTHORITIES SAY IT HAS
KILLED AT LEAST 273
PEOPLE.
TONIGHT RESCUERS
REMAIN ON THE SCENE OF
A COLLAPSED SCHOOL
URGENTLY SEARCHING FOR
VICTIMS WHO MAY STILL
BE TRAPPED.
NBC'S MIGUEL ALMAGUER
IS THERE.
>> Reporter: AFTER THE
FRANTIC CALLS FOR
SILENCE, RESCUE TEAMS
BURROWING DEEPER INTO
THIS ELEMENTARY
SCHOOL.
CONFLICTING REPORTS OF
WHO MAY BE TRAPPED
INSIDE.
EARLIER RESCUERS
SAYING IT WAS
CHILDREN.
TONIGHT THE MEXICAN
NAVY SAYS THEY'RE ALL
ACCOUNTED FOR, BUT
THEY ARE PICKING UP
SIGNS OF LIFE.
INSIDE THIS COURTYARD,
THE CENTER OF THE
RESCUE EFFORTS, THERE
IS A CLEAR SENSE OF
URGENCY, A RACE
AGAINST TIME FOR FIRST
RESPONDERS WHO HAVEN'T
SLEPT OR EATEN IN
DAYS.
ONE OF THE VOLUNTEERS,
AN ELECTRICIAN,
CHRISTIAN JIMENEZ,
FROM L.A.
>> THE THIRD FLOOR, HE
CAME ALL THE WAY TO
THE GROUND.
HE'S REALLY BAD.
>> Reporter: THIS
RESCUE MISSION IS
DANGEROUS.
AS SEARCH TEAMS CRAWL
THROUGH SMALL POCKETS
WHERE WOODEN SUPPORT
BEAMS COULD SNAP AT
ANY MOMENT.
CHILDREN WHO SURVIVED
THE QUAKE HAVE COME TO
WATCH AS THEIR PARENTS
CLING TO HOPE.
"I HAVE NO WORDS FOR
THE FAMILY" SAYS
GABRIELA RODRIGUEZ.
IT HURTS TO KNOW THEIR
PAIN.
HEARTBREAK IS RATTLING
THE REGION.
BUSINESSES AND
COUNTLESS HOMES ARE
NOW GONE.
OVERNIGHT THREE PEOPLE
PULLED FROM THE
RUBBLE, 36 HOURS AFTER
THE EARTHQUAKE, BUT
TEARS STILL FLOOD
RESCUE SITES.
BEYA TRIZ DIAZ HAS
BEEN LOOKING FOR HER
NEPHEW SINCE TUESDAY
AND FEARS HE IS STILL
BURIED ALIVE AT WORK.
NBC'S RON MOTT
TRAVELED TO THE
EPICENTER 75 MILE FROM
MEXICO CITY.
>> THE DAMAGE IS
SIGNIFICANT.
EVERYTHING FROM THIS
300-YEAR-OLD CHURCH TO
2,000 HOMES DAMAGED OR
DESTROYED, EVEN A
CRUCIAL ROADWAY IN AND
OUT OF TOWN.
ONE BUSINESSMAN SAYS
IT WILL TAKE DECADES
TO REBUILD.
>> Reporter: THE
HEARTBREAK IS WHY THEY
NEED HOPE.
TONIGHT THIS COUNTRY
WATCHING MORE THAN
JUST A RESCUE.
THIS IS A FIGHT FOR
SURVIVAL.
HERE AT THE RESCUE
PIT, THEY ARE PUSHING
SOME FIRST RESPONDERS
AWAY.
THEY'RE CONCERNED THAT
THIS SCHOOL COULD
COLLAPSE ON RESCUE
TEAMS BELOW.
MEANTIME, THEY ARE
STILL LOOKING FOR ANY
SIGNS OF LIFE INSIDE
THAT BUILDING BELOW.
THEY SAY SURVIVORS CAN
ONLY LAST ABOUT FOUR
DAYS IN THE RUBBLE.
LESTER?
>> ALL RIGHT, MIGUEL
ALMAGUER TONIGHT.
THANK YOU.
>>> PRESIDENT TRUMP
IMPOSED NEW ECONOMIC
SANCTIONS ON NORTH
KOREA TODAY IN AN
EFFORT TO DRIVE THE
REGIME TO THE
BARGAINING TABLE TO
NEGOTIATE ITS NUCLEAR
PROGRAM.
KIM JONG-UN WITH A
FIERY RESPONSE LATE
TONIGHT CALLING
TRUMP'S U.N. SPEECH
MENTALLY DERANGED.
OUR WHITE HOUSE
CORRESPONDENT KRISTEN
WELKER HAS DETAILS.
>> Reporter: A UNITED
FRONT AT THE U.N.
TODAY AS PRESIDENT
TRUMP ORDERED SOME OF
THE TOUGHEST SANCTIONS
YET AGAINST NORTH
KOREA FLANKED BY THE
LEADERS OF JAPAN AND
SOUTH KOREA.
>> OUR NEW EXECUTIVE
ORDER WILL CUT OFF
SOURCES OF REVENUE
THAT FUND NORTH
KOREA'S EFFORTS TO
DEVELOP THE DEADLIEST
WEAPONS KNOWN TO
HUMANKIND.
>> Reporter: THE
SANCTIONS TARGET ALL
INDIVIDUALS AND
COMPANIES THAT DO
BUSINESS WITH THE
ROGUE REGIME INCLUDING
TRADING GOODS,
SERVICES, AND
TECHNOLOGY, AND IN A
SURPRISING MOVE, THE
PRESIDENT SAID CHINA'S
CENTRAL BANK HAS
ORDERED ITS OTHER
BANKS TO CUT OFF NORTH
KOREA.
MR. TRUMP HAS BEEN
PUSHING CHINA TO GET
TOUGHER FOR MONTHS.
>> THAT WAS A SOMEWHAT
UNEXPECTED MOVE, AND
WE APPRECIATE IT.
>> Reporter: ANALYSTS
SAY CHINA'S
INVOLVEMENT IS
CRITICAL.
>> IF THERE'S ANY
COUNTRY THAT HAS THE
ABILITY TO MOVE THE
NORTH KOREANS TOWARDS
NEGOTIATIONS IN A MORE
PEACEFUL OUTCOME OF
THIS CRISIS, IT'S
CHINA.
>> Reporter: THE
SANCTI
SANCTIONS, A SIGN THE
PRESIDENT STILL WANTS
TO GIVE DIPLOMACY A
CHANCE EVEN AFTER
UNLEASHING THIS THREAT
EARLIER IN THE WEEK.
>> BUT IF IT IS FORCED
TO DEFEND ITSELF OR
ITS ALLIES, WE WILL
HAVE NO CHOICE BUT TO
TOTALLY DESTROY NORTH
KOREA.
>> WHAT WOULD BE THE
DEFINITION OF BEING
FORCED TO DEFEND
OURSELVES?
>> IT'S ATTACKS ON US
OR OUR ALLIES.
>> ACTUAL ATTACK?
>> OF COURSE, OF
COURSE.
>> Reporter: STILL,
THE PRESIDENT'S
COMBATIVE LANGUAGE.
>> ROCKET MAN IS ON A
SUICIDE MISSION FOR
HIMSELF AND FOR HIS
REGIME.
>> Reporter: PROMPTING
NORTH KOREA TO COMPARE
HIM TO A DOG BARKING.
THE ROGUE REGIME HAS
ESCALATED TENSIONS BY
TESTING 22 MISSILES
SINCE FEBRUARY
INCLUDING A NUCLEAR
BOMB IN RECENT WEEKS.
LATE TONIGHT NORTH
KOREA'S STATE-RUN NEWS
AGENCY RELEASED THIS
PHOTO OF KIM JONG-UN
AS HE CALLED THE
PRESIDENT MENTALLY
DERANGED AND
THREATENED TO TAME HIM
WITH FIRE.
EARLIER IN THE DAY
PRESIDENT TRUMP WAS
ASKED IF DIALOGUE WAS
STILL POSSIBLE.
HE RESPONDED WHY NOT?
BUT FOR NOW THE WAR OF
WORDS CONTINUES.
>> KRISTEN WELKER
TONIGHT, THANK YOU.
>>> AFTER BEING
ACCUSED OF NOT DOING
ENOUGH TO STOP RUSSIA
FROM INFLUENCING THE
2016 ELECTION, THE
SOCIAL MEDIA GIANT
TODAY BOWED TO
PRESSURE FROM CONGRESS
AGREEING TO TURN OVER
THOUSANDS OF ADS TO
INVESTIGATORS IN THE
RUSSIA PROBE.
NBC NEWS BUSINESS
CORRESPONDENT JO LING
KENT HAS LATE DETAILS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
CEO MARK ZUCKERBERG
SAYS FACEBOOK WILL
HAND OVER 3,000 ADS
LINKED TO RUSSIA TO
BOTH CONGRESS AND
SPECIAL COUNSEL ROBERT
MUELLER.
>> WE'RE LOOKING TO
FOREIGN ACTORS
INCLUDING ADDITIONAL
RUSSIAN GROUPS AND
OTHER FORMER SOVIET
STATES.
>> Reporter: TAKING
NEW STEPS TO FIND OUT
HOW RUSSIA MAY HAVE
INTERFERED IN THE 2016
PRESIDENTIAL ELECTION
THROUGH TARGETED
ADVERTISING ON
FACEBOOK.
>> ANY ATTEMPTED
INTERFERENCE IS A
SERIOUS ISSUE.
>> Reporter: THE
COMPANY ADDING IT'S
POSSIBLE THAT MORE ADS
FROM RUSSIAN OR OTHER
FOREIGN ACTORS WILL BE
FOUND IN THEIR ONGOING
INTERNAL
INVESTIGATION.
SENATE INTELLIGENCE
COMMITTEE RANKING
MEMBER MARK WARNER
RESPONDED TWEETING,
IMPORTANT AND
ABSOLUTELY NECESSARY
FIRST STEP.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE
DESERVE TO KNOW THE
TRUTH ABOUT RUSSIA'S
INTERFERENCE IN THE
2016 ELECTION.
>> I WISH I COULD TELL
YOU THAT WE'RE GOING
TO BE ABLE TO STOP ALL
INTERFERENCE, BUT THAT
JUST WOULDN'T BE
REALISTIC.
BUT WE CAN MAKE IT
HARDER.
WE CAN MAKE IT MUCH
AND THAT'S WHAT WE'RE
GOING TO FOCUS ON
DOING.
>> Reporter: BUT
ZUCKERBERG WILL NOT
RELEASE WHAT HIS
COMPANY HAS FOUND TO
THE PUBLIC.
INSTEAD, FACEBOOK WILL
HIRE 250 NEW STAFFERS
TO INCREASE SCRUTINY
OF ADVERTISERS AND
DISCLOSE WHO PAYS FOR
THE ADS.
JO LING KENT, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> AS REPUBLICANS TRY
TO FIND THE VOTES FOR
THEIR LATEST ATTEMPT
TO APPEAL OBAMACARE, A
WAR OF WORDS CONTINUES
BETWEEN THE SPONSORS
OF THE BILL AND A
LATE-NIGHT TV HOST.
BUT WHO IS CORRECT
WHEN IT COMES TO A KEY
PART OF THE BILL
REGARDING COVERAGE FOR
PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS?
NBC'S KASIE HUNT HAS A
REALITY CHECK.
>> Reporter:
REPUBLICAN SENATORS
FIGHTING OVER THE
FACTS OF THEIR NEW
HEALTHCARE PLAN WITH A
LATE-NIGHT COMIC.
>> AM I NOT
UNDERSTANDING THE PART
WHERE STATE WAS BE
ALLOWED TO LET
INSURANCE COMPANIES
PRICE YOU OUT OF
COVERAGE FOR HAVING
PRE-EXISTING
CONDITIONS?
>> Reporter: SENATORS
BILL KAZ IDY AND
LINDSEY GRAHAM INSISTS
THEIR BILL MEETS THE
JIMMY KIMMEL TEST,
GUARANTEEING
AFFORDABLE COVERAGE
FOR PEOPLE LIKE
KIMMEL'S SON BILLY
BORN WITH A RARE HEART
DEFECT.
>> WE'RE GOING TO GIVE
FLEXIBILITY TO COVER
SICK PEOPLE, BUT SICK
PEOPLE WILL BE
COVERED.
>> Reporter: SO WHO IS
RIGHT?
THERESA BOHANON WOULD
LIKE TO KNOW.
HER SON DEAN WAS ALSO
BORN WITH A RARE HEART
CONDITION.
>> IT'S ALMOST CRAZY
TO ME THAT YOU NOT
ONLY HAVE TO WORRY
ABOUT YOUR CHILD'S
CARE, BUT YOU HAVE TO
WORRY ABOUT, OH, MY
GOSH, WHAT ARE THEY
DOING IN D.C. THAT
COULD POTENTIALLY
IMPACT US.
>> Reporter: THE
AFFORDABLE CARE ACT
MADE IT ILLEGAL FOR
INSURANCE COMPANIES TO
DENY SICK PEOPLE
COVERAGE.
THAT BAN WOULD STAY IN
PLACE, BUT OBAMACARE
ALSO OUTLAWED CHARGING
SICK PEOPLE DRAMATIC
CANCALLY HIGHER
PREMIUMS.
AND UNDER THIS BILL
INDIVIDUAL STATES
COULD DECIDE TO CHANGE
THAT.
>> THE STATE JUST HAS
TO SAY THAT IT INTENDS
TO MAINTAIN AFFORDABLE
ADEQUATE COVERAGE.
>> Reporter: THAT
COULD DEVASTATE THE
BOHANON FAMILY.
THEY'RE ALREADY
COLLECTING DONATIONS
TO PAY FOR THEIR SON'S
COVERAGE JUST IN CASE.
KASIE HUNT,CAPITAL.
>>> ANOTHER CYBER
ATTACK TO ALERT YOU
TO.
THIS TIME AMONG WALL
STREET'S TOP
REGULATOR, THE
SECURITIES AND
EXCHANGE COMMISSION
UNDER FIRE AFTER
ADMITTING A DATABASE
WAS BREACHED IN 2016
AND HACKERS MAY HAVE
BEEN MAKING ILLEGAL
TRADES EVEN UP TO LAST
MONTH.
THIS AFTER EQUIFAX
REVEALED A HACK THAT
AFFECTED NEARLY HALF
THE U.S. POPULATION.
>>> A MAJOR DRUGSTORE
CHAIN PUTS SHARP
LIMITS ON OPIOID
PRESCRIPTIONS IN A NEW
EFFORT TO CONTROL THE
ADDICTION CRISIS.
>>> ALSO DO BALLPARKS
NEED TO DO MORE TO
PROTECT FANS?
NEW CONCERNS TONIGHT
AFTER A FOUL BALL HIT
A GIRL A
For adults with advanced
non-small cell lung cancer,
previously treated with
platinum-based chemotherapy,
including those with an
abnormal ALK or EGFR gene
who've tried an FDA-approved
targeted therapy,
here's a question:
Who wouldn't want a chance
for another...?
Who'd say no to a...?
Who wouldn't want...
a chance to live longer.
OPDIVO (nivolumab).
OPDIVO demonstrated longer
life versus chemotherapy.
Over 40,000 of these
patients have been
prescribed OPDIVO.
OPDIVO works with
your immune system.
OPDIVO can cause your immune
system to attack normal
organs and tissues in your
body and affect how they work.
This may happen any time
during or after treatment
has ended, and may become
serious and lead to death.
See your doctor right away
if you experience new or
worsening cough; chest
pain; shortness of breath;
diarrhea; severe stomach
pain or tenderness;
severe nausea or
vomiting; extreme fatigue;
constipation;
excessive thirst or urine;
swollen ankles;
loss of appetite;
rash; itching;
headache; confusion;
hallucinations;
muscle or joint pain;
flushing; fever;
or weakness,
as this may keep
these problems
from becoming
more serious.
These are not
all the possible
side effects
of OPDIVO.
Tell your doctor about all
your medical conditions,
including immune
system problems,
or if you've had an
organ transplant,
or lung, breathing,
or liver problems.
Because who
wouldn't want...that?
Ask your doctor
about OPDIVO.
See OpdivoTV.com for
this and other indications.
Bristol-Myers Squibb
thanks the patients, nurses,
and physicians involved
in OPDIVO clinical trials.
Steve was born to move.
Over the course of 9 days
he walks 26.2 miles,
that's a marathon.
Because he chooses to
walk whenever he can.
And he does it with support
from Dr. Scholl's.
Only Dr. Scholl's has
Massaging Gel insoles
that provide all-day comfort to
keep him feeling more energized.
So he even has the energy
to take the long way home.
Keep it up, Steve!
Dr. Scholl's.
Born to Move.
>>> AS THIS COUNTRY
TRIES TO DEAL WITH A
DEADLY OPIOID DRUG
EPIDEMIC, THE PHARMACY
GIANT CVS SAID TODAY
IT WILL PLACE NEW
LIMITS ON PRI
PRESCRIPTIONS OF THE
POWERFUL AND ADDICTIVE
PAINKILLERS AS OF
FEBRUARY.
NBC'S KRISTEN DAHLGREN
REPORTS.
>> Reporter: AT CVS
STORES ACROSS THE
COUNTRY PATIENTS
SEEKING OPIOIDS FOR
SHORT-TERM PAIN
MANAGEMENT WILL SOON
BE LIMITED TO JUST A
SEVEN-DAY SUPPLY.
THE PHARMACY CHAIN
ATTEMPTS TO TURN THE
TIDE ON THE OPIOID
EPIDEMIC.
>> THE FEWER PEOPLE
THAT BECOME ADDICTED,
THEY'LL LEAD BETTER
LIVES.
WE'LL ELIMINATE HUMAN
SUFFERING.
>> Reporter: THIS
MAN'S ADDICTION
STARTED WITH A KNEE
INJURY AT 14.
>> I GOT ANOTHER
REFILL AT 30 WHEN I
DIDN'T EVEN NEED THE
REFILL.
>> Reporter: THAT LED
TO HEROIN.
>> IT TOOK MY
HAPPINESS.
IT TOOK AWAY, YOU
KNOW, WHAT LIFE IS
REALLY ABOUT.
>> Reporter: DOCTORS
WROTE MORE THAN 225
MILLION OPIOID
PRESCRIPTIONS IN 2015.
THAT'S 71
PRESCRIPTIONS PER 100
PATIENTS.
CVS' PLAN MIRRORS CDC
RECOMMENDATION ASKING
PHARMACISTS TO CONTACT
DOCTORS WHEN THEY SEE
PRESCRIPTIONS FOR MORE
MEDICATION THAN A
TYPICAL RECOVERY TIME.
THE COMPANY ALSO PLANS
TO BOOST FUNDING FOR
ADDICTION COUNSELING
AND SAFE OPIOID
DISPOSAL PROGRAMS.
>> I THINK OUR
CUSTOMERS OVERALL ARE
GOING TO BE HEARTENED
BY THIS.
>> Reporter: PATIENTS
WITH CHRONIC
CONDITIONS WOULD HAVE
DOSAGE LIMITS, WITH A
FEW EXCEPTIONS LIKE
CANCER TREATMENT.
TODAY THE NATIONAL
ACADEMY OF MEDICINE
ISSUED A REPORT
SUGGESTING DOCTORS BE
MORE CAREFUL WHEN
PRESCRIBING OPIATES.
>> WE ALL HAVE TO BEAR
RESPONSIBILITY AND
PLAY A ROLE IF WE'RE
GOING TO GET OURSELVES
OUT OF THIS EPIDEMIC.
>> Reporter: JOHN
SHOT, NOW 15 MONTHS
CLEAN, SAYS FOR HIM
LIMITS MIGHT HAVE MADE
A DIFFERENCE.
>> IT WAS JUST SAVING
THAT ONE PERSON THAT
COULD HAVE BEEN, YOU
KNOW, HAD A MORE
SUCCESSFUL LIFE.
>> Reporter: SO THAT
ONE PRESCRIPTION
DOESN'T BECOME AN
ADDICTION.
KRISTEN DAHLGREN, NBC
NEWS, LOS ANGELES.
>>> WE'LL TAKE A SHORT
BREAK.
UP NEXT YOUR FIRST
LOOK AT WHAT THE
WORLD'S TOP ATHLETES
The day after chemo might mean
a trip back to
the doctor's office,
just for a shot.
But why go back there,
when you can stay home...
...with Neulasta Onpro?
Strong chemo can put you
at risk of serious infection.
Neulasta helps
reduce infection risk
by boosting your
white blood cell count,
which strengthens
your immune system.
In a key study,
Neulasta reduced the risk
of infection from 17% to 1%...
...a 94% decrease.
Applied the day of chemo,
Neulasta Onpro is designed to
deliver Neulasta the next day.
Neulasta is for
certain cancer patients
receiving strong chemotherapy.
Do not take Neulasta
if you're allergic to
Neulasta or Neupogen
(filgrastim).
Ruptured spleen,
sometimes fatal as well as
serious lung problems,
allergic reactions,
kidney injuries,
and capillary leak syndrome
have occurred.
Report abdominal or
shoulder tip pain,
trouble breathing
or allergic reactions
to your doctor right away.
In patients with
sickle cell disorders,
serious, sometimes
fatal crises can occur.
The most common side effect
is bone and muscle ache.
So why go back there?
If you'd rather be home,
ask your doctor about
Neulasta Onpro.
I tabut with my back paines,
I couldn't sleep
and get up in time.
Then I found Aleve PM.
Aleve PM is the only one to
combine a safe sleep aid plus
the 12 hour pain relieving
strength of Aleve.
I'm back.
Aleve PM for a better AM.
♪
So, I was at Mom and Dad's
and found this.
CD's, Baseball cards...
Your old magic set?
And this wrestling ticket...
Which you still owe me for.
Seriously?
$25?
I didn't even want to go.
Ahhh, your diary.
"Mom says it's totally
natural..."
$25 is nothing.
Abracadabra, Bro.
The Bank of America
Mobile Banking App.
The fast, secure and simple way
to send money.
Ugh. Heartburn.
Sorry Ma'am.
No burning here.
Try Alka-Seltzer
Heartburn relief
gummies.
They don't taste
chalky and work fast.
MMMM. Incredible.
Can I try?
She doesn't
have heartburn.
Alka-Seltzer heartburn
relief gummies.
Enjoy the relief.
how much money do you
think you'll need in retirement?
Then we found out how many years
that money would last them.
How long do you
think we'll keep --
Oooooohhh! You stopped!
You're gonna leave me
back here at year 9?
How did this happen?
It turned out, a lot
of people fell short,
of even the average
length of retirement.
We have to think about
not when we expect to live to,
but when we could live to.
Let's plan for income that lasts
all our years in retirement.
Prudential.
Bring your challenges.
>>> WE'RE BACK NOW
WITH MAJOR LEAGUE
BASEBALL UNDER GROWING
PRESSURE TO DO MORE TO
PROTECT FANS AFTER A
HORRIFYING INCIDENT
INVOLVING A CHILD.
HERE'S NBC'S ANNE
THOMPSON.
>> Reporter: THE
ANGUISH ON THEIR
FACES.
>> JUST CROSS OUR
FINGERS AND HOPE
EVERYTHING'S OKAY.
>> Reporter: -- TELLS
THE STORY OF THE
IMPACT.
THE SEARING FOUL BALL
CLOCKED AT 100 MILES
PER HOUR.
INJURING A LITTLE
GIRL.
>> THEY'RE GOING TO
GET HELP FOR THE
PERSON THAT WAS STRUCK
BY THE BASEBALL.
>> Reporter: THE
MINNESOTA TWINS AND
THE YANKEES VISIBLY
SHAKEN INCLUDING
FRAZIER, A FATHER
HIMSELF.
>> I THOUGHT OF MY
KIDS, YOU KNOW.
I HAVE TWO KIDS UNDER
3 YEARS OLD.
AND JUST HOPE SHE'S
ALL RIGHT.
>> Reporter: TODAY THE
LITTLE GIRL'S
GRANDFATHER WENT TO
THE NEW YORK HOSPITAL
WHERE SHE'S RECOVERING
AFTER CARRYING HER OUT
OF THE STADIUM IN HIS
ARMS.
BASEBALL COMMISSIONER
ROB MANFRED NOW VOWING
TO REDOUBLE EFFORTS ON
THIS IMPORTANT ISSUE.
AFTER THE 2015
RECOMMENDATION TO
INCREASE NETTING TO
THE NEAR END OF THE
DUGOUTS AND WITHIN 70
FEET OF HOME PLATE.
TEN TEAMS HAVE GONE
EVEN FARTHER, BUT NOT
THE YANKEES.
THIS IS AT LEAST THE
THIRD TIME THIS SEASON
A FAN'S BEEN INJURED
HERE.
A BOY WITH A PIECE OF
BAT, THIS MAN WITH A
FOUL BALL, AND NOW THE
LITTLE GIRL.
>> I DON'T CARE ABOUT
THE DAMN VIEW OF THE
FAN OR WHAT.
IT'S ALL ABOUT SAFETY.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT
THE YANKEES OFFER
THOUGHTS AND PRAYERS
FOR THE CHILD, BUT NO
WORD ON WHETHER
THEY'LL DO MORE TO
PROTECT FANS.
ANNE THOMPSON, NBC
NEWS, NEW YORK.
>>> TESTS CONDUCTED ON
FORMER NFL STAR AARON
HERNANDEZ, WHO WAS
CONVICTED OF MURDER,
SHOWED THAT HE HAD THE
DEGENERATIVE BRAIN
DISEASE CTE.
THOSE TESTS FOUND THAT
THE NEW ENGLAND
PATRIOT'S TIGHT END
HAD A SEVERE FORM OF
THE DISEASE.
HERNANDEZ COMMITTED
SUICIDE IN APRIL WHILE
SERVING A LIFE
SENTENCE.
THE DISEASE HAS BEEN
FOUND IN MORE THAN 100
FORMER NFL PLAYERS AND
IS LINKED TO REPEATED
HEAD TRAUMA.
>>> JUST 140 DAYS NOW
BEFORE THE WINTER
OLYMPICS IN SOUTH
KOREA AND HERE IS WHAT
THE 2900 ATHLETES FROM
95 COUNTRIES WILL BE
CHASING -- THE GOLD,
SILVER AND BRONZE
MEDALS WERE JUST
UNVEILED.
THEY WERE DESIGNED
WITH ENGLISH LETTERING
ON THE FACE AND KOREAN
LETTERS ON THE EDGES.
>>> UP NEXT HERE
TONIGHT, THE WOMAN WHO
WAS THROWN 25,000
What are the ingredients
of a life well lived?
Is it the places you go?
The things you own?
Or the people that fill it
with meaning?
For 150 years,
generations of families
have chosen Pacific Life
for retirement and
life insurance solutions.
Protecting what's most
important to you.
That's the Power of Pacific.
Ask a financial advisor
about Pacific Life.
But he's got work to do.
with a sore back.
So he took Aleve this morning.
If he'd taken Tylenol,
he'd be stopping for
more pills right now.
Only Aleve has the
strength to stop tough pain
for up to 12 hours
with just one pill.
Tylenol can't do that.
Aleve. All Day Strong.
All Day Long.
Also try Aleve
Direct Therapy with
TENS technology for
lower back pain relief.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
When a critical patient is far
from the hospital,
the hospital must come to the
patient.
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
The AT&T network is helping
first responders
connect with medical teams in
near real time...
Stay with me, Mr. Parker.
...Saving time when it matters
most.
Stay with me, Mrs. Parker.
That's the power of and.
My friI say not if you this
protect yourself.ary.
What is scary?
Pneumococcal pneumonia.
It's a serious disease.
My doctor said the risk is
greater now that I'm over 50!
Yeah...ya-ha...
Just one dose of the PREVNAR 13®
vaccine can help protect you
from pneumococcal pneumonia-
an illness that can cause
coughing, chest pain,
difficulty breathing,
and may even put you
in the hospital.
PREVNAR 13® is approved for
adults 18 and older to help
prevent infections from
13 strains of the bacteria that
cause pneumococcal pneumonia.
You should not receive
PREVNAR 13® if you have had
a severe allergic reaction to
the vaccine or its ingredients.
If you have a weakened
immune system,
you may have a lower
response to the vaccine.
The most common side effects
were pain, redness,
and swelling at
the injection site,
limited arm movement, fatigue,
headache, muscle pain,
joint pain, less appetite,
vomiting, fever, chills,
and rash.
Get this one done!
Ask about PREVNAR 13®
at your next visit to your
doctor's office or pharmacy.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, A
STORY ABOUT SOMETHING
KIDS LOOK FORWARD TO
ALL YEAR -- BIRTHDAY
PARTIES.
AND A MOM WHO HAS
THROWN THOUSANDS OF
THEM FOR CHILDREN WHO
MIGHT NOT OTHERWISE BE
ABLE TO CELEBRATE.
NBC'S REHEMA ELLIS HAS
OUR "INSPIRING
AMERICA" REPORT.
>> Reporter: THIS IS A
BIRTHDAY PARTY FOR
KIDS WHO COULD USE
SOMETHING TO
CELEBRATE.
HOW HAPPY ARE YOU?
>> GOOD.
>> Reporter: LIKE
5-YEAR-OLD CHARLOTTE
ROGERS.
THE PARTY PLANNER IS
THE CAT IN THE HAT.
>> TODAY IS A
BIRTHDAY.
>> Reporter: ALSO
KNOWN AS MEGS YOUNG.
A MOTHER OF THREE WHO
WAS SHOCKED BY WHAT AN
11-YEAR-OLD GIRL ONCE
TOLD HER.
>> SHE SAID, MISS
MEGS, I'VE NEVER HAD A
BIRTHDAY PARTY, I'VE
NEVER EVEN HAD MY OWN
SLICE OF BIRTHDAY
CAKE.
I HONESTLY FELT IN
THAT MOMENT LIKE
SOMEONE KNOCKED THE
WIND OUT OF ME.
>> Reporter: SHE GOT
BUSY.
WHEN SHE WON $2500 IN
A CONTEST URGING
PEOPLE TO DO GOOD IN
THEIR COMMUNITY, SHE
QUIT HER JOB AND
STARTED A NONPROFIT.
THE MISSION -- CREATE
BIRTHDAY PARTIES FOR
KIDS WHO ARE POOR OR
HOMELESS.
>> IF FAMILIES ARE
STRUGGLING TO PUT FOOD
ON THE TABLE, SHELTER
THEIR FAMILIES, PAY
THEIR BILLS, THERE'S
NOT A LOT OF EXTRA.
>> Reporter: FIVE
YEARS LATER WITH MORE
HELP FROM THE
COMMUNITY, SHE
CELEBRATED 25,000
BIRTHDAYS.
BEHIND THE SCENES TOYS
ARE GIFT WRAPPED READY
TO GO AND MEGS GETS IN
CHARACTER.
>> WELCOME, EVERYBODY.
>> Reporter: KIDS GET
ALL THE PARTY
TRIMMINGS.
GAMES, TREATS.
>> MAKE A WISH.
>> Reporter: BLOWING
OUT THE CANDLES.
>> I HOPE WITH MY
WHOLE HEART THAT THAT
WISH COMES TRUE
BECAUSE THE KIDS
DESERVE IT.
>> DO YOU LOVE IT?
>> MM-HMM.
>> Reporter: AND, OF
COURSE, GIFTS.
>> I NEVER LET IT GO.
I'LL PLAY WITH IT LIKE
EVERY DAY.
>> Reporter: CREATING
THE HAPPY BIRTHDAY
MEMORIES EVERY CHILD
DREAMS ABOUT.
REHEMA ELLIS, NBC
NEWS, McKEESPORT,
PENNSYLVANIA.
>> SOMETHING TO
CELEBRATE.
WE APPRECIATE YOU
SPENDING PART OF YOUR
EVENING WITH US.
THAT IS "NIGHTLY NEWS"
FOR THIS THURSDAY
NIGHT.
I'M LESTER HOLT.
FOR ALL OF US AT NBC
NEWS
>> HOW ARE YOU DOING?
>> GOOD.
>> FERGIE'S FIRST INTERVIEW
ABOUT HER SPLIT FROM JOSH
DUHAMEL.
>> YOU'VE GOT TO LET YOUR
FEELINGS OUT SOMEWHERE OR YOU'RE
GOING TO IMPLODE.
>> WILL THERE BE A CUSTODY WAR
OVER THEIR SON AXL?
>>> AND HOE OPERA SAYS DEEPAK
CHOPRA HELPED HER GET THROUGH
LOW MOMENTS.
>> AND SURVIVING MEXICO'S LAST
DEVASTATING EARTHQUAKE.
>> A LOT OF FRIENDS DIED.
>> AND THE STAR UNDER FIRE FOR
COMPLAINING THE HURRICANE RUINED
HER VACATION.
>>> 12 YEARS OLD AND A MILLION
DOLLARS RICHER.
>> THE WINNER OF "AMERICA'S GOT
TALENT" DARCI LYNNE IS HERE WITH
ME.
>> NOW ON "EXTRA" --
>> HEY, GUYS, WHO WHO IT IS.
I'M WITH DEBRA MESSING.
>> "WILL & GRACE," IT'S COMING.
>> THE SURPRISE GUEST STAR.
>> MICHELLE OBAMA ON THE SHOW
SNOWE.
>> THE BIGGEST SECRETS.
>> I CANNOT TELL YOU.
>> THEN OUR NEW A-LIST INTERVIEW
WITH CATHERINE ZETA-JONES.
WHAT MOTHERHOOD'S TAUGHT HER
ABOUT THE SECRET LIVES OF
AMERICAN TEENAGERS.
>> I GO, WHOA, STOP.
I'M YOUR MOTHER.
I DON'T WANT TO KNOW THAT.
>> PLUS WHEN NEWS ANCHORS
EXPLODE.
LAWRENCE O'DONNELL'S LIVE TV
MELTDOWN.
>> STOP THE HAMMERING!
♪ EXTRA EXTRA
♪