>> WELCOME TO
"WORLD NEWS TONIGHT."
CRISIS IN SYRIA.
THE REPORTED NEW BOMBING IN THAT
SAME TOWN WHERE THE CHEMICAL
ATTACK KILLED DOZENS.
PLUS SYRIAN JETS TAKING OFF FROM
THE AIRBASE HIT BY U.S.
MISSILES.
TONIGHT PRESIDENT TRUMP
DEFENDING THE DECISION NOT TO
BOMB THE RUNWAYS.
WEST WING WAR.
STEPHEN BANNON VERSUS
JARED KUSHNER.
THE CHIEF WHITE HOUSE STRATEGIST
CLASHING WITH THE PRESIDENT'S
SON-IN-LAW.
TONIGHT INSIDE THEIR MAR-A-LAGO
SIT-DOWN TO END THEIR
DIFFERENCES.
MANHUNT.
NEW IMAGES OF THE ARMED SUSPECT
AT THE CENTER OF A NATIONWIDE
MANHUNT.
IS HE PLOTTING TO KILL, PLUS HIS
MESSAGE FOR THE PRESIDENT.
BREAKING NEWS.
BOUNCE HOUSE DISASTER.
MULTIPLE CHILDREN RUSHED TO THE
HOSPITAL.
TWO BOUNCE HOUSES SENT AIRBORNE
HITTING POWER LINES.
THE DANGER WITH THIS PARTY
ATTRACTION.
AND TAX WARNING.
THE NEW CHANGE AFFECTING
MILLIONS OF TAXPAYERS.
>>> GOOD EVENING.
THANKS FOR JOINING US ON A
SATURDAY.
I'M TOM LLAMAS.
WE BEGIN
WITH NEW BOMBINGS BY PRESIDENT
BASHAR AL ASSAD ON HIS OWN
PEOPLE IN THAT CHEMICAL ATTACK.
THIS AS IMAGES ARE EMERGING OF
SYRIAN JETS TAKING OFF FROM THE
AIRBASE TARGETED BY U.S.
TOMAHAWK MISSILES.
PRESIDENT TRUMP DEFENDING AND
EXPLAINING THE DECISION NOT TO
BOMB THE RUNWAYS AND TONIGHT WE
HEAR FROM ONE OF THE MOST
VISIBLE VICTIMS FROM THE SYRIAN
ATTACK.
THE FATHER OF BABY TWINS KILLED
BY THE CHEMICAL WEAPONS.
ABC EAST ALEX MARQUARDT LEADS US
OFF TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THE
SYRIAN AIRBASE HIT BY THE U.S.
MILITARY BACK UP AND
RUNNING, NEW PHOTOS SHOWING
SYRIAN JETS TAKING OFF LESS THAN
24 HOURS AFTER THE U.S. STRIKE.
THE MARKINGS FROM THE BOMBINGS
SEEN ON BUNKERS.
IMAGES SHOWING AIRCRAFT AND
BOMBED OUT FUEL TANKS AND DAMAGE
TO AIRCRAFT SHELTERS.
BUT THE RUNWAYS UNTOUCHED.
TONIGHT THE PRESIDENT TWEETING A
DEFENSE.
THE REASON YOU GENERALLY DON'T
HIT RUNWAYS IS THAT THEY ARE
EASY AND INEXPENSIVE TO QUICKLY
FIX.
THE PENTAGON SAYS IT WAS FROM
THIS BASE THAT A PLANE TOOK OFF
WITH THE DEADLY NERVE AGENT USED
IN TUESDAY'S CHEMICAL ATTACK
THAT KILLED MORE THAN 80 PEOPLE.
AND THAT TOWN BOMBED AGAIN TODAY
ACCORDING TO A WATCHDOG GROUP.
>> THERE IS IRONY HERE THAT IT
DOES APPEAR THAT IT'S OKAY FOR
MR. ASSAD TO BLOW UP HIS PEOPLE.
IT'S JUST NOT OKAY TO GAS THEM.
>> WHEN PRESIDENT TRUMP
ANNOUNCED THE STRIKE HE POINTED
TO THE CHILDREN WHO WERE KILLED.
>> IT WAS A SLOW AND BRUTAL
DEATH FOR SO MANY.
EVEN BEAUTIFUL BABIES WERE
CRUELLY MURDERED IN THIS VERY
BARBARIC ATTACK.
>> PERHAPS NO IMAGE MORE GUT
WRENCHING OF THIS ONE OF ABDUL
HAMEEM YOUSSEF HUGGING HIS
TWO LIFELESS
TWINS.
HE WENT HOUSE TO HOUSE TRYING TO
RESCUE NEIGHBORS AND FAMILY.
MANY FOAMING AT THE MOUTH.
HE LOST 25 RELATIVES IN THE
ATTACK DURING WHICH HE FAINTED.
>> Translator: WHEN I CAME TO I
ASKED FOR THEM HE SAID.
I TOLD THEM HELLO DARLINGS I
TOOK TOO LONG.
I RESCUED EVERYONE ELSE BUT I
COULDN'T RESCUE YOU.
DESCRIBING THE MOMENT THE PHOTO
WAS TAKEN YOUSSEF SAID I WASN'T
AWARE OF ANYTHING.
I THOUGHT THEY WERE ALIVE.
I WAS EXPECTING THEM TO HUG ME
BACK.
>> THAT FATHER'S STORY AND THE
IMAGES SO DEVASTATING.
ALEX JOINS US LIVE.
THE BIG QUESTION, WILL SYRIA
RESPOND TO THE U.S. ATTACK AND
DO WE KNOW IF TODAY'S NEW
BOMBING BY SYRIA OF THAT TOWN
WHERE THE CHEMICAL ATTACK
OCCURRED WAS THAT RETALIATION?
>> Reporter: IT'S UNCLEAR
WHETHER THAT SYRIAN ATTACK WAS
IN DIRECT RESPONSE TO THE
AMERICAN STRIKE WHICH PRESIDENT
ASSAD HAS CALLED AN UNJUST ACT
OF AGGRESSION BUT WE ARE SEEING
THE REACTION.
A DEFIANT
ASSAD SAYING WE ARE GOING TO
CONTINUE CARRYING BOMBING RUNS
AND LAUNCHING OUR PLANES FROM
THE BASE THAT YOU JUST STRUCK.
TOM.
>> ALEX, THANK YOU.
DIGGING DEEPER INTO THE DECISION
AROUND THAT STRIKE PLUS THE
BREWING CIVIL WAR INSIDE THE
WEST WING BETWEEN TWO OF THE
PRESIDENT'S TOP AIDES.
ABC'S DAVID WRIGHT REPORTING
FROM WEST PALM BEACH TONIGHT.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT THE
PRESIDENT STILL INSISTS THE
TOMAHAWK MISSILE STRIKE WAS AN
UNQUALIFIED SUCCESS.
TWEETING OUT, "CONGRATULATIONS
TO OUR GREAT MILITARY MEN AND
WOMEN FOR REPRESENTING THE
UNITED STATES, AND THE WORLD SO
WELL."
NOT LONG AGO TRUMP WAS RELUCTANT
TO INTERVENE IN SYRIA.
WE DON'T WANT WORLD WAR III OVER
SYRIA.
>> BACK WHEN PRESIDENT OBAMA
WANTED TO PUNISH SYRIA FOR A
PREVIOUS CHEMICAL ATTACK.
TRUMP TWEETED WHAT WILL WE GET
FOR BOMBING SYRIA BESIDES MORE
DEBT AND A LONG TERM CONFLICT.
OBAMA NEEDS CONGRESSIONAL
APPROVAL.
TRUMP INFORMED CONGRESS AFTER
THE MISSILES WERE LAUNCHED.
GEORGE STEPHANOPOULOS ASKED
SECRETARY OF STATE REX TILLERSON
IF THE STRIKE SIGNALS A CHANGE
IN U.S. POLICY.
>> THIS STRIKE WAS RELATED
SOLELY TO THE MOST RECENT
HORRIFIC USE OF CHEMICAL WEAPONS
AGAINST WOMEN, CHILDREN AND AS
THE PRESIDENT SAID EVEN SMALL
BABIES.
WE ARE CALLING ON BASHAR AL
ASSAD TO CEASE THE USE OF THE
WEAPONS.
OTHER THAN THAT THERE IS NO
CHANGE TO OUR MILITARY POSTURE.
>> EVEN AS THE PRESIDENT WAS
JUGGLING TWO FOREIGN ISSUES,
CHINA AND SYRIA.
HE HAD TO INTERVENE IN A
CONFLICT AMONG HIS OWN SENIOR
STAFF.
CHIEF STRATEGIST
STEVE BANNON AND SON-IN-LAW
JARED KUSHNER WERE ALLIES DURING
THE CAMPAIGN BUT SOURCES SAY
LATELY THE TWO HAVE CLASHED WITH
KUSHNER PUSHING FOR GREATER
ENGAGEMENT WITH THE WORLD,
BANNON FOR THE STRATEGY AMERICA
FIRST.
ABC NEWS LEARNED THE DAY AFTER
THESE PHOTOS WERE TAKEN AT
MAR-A-LAGO KUSHNER AND BANNON
SAT DOWN FRIDAY IN AN ATTEMPT TO
SETTLE THEIR DIFFERENCES.
CHIEF OF STAFF REINCE PRIEBUS
ALSO ATTENDED THE MEETING BUT
WHITE HOUSE OFFICIALS DENY ANY
IMMINENT SHAKEUP.
>> DAVID, THE PRESIDENT IS
DEALING WITH SYRIA, A NEW
SUPREME COURT JUSTICE, THIS
PUBLIC FEUD BETWEEN AIDES IS THE
LAST THING HE NEEDS RIGHT NOW?
>> Reporter: THAT'S RIGHT.
THIS IS A HUGE MOMENT FOR THE
PRESIDENT.
YOU HAVE GOT A CHINA SUMMIT THAT
CAME OFF WITHOUT INCIDENT.
MISSILES THAT HIT THEIR TARGETS
IN SYRIA AND A NEW SUPREME COURT
PICK TO BE SWORN IN ON MONDAY.
THE LAST THING THE WHITE HOUSE
WANTS IS TALK OF INFIGHTING,
TOM.
>> DAVID, THANKS.
THERE'LL BE MUCH MORE ON THE
INTERVIEW WITH SECRETARY OF
STATE TOMORROW ON "THIS WEEK."
>>> TURNING TO SWEDEN.
A COUNTRY STILL IN SHOCK OVER A
TRUCK ATTACK MOWING DOWN
PEDESTRIANS IN THE CAPITAL.
A 39-YEAR-OLD SUSPECT UNDER
ARREST AND INVESTIGATORS
EXAMINING A DEVICE THEY SAY WAS
FOUND INSIDE THE TRUCK.
THE COUNTRY'S PRIME MINISTER
PAYING HIS RESPECTS AT A
MA
MAKE-SHIFT
MEMORIAL.
TERRY MORAN WITH THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: IT WAS SWEDEN'S
MOMENT OF TERROR.
A STOLEN BEER TRUCK SUDDENLY
TRANSFORMED INTO A MASSIVE
WEAPON, BARRELING DOWN A CROWDED
SHOPPING STREET.
>> THERE WERE BODIES ON THE
GROUND EVERYWHERE, AND A SENSE
OF PANIC.
>> Reporter: AND TODAY, WE KNOW
THE MAN AUTHORITIES SAY WAS
BEHIND THE WHEEL, SEEN HERE IN
GRAINY SECURITY CAMERA IMAGES
RELEASED WHILE HE WAS ON THE RUN
AFTER THE ATTACK.
HE'S 39 YEARS OLD, ORIGINALLY
FROM UZBEKISTAN IN CENTRAL ASIA,
KNOWN TO SECURITY SERVICES HERE
AS A POSSIBLE ISLAMIC EXTREMIST,
BASED ON HIS SOCIAL MEDIA POSTS,
BUT HE WASN'T BEING MONITORED.
AND THIS TODAY, HE MAY HAVE HAD
A BOMB IN THAT TRUCK.
>> WE HAVE FOUND SOMETHING IN
THE TRUCK, IN THE DRIVER'S SEAT,
A TECHNICAL DEVICE WHICH SHOULD
NOT BE THERE.
>> Reporter: OVERNIGHT, A RAID
IN A STOCKHOLM SUBURB, SEVERAL
PEOPLE DETAINED FOR QUESTIONING.
THE SUSPECT, WHO AUTHORITIES
HAVEN'T NAMED, ISN'T TALKING,
AND THE INVESTIGATION CONTINUES.
>> WE DO NOT KNOW WHETHER THERE
ARE FURTHER PERSONS INVOLVED IN
THIS ACT, OR NOT.
>> Reporter: FOUR PEOPLE WERE
KILLED IN THE ATTACK.
TEN REMAIN HOSPITALIZED,
INCLUDING A CHILD.
>> THE ATTACK SHUT DOWN CENTRAL
STOCKHOLM FOR HOURS AND IT
SHOCKED THE PEOPLE OF THIS
NORMALLY PLACID COUNTRY TO THEIR
CORE.
TODAY THEY'RE ERECTING THIS ALL
TOO FAMILIAR MAKESHIFT MEMORIAL
WHICH WE'RE SEEING IN CITY AFTER
CITY ACROSS EUROPE.
AND NOW A GRIM PATTERN IS CLEAR.
TRUCKS AND CARS, SO ORDINARY, SO
UBIQUITOUS, INCREASINGLY
WEAPONIZED BY TERRORISTS.
NICE, IN FRANCE, LAST JULY, A
SLAUGHTER ON BASTILLE DAY,
86 DEAD.
BERLIN, CHRISTMASTIME,
12 MURDERED.
JUST LAST MONTH IN LONDON,
5 KILLED.
AND NOW, STOCKHOLM.
TERRY MORAN ABC NEWS, STOCKHOLM.
>> BACK HERE AT HOME TO THE
INTENSIFYING MANHUNT FOR THE
SUSPECT CALLED ARMED AND
DANGEROUS.
INVESTIGATORS TRACKING MORE THAN
200 LEADS TO PIN DOWN THE
WISCONSIN MAN WHO APPARENTLY
FILMED HIMSELF MAILING A
MANIFESTO TO PRESIDENT TRUMP.
WHAT HE'S ACCUSED OF PLOTTING.
HERE'S EVA PILGRIM.
>> Reporter: AUTHORITIES ARE
ASKING FOR THE PUBLIC'S HELP TO
FIND THIS MAN IN A NEWLY
RELEASED IMAGE PLOTTING
AN ACT OF MASS
VIOLENCE.
>> THIS SUBJECT CONTINUES TO
REMAIN A THREAT AND NEED TO BE
VIGILANT FOR THEIR PERSONAL
SAFETY.
>> Reporter: THIS IS JOSEPH
JAKUBOWSKI SEEN TUESDAY AT A GAS
STATION.
IN WISCONSIN.
>> NEVER FORGET HIS FACE.
EVER.
>> Reporter: HE POSTED THIS
VIDEO TO HIS SOCIAL MEDIA
ACCOUNT AND MAILING THIS
ENVELOPE TO THE PRESIDENT.
>> HERE IT IS.
YOU SEE IT'S GETTING SHIPPED.
REVOLUTION.
IT'S TIME FOR CHANGE.
>> Reporter: INSIDE,
INVESTIGATORS SAY PLANS OF A
BRUTAL ATTACK AND DISPARAGING
COMMENTS ABOUT THE PRESIDENT ALL
IN A 161-PAGE ANTI-GOVERNMENT
MANIFESTO.
>> ADDRESS.
LEAVING.
>> Reporter: POLICE SAY YOU CAN
SEE JAKUBOWSKI IN THIS PHOTO
STEALING 16 FIREARMS FROM A GUN
SHOP BEFORE SETTING HIS CAR ON
FIRE AND DISAPPEARING.
AUTHORITIES ARE CALLING HIM
ARMED AND DANGEROUS.
INVESTIGATORS USING DOGS, PLANES
AND MORE THAN 150 OFFICERS TO
SEARCH.
TONIGHT HIS NEIGHBOR ON EDGE.
>> I JUST WANT THIS TO END.
I JUST -- I WANT TO FEEL SAFE IN
MY HOME AGAIN.
>> Reporter: THE FBI IS NOW
OFFERING A $10,000 REWARD FOR
INFORMATION LEADING TO
JAKUBOWSKI'S ARREST.
THEY'RE HOPING HE TURNS HIMSELF
IN BUT ASKING FOR THE PUBLIC'S
HELP.
TOM.
>> STILL SO MANY QUESTIONS ABOUT
HIS MOTIVE.
THANKS EVA.
>>> BREAKING NEWS.
AT LEAST FIVE CHILDREN RACED TO
THE HOSPITAL IN SOUTH CAROLINA.
THE TWO BOUNCE HOUSES GOING
AIRBORNE.
MARCI GONZALEZ WITH THE LATEST.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, THIS
INFLATABLE SLIDE, AND A BOUNCE
HOUSE WITH CHILDREN INSIDE,
SUDDENLY GOING AIRBORNE, LIFTED
BY A STRONG GUST OF WIND.
>> BIG GUSH OF AIR AND THE
BOUNCE HOUSE PROBABLY WENT UP A
GOOD 20, 30 FEET.
>> Reporter: FIRST RESPONDERS
SAY THE BOUNCE HOUSE THEN, HIT
NEARBY POWER LINES, SENDING THE
CHILDREN, FALLING TO THE GROUND.
>> I'VE ONLY GOT FOUR PATIENTS
SO FAR.
THEY'RE ALL JUVENILES.
>> Reporter: RESCUERS, WHO
RUSHED TO THE SCENE AT THIS
SOUTH CAROLINA SAY INCREDIBLY,
NO ONE WAS ELECTROCUTED BUT FIVE
CHILDREN WERE HURT AND RUSHED TO
THE HOSPITAL.
THESE KINDS OF ACCIDENTS
HAPPENING OVER AND OVER AGAIN.
IN 2015, THIS BOUNCE HOUSE ON
THE BEACH IN FLORIDA, TUMBLING
AND SENT FLYING, INJURING THREE
CHILDREN.
>> I WAS THINKING I WAS ABOUT TO
DIE.
>> Reporter: AND IN COLORADO,
TWO CHILDREN HURT.
>> THERE'S NOT A KID IN THERE?
THERE'S NOT A KID IN THERE IS
THERE?
>> Reporter: WIND PICKED UP THIS
BLOW-UP SLIDE AND SLAMMED IT
REPEATEDLY INTO THE GROUND.
>> I WAS PICKED UP INTO THE AIR
AND THROWN AROUND A LOT.
>> TONIGHT WE'RE TOLD THE
CHILDREN'S INJURIES IN SOUTH
CAROLINA ARE NOT
LIFE-THREATENING.
>> THANK YOU.
NEXT TO THE TRAVEL HEADACHES
THAT WON'T QUIT FOR DELTA
AIRLINE PASSENGERS.
HUNDREDS OF FLIGHTS CANCELLED
TODAY.
WHAT'S BEHIND THE ONGOING
PROBLEMS TRYING THE PATIENCE OF
SO MANY?
ADRIENNE BANKERT HAS SOME
ANSWERS.
>> Reporter: TONIGHT, FLIGHT
FRUSTRATIONS.
FIRST WILD WEATHER, AND NOW
SPRING BREAK, CREATING A
DISASTROUS DOMINO EFFECT
IMPACTING DELTA.
>> I WAS ISSUED TWO MORE TICKETS
THAT DAY.
BOARDED THREE SEPARATE AIRCRAFT.
ALL OF WHICH EITHER WERE GROUND
STOPPED OR NEVER LEFT THE GATE.
>> Reporter: SEVERE STORMS
WEDNESDAY STRUCK THE AIRLINES
HUB IN ATLANTA, CANCELLING
3,500 DELTA FLIGHTS, AT LEAST
275 TODAY ALONE.
>> WITH DELTA DELAYING FLIGHTS
EVERY 30 MINUTES UNTIL THEY
FINALLY CANCEL THEM, I HAVE
OPTED TO RENT A CAR.
>> Reporter: MALLORY BERGESON,
WAS RESCHEDULED ON DIFFERENT
FLIGHTS FOR FIVE DAYS STRAIGHT.
>> I'VE BEEN
DRIVING TWO HOURS, STILL HAVE
SEVEN HOURS TO GO, BUT MOVING
FASTER THAN DELTA IS.
>> Reporter: MALLORY AND SO MANY
OTHERS STUCK BECAUSE OF THE
SURGE OF SPRING BREAK TRAVELERS
WITH STORMS FORCING PLANES AND
CREWS OUT OF POSITION.
PASSENGERS VENTING ONLINE,
REALITY TV'S TODD CHRISLEY
TWEETING, "I USED TO BE PROUD TO
SAY I ONLY FLY DELTA, THE FACT I
NOW HAVE 2 SAY 'USE TO' IS SAD."
DELTA RELEASING A STATEMENT,
"WHILE WE CAN'T CONTROL THE
WEATHER, WE UNDERSTAND THE
RESULTING RECOVERY HAS NOT BEEN
IDEAL, AND WE APOLOGIZE FOR
THAT."
A TRAVEL WAIVER HAS BEEN
EXTENDED FOR PASSENGERS WHOSE
TRAVEL PLANS ARE FLEXIBLE.
TOM.
>>> MORE NOW ON THE WILD WEATHER
AND THE DAMAGING
WINDS OUT WEST.
THE CLEANUP UNDER WAY FOR
HOMEOWNERS IN OREGON.
MANY DOWNED TREES.
THOSE FIERCE WINDS SLAMMING
PORTLAND AS WELL.
ALL PART OF A SYSTEM MOVING
EAST.
WITH THOSE PLANES IN THE CROSS
HAIRS FROM OKLAHOMA TO
MINNESOTA.
LET'S GET TO ROB MARCIANO.
>> THE STORM THROUGH THE
NORTHWEST, UNLIKE ANY I'VE SEEN.
MORE LIKE A FALL WIND STORM.
IT'S A MESS OUT THERE.
WINTER STORM WARNING FROM
CALIFORNIA TO WYOMING.
A SEVERE WEATHER THREAT
FROM IOWA BACK DOWN THROUGH
OKLAHOMA CITY.
A CHANCE WE DON'T BREAK WHAT WE
CALL THE CAP BUT IF WE DO IT'S
GOING TO BE VERY ACTIVE TOMORROW
AFTERNOON AND A LOT OF WARM AIR.
80 DEGREES IN ST. LOUIS SURGING
TO THE EAST INTO THE LOWER 70s
AND WARMER ON TUESDAY.
IT WILL START TO FEEL LIKE JUNE
IN SOME SPOTS TOM.
>>> STILL MUCH MORE AHEAD THIS
SATURDAY.
A MASSIVE EXPLOSION AND FIRE
FLATTEN A HOME.
WE'LL TELL YOU WHERE THIS HAPPEN
AND WHAT INVESTIGATORS ARE NOW
SAYING.
PLUS WITH THE TAX DEADLINE
LOOMING A NEW PROBLEM TO WORRY
ABOUT.
WHY IT MIGHT BE HARDER TO TELL
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN THE IRS
AND SWAMMERS.
THE INFORMATION YOU NEED TO
KNOW.
AND WOULD YOU JUMP OUT OF AN
AIRPLANE TO ASK SOMEONE OUT ON A
DATE?
THIS TEENAGER DID.
DID HIS PROM STRATEGY WORK?
THAT'S COMING UP.
My hygienist told me to try...
...a mouthwash.
So I tried Crest.
It does so much more than
give me fresh breath.
Crest Pro-Health mouthwash
provides all...
...of these benefits to help you
get better dental check-ups.
Go Pro with Crest mouthwash.
Checkup? Nailed it
This
This is my body of proof.
Proof of less joint pain
and clearer skin.
This is my body of proof that I
can take on psoriatic
arthritis with HUMIRA.
HUMIRA works by targeting and
helping to block a specific
source of inflammation that
contributes to both joint and
skin symptoms.
It's proven to help relieve
pain, stop further joint damage,
and clear skin in many adults.
HUMIRA is the #1
prescribed biologic
for psoriatic arthritis.
HUMIRA can lower your ability to
fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections and cancers,
including lymphoma, have
happened; as have blood, liver,
and nervous system problems,
serious allergic reactions,
and new or worsening heart
failure.
Before treatment, get tested for
TB.
Tell your doctor if you've been
to areas where certain
fungal infections are common,
and if you've had TB,
hepatitis B,
are prone to infections, or have
flu-like symptoms or sores.
Don't start HUMIRA if you have
an infection.
Want more proof? Ask your
rheumatologist about HUMIRA.
What's your body of proof?
>>> BACK NOW WITH A NEW IRS
PROGRAM THAT COULD CONFUSE
TAXPAYERS.
ABC'S STEPHANIE RAMOS WITH WHAT
YOU NEED TO KNOW TO PROTECT YOUR
MONEY.
>> Reporter: SCAMMERS POSING AS
IRS AGENTS HAVE BEEN THREATENING
FOR YEARS LIKE THIS.
>> BEFORE THERE IS AN ARREST
WARRANT ISSUED, I WANT YOU OR
YOUR ATTORNEY TO GIVE US A CALL
BACK.
>> Reporter: THE IRS FORCED TO
RELEASE THESE WARNINGS TO
TAXPAYERS.
>> ANGRY HARASSING CALLS LIKE
THESE ARE NOT HOW WE DO
BUSINESS.
>> Reporter: THEY HAVE HIRED
FOUR COMPANIES TO CHASE DOWN AND
CALL PEOPLE WITH LONG OVERDUE
TAXES THAT THEY CAN'T GET TO.
THIS WEEK THE IRS COMMISSIONER
WENT TO CAPITOL HILL TO DEFEND
HIRING OUTSIDE
COMPANIES THAT MAKE CALLS THAT
SOME SAY CAN CAUSE CONFUSION.
AND HELP SCAMMERS.
>> I'M PROTECTING TAXPAYERS.
WE HAVE HAD GOOD SESSIONS WITH
THE PRIVATE DEBT COLLECTORS.
PEOPLE UNDERSTAND THEY HAVE
TO --
>> WHAT'S THE CONSEQUENCES IF
THEY DON'T FOLLOW YOUR
DIRECTION?
>> WE CAN TERMINATE THE
CONTRACT.
>> Reporter: HERE'S WHAT THE IRS
SAYS, TO REMEMBER IF YOU GET A
CALL, THE IRS WILL CONTACT YOU
MULTIPLE TIMES IN WRITING BEFORE
YOU'RE CALLED BY CONTRACTORS OF
THE IRS AND YOU WON'T HEAR FROM
A PRIVATE COLLECTOR UNLESS YOU
HAVE MULTIPLE YEARS OF OVERDUE
TAXES.
THE IRS SAYS THESE PRIVATE
COLLECTORS WILL NEVER THREATEN
YOU WITH LAW ENFORCEMENT OR ASK
FOR YOUR CREDIT CARD.
ALL PAYMENTS WOULD GO ONLY TO
THE IRS.
TOM.
>> STEPHANIE RAMOS WITH
IMPORTANT TIPS.
THANK YOU.
STILL AHEAD, A FATHER SPEAKS
OUT.
STARTLING COMMENTS FROM THE
FATHER OF THE GIRL WHO RAN OFF
WITH THE TEACHER.
WAS SHE COERCED INTO GOING WITH
HIM?
AN INCREDIBLE SCENE, A GREAT
WHITE SHARK STUCK ON A REEF.
WHY IT'S RESISTING TO GET IT
BACK IN THE WATER.
STAY WITH US.
A
SPONTANEOUS MOMENT?
CIALIS FOR DAILY USE TREATS ED
AND THE URINARY SYMPTOMS OF BPH.
TELL YOUR DOCTOR
ABOUT YOUR MEDICINES,
AND ASK IF YOUR HEART IS
HEALTHY ENOUGH FOR SEX.
DO NOT TAKE CIALIS IF YOU
TAKE NITRATES FOR CHEST PAIN,
OR ADEMPAS® FOR
PULMONARY HYPERTENSION,
AS THIS MAY CAUSE AN UNSAFE
DROP IN BLOOD PRESSURE.
DO NOT DRINK ALCOHOL IN EXCESS.
TO AVOID LONG-TERM INJURY,
GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY
FOR AN ERECTION LASTING
MORE THAN FOUR HOURS.
IF YOU HAVE A SUDDEN DECREASE
OR LOSS OF HEARING OR VISION,
OR AN ALLERGIC REACTION,
STOP TAKING CIALIS
AND GET MEDICAL HELP RIGHT AWAY.
ASK YOUR DOCTOR ABOUT CIALIS.
Working on my feet all
day gave me pain here.
In my knees.
So I stepped on this
machine and got my number,
which matched my Dr. Scholl's
Custom Fit Orthotic Inserts.
So I get immediate relief
from my foot pain.
My knee pain.
Find a machine at DrScholls.com.
♪
That's life.
You diet. You exercise.
And if you still need help
lowering your blood sugar...
...this is JARDIANCE.
Along with diet and exercise...
JARDIANCE lowers blood sugar
and A1C
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
JARDIANCE is also the only type
2 diabetes treatment with heart-
proven to reduce the risk
of cardiovascular death
in adults with type 2 diabetes
and cardiovascular disease.
JARDIANCE can cause serious side
effects, including dehydration.
This may cause you to feel
dizzy, faint, or lightheaded,
or weak upon standing.
Ketoacidosis is a serious side
effect that may be fatal.
Symptoms include nausea,
vomiting, stomach pain,
tiredness, and
trouble breathing.
Stop taking JARDIANCE and call
your doctor right away
if you have symptoms
of ketoacidosis
or an allergic reaction.
Symptoms of an allergic
reaction include rash,
swelling, and difficulty
breathing or swallowing.
Do not take JARDIANCE
if you are on dialysis
or have severe kidney problems.
Other side effects are sudden
kidney problems,
genital yeast infections,
increased bad cholesterol,
and urinary tract infections,
which may be serious.
Taking JARDIANCE with
a sulfonylurea or insulin
may cause low blood sugar.
Tell your doctor about all
the medicines you take
and if you have any
medical conditions.
So talk to your doctor
about JARDIANCE-
the one and only type 2 diabetes
treatment with heart.
Visit JARDIANCE.com for a free
consultation with
a Certified Diabetes Educator
if you qualify.
♪
Predictable.
The comfort in knowing where
things are headed.
Because as we live longer...
And markets continue to
rise and fall...
Predictable is one thing you
need in retirement
to help protect what you've
earned and ensure it lasts.
Introducing
Brighthouse Financial.
A new company established
by MetLife
to specialize in annuities
& life insurance.
Talk to your advisor about a
brighter financial future.
>>> BACK NOW WITH OUR "INDEX".
A MASSIVE EXPLOSION LEVELS A
HOME IN MISSISSIPPI TO THE
GROUND.
SMOKE AND FLAMES POURING FROM
THE HOUSE FOLLOWING THE
EXPLOSION YESTERDAY.
IT WAS EMPTY AT THE TIME.
INVESTIGATORS DO NOT KNOW YET
WHAT CAUSED THE BLAST BUT SO FAR
THEY SAY IT DOES NOT LOOK
SUSPICIOUS.
>>> NEW DEVELOPMENTS IN THE
SEARCH FOR A TEEN AND A TEACHER.
THE FATHER OF ELISABETH TOMS
SAYING IN COURT PAPERS HIS
DAUGHTER FEARED THE TEACHER AND
HE USED THREATS TO GET HER TO
RUN AWAY WITH HER.
TEACHER TAD CUMMINS IS ACCUSED
OF ABDUCTING THE 15-YEAR-OLD
THREE WEEKS AGO.
>>> TO RESCUE A SHARK ON A
CALIFORNIA REEF.
THE INJURED GREAT WHITE WASHING
UP ON THE ROCKS IN SANTA CRUZ.
ANIMAL RESCUE WORKERS WERE ABLE
TO GET THE SHARK
INTO THE WATER BUT IT TURNED
BACK.
SCIENTISTS SAY THEY'RE NOT SURE
IF IT STRANDED ITSELF OR IS
SICK.
>>> ACROSS THE POND A WORLD
RECORD.
85 HOT AIR BALLOONS TAKING OFF
FOR A FLIGHT ACROSS THE ENGLISH
CHANNEL LANDING IN FRANCE THREE
HOURS LATER.
THE PREVIOUS RECORD WAS 49.
ORGANIZERS DID NOT FILE THE
PROPER FORMS WITH GUINNESS SO
THE NEW RECORD IS UNOFFICIAL BUT
THEY DID MAKE "WORLD NEWS
TONIGHT."
SO IT'S NOT THAT BAD.
UP NEXT, TAKING THE PROM-POSAL
TO NEW HEIGHTS.
THIS KID JUMPING OUT OF A PLANE
TO WIN HIS DATE'S HEART.
DID SHE SAY YES?
I HOPE SO.
THAT'S COMING UP.
Hi, I'm Frank.
I take MOVANTIK for OIC,
opioid-induced constipation.
Had a bad back injury,
my doctor prescribed opioids
which helped with the chronic
pain,
but backed me up big-time.
Tried prunes, laxatives, still
constipated...
had to talk to my doctor.
She said, "How long you been
holding this in?" (laughs)
That was my MOVANTIK MOMENT.
My doctor told me that MOVANTIK
is specifically designed
for OIC and can help you go more
often.
Don't take MOVANTIK if you have
a bowel blockage
or a history of them.
MOVANTIK may cause serious side
effects,
including symptoms of opioid
withdrawal,
severe stomach pain and/or
diarrhea,
and tears in the stomach or
intestine.
Tell your doctor about any side
effects
and about medicines you take.
MOVANTIK may interact with them
causing side effects.
Why hold it in? Have your
MOVANTIK moment.
Talk to your doctor about
opioid-induced constipation.
If you can't afford your
medication,
AstraZeneca may be able to help.
♪ She'll unease you
♪ All the better just
to please you ♪
♪ She's precocious,
and she knows just ♪
♪ What it takes to
make a pro blush ♪
♪ All the boys
think she's a spy, ♪
♪ She's got Bette Davis eyes
Bounty is more absorbent,Mom"
per roll
♪
so the roll can last 50% longer
than the leading ordinary brand.
So you get more "Life" per roll.
Bounty, the Quicker Picker Upper
with CHANTIX.and
I quit smoking
I finally broke out
of my man shell,
went to the doctor,
tell him
"I need help quitting smoking."
He prescribed CHANTIX
and it worked.
Along with support,
CHANTIX (varenicline) is proven
to help people quit smoking.
CHANTIX really
reduced my urge to smoke.
Some people had changes
in behavior, thinking or mood,
hostility, agitation, depressed
mood and suicidal thoughts
or actions while taking or
after stopping CHANTIX.
Some reported seizures or
sleepwalking with CHANTIX.
If you have any of these,
stop CHANTIX and call your
doctor right away.
Tell your doctor about any
history of
mental health problems,
which could get worse
or of seizures.
Don't take CHANTIX
if you've had a serious
allergic or skin reaction to it.
If you have these, stop CHANTIX
and call your doctor right away
as some can be life-threatening.
Tell your doctor if you have
heart or blood vessel problems,
or develop new
or worse symptoms.
Get medical help right away
if you have symptoms
of a heart attack or stroke.
Decrease alcohol use
while taking CHANTIX.
Use caution driving
or operating machinery.
Most common side effect
is nausea.
Quitting changed my life.
Ask your doctor if CHANTIX
is right for you.
>>> FINALLY TONIGHT, ASKING A
DATE TO PROM HAS CHANGED A LOT
OVER THE YEARS.
BIGGER, FLASHIER.
TONIGHT ONE THAT PROVES THE SKY
IS THE LIMIT.
HERE'S GLORIA RIVERA.
>> Reporter: HIGH SCHOOL SENIOR
TY MYERS, READY TO JUMP OUT of A
PLANE, HAD ONE THING ON HIS
MIND, PROM.
>> WHAT BETTER WAY TO GO ABOVE
AND BEYOND THAN JUMP OUT OF A
PLANE TWO MILES ABOVE THE EARTH?
>> Reporter: THIS IS WHAT HE
DECIDED ON, A SO-CALLED
PROM-POSAL FROM 12,000 FEET.
AND LOOK CLOSELY, THAT'S NOT A
JUMPSUIT HE'S WEARING, IT'S A
SUIT AND TIE.
VERY ROMANTIC.
HIS SIGN READING, "I'M FALLING
FOR YOU!
PROM?"
♪
OVER-THE-TOP PROM PROPOSALS AT A
FEVER PITCH THIS YEAR.
♪
THIS PHOENIX TEEN RECREATING THE
OPENING SCENE OF "LA LA LAND" TO
ASK EMMA STONE TO THE PROM.
THE STAR BUSY FILMING IN ENGLAND
SAID NO.
AS FOR TY, WHEN HE LANDED, KATIE
HAD A DIFFERENT ANSWER.
>> KATIE, GO TO PROM WITH ME?
>> I WILL DEFINITELY ACCEPT.
THIS DOES NOT SURPRISE ME ONE
BIT.
BECAUSE HE'S THE TYPE OF GUY TO
GO ABOVE AND BEYOND LIKE NO
MATTER WHAT HE DOES FOR ANYONE.
>> AW.
>> ESPECIALLY ME THOUGH.
>> Reporter: AND TONIGHT IS THE
BIG NIGHT, TY GIVING HIS HIGH
SCHOOL SWEETHEART HER CORSAGE.
THIS COUPLE GIVING A NEW MEANING
TO FALLING IN LOVE.
ABC NEWS, WASHINGTON.
>> GLAD SHE SAID YES AND GLAD HE
LANDED.
"GMA" IN THE MORNING.
HAVE A GREAT EVENING.
Are allergies holding you back?
Break through your allergies.
Try New Flonase Sensimist
instead of allergy pills.
It's more complete allergy
relief in a gentle mist
you may not even notice.
Using unique MistPro technology,
New Flonase Sensimist delivers
a gentle mist to help block
six key inflammatory substances
that cause your symptoms.
Most allergy pills
only block one.
And six is greater than one.
Break through your allergies.
New Flonase Sensimist
>> I'M KAREN ROGERS.
>> AND I'M MELISSA MAGEE,
TONIGHT ON FYI PHILLY.
>> IT'S TIME TO GET HOPPING
FOR THE 86TH ANNUAL EASTER
PROMENADE.
>> A FLOWER MARKET!
>> WE MEET A DESIGNER CREATING
THE ETERNAL SPRING.
>> PHILADELPHIA'S SO-CALLED
SEAFOOD WHISPERER HAS A NEW
HOME IN HADDONFIELD.
>> AFTER THE MEAL, WE DEVOUR
HAND-CRAFTED DESSERTS
>> AND WE'RE BACKSTAGE ON
BROADWAY  FAMILY-FRIENDLY
SHOWS HEADED TO PHILLY.
>> HI EVERYONE AND WELCOME TO
FYI PHILLY!
>> WE ARE GETTING INTO THE
SPIRIT OF SPRING WITH THIS
GORGEOUS FLORAL WALL.
>> TIME TO STEP AND REPEAT
>> AND TIME TO GET HOPPING!
EASTER'S ON ITS WAY.
>> AND FOR PHILADELPHIA, THERE
IS A LONG TRADITION OF
CELEBRATING.
>> WE'RE TALKING ABOUT THE
EASTER PROMENADE NOW IN ITS
86TH YEAR.
>> SO BREAK OUT THOSE FANCY
BONNETS AND SUNDAY BEST AND
MEET ME ON SOUTH STREET.